Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Mueren al menos 4 personas en un tiroteo y un incendio en una iglesia mormona en Michigan,At least 4 people die in a shooting and a fire in a Mormon church in Michigan,-0.3,"[('At least 4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mormon', 'NORP'), ('Michigan', 'GPE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Bad Bunny actuará en el espectáculo del medio tiempo del Super Bowl en febrero,Bad Bunny will perform in the mid -time show of the Super Bowl in February,-0.12222222222222218,"[('Bad Bunny', 'PERSON'), ('the Super Bowl', 'EVENT'), ('February', 'DATE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अमेरिका को भारत के बजाय पाकिस्तान से दोस्ती करने में क्यों फ़ायदा नज़र आ रहा है?,Why is America a benefit in befriending Pakistan instead of India?,0.0,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que é o metanol, substância ilegal em bebidas que causou cegueira e danos cerebrais em jovens de SP","What is methanol, an illegal substance in beverages that caused blindness and brain damage in young people in SP",-0.2,[]
https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Miguel, Rafael e Gabriel, os anjos que são reverenciados em três diferentes religiões","Miguel, Rafael and Gabriel, the angels who are revered in three different religions",0.0,"[('Miguel', 'PERSON'), ('Rafael', 'PERSON'), ('Gabriel', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,4 momentos que contam a história da destruição das ferrovias no Brasil,4 moments that tell the history of the destruction of railways in Brazil,0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como evitar comer microplásticos presentes na nossa comida,How to avoid eating microplastics present in our food,0.0,"[('microplastics', 'ORDINAL')]"
https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que se sabe sobre ataque com 4 mortes em igreja mórmon nos EUA,What is known about attack with 4 Mormon Church deaths in the USA,0.0,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mormon Church', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Кремль будет повышать ставки». Замминистра обороны Украины прогнозирует усиление российских ударов,"""The Kremlin will increase bets."" Deputy Minister of Defense of Ukraine predicts the strengthening of Russian strokes",0.0,"[('Kremlin', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп будет продвигать новый мирный план на переговорах с Нетаньяху,Trump will promote a new peace plan in negotiations with Netanyahu,0.13636363636363635,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Кремле «внимательно анализируют» заявления о возможной передаче Украине ракет Tomahawk","Livelive, War in Ukraine: The Kremlin “carefully analyzes” applications for the possible transfer of Tomahawk missiles to Ukraine",-0.05,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG'), ('Tomahawk', 'PRODUCT'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Пожарная команда Сырского». Как и зачем Украина создает штурмовые войска?,"""Fire team of Syresky."" How and why Ukraine creates assault troops?",0.0,"[('Syresky', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Тебе больше никогда не придется зарабатывать на жизнь». Хакеры  предложили корреспонденту деньги за взлом Би-би-си,"""You will never have to earn a living again."" Hackers offered the correspondent money for hacking BBC",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,シンガポール、香港の民主活動家の入国拒否　「国益に適さない」と,"Singapore and Hong Kong's democratic activists refuse to enter Japan saying ""not suitable for national interests""",-0.275,"[('Singapore', 'GPE'), (""Hong Kong's"", 'GPE'), ('democratic', 'NORP'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ミシガン州のモルモン教会で銃撃・放火、少なくとも4人死亡,At least four people killed in arson shooting and arson at Mormon Church in Michigan,-0.25,"[('At least four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mormon Church', 'ORG'), ('Michigan', 'GPE')]"
https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,住宅地の中心に着弾　ロシアの攻撃受けたキーウからBBC報告, 所要時間 2,34","Video, BBC report from Kiu attacked by Russia, travel time: 2,34",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Kiu', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('2,34', 'CARDINAL')]"
https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米オレゴン州、トランプ政権を提訴　派兵計画は「違法」と,"Oregon, US state, filed a lawsuit against Trump administration; plans to send troops are ""illegal""",-0.5,"[('Oregon', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー大統領、ロシアの「卑劣」な12時間空爆を非難,"President Zelensky criticizes Russia's ""despicable"" 12-hour air strike",0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('12-hour', 'TIME')]"
