Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo logra Putin mantener la lealtad de los oligarcas rusos a pesar de las millonarias sanciones de Occidente,How Putin manages to maintain the loyalty of Russian oligarchs despite million-dollar sanctions from the West,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('million-dollar', 'MONEY')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Accidente de tren en México deja 13 muertos y casi 100 heridos,Train accident in Mexico leaves 13 dead and almost 100 injured,-0.2,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('almost 100', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El niño que pasó 2 años escondido en un bosque para escapar de los nazis,The boy who spent 2 years hiding in a forest to escape the Nazis,-0.1,"[('2 years', 'DATE'), ('Nazis', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Muere a los 91 años Brigitte Bardot, el ícono del cine que abandonó su carrera para dedicarse a los derechos de los animales","Brigitte Bardot, the film icon who abandoned her career to dedicate herself to animal rights, dies at 91",0.0,"[('Brigitte Bardot', 'PERSON'), ('91', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Encontré una espada con una mano empuñándola""","""I found a sword with one hand holding it""",0.0,[]
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्रिकेट अंपायर कैसे बनते हैं और इस प्रोफ़ेशन में कमाई कितनी है?,How to become a cricket umpire and what is the earning in this profession?,0.0,[]
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अरावली मामले में सुप्रीम कोर्ट ने अपने ही फ़ैसले पर रोक लगाई,Supreme Court stays its own decision in Aravali case,0.6,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Aravali', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,ललित मोदी ने वायरल वीडियो के बाद मांगी माफ़ी, भारत सरकार से ये कहा","Live, Lalit Modi apologized after the viral video, said this to the Government of India",0.13636363636363635,"[('Lalit Modi', 'PERSON'), ('the Government of India', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'कुलदीप सेंगर को रिहा नहीं किया जा सकता', सुप्रीम कोर्ट ने दिल्ली हाई कोर्ट के आदेश पर रोक लगाते हुए क्या कहा?","'Kuldeep Sengar cannot be released', what did the Supreme Court say while staying the Delhi High Court order?",0.16,"[('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Delhi High Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,छत्तीसगढ़: ईसाई धर्म अपनाने वाली महिला का शव तीन दिन तक गाँव-गाँव भटकता रहा,Chhattisgarh: The dead body of a woman who converted to Christianity kept wandering from village to village for three days.,-0.2,"[('Christianity', 'NORP'), ('three days', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"किसी की रहस्यमय हालात में मौत, किसी को रूस से भागना पड़ा, पुतिन के सामने नतमस्तक अरबपति","Someone died under mysterious circumstances, someone had to flee Russia, the billionaire bowed before Putin.",0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,उस्मान हादी और दीपू चंद्र दास की हत्या को लेकर एक बार फिर भारत-बांग्लादेश आमने-सामने,India-Bangladesh once again face to face over the murder of Osman Hadi and Dipu Chandra Das.,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Osman Hadi', 'PERSON'), ('Dipu Chandra Das', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मनु की प्रतिमा पर कालिख पोतने राजस्थान गई थीं महाराष्ट्र की दो सहेलियां, उसके बाद क्या हुआ","Two friends from Maharashtra had gone to Rajasthan to blacken Manu's statue, what happened after that",0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Maharashtra', 'ORG'), ('Rajasthan', 'GPE'), ('Manu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"यूपी: एक छात्रा की बर्थडे पार्टी में उत्पात का मामला, पुलिस की इस वजह से हो रही है आलोचना","UP: Case of violence in a student's birthday party, police is being criticized for this reason",0.0,[]
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Trump descartou Bolsonaro porque não suporta perdedores', diz ex-embaixador dos EUA","'Trump discarded Bolsonaro because he can't stand losers', says former US ambassador",-0.1,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Por que Trump e Zelensky dizem haver progresso em acordo de paz, mas ele ainda parece distante","Why Trump and Zelensky say there is progress on a peace deal, but it still seems far away",0.1,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As táticas de Putin para manter o apoio dos bilionários russos,Putin's tactics to maintain the support of Russian billionaires,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Doutrina Donroe': como Trump vê a América Latina, segundo sua estratégia de segurança nacional","'Donroe Doctrine': how Trump sees Latin America, according to his national security strategy",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As 'escolas militares' chinesas para adolescentes 'rebeldes': 'castigo corporal está sempre presente',Chinese 'military schools' for 'rebellious' teenagers: 'corporal punishment is always present',-0.03333333333333333,"[('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os humanos poderão ser esquecidos daqui a milhões de anos?,Could humans be forgotten millions of years from now?,0.0,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,7 vitórias para o clima e a natureza em 2025,7 victories for climate and nature in 2025,0.0,"[('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Morre Brigitte Bardot: a atriz francesa que revolucionou o cinema nos anos 1950,Brigitte Bardot dies: the French actress who revolutionized cinema in the 1950s,0.0,"[('Brigitte Bardot', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('the 1950s', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que é 'futtitinni', a filosofia siciliana para tornar a vida mais leve","What is 'futtitinni', the Sicilian philosophy to make life lighter",0.0,"[('Sicilian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Все, кроме Донбасса и еще пары пунктов. О чем договорились Дональд Трамп и Владимир Зеленский во Флориде",Everything except Donbass and a couple more points. What Donald Trump and Vladimir Zelensky agreed on in Florida,0.5,"[('Donbass', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Vladimir Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский и Трамп позитивно высказались об итогах встречи во Флориде","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky and Trump spoke positively about the results of the meeting in Florida",0.22727272727272727,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Правящая националистическая партия уверенно побеждает на выборах в Косово,Ruling nationalist party wins elections in Kosovo,0.3,"[('Kosovo', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Правозащитники: количество смертных казней в Иране за год удвоилось,Human rights activists: the number of executions in Iran has doubled in a year,0.0,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('a year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Брижит Бардо: актриса, секс-символ и защитница животных","Brigitte Bardot: actress, sex symbol and animal advocate",0.0,"[('Brigitte Bardot', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Три человека погибли в Швеции в результате сильного шторма, прошедшего по странам Северной Европы",Three people died in Sweden as a result of a strong storm that passed through the countries of Northern Europe,0.4333333333333333,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('Northern Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Все более таинственная темная энергия: может ли Вселенная закончиться «Большим сжатием»,Increasingly Mysterious Dark Energy: Could the Universe End in a Big Crunch?,-0.049999999999999996,[]
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Всплеск антисемитизма и отношение к Израилю. Почему евреи Британии переживают самые серьезные перемены за 60 лет,A surge of anti-Semitism and attitudes towards Israel. Why Britain's Jews are experiencing their biggest changes in 60 years,0.0,"[('anti-Semitism', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Jews', 'NORP'), ('60 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как снеки и перекусы изменили наше пищевое поведение,How snacking has changed our eating behavior,0.0,[]
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Умерла Брижит Бардо,Brigitte Bardot died,0.0,"[('Brigitte Bardot', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏とゼレンスキー氏が会談、和平案で進展と　「難しい問題」が残っているとも,"Trump and Zelensky meet, say progress on peace plan, but ``difficult issues'' remain",-0.5,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ミャンマーで総選挙始まる、軍事政権下で5年ぶり　「いかさま」と批判される中,"General elections begin in Myanmar for the first time in five years under military rule, amid criticism that they are ""cheating""",0.06666666666666668,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('five years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ブリジット・バルドーさん死去、91歳　仏映画に革命もたらした俳優,"Brigitte Bardot, the actor who revolutionized French cinema, dies at the age of 91",0.0,"[('Brigitte Bardot', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('the age of 91', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイとカンボジアが停戦で合意、数週間にわたる激しい衝突で,Thailand and Cambodia agree to ceasefire after weeks of violent clashes,-0.8,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('weeks', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,新年の目標はどうやって守る？　避けた方がいい言葉とは,How do you keep your New Year's goals? What words should you avoid?,0.13636363636363635,"[(""New Year's"", 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエルがソマリランドを承認、世界初　ソマリアや近隣国は非難,"Israel recognizes Somaliland, world's first, Somalia and neighboring countries condemn",0.25,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Somaliland', 'PRODUCT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Somalia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,シリアのモスクで金曜礼拝中に爆発、少なくとも8人死亡,Explosion at Syrian mosque during Friday prayers kills at least 8 people,-0.3,"[('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('at least 8', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル北部で襲撃事件、2人死亡　容疑者はパレスチナ人と当局,Two killed in attack in northern Israel; suspects are Palestinians and authorities,-0.2,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、トランプ氏と近くフロリダで会談予定と表明　戦争終結に向け,Zelenskiy announces plans to meet with Trump in Florida soon to end the war,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump asema kuna maendeleo katika mazungumzo ya kumaliza vita vya Ukraine","Directly, Trump says there is progress in negotiations to end the war in Ukraine",0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Somaliland inanufaika nini kutambuliwa na Israel?",What does Somaliland benefit from being recognized by Israel?,0.0,"[('Somaliland', 'PRODUCT'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wafahamu wanariadha wanaotarajiwa kugonga vichwa vya habari 2026,Meet the athletes expected to hit the headlines in 2026,-0.1,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tajiri na asiye na sauti: Jinsi Putin alivyowaingiza vitani mabilionea wa Urusi,Rich and silent: How Putin ushered Russia's billionaires into war,0.1875,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Semenyo kutua Liverpool au  Manchester City?,European Football Rumors Monday: Semenyo to land at Liverpool or Manchester City?,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Semenyo', 'PERSON'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini mihuri ya pasipoti inaweza kupitwa na wakati?,Why can passport stamps expire?,0.0,[]
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini awamu ya pili ya usitishaji mapigano Gaza imekwama?,Why is the second phase of the cease-fire in Gaza stalled?,0.0,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mzaha kuhusu upara wangu ulivyobadilisha maisha yangu,How a joke about my baldness changed my life,0.0,[]
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Marekani yafanya shambulizi Nigeria,  dhidi ya nani na kwa nini?","The United States is attacking Nigeria, against whom and why?",0.0,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Muonekano wa Yesu ulikuwa vipi, Wanahistoria wanasema nini?","What was the appearance of Jesus, what do Historians say?",0.0,"[('Jesus', 'PERSON')]"
