Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El misterioso empresario que orquestó un fraude de US$14.000 millones con criptomonedas ""con la tortura y extorsión de sus trabajadores""","The mysterious businessman who orchestrated a US$14 billion fraud with cryptocurrencies ""with the torture and extortion of his workers""",0.0,"[('US$14 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Diez heridos, nueve de ellos graves, en un ataque con arma blanca en un tren que se dirigía a Londres","Ten injured, nine of them seriously, in a knife attack on a train heading to London",-0.16666666666666666,"[('Ten', 'CARDINAL'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Buscando cualquier cosa para comer por las calles: la desesperación en Jamaica tras la devastación causada por el huracán Melissa,Looking for anything to eat on the streets: desperation in Jamaica after the devastation caused by Hurricane Melissa,0.0,"[('Jamaica', 'GPE'), ('Melissa', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Proyecto ""Furia de tormenta"": los intentos de científicos estadounidenses para controlar los huracanes (y qué hemos aprendido de sus experimentos)","Project ""Storm Fury"": American scientists' attempts to control hurricanes (and what we have learned from their experiments)",0.0,"[('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"6 hechos de la vida de Juan Gabriel que destacan en ""Debo, puedo y quiero"", el nuevo documental sobre el Divo de Juárez","6 facts from Juan Gabriel's life that stand out in ""I must, I can and I want"", the new documentary about the Divo de Juárez",0.06818181818181818,"[('6', 'CARDINAL'), (""Juan Gabriel's"", 'PERSON'), ('the Divo de Juárez', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ब्रिटेन: कैम्ब्रिजशर में ट्रेन में चाकू से हमला, नौ लोगों की हालत गंभीर, चश्मदीदों ने क्या बताया","Britain: Knife attack on train in Cambridgeshire, nine people in critical condition, what eyewitnesses told",0.0,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Cambridgeshire', 'GPE'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अनंत सिंह की गिरफ़्तारी पर पवन खेड़ा बोले- 'पीएम का रोड शो है, इसलिए...'","Live, on the arrest of Anant Singh, Pawan Kheda said - 'It is PM's road show, so...'",0.043181818181818175,"[('Anant Singh', 'PERSON'), ('Pawan Kheda', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पश्चिम बंगाल में एसआईआर कराना क्यों मुश्किल हो सकता है? और बिहार चुनाव में यह कितना बड़ा मुद्दा है?,Why can it be difficult to get SIR done in West Bengal? And how big an issue is this in Bihar elections?,-0.25,"[('SIR', 'ORG'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अनंत सिंह: दुलारचंद यादव की हत्या के आरोप में गिरफ़्तार,Anant Singh: Arrested for the murder of Dularchand Yadav.,0.0,"[('Anant Singh', 'PERSON'), ('Dularchand Yadav', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारतीय महिला क्रिकेट के लिए दुनिया मुट्ठी में करने वाला मौक़ा,An opportunity to capture the world for Indian women's cricket.,0.0,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,हिन्दी फ़िल्मों के ब्रांड एंबेसडर और 'रोमांस के किंग' शाहरुख़ ख़ान की कहानी,Story of Hindi films brand ambassador and 'King of Romance' Shahrukh Khan,0.0,[]
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुलिस विभाग और अफ़सरशाही में जातिगत भेदभाव कितना गहरा?,How deep is the caste discrimination in the police department and bureaucracy?,0.0,[]
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,हिमंत बिस्वा सरमा और प्रियांक खड़गे के बीच क्यों छिड़ी तीखी जुबानी जंग?,Why did a heated war of words break out between Himanta Biswa Sarma and Priyank Kharge?,0.0,"[('Himanta Biswa Sarma', 'PERSON'), ('Priyank Kharge', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,'चीन से क़रीबी पर भी ख़त्म नहीं होगा पाकिस्तान से ख़तरा': डॉ. सना हाशमी - इंटरव्यू, अवधि 19,05","Video,'The threat from Pakistan will not end even if we are close to China': Dr. Sana Hashmi - Interview, Duration 19,05",0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Sana Hashmi - Interview', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os mapas que mostram por onde viaja a droga da América Latina para os EUA,Maps that show where drugs travel from Latin America to the USA,0.0,"[('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Policiais sem expertise de território foram expostos no Rio para fazer espetáculo, diz especialista em segurança","Police officers without territorial expertise were exposed in Rio to make a spectacle, says security expert",0.0,"[('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Polícia divulga lista parcial de mortos; apoio à operação é majoritário no Brasil, no Rio e em favelas cariocas, diz pesquisa","Police release partial list of dead; Support for the operation is majority in Brazil, Rio and Rio favelas, says research",-0.15000000000000002,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Rio', 'ORG'), ('Rio', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que grandes empresas de tecnologia como a Amazon estão demitindo milhares de funcionários,Why Big Tech Companies Like Amazon Are Laying Off Thousands of Employees,0.0,[]
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Tumba do faraó Tutancâmon é exibida por inteiro pela primeira vez em novo museu egípcio,Pharaoh Tutankhamun's tomb is displayed in its entirety for the first time in new Egyptian museum,0.19318181818181818,"[(""Pharaoh Tutankhamun's"", 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Egyptian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que namoro entre Katy Perry e Justin Trudeau pode ser bom para a imagem dos dois,Why Katy Perry and Justin Trudeau dating could be good for both their images,0.7,"[('Katy Perry', 'PERSON'), ('Justin Trudeau', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que devemos agradecer a Einstein pelas câmeras dos nossos smartphones,Why we should thank Einstein for our smartphone cameras,0.0,"[('Einstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Ser gay não parecia normal, até eu começar a jogar futebol'",'Being gay didn't seem normal until I started playing football',0.2833333333333333,[]
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A história de amor entre um muçulmano e uma judia durante resgate de pessoas das mãos do Talebã,The love story between a Muslim and a Jewish woman during the rescue of people from the hands of the Taleban,0.25,"[('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('Taleban', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в порту Туапсе из-за атаки беспилотников загорелся танкер; двое погибших при ударе по Днепропетровской области","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: a tanker caught fire in the port of Tuapse due to a drone attack; two killed in an attack in the Dnepropetrovsk region",-0.1625,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Tuapse', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dnepropetrovsk', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Нападение в поезде в Англии: 10 пострадавших, девять из них — с опасными для жизни ранениями","Train attack in England: 10 injured, nine with life-threatening injuries",0.0,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,О вас позаботится робот. Готовы ли мы доверить машинам уход за пожилыми людьми?,The robot will take care of you. Are we ready to trust machines to care for the elderly?,0.2,[]
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Памяти Бориса Максимова — коллеги и замечательного рассказчика,In memory of Boris Maksimov - colleague and wonderful storyteller,1.0,"[('Boris Maksimov - colleague', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Ход королевы». Почему женщины из Казахстана успешнее в шахматах, чем мужчины?","""Queen's Move"" Why are women from Kazakhstan more successful in chess than men?",0.625,"[('Queen\'s Move""', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Kazakhstan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Большой Египетский музей: все сокровища Тутанхамона выставлены на всеобщее обозрение,Grand Egyptian Museum: all the treasures of Tutankhamun are on display,0.5,"[('Grand Egyptian Museum', 'ORG'), ('Tutankhamun', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Ограбление Лувра: ещё двоим задержанным, в том числе женщине, предъявили обвинения","Louvre robbery: two more detainees, including a woman, were charged",0.5,"[('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Revolut начал блокировать счета россиян без вида на жительство в Евросоюзе,Revolut began blocking accounts of Russians without a residence permit in the European Union,0.0,"[('Revolut', 'ORG'), ('Russians', 'NORP'), ('the European Union', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Королевский аналог Сибири»: где будет жить Эндрю, который больше не принц","“The royal analogue of Siberia”: where will Andrew, who is no longer a prince, live?",0.13636363636363635,"[('Siberia', 'LOC'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Экс-президент Украины Леонид Кучма: Третья мировая вряд ли начнется,Former Ukrainian President Leonid Kuchma: World War III is unlikely to start,-0.25,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Leonid Kuchma', 'PERSON'), ('World War III', 'EVENT')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イギリス中部の列車内で複数人刺される　 9人重体と警察発表,Police say nine people are in critical condition after multiple stabbings on train in central England,0.0,"[('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('England', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】アンドリュー・マウントバッテン・ウィンザー氏はここがどん底なのか,[Commentary] Is this the lowest point for Andrew Mountbatten-Windsor?,0.0,"[('Andrew Mountbatten-Windsor', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 ジュフリー氏の回顧録には何が書かれているのか　アンドリュー氏やエプスティーン元被告からの性被害を訴えた女性,[Commentary] What is written in Mr. Giuffre's memoir? A woman who complained of sexual assault by Mr. Andrew and former defendant Epstein,0.06666666666666667,"[('Giuffre', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍の船舶攻撃は「国際法違反」と国連人権トップ　トランプ政権は麻薬密輸船だと主張,"U.S. military ship attack is a ``violation of international law'', UN human rights chief says, Trump administration claims it is a drug smuggling vessel",-0.03333333333333333,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,オランダ総選挙、中道リベラル政党が勝利を宣言　極右与党と接戦,Centrist liberal party declares victory in Dutch general election; close battle with far-right ruling party,0.05000000000000002,"[('Dutch', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タンザニアで選挙めぐり抗議デモ、弾圧で数百人死亡か,Hundreds killed in crackdown on election protests in Tanzania,-0.2,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ハリケーン「メリッサ」、ジャマイカで少なくとも19人死亡　BBC記者が被災地を取材, 所要時間 0,58","Video, Hurricane Melissa kills at least 19 people in Jamaica; BBC reporter covers affected area, Duration 0,58",-0.3,"[('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('at least 19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jamaica', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ政権に食料支援の継続を命令、米連邦2地裁　政府機関の閉鎖中であっても,Two US District Courts Order Trump Administration to Continue Food Assistance Even During Government Shutdown,0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 米中貿易戦争、「休戦」で合意も中国は長期戦の構え,"[Commentary] US-China trade war, ``truce'' agreed, but China is poised for a long war",-0.05,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Samia Suluhu Hassan aliyeshinda uchaguzi kwa zaidi ya asilimia 97 ni nani?,Who is Samia Suluhu Hassan who won the election by more than 97 percent?,0.5,"[('Hassan', 'PERSON'), ('more than 97 percent', 'PERCENT')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Matokeo ya Uchaguzi Tanzania ni kejeli kwa demokrasia - Upinzani","Directly, the Tanzania Election Results are a mockery for democracy - Opposition",0.1,"[('the Tanzania Election Results', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Samia ashinda uchaguzi Tanzania huku mamia wakihofiwa kufariki katika maandamano,Samia wins the elections in Tanzania while hundreds are feared to have died in the protests,0.3,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Bomu la KAB ambalo Urusi inatumia kushambulia miji ya Ukraine ni tishio kiasi gani'?,'How much of a threat is the KAB bomb that Russia is using to attack Ukrainian cities'?,0.2,"[('KAB', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumapili: Aston Villa na Man United zataka kumsajili mshambuliaji wa Brazil  Endrick,European football rumors Sunday: Aston Villa and Man United want to sign Brazilian striker Endrick,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Aston Villa', 'PERSON'), ('Man United', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,20 wafariki kwenye maporomoko ya ardhi katika bonde la Kerio Kenya,20 die in landslides in Kerio valley Kenya,0.0,"[('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kerio valley', 'LOC'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Wapinzani kukamatwa, vurugu na 'ushindi wa kihistoria'- matukio muhimu","Tanzania 2025 elections: Opposition arrested, violence and 'historic victory' - key events",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Uchaguzi umeisha tusimame pamoja kama Taifa' – Hotuba ya Kwanza ya Samia Suluhu,"'The election is over, let's stand together as a Nation' - Samia Suluhu's First Speech",0.25,"[('Nation', 'ORG'), ('First', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Waandamanaji wakaidi amri ya Mkuu wa Majeshi Tanzania,The protesters defied the order of the Chief of Army Staff of Tanzania,0.0,"[('Army', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Bunge la Ulaya laiomba INEC kutotangaza matokeo ya uchaguzi Tanzania,The European Parliament asks INEC not to announce the election results in Tanzania,0.0,"[('The European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
