Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नोबेल शांति पुरस्कार, इसराइल और पाकिस्तान ट्रंप के पक्ष में, जानिए पहले के विवाद","Nobel Peace Prize, Israel and Pakistan in favor of Trump, know earlier controversies",0.0,"[('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मिस्र ने इसराइल को सबसे पहले मान्यता दी थी, वही अब उसे दुश्मन क्यों कह रहा है?","Egypt was the first to recognize Israel, why is it now calling it an enemy?",0.25,"[('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत में बना ये मैसेजिंग ऐप क्या व्हॉट्सऐप को दे पाएगा टक्कर,Will this messaging app made in India be able to compete with WhatsApp?,0.5,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('WhatsApp', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ओटीपी हैकिंग का अंत करेगी ये तकनीक, भारत में हुए शोध का नतीजा","This technology will end OTP hacking, the result of research done in India",0.0,"[('OTP', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सोने की क़ीमतें क्यों बढ़ रही हैं और क्या ये सोना ख़रीदने का सही समय है?,Why are gold prices increasing and is this the right time to buy gold?,0.2857142857142857,[]
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Milionários pagarão mesmo IR de professores e policiais com proposta de Lula: 'É um avanço, mas insuficiente'","Millionaires will even pay IR for teachers and police officers with Lula's proposal: 'It's an advance, but insufficient'",0.0,"[('Millionaires', 'ORG'), ('IR', 'ORG'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Hamas e Israel confirmam primeira fase de acordo para acabar guerra em Gaza,Hamas and Israel confirm first phase of agreement to end war in Gaza,0.25,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Brasileiro é condenado por tentar matar Cristina Kirchner, Duration 0,44","Video,Brazilian is convicted of trying to kill Cristina Kirchner, Duration 0.44",0.0,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Cristina Kirchner', 'PERSON'), ('0.44', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que o Brasil não tem sistema de monitoramento de bebidas alcoólicas?,Why doesn't Brazil have a monitoring system for alcoholic beverages?,-0.25,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,5 mortes por intoxicação de metanol em São Paulo: os números da crise até agora,5 deaths from methanol poisoning in São Paulo: the numbers of the crisis so far,0.1,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('São Paulo', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Petro diz ter 'indícios' de que EUA explodiram barco colombiano: 'Agressão contra toda a América Latina',Petro says he has 'evidence' that the US blew up a Colombian boat: 'Aggression against all of Latin America',0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('Aggression', 'PERSON'), (""Latin America'"", 'LOC')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Brasileiro é obcecado por ricos por 'crença ilusória' na mobilidade social, diz antropólogo que se infiltrou na elite","Brazilians are obsessed with the rich due to 'illusory belief' in social mobility, says anthropologist who infiltrated the elite",-0.05416666666666667,"[('Brazilians', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que governo Trump faz ouro atingir seu preço mais alto em 100 anos?,Why is the Trump administration making gold reach its highest price in 100 years?,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('100 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Mortes de crianças por xaropes para tosse falsificados deixam Índia em alerta,Child deaths from counterfeit cough syrups leave India on alert,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Жиросжигатель для молодежи. Российские подростки скупают запрещенную «Молекулу» благодаря соцсетям и маркетплейсам,Fat burner for youth. Russian teenagers are buying banned Molecule thanks to social networks and marketplaces,0.07777777777777778,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Molecule', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп заявил, что Израиль и ХАМАС согласились с первым этапом мирного урегулирования в Газе",Trump said Israel and Hamas agreed to the first stage of a peace settlement in Gaza,0.25,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Макрон планирует назначить нового премьер-министра Франции в течение 48 часов,Macron plans to appoint a new French prime minister within 48 hours,0.06818181818181818,"[('Macron', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('48 hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: власти сообщили о трех погибших в результате атак на Сумскую область","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: authorities report three dead as a result of attacks on Sumy region",-0.2,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sumy', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Молитесь о нас и о нем». Что известно о деле обвиняемых в покушении на митрополита Тихона Шевкунова,“Pray for us and for him.” What is known about the case of those accused of the assassination attempt on Metropolitan Tikhon Shevkunov,0.0,"[('Metropolitan Tikhon Shevkunov', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Спецпосланник США и зять Трампа присоединились к мирным переговорам по Газе в Египте. СМИ пишут об «осторожном оптимизме»,The US special envoy and Trump's son-in-law have joined Egypt's Gaza peace talks. The media writes about “cautious optimism”,0.35714285714285715,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Эфиопия обвинила Эритрею в сговоре с повстанцами и подготовке к войне,Ethiopia accuses Eritrea of ​​colluding with rebels and preparing for war,0.0,"[('Ethiopia', 'GPE'), ('Eritrea', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что будет с Францией? Рассылка «Контекст»,"What will happen to France? Newsletter ""Context""",0.0,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как нападение на синагогу в Манчестере повлияло на жизнь еврейской общины Британии,How the Manchester synagogue attack affected Britain's Jewish community,0.0,"[('Manchester', 'PRODUCT'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Jewish', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нобелевскую премию по химии присудили за разработку новых металлоорганических соединений. Они могут стать «материалом XXI века»,The Nobel Prize in Chemistry was awarded for the development of new organometallic compounds. They can become “the material of the 21st century”,0.06818181818181818,"[('The Nobel Prize in Chemistry', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the 21st century', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエルとハマス、ガザ和平案の第1段階に合意　トランプ氏と当事者が発表,Israel and Hamas agree to first phase of Gaza peace plan announced by Trump and parties involved,0.25,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ガザ住民ら歓喜、「戦争と流血を止めようとしてくれた」人々に感謝　和平案の第1段階合意, 所要時間 0,45","Video, Gaza residents rejoice as they thank those who ""tried to stop war and bloodshed""; first phase of peace plan agreed, Duration 0,45",0.25,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノーベル化学賞、北川進氏ら3人に　地球規模の問題解決に役立つ新素材を開発,Nobel Prize in Chemistry awarded to Susumu Kitagawa and three others for developing new materials that will help solve global problems,0.06818181818181818,"[('Nobel Prize in Chemistry', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Susumu Kitagawa', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナがロシア西部を攻撃、3人死亡　3日連続で空爆,"Ukraine attacks western Russia, kills 3 people, carries out airstrikes for 3rd day in a row",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('3rd day in a row', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,元FBI長官のコーミー氏、無罪を主張　米上院での偽証疑惑めぐり,元FBI長官のコーミー氏、無罪を主張　米上院での偽証疑惑めぐり,0.0,[]
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,急増するスマホ盗難、ロンドン警視庁の捜査を取材　昨年は4万台が中国へ, 所要時間 2,48","Video, coverage of the London Metropolitan Police's investigation into the rapidly increasing number of smartphone thefts, 40,000 smartphones went to China last year, time required 2,48",0.0,"[(""the London Metropolitan Police's"", 'ORG'), ('40,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('last year', 'DATE'), ('2,48', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ハマスのイスラエル襲撃から2年……各地で集会、ガザでは攻撃続く　エジプトで交渉2日目,"Two years since Hamas attacked Israel... Gatherings in various places, attacks continue in Gaza, second day of negotiations in Egypt",0.0,"[('Two years', 'DATE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('second day', 'DATE'), ('Egypt', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノーベル物理学賞、米国拠点の3教授に　量子コンピューターの基礎技術を発見,Nobel Prize in Physics awarded to three US-based professors for discovering fundamental technology for quantum computers,0.0,"[('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Physics', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「あまりにも多くを失った」　戦争開始から2年の犠牲を見つめるパレスチナ人たち,'We've lost too much' - Palestinians look at the sacrifices made two years after the start of the war,0.2,"[('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('two years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump asema awamu ya kwanza ya makubaliano ya amani ya Gaza yamefikiwa","Directly, Trump says the first phase of the Gaza peace agreement has been reached",0.175,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ethiopia yaishutumu Eritrea kwa kujiandaa kwa vita huku mvutano wa Bahari ya Shamu ukiongezeka,Ethiopia accuses Eritrea of ​​preparing for the war as the Red Sea tensions increase,0.0,"[('Ethiopia', 'GPE'), ('Eritrea', 'GPE'), ('Red Sea', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, baadhi ya watu huzaliwa wakiwa dhaifu katika hisabati?",Are some people born weak in mathematics?,-0.375,[]
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Alhamisi: Fernandes anataka kusalia Man Utd,European football rumors on Thursday: Fernandes wants to remain Man utd,0.1,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Fernandes', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Shirika la Amnesty International lazitaka mamlaka za Tanzania kufichua alipo Polepole,Amnesty International wants Tanzanian authorities to expose her,0.1,"[('Amnesty International', 'ORG'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Simulizi ya marubani wa Marekani kuhusu usiku ambao Iran ilishambulia Israel kwa mara ya kwanza,US pilots' story about the night that Iran attacked Israel for the first time,0.25,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('about the night', 'TIME'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mama Polepole: Nirudishieni mwanangu akiwa hai au amekufa,Mother slowly: Return me to my son alive or dead,-0.13333333333333333,[]
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ronaldo atajwa kuwa mwanasoka wa kwanza bilionea,Ronaldo will be named the first billionaire football,0.25,"[('Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Mambo matatu yanayoutofautisha uchaguzi wa Zanzibar na Tanzania,ELECTION TANZANIA 2025: Three things that distinguish Zanzibar and Tanzania elections,0.0,"[('2025', 'CARDINAL'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Zanzibar', 'NORP'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Waridi wa BBC: Msichana mfupi zaidi Kenya anayevikabili vizingiti alivyowekewa na jamii,BBC Roses: The shortest Kenyan girl facing the thresholds she has placed by the community,0.0,"[('BBC Roses', 'ORG'), ('Kenyan', 'NORP')]"
