Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La instalación secreta a la que tuvo acceso la BBC y en la que Ucrania fabrica misiles de largo alcance,The secret facility to which the BBC had access and where Ukraine manufactures long-range missiles,-0.4,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo logró Colombia convertirse en una de las mejores economías de 2025 y qué retos afronta,How Colombia managed to become one of the best economies of 2025 and what challenges it faces,1.0,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Trump amplía el acceso a la marihuana en el mayor cambio de la política de drogas de EE.UU. en décadas,Trump expands access to marijuana in biggest shift in US drug policy in decades,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Condenan a cadena perpetua al ""Doctor Muerte"" que envenenó a decenas de pacientes en Francia","""Doctor Death"" who poisoned dozens of patients in France is sentenced to life in prison",0.0,"[('Death', 'PERSON'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La mujer del video viral del concierto de Coldplay habla por primera vez de los abusos y amenazas que sufrió,The woman in the viral video of the Coldplay concert speaks for the first time about the abuse and threats she suffered,0.25,"[('Coldplay', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"शरीफ़ उस्मान हादी कौन थे, जिनकी मौत के बाद बांग्लादेश में भड़की हिंसा","Who was Sharif Usman Hadi, after whose death violence broke out in Bangladesh?",0.0,"[('Sharif Usman Hadi', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,लोकसभा और राज्यसभा अनिश्चितकाल के लिए स्थगित, जानिए अहम बातें","Live, Lok Sabha and Rajya Sabha adjourned indefinitely, know important things",0.2681818181818182,"[('Lok Sabha', 'PERSON'), ('Rajya Sabha', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पाकिस्तान का कबड्डी प्लेयर 'भारत' की तरफ़ से खेला और झंडा भी लहराया, अब करियर पर लटकी तलवार","Pakistan's Kabaddi player played for 'India' and also waved the flag, now his career is in danger.",0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Kabaddi', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नौ साल से फरार चल रहे एक हत्यारे को बिस्किट के एक पैकेट ने कैसे पकड़वाया?,How did a packet of biscuits catch a murderer who had been on the run for nine years?,0.0,"[('nine years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'मैं कभी दिल्ली वापस नहीं जाऊँगी'... बांग्लादेश भेजी गई और फिर भारत आने वाली सुनाली ख़ातून की कहानी,'I will never go back to Delhi'... The story of Sunali Khatoon who was sent to Bangladesh and then came to India,0.0,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Sunali Khatoon', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बांग्लादेश: हसनत अब्दुल्लाह ने अब भारतीय उच्चायुक्त को निकालने के लिए कहा, तौहीद हुसैन ने भी भारत पर उठाया सवाल","Bangladesh: Hasnat Abdullah now asked to expel Indian High Commissioner, Tauheed Hussain also raised questions on India",0.16,"[('Hasnat Abdullah', 'PERSON'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Tauheed Hussain', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"अभिनेत्री निधि अग्रवाल के बेक़ाबू भीड़ से घिरने से जुड़े मामले में केस दर्ज, सोशल मीडिया पर क्या कह रहे हैं लोग?","Case registered in connection with actress Nidhi Agarwal being surrounded by uncontrollable crowd, what are people saying on social media?",0.03333333333333333,"[('Nidhi Agarwal', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,न्यूक्लियर एनर्जी क्या है और भारत इसमें पीछे क्यों है?,What is nuclear energy and why is India lagging behind in it?,-0.4,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"हिजाब विवाद को पाकिस्तान ने बताया 'शर्मनाक', नीतीश कुमार के बचाव में उतरे गिरिराज सिंह","Pakistan called Hijab controversy 'shameful', Giriraj Singh came to the defense of Nitish Kumar",0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Hijab', 'ORG'), ('Giriraj Singh', 'PERSON'), ('Nitish', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Câmara decide cassar mandatos de Eduardo Bolsonaro e Alexandre Ramagem: o que pesa contra eles?,Chamber decides to revoke the mandates of Eduardo Bolsonaro and Alexandre Ramagem: what counts against them?,0.0,"[('Eduardo Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Alexandre Ramagem', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula diz que vetará projeto de redução de penas que beneficia Bolsonaro: 'Cometeram um crime contra a democracia',Lula says he will veto sentence reduction project that benefits Bolsonaro: 'They committed a crime against democracy',0.0,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Acordo UE-Mercosul, Trump e Venezuela: os recados da entrevista de Lula","EU-Mercosur Agreement, Trump and Venezuela: the messages from Lula's interview",0.0,"[('EU-Mercosur Agreement', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,TikTok assina acordo para vender operação nos EUA,TikTok signs agreement to sell operation in the US,0.0,"[('TikTok', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que governo Trump pode promover maior mudança na política de drogas dos EUA em décadas,Why the Trump administration could bring about the biggest change in US drug policy in decades,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula: 'Ataque de Zezé di Camargo a filhas de Silvio Santos foi cretinice',Lula: 'Zezé di Camargo's attack on Silvio Santos' daughters was stupid',-0.7999999999999999,"[(""Zezé di Camargo's"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), (""Silvio Santos'"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Eleitor com medo da violência tem chance enorme de votar contra Lula, diz Felipe Nunes, da Quaest","Voters afraid of violence have a huge chance of voting against Lula, says Felipe Nunes, from Quaest",-0.09999999999999995,"[('Lula', 'PRODUCT'), ('Felipe Nunes', 'ORG'), ('Quaest', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Os mistérios e as descobertas sobre o cometa 3I/Atlas, que está de passagem pelo Sistema Solar","The mysteries and discoveries about comet 3I/Atlas, which is passing through the Solar System",0.0,"[('the Solar System', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Sofri um estupro coletivo no dia do meu casamento','I was gang-raped on my wedding day',0.0,[]
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Лидеры ЕС договорились выделить Украине 90 млрд евро. Замороженные российские активы при этом использоваться не будут,EU leaders agreed to allocate 90 billion euros to Ukraine. Frozen Russian assets will not be used in this case,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('90 billion', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Frozen Russian', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Небоевые и непризнанные: самоубийства в украинской армии, о которых молчат","Non-combat and unrecognized: suicides in the Ukrainian army, which are silent",0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Режиссер Роб Райнер: шесть классических фильмов «гения с большим сердцем»,Director Rob Reiner: six classic films from a 'genius with a big heart',0.08333333333333333,"[('Rob Reiner', 'PERSON'), ('six', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский поблагодарил лидеров ЕС за решение о финансовой поддержке Украины","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky thanked EU leaders for the decision to provide financial support to Ukraine",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Кеннеди-центр переименуют в Трамп-Кеннеди-центр,Kennedy Center to be renamed Trump Kennedy Center,-0.1,"[('Kennedy Center', 'FAC'), ('Trump Kennedy', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Госдума приняла закон, отменяющий ежегодные декларации госслужащих о доходах. Почему это важно?",The State Duma adopted a law abolishing the annual income declarations of civil servants. Why is this important?,0.4,"[('The State Duma', 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Подкастер и конспиролог Дэн Бонджино уходит с поста замдиректора ФБР,Podcaster and conspiracy theorist Dan Bongino steps down as FBI deputy director,-0.15555555555555559,"[('Dan Bongino', 'PERSON'), ('FBI', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Кристин Кэбот, попавшая на «камеру для поцелуев» на концерте Coldplay, рассказала об угрозах и шейминге","Christine Cabot, who was caught on a “kissing camera” at a Coldplay concert, spoke about threats and shaming",0.0,"[('Christine Cabot', 'PERSON'), ('Coldplay', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Туда и обратно: как украинский подросток сбежал из Финляндии в Россию,There and back: how a Ukrainian teenager ran away from Finland to Russia,0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Finland', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Политзаключенные в обмен на санкции. Какую выгоду дипломатия приносит Трампу и Лукашенко?,Political prisoners in exchange for sanctions. How does diplomacy benefit Trump and Lukashenko?,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Lukashenko', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU、ウクライナへ900億ユーロ融資で合意　凍結ロシア資産は使わず,EU agrees to loan 90 billion euros to Ukraine without using frozen Russian assets,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('90 billion', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,TikTokのアメリカ事業売却、オーナーが契約締結,Owner signs deal to sell TikTok's U.S. business,0.0,"[('TikTok', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ブラウン大学銃撃、容疑者を遺体で発見　MIT教授殺害にも関係か,Brown University shooting suspect found dead; may be related to MIT professor's murder,-0.1,"[('Brown University', 'ORG'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,カンボジア・ポイペト付近をタイが爆撃　カジノと国境検問所の町,"Thailand bombs near Poipet, Cambodia - casino and border crossing town",0.1,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Poipet', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日銀が利上げ決定、1995年以降で最高水準に　インフレ圧力の中,Bank of Japan decides to raise interest rates to highest level since 1995 amid inflationary pressures,0.0,"[('Bank of Japan', 'ORG'), ('1995', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】EUはロシア凍結資産を使う対ウクライナ融資を認めるか　ゼレンスキー氏は必要性を強調,[Commentary] Will the EU approve financing to Ukraine using frozen Russian assets? Mr. Zelenskyy emphasizes the necessity,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Zelenskyy', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「ロリータ」の引用が女性の体に書かれ　エプスティーン元被告関連の写真、米民主党がさらに公開,US Democratic Party releases more photos of former Epstein defendant with 'Lolita' quote written on woman's body,0.25,"[('US Democratic Party', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Lolita', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシア富豪アブラモヴィッチ氏に英首相が警告、チェルシー売却益を「今すぐ拠出せよ」　法的措置も示唆,"British Prime Minister warns Russian billionaire Abramovich to ""donate the proceeds from sale of Chelsea immediately"", suggesting legal action",0.07500000000000001,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ウクライナで拡大する兵器製造、秘密のミサイル工場を取材, 所要時間 3,05","Video, Expanding weapons manufacturing and secret missile factories in Ukraine, Duration 3,05",-0.4,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,EU yaamua kukopa fedha kusaidia Ukraine badala ya kutumia mali za Urusi","Directly, the EU decides to borrow money to help Ukraine instead of using Russian assets",0.05,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Unyanyapaa wa wanajeshi wa Ukraine 'walikufa kwa njia mbaya',Stigma of Ukrainian soldiers 'died the wrong way',-0.5,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Man Utd kumsajili Semenyo Januari,European Football Rumors Friday: Man Utd to sign Semenyo in January,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Semenyo', 'PERSON'), ('January', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi ya kujilinda dhidi ya walaghai  mitandaoni msimu wa Krismasi,How to protect yourself from online fraudsters this Christmas season,0.0,"[('this Christmas season', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanawake 10 waliobadili mwelekeo wa Afrika mwaka 2025,10 women who changed the direction of Africa in 2025,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hiki ndicho kiwanda cha siri cha makombora mapya ya 'kumtetemesha' Putin,This is the secret factory of new missiles to 'shake' Putin,-0.13181818181818183,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Zifahamu familia 5 tajiri zaidi duniani,Get to know the 5 richest families in the world,0.0,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Zirkzee njia panda Roma,European Football Rumors: Zirkzee cross paths with Roma,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Roma', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marekani yaweka vikwazo vipya kwa wasafiri kutoka Tanzania,The United States imposes new restrictions on travelers from Tanzania,0.13636363636363635,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwenda haja kubwa mara tu baada ya kula kunaashiria  ugonjwa?,Going to defecate immediately after eating indicates a disease?,0.0,[]
