Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué resultados dio uno de los experimentos más ambiciosos del mundo para aumentar la natalidad de un país,What results did one of the most ambitious experiments in the world give to increase the birth rate of a country?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo el creciente y brutal conflicto interno de Colombia define sus elecciones presidenciales,How Colombia's growing and brutal internal conflict defines its presidential elections,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Irán anuncia el cierre del estrecho de Ormuz en respuesta a los ataques de Israel contra el Líbano,Iran announces closure of the Strait of Hormuz in response to Israel's attacks on Lebanon,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Incendios, robos y amor: qué hacen los agentes de IA cuando los humanos no los vigilan","Fires, robberies and love: what AI agents do when humans are not watching them",0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Muere una mujer y desalojan a 1.700 turistas en República Dominicana por un incendio voraz en un hotel de lujo,"A woman dies and 1,700 tourists are evacuated in the Dominican Republic due to a raging fire in a luxury hotel",0.0,neutral,"[('1,700', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Dominican Republic', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Uno de los mayores misterios sin resolver de la historia británica"": el conde que desapareció tras asesinar a la niñera de sus hijos","""One of the greatest unsolved mysteries in British history"": the earl who disappeared after murdering his children's nanny",1.0,positive,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El ataque a una refinería en Moscú acerca la guerra de Rusia contra Ucrania a territorio ruso,The attack on a refinery in Moscow brings Russia's war against Ukraine closer to Russian territory,-1.0,negative,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué nos puede enseñar el Crash de 1929 sobre los peligros que enfrenta la economía en la actualidad,What the Crash of 1929 can teach us about the dangers facing the economy today,0.0,neutral,"[('1929', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué tipo de país representan De la Espriella y Cepeda, los antagónicos aspirantes a presidir Colombia","What type of country do De la Espriella and Cepeda, the antagonistic candidates to preside over Colombia, represent?",0.0,neutral,"[('De la Espriella and Cepeda', 'ORG'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Islandia, el país ártico que nunca tuvo ejército y ahora tiene que replantearse su defensa","Iceland, the Arctic country that never had an army and now has to rethink its defense",0.0,neutral,"[('Iceland', 'GPE'), ('Arctic', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,गोरक्षा के नाम पर ह‍िंसा झेलने के बाद पीड़‍ितों की ज़‍िंदगी में क्‍या बदल जाता है,What changes in the lives of victims after facing violence in the name of cow protection?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,अमेरिका और ईरान वार्ता: स्विट्ज़रलैंड में किन मध्यस्थ देशों के नेता पहुंचे, अब तक क्या-कुछ हुआ","Live, America and Iran talks: Leaders of which mediator countries reached Switzerland, what has happened so far",0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"गाड़ियों पर नंबर प्लेट लगाने की परंपरा कब, कहां और क्यों शुरू हुई?","When, where and why did the tradition of putting number plates on vehicles start?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी: अभिजीत दीपके ने की नई अपील, जंतर-मंतर पर रात भर क्या-क्या हुआ","Cockroach Janata Party: Abhijeet Deepke made a new appeal, what happened at Jantar Mantar overnight",0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG'), ('Abhijeet Deepke', 'PERSON'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका-ईरान समझौते में पाकिस्तान की बढ़ी अहमियत, क्या भारत के लिए है इसमें कोई सबक- द लेंस","Pakistan's importance increased in US-Iran agreement, is there any lesson in this for India - The Lens",0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वाराणसी की मस्जिद पर पाकिस्तान के बयान को लेकर भारत की तीखी प्रतिक्रिया, क्या है पूरा मामला","India's sharp reaction to Pakistan's statement on Varanasi mosque, what is the whole matter",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Varanasi', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"होर्मुज़ बंद करने के ईरानी दावे के बाद जेडी वेंस बातचीत के लिए स्विट्ज़रलैंड रवाना, क्या संकट में है समझौता","After Iranian claim to close Hormuz, JD Vance leaves for Switzerland for talks, is the agreement in trouble?",0.0,neutral,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('JD Vance', 'PERSON'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"नीट की दोबारा परीक्षा आज, जानिए पेपर लीक से लेकर अबू धाबी में सेंटर देने तक सब कुछ","NEET re-exam today, know everything from paper leak to giving center in Abu Dhabi",0.0,neutral,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('Abu Dhabi', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पत्नी को 120 पुरुषों से यौन संबंध बनाने के लिए किया मजबूर, ऐसे भागकर महिला ने पुलिस को बताई आपबीती","Wife forced to have sex with 120 men, woman ran away and told her ordeal to police",0.0,neutral,"[('120', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,एमबीए करने की जगह क्या प्लम्बर बनने का दौर है? मुख्य आर्थिक सलाहकार के दावे में कितना दम,Is it time to become a plumber instead of doing MBA? How much truth is there in the Chief Economic Advisor's claim?,0.0,neutral,"[('MBA', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Que tipo de Colômbia representam De la Espriella e Cepeda, adversários no 2º turno da eleição deste domingo","What kind of Colombia do De la Espriella and Cepeda, opponents in the 2nd round of this Sunday's election, represent?",0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('De la Espriella and Cepeda', 'ORG'), ('2nd', 'ORDINAL'), ('Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que aconteceu com país que prometeu R$ 170 mil para quem tivesse dois filhos,"What happened to a country that promised R$170,000 to anyone with two children?",0.0,neutral,"[('R$170,000', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Bishkek, a moderna capital onde herança soviética é destruída","Bishkek, the modern capital where Soviet heritage is destroyed",0.0,neutral,"[('Bishkek', 'ORG'), ('Soviet', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Irã acusa EUA e Israel de violar novo acordo de cessar-fogo e anuncia fechamento do estreito de Ormuz,Iran accuses US and Israel of violating new ceasefire agreement and announces closure of Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Strait of', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que caso Mariana Ferrer se tornou emblemático e será julgado de novo após decisão do STF,Why the Mariana Ferrer case became emblematic and will be tried again after the STF’s decision,0.0,neutral,"[('Mariana Ferrer', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As extraordinárias pessoas resistentes ao HIV - e como elas podem ser peça-chave no combate ao vírus,The extraordinary people resistant to HIV - and how they can be a key player in combating the virus,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,XG: como grupo pop do Japão encarou treinamento intenso de 5 anos — e chegou ao sucesso global,XG: how a pop group from Japan faced intense training for 5 years — and achieved global success,1.0,positive,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('5 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o polêmico bilionário de tecnologia Peter Thiel se mudou para a Argentina e qual sua ligação com Javier Milei,Why controversial technology billionaire Peter Thiel moved to Argentina and what is his connection with Javier Milei,0.0,neutral,"[('Peter Thiel', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Javier Milei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Misantropia': a mensagem enviada com alerta pela Defesa Nacional após invasão hacker,'Misanthropy': the message sent with warning by National Defense after hacker invasion,-1.0,negative,"[('Misanthropy', 'PERSON'), ('National Defense', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil x Escócia: qual resultado a Seleção precisa para se classificar na liderança do grupo?,Brazil x Scotland: what result does the Seleção need to qualify at the top of the group?,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Seleção', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский сообщил об ударах по объектам России «по обе стороны Крымского моста», в Крыму прекращена продажа топлива","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky reported strikes on Russian targets “on both sides of the Crimean Bridge”, fuel sales have been stopped in Crimea",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Crimean Bridge', 'EVENT'), ('Crimea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Швейцарии начнутся переговоры США и Ирана,US-Iran talks to begin in Switzerland,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Величайшее достижение человечества в исследовании космоса». Как «Вояджеры» изменили наши представления о Солнечной системе,"""Mankind's greatest achievement in space exploration."" How Voyagers changed our understanding of the solar system",1.0,positive,[]
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Льготные кредиты при условии рождения детей. Как «семейная политика» Венгрии оставила многие семьи с непосильными долгами,Preferential loans subject to the birth of children. How Hungary's 'family policy' left many families with crippling debt,0.0,neutral,"[('Hungary', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Зеленский отправил в Польшу орден Белого орла, которого его лишил президент Навроцкий","Zelensky sent the Order of the White Eagle to Poland, which President Nawrocki deprived him of",0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('the Order of the White Eagle', 'PERSON'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Nawrocki', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Моя популярность — не ваше дело». Премьер Италии Джорджа Мелони ответила Трампу на очередной поток колкостей в свой адрес,“My popularity is none of your business.” Italian Prime Minister Giorgia Meloni responded to Trump for another stream of barbs directed at her,0.0,neutral,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Giorgia Meloni', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Наступил ли перелом в войне России с Украиной?,Has there been a turning point in the war between Russia and Ukraine?,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Быстрее, выше, старше: как изменилось телосложение лучших футболистов планеты за 50 лет","Faster, taller, older: how the physique of the best football players on the planet has changed over 50 years",0.0,neutral,"[('50 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Возвращение Белого орла. Пять последствий отзыва президентом Польши награды у президента Украины,Return of the White Eagle. Five consequences of the President of Poland revoking an award from the President of Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('the White Eagle', 'ORG'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Иран объявил о закрытии Ормузского пролива в ответ на продолжение боевых действий в Ливане,Iran announced the closure of the Strait of Hormuz in response to continued fighting in Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本、チュニジアを4-0で下す　最も一方的な試合で初勝利,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Japan defeats Tunisia 4-0, first victory in the most one-sided match",1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Tunisia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イランがホルムズ海峡の再封鎖を発表、イスラエルによるレバノン攻撃が理由と　米軍は封鎖を否定,"Iran announces re-blocking of the Strait of Hormuz, citing Israel's attack on Lebanon as the reason, US military denies blockade",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】　いったい何のための戦争だったのか……米・イラン合意で浮かぶ避けがたい疑問　BBC国際編集長,[Commentary] What on earth was the war for? Unavoidable questions that arise in the US-Iran agreement BBC International Editor-in-Chief,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('BBC International', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英与党の内部、スターマー首相に退任予定示すよう圧力高まる　閣僚や議員から,Pressure grows within Britain's ruling party on Prime Minister Starmer to announce plans to step down from ministers and MPs,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエルとヒズボラ、停戦で合意とアメリカが発表　発効後もレバノンでは空爆の報告相次ぐ,Israel and Hezbollah agree to ceasefire; US announces ceasefire; reports of airstrikes continue to occur in Lebanon even after it takes effect,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イタリア首相、トランプ氏が自分について「でまかせ」と反発　単発的な口論ではなく,"Italian Prime Minister criticizes Trump, calling him a ``fake'' It's not just a one-off argument",0.0,neutral,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イングランド中部で旅客列車同士が衝突　運転士1人死亡、89人負傷,"Passenger trains collide in central England; 1 driver killed, 89 injured",-1.0,negative,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('89', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英下院補選、労働党のバーナム市長が当選　党首選でスターマー首相への挑戦の道開く,"Labor Party's Mayor Burnham wins British House of Commons by-election, paving the way for challenge to Prime Minister Starmer in leadership race",1.0,positive,"[(""Labor Party's"", 'ORG'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('British House of Commons', 'ORG'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、モスクワに最大規模の攻撃で製油所直撃　地面や服に黒い染みと住民,"Ukraine's largest attack hits Moscow refinery, leaving residents with black stains on ground and clothes",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカがイランの海上封鎖を解除　イラン最高指導者はトランプ氏が「絶望」して合意と,"US lifts naval blockade of Iran; Iran's supreme leader says Trump is ""desperate"" to agree",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Mazungumzo ya Marekani na Iran kuanza Uswisi","Directly, US-Iran talks begin in Switzerland",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Dunia yasherehekea Siku ya Baba huku mjadala wa malezi ukiongezeka,The world celebrates Father's Day as the discussion of parenting increases,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mkataba wa Iran wamuweka Netanyahu katika changamoto kubwa kisiasa,The Iran deal puts Netanyahu in a big political challenge,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ugonjwa nadra unaomfanya mtu amjue kile anayemuona,A rare disease that makes a person know what he sees,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wakati mila za mazishi zinapokutana na tishio la Ebola,When funeral traditions meet the threat of Ebola,0.0,neutral,"[('Ebola', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Chelsea wanafikiria kumnunua Wirtz,European Football Rumors: Chelsea are considering a move for Wirtz,0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Chelsea', 'PERSON'), ('Wirtz', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tunafunga Mlango-Bahari wa Hormuz - Iran,We are closing the Strait of Hormuz - Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ivory Coast yaumizwa dakika za mwisho na Ujerumani,World Cup 2026: Ivory Coast is hurt in the last minutes by Germany,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Ivory Coast', 'LOC'), ('the last minutes', 'TIME'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ratiba, msimamo na matokeo","World Cup 2026: Schedule, standings and results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la dunia 2026: Kanuni mpya za FIFA zatikisa hesabu za kufuzu,World Cup 2026: New FIFA rules shake up qualifying calculations,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup Day 11: Spain face Saudi Arabia as Iran’s travel issues persist,World Cup Day 11: Spain face Saudi Arabia as Iran’s travel issues persist,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day 11', 'EVENT'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US-Iran talks in Switzerland: Is Lebanon top of agenda; who is attending?,US-Iran talks in Switzerland: Is Lebanon top of agenda; who is attending?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Vance arrives in Switzerland for US-Iran talks,Vance arrives in Switzerland for US-Iran talks,0.0,neutral,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 114: Tehran warns of halting oil flow ahead of talks,Iran war day 114: Tehran warns of halting oil flow ahead of talks,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('114', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ueda’s brace helps Japan knock Tunisia out of World Cup 2026,Ueda’s brace helps Japan knock Tunisia out of World Cup 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('Ueda', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Tunisia', 'GPE'), ('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup knockouts: Who has made it to the round of 32 stage?,World Cup knockouts: Who has made it to the round of 32 stage?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Egypt coach denies Salah rift as Pharaohs seek first World Cup win,Egypt coach denies Salah rift as Pharaohs seek first World Cup win,1.0,positive,"[('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Salah', 'NORP'), ('Pharaohs', 'PRODUCT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Eloy gives no Room as tiny Curacao hold Ecuador, earn first World Cup point","Eloy gives no Room as tiny Curacao hold Ecuador, earn first World Cup point",0.0,neutral,"[('Curacao', 'PERSON'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"US, Iran set to hold talks on Lebanon truce, Tehran’s nuclear programme","US, Iran set to hold talks on Lebanon truce, Tehran’s nuclear programme",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US refuses to ease World Cup travel restrictions for Iranian team,US refuses to ease World Cup travel restrictions for Iranian team,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Over 60 workers hospitalised following ammonia gas leak in seafood factory in Tamil Nadu,Over 60 workers hospitalised following ammonia gas leak in seafood factory in Tamil Nadu,1.0,positive,"[('60', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,NEET-UG 2026: 2.2 million aspiring medical students appear for re-exam amid tight security,NEET-UG 2026: 2.2 million aspiring medical students appear for re-exam amid tight security,0.0,neutral,"[('2.2 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Iran says can't enter final U.S. deal talks without end to Lebanon war | LIVE,Iran says can't enter final U.S. deal talks without end to Lebanon war | LIVE,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"India’s ODI team for England tour: Kohli named in squad, subject to fitness clearance","India’s ODI team for England tour: Kohli named in squad, subject to fitness clearance",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Kohli', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Can AI crack UPSC? How technology is disrupting India’s coaching industry,Can AI crack UPSC? How technology is disrupting India’s coaching industry,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Congress makes strong pitch for making right to vote a fundamental right,Congress makes strong pitch for making right to vote a fundamental right,0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Decoupling footpaths from accidents,Decoupling footpaths from accidents,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Panel sets deadline for Meghalaya govt. to stop ‘faceless’ illegal coal trade,Panel sets deadline for Meghalaya govt. to stop ‘faceless’ illegal coal trade,0.0,neutral,"[('Meghalaya', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"International Yoga Day 2026 LIVE: Leaders, yoga enthusiasts participate in celebrations across India","International Yoga Day 2026 LIVE: Leaders, yoga enthusiasts participate in celebrations across India",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Similipal’s black tigers are getting help,Similipal’s black tigers are getting help,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US-Iran talks to begin in Switzerland as Tehran says it closed Strait of Hormuz,US-Iran talks to begin in Switzerland as Tehran says it closed Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,BBC sees destroyed villages in Israeli-occupied southern Lebanon,BBC sees destroyed villages in Israeli-occupied southern Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Lebanese turtle conservationist Mona Khalil killed by Israeli strike,Lebanese turtle conservationist Mona Khalil killed by Israeli strike,-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanese', 'NORP'), ('Mona Khalil', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Colombia's escalating, brutal internal conflict is defining its presidential election","Colombia's escalating, brutal internal conflict is defining its presidential election",-1.0,negative,"[('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Former Olympian denies vandalising Washington Reflecting Pool after arrest,Former Olympian denies vandalising Washington Reflecting Pool after arrest,0.0,neutral,"[('Olympian', 'NORP'), ('Washington Reflecting Pool', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Meloni tells Trump to 'focus on your own popularity' as row escalates,Meloni tells Trump to 'focus on your own popularity' as row escalates,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Israeli strikes kill six people in Gaza including Al Jazeera cameraman, officials say","Israeli strikes kill six people in Gaza including Al Jazeera cameraman, officials say",-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Al Jazeera', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Zelensky returns highest Polish honour after award stripped,Zelensky returns highest Polish honour after award stripped,-1.0,negative,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Polish', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,France bans alcohol at music festival events under red heatwave alert,France bans alcohol at music festival events under red heatwave alert,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US to stop funding HIV programmes in South Africa,US to stop funding HIV programmes in South Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mideast Live Updates: New Round of U.S.-Iran Talks Set to Start in Switzerland,Mideast Live Updates: New Round of U.S.-Iran Talks Set to Start in Switzerland,0.0,neutral,"[('Mideast Live Updates: New Round', 'ORG'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Women Running Businesses Under Taliban Rules,The Women Running Businesses Under Taliban Rules,0.0,neutral,"[('The Women Running Businesses', 'ORG'), ('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Neither the War Nor Trump’s Deal Terminated the Main Threats in Iran, Analysts Say","Neither the War Nor Trump’s Deal Terminated the Main Threats in Iran, Analysts Say",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Analysts Say', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Luxury Kushner Project Collides With Albanian Discontent,Luxury Kushner Project Collides With Albanian Discontent,0.0,neutral,"[('Luxury Kushner Project Collides With Albanian Discontent', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Colombia’s High-Stakes Election: What to Know About the Candidates, Issues and Expected Results","Colombia’s High-Stakes Election: What to Know About the Candidates, Issues and Expected Results",0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Wife of Spanish Prime Minister to Stand Trial for Corruption,Wife of Spanish Prime Minister to Stand Trial for Corruption,0.0,neutral,"[('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Father and Uncle of Slain New York Girl Given Life Sentences in Pakistan,Father and Uncle of Slain New York Girl Given Life Sentences in Pakistan,0.0,neutral,"[('Uncle', 'PERSON'), ('Slain New York Girl Given Life Sentences', 'ORG'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"After Andy Burnham’s Win, the UK Is Set to Test How Far Charisma Can Shift Electoral Dynamics","After Andy Burnham’s Win, the UK Is Set to Test How Far Charisma Can Shift Electoral Dynamics",1.0,positive,"[('Andy Burnham’s Win', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A 175-Year-Old Shipwreck, Lots of Booze and a Korean Island’s Quest to Survive","A 175-Year-Old Shipwreck, Lots of Booze and a Korean Island’s Quest to Survive",0.0,neutral,"[('175-Year-Old Shipwreck', 'DATE'), ('a Korean Island’s Quest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Huge Blaze Ravages Dominican Republic Beach Resort,Huge Blaze Ravages Dominican Republic Beach Resort,0.0,neutral,"[('Republic Beach', 'GPE')]"
