Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es Paul Biya, el presidente más longevo del mundo que dirige Camerún desde hace cuatro décadas y vive parte del año en Suiza","Who is Paul Biya, the oldest president in the world who has led Cameroon for four decades and lives part of the year in Switzerland",0.0,"[('Paul Biya', 'PERSON'), ('Cameroon', 'FAC'), ('four decades', 'DATE'), ('the year', 'DATE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El huracán Melissa alcanza la categoría 5 y llega a Jamaica, donde deja al menos 3 muertos","Hurricane Melissa reaches category 5 and reaches Jamaica, where it leaves at least 3 dead",-0.25,"[('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jamaica', 'GPE'), ('at least 3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Trump no tiene ninguna intención de invadir; todo es una operación psicológica"": Elliott Abrams, exenviado de EE.UU. para Venezuela","""Trump has no intention of invading; everything is a psychological operation"": Elliott Abrams, former US envoy for Venezuela",0.0,"[('Elliott Abrams', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cuáles son las razones que explican el triunfo de Milei en las elecciones legislativas de Argentina en medio de crisis y escándalos (y qué efecto tuvo Trump),What are the reasons that explain Milei's victory in the Argentine legislative elections in the midst of crises and scandals (and what effect did Trump have),0.0,"[('Milei', 'ORG'), ('Argentine', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La única doctora especializada en veneno de serpientes en uno de los países con más víboras del mundo,The only doctor specialized in snake venom in one of the countries with the most vipers in the world,0.25,"[('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'पता नहीं वो पूरी तरह ठीक होगा भी या नहीं' मध्य प्रदेश में दिवाली पर कार्बाइड गन फटने से कई लोगों की आंखों की रोशनी जाने का ख़तरा,'Don't know whether he will be completely cured or not' Many people are in danger of losing their eyesight due to the explosion of carbide gun on Diwali in Madhya Pradesh.,-0.09166666666666667,"[('Diwali', 'NORP'), ('Madhya Pradesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,सऊदी के क्राउन प्रिंस से मिले पाकिस्तानी पीएम शहबाज़ शरीफ़, क्या चर्चा हुई?","Live, Pakistani PM Shahbaz Sharif meets Saudi Crown Prince, what was discussed?",0.13636363636363635,"[('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('Shahbaz Sharif', 'PERSON'), ('Saudi Crown Prince', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'मोंथा' साइक्लोन का नाम किसने दिया? दिलचस्प है समुद्री तूफ़ानों के नामकरण की कहानी,Who named the cyclone 'Montha'? The story of naming of storms is interesting.,0.5,"[('Montha', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ग़ज़ा में ट्रंप के 'पीस प्लान' को लेकर जॉर्डन के किंग का सवाल, बीबीसी से क्या कहा","Jordan's king asked about Trump's peace plan in Gaza, what he told BBC",0.0,"[('Jordan', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दिल्ली में 'क्लाउड सीडिंग' से बारिश कराने की तैयारी, कितना कारगर है ये तरीक़ा","Preparation for rain in Delhi through 'Cloud Seeding', how effective is this method?",0.6,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), (""Cloud Seeding'"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान सेमीकंडक्टर इंडस्ट्री की तरक़्क़ी के लिए चाहता है सऊदी अरब का साथ,Pakistan wants Saudi Arabia's support for the development of semiconductor industry,0.2,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), (""Saudi Arabia's"", 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"श्रेयस अय्यर की अब कैसी है तबीयत? स्प्लीन में लगी चोट कितनी ख़तरनाक, क्या काम करता है ये अंग","How is Shreyas Iyer's health now? How dangerous is an injury to the spleen, what does this organ do?",-0.6,"[(""Shreyas Iyer's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान और अफ़ग़ानिस्तान के बीच युद्ध विराम जारी रखना क्यों हो रहा है मुश्किल?,Why is it becoming difficult to continue the ceasefire between Pakistan and Afghanistan?,-0.024999999999999994,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"चुनाव आयोग ने किया यूपी और पश्चिम बंगाल समेत 12 राज्यों में एसआईआर का एलान, विपक्ष ने उठाए ये सवाल","Election Commission announced SIR in 12 states including UP and West Bengal, opposition raised these questions",0.0,"[('Election Commission', 'ORG'), ('SIR', 'ORG'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('UP', 'ORG'), ('West Bengal', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como Milei conseguiu vitória nas eleições legislativas da Argentina apesar de crises e escândalos,How Milei achieved victory in Argentina's legislative elections despite crises and scandals,0.0,"[('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Irmãos na floresta': a luta para proteger aldeia isolada da Amazônia,'Brothers in the forest': the fight to protect isolated village in the Amazon,0.0,"[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como camisinhas ajudaram a estudar cigarras na Amazônia,How condoms helped study cicadas in the Amazon,0.0,"[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Lula sobre tarifaço: 'Trump me garantiu que fará acordo, e vai ser mais rápido do que muita gente pensa'","Lula on tariffs: 'Trump assured me that he will make an agreement, and it will be faster than many people think'",0.5,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Como é fazer entrevista de emprego com uma inteligência artificial: 'Tempo foi otimizado, mas desumaniza'","What it's like to do a job interview with artificial intelligence: 'Time was optimized, but it dehumanizes'",-0.6,[]
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que bolsonaristas falam sobre encontro de Trump com Lula: 'Foto pra inglês ver',What Bolsonaro supporters say about Trump's meeting with Lula: 'Photo for the English to see',0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump 'sem dúvida' quer derrubar governo da Venezuela, diz aliado de Maduro à BBC","Trump 'without a doubt' wants to overthrow Venezuela's government, Maduro ally tells BBC",0.2,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Tropas internacionais não vão querer impor a paz em Gaza, diz rei da Jordânia à BBC","International troops will not want to impose peace in Gaza, Jordan's king tells the BBC",0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Jordan', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que celebridades estão comprando clubes de futebol,Why celebrities are buying football clubs,0.0,[]
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Ураган «Мелисса»: Ямайка готовится к самому мощному шторму 2025 года,Hurricane Melissa: Jamaica braces for worst storm of 2025,-1.0,"[('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('Jamaica', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: новые обстрелы Херсона и Черниговской области","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: new shelling of Kherson and Chernihiv region",0.13636363636363635,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kherson', 'GPE'), ('Chernihiv', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Принц Эндрю принимал Эпштейна, Максвелл и Вайнштейна в особняке Royal Lodge в Виндзоре","Prince Andrew hosted Epstein, Maxwell and Weinstein at the Royal Lodge in Windsor",0.0,"[('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PRODUCT'), ('Maxwell', 'ORG'), ('Weinstein', 'PERSON'), ('the Royal Lodge', 'FAC'), ('Windsor', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Париже начался суд над людьми, утверждавшими, что жена президента Франции Брижит Макрон — трансгендер",A trial began in Paris of people who claimed that the wife of French President Brigitte Macron is transgender,0.0,"[('Paris', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Brigitte Macron', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Основателя ChronoPay Павла Врублевского приговорили к 10 годам колонии,ChronoPay founder Pavel Vrublevsky was sentenced to 10 years in prison,0.0,"[('ChronoPay', 'ORG'), ('Pavel Vrublevsky', 'PERSON'), ('10 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Бывший муж Бритни Спирс выпустил книгу об их совместной жизни. Он считает, что ей нужна помощь",Britney Spears' ex-husband has released a book about their life together. He thinks she needs help,0.0,"[(""Britney Spears'"", 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Камеруне самый старый президент в мире переизбрался на новый, восьмой срок","In Cameroon, the oldest president in the world was re-elected for a new, eighth term.",0.13636363636363635,"[('Cameroon', 'GPE'), ('eighth', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Литва закрыла границу с Беларусью из-за участившихся залетов шаров с контрабандой,Lithuania closed its border with Belarus due to increased frequency of smuggling balloons,-0.1125,"[('Lithuania', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Король Карл III принял участие в первом мероприятии ЛГБТ+: открыл мемориал ветеранам, уволенным за сексуальную ориентацию",King Charles III took part in the first LGBT+ event: opened a memorial to veterans fired for their sexual orientation,0.375,"[('Charles III', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Мэра Стамбула, главного оппонента Эрдогана, обвинили в политическом шпионаже","The mayor of Istanbul, Erdogan's main opponent, was accused of political espionage",0.08333333333333333,"[('Istanbul', 'GPE'), ('Erdogan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏と高市氏が会談　日米「黄金時代」に関する合意文書に署名,Mr. Trump and Mr. Takaichi meet and sign agreement regarding the Japan-U.S. “Golden Era”,0.3,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Takaichi', 'PERSON'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Golden Era', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、3期目を目指すこと否定せず　ただし副大統領を経由する「抜け道」は使わないと,"Trump does not deny seeking a third term, but he must use the ``loophole'' that goes through the vice president position",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日本の人口危機　ロボットで解決できるのか,Can robots solve Japan's population crisis?,0.0,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,カナダの州首相、米関税に反対の広告を断固支持　トランプ氏が税率引き上げを表明した後も,"Canadian premier firmly supports advertisement against US tariffs, even after Trump announces tax hike",-0.2,"[('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 その症状は風邪、インフル、それともコロナ？　悪化を防ぐには,"[Explanation] Are the symptoms cold, flu, or coronavirus? To prevent deterioration",-0.6,[]
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,トランプ氏、3期目の可能性について聞かれ意欲示す, 所要時間 1,03","Video, Trump expresses interest when asked about possibility of third term, Duration 1,03",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「究極の共生」か、それとも……日本の高齢化と介護ロボットの未来, 所要時間 3,10","Video, ""Ultimate symbiosis"" or... Japan's aging population and the future of nursing care robots, Duration 3,10",0.0,"[('Ultimate', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('3,10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米移民当局、イスラエルを批判するイギリス人ジャーナリストを拘束　「テロ支援」と主張,"US immigration authorities detain British journalist who criticizes Israel, accusing him of 'supporting terrorism'",0.125,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アンドリュー王子、2006年にエプスティーン元被告らを公邸で歓待　BBC調査で判明,"Prince Andrew hosted Epstein and others at his official residence in 2006, revealed by BBC investigation",0.0,"[('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('2006', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Mkuu Tanzania 2025: Kura au maandamano? mizani ya haki za kikatiba inavyopimwa,Tanzania General Election 2025: Vote or protest? the balance of constitutional rights is measured,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzania General', 'ORG'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Mkuu Tanzania 2025: Upigaji kura wa mapema wafanyika Zanzibar,Tanzania General Election 2025: Early voting will be held in Zanzibar,0.07500000000000001,"[('Tanzania General', 'ORG'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE'), ('Zanzibar', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Jeshi la Sudan lapoteza mji muhimu wa el-Fasher kwa wanamgambo wa RSF","Directly, the Sudanese Army lost the important town of el-Fasher to the RSF militia",0.25,"[('the Sudanese Army', 'ORG'), ('el-Fasher', 'ORG'), ('RSF', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Mkuu Tanzania 2025: Unajua safari ya kura yako na unavyoipiga?,Tanzania General Election 2025: Do you know the journey of your vote and how you cast it?,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzania General', 'ORG'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais mwenye umri wa miaka 92 asiyeshindwa katika uchaguzi,The 92-year-old president is undefeated in elections,0.0,"[('92-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumanne: Barcelona yaongoza mbio za kumsajili Mason Greenwood,European football rumors Tuesday: Barcelona lead the race to sign Mason Greenwood,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('Mason Greenwood', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Ni kutawazwa sio ushindani' - Rais wa kwanza mwanamke wa Tanzania akabiliwa na upinzani mdogo,'It's coronation not competition' - Tanzania's first female president faces little opposition,0.020833333333333332,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mstari mwembamba kati ya dini na siasa unavyotikisa uchaguzi Tanzania,The thin line between religion and politics is shaking the elections in Tanzania,-0.4,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Binti yangu alinaswa katika mtego wa kundi la Shetani 764','My daughter was caught in the trap of Satan's group 764',0.0,"[('Satan', 'GPE'), ('764', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, ni kwanini kuna ""uadui wa kihistoria"" kati ya Real Madrid na Barcelona?","Why is there a ""historical enmity"" between Real Madrid and Barcelona?",0.1,"[('Real Madrid', 'ORG'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE')]"
