Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El estudiante que repara billetes en Gaza, donde no entra dinero desde hace más de 2 años","The student who repairs banknotes in Gaza, where no money has entered for more than 2 years",0.5,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('more than 2 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El gobierno de Trump paraliza los procesos de residencia y ciudadanía para migrantes de Venezuela, Cuba, Haití y otros 16 países","The Trump administration paralyzes the residency and citizenship processes for migrants from Venezuela, Cuba, Haiti and 16 other countries",-0.125,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Apoyo a Maduro para la defensa de nuestra nación por la vía de las armas y para abrir el diálogo con EE.UU."": el Fiscal General de Venezuela en entrevista con la BBC","""I support Maduro to defend our nation through arms and to open dialogue with the US"": the Attorney General of Venezuela in an interview with the BBC",0.02500000000000001,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Honduras en vilo tras el reinicio del conteo de votos de las presidenciales: el centrista Nasralla supera por la mínima al conservador Asfura,Honduras in suspense after the restart of the presidential vote count: the centrist Nasralla narrowly beats the conservative Asfura,-0.2,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('Nasralla', 'PERSON'), ('Asfura', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Fue una tragedia anunciada"": el joven brasileño que murió tras meterse en el recinto de los leones en un zoológico de Brasil","""It was a tragedy foretold"": the young Brazilian who died after getting into the lion enclosure at a zoo in Brazil",0.1,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पुतिन के दौरे से पहले रूस ने भारत के पाले में डाली गेंद, भारत क्या करेगा फ़ैसला?","Before Putin's visit, Russia put the ball in India's court, what will India decide?",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,दिल्ली एमसीडी उपचुनाव नतीजे पर आम आदमी पार्टी ने लगाया आरोप, बीजेपी ने ये कहा","Live, Aam Aadmi Party made allegations on Delhi MCD by-election results, BJP said this",0.13636363636363635,"[('Delhi MCD', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,रुबैया सईद के अपहरण ने पूरे भारत को कैसे हिला दिया था,How Rubaiya Saeed's kidnapping shook the whole of India,0.2,"[(""Rubaiya Saeed's"", 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,असम का 'स्पेशल रिवीज़न' दूसरे राज्यों में SIR से अलग कैसे? क्या हैं आशंकाएं?,How is Assam's 'Special Revision' different from SIR in other states? What are the fears?,0.07738095238095238,"[('SIR', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'एक मक़सद ने दुश्मनों को एक साथ ला दिया': श्रीलंका में पाकिस्तानी और भारतीय सेना के बचाव कार्यों की चर्चा,'One cause brought together enemies': Discussion of rescue operations by Pakistani and Indian armies in Sri Lanka,0.0,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Sri Lanka', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दुनिया की सबसे तेज़ अर्थव्यवस्थाओं में शामिल भारत का रुपया दबाव में, क्या हैं संकेत?","India's rupee, which is among the fastest economies of the world, is under pressure, what are the signs?",0.0,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पुतिन के भारत दौरे से पहले फ़्रांस, ब्रिटेन और जर्मनी के राजनयिकों के लेख पर विवाद","Controversy over article by diplomats of France, Britain and Germany before Putin's visit to India",0.0,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,संचार साथी ऐप: 12 ज़रूरी सवालों के आसान जवाब,Sanchar Sathi App: Easy answers to 12 important questions,0.4166666666666667,"[('Sanchar Sathi App:', 'PERSON'), ('12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जब पश्तून कबायलियों ने भारत की जगह पाकिस्तान को चुना,When Pashtun tribals chose Pakistan instead of India,0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O fator Michelle: a aposta que irrita os filhos de Bolsonaro,The Michelle factor: the bet that irritates Bolsonaro's children,0.0,"[('Michelle', 'ORG'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Justiça brasileira abre caminho para retorno de suposto espião à Rússia,Brazilian justice clears the way for alleged spy to return to Russia,-0.1,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Mate todos': a investigação sobre ataque a barco no Caribe que põe Trump sob pressão,'Kill them all': Caribbean boat attack investigation that puts Trump under pressure,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Era um menino abandonado por todo sistema, foi uma tragédia anunciada': o jovem morto por leoa após invadir jaula em João Pessoa","'He was a boy abandoned by the entire system, it was a tragedy announced': the young man killed by a lioness after breaking into a cage in João Pessoa",-0.03333333333333333,"[('João Pessoa', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que Lula pediu a Trump em nova conversa por telefone,What Lula asked Trump in a new telephone conversation,0.13636363636363635,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Copa do Mundo Fifa 2026: os 5 azarões que desafiam as probabilidades,FIFA World Cup 2026: the 5 underdogs who defy the odds,0.0,"[('FIFA World Cup', 'ORG'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A vida dos milionários na capital do 'agroluxo' no Brasil,The lives of millionaires in the capital of 'agroluxury' in Brazil,0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Direita brasileira procura novo líder após clã Bolsonaro 'se autodestruir', diz Financial Times","Brazilian right seeks new leader after Bolsonaro clan 'self-destructed', says Financial Times",0.14069264069264067,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Financial Times', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O Brasil que Dom Pedro 2º imaginou — e o que fizemos dele,The Brazil that Dom Pedro II imagined — and what we made of it,0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Пока компромиссного варианта нет». Как прошли переговоры Путина с Уиткоффом и Кушнером в Кремле,“There is no compromise option yet.” How did Putin’s negotiations with Witkoff and Kushner go in the Kremlin?,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Witkoff', 'ORG'), ('Kushner', 'ORG'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Путин и Уиткофф не достигли компромисса на переговорах, заявил Кремль","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Putin and Witkoff did not reach a compromise in negotiations, the Kremlin said",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Witkoff', 'PERSON'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Единственный европеец. Что ждет Эммануэля Макрона в Китае,The only European. What awaits Emmanuel Macron in China,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Emmanuel Macron', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Как бывший глава правительства Крыма вернул Украине тысячи артефактов, украденных из музеев",How the former head of the Crimean government returned thousands of artifacts stolen from museums to Ukraine,0.0,"[('Crimean', 'NORP'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Германии украли 20 тысяч патронов для Бундесвера. Водитель грузовика оставил их на стоянке,20 thousand rounds of ammunition for the Bundeswehr were stolen in Germany. The truck driver left them in the parking lot.,0.0,"[('20 thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bundeswehr', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как Москва и Вашингтон готовились к встрече Путина и Уиткоффа в Кремле,How Moscow and Washington prepared for the meeting between Putin and Witkoff in the Kremlin,0.0,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Witkoff', 'GPE'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Меня подвешивали за запястья и били». Израильтянка российского происхождения рассказала, что пережила в плену у иракских боевиков",“They hung me up by my wrists and beat me.” An Israeli woman of Russian origin told what she experienced in captivity by Iraqi militants,0.4,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Iraqi', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Все возможности для Мадуро исчерпаны? Что известно о телефонном разговоре Трампа с президентом Венесуэлы,Have all options for Maduro been exhausted? What is known about Trump's telephone conversation with the President of Venezuela,-0.4,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Массовые антикоррупционные протесты в Болгарии заставили правительство отозвать проект бюджета,Massive anti-corruption protests in Bulgaria forced the government to withdraw the draft budget,-0.15000000000000002,"[('Bulgaria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Дай пять, Паваротти». Мэру итальянского города пришлось извиняться за рождественский каток вокруг статуи тенора","""High five, Pavarotti."" The mayor of an Italian city had to apologize for the Christmas skating rink around the statue of a tenor",0.08,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pavarotti', 'ORG'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ロがウクライナの和平案を協議、進展みられず,"US and Russia discuss peace plan for Ukraine, no progress seen",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,戦争の終わり見えないとウクライナ兵、和平協議への期待感薄く　荒廃した東部からの住民避難続く, 所要時間 1,11","Video, Ukrainian soldiers say there is no end to the war in sight, and hopes for peace talks are low; evacuation of residents from devastated eastern region continues, Duration 1,11",0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イギリス政府、ガザ支援物資搬入の遅れを批判　テント到着に1年かかったと,British government criticizes delays in bringing aid supplies to Gaza; tents took a year to arrive,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('a year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米コストコが政府を提訴、「トランプ関税」の全額返還目指し　最高裁で審理続くなか,"U.S. Costco sues government, seeking full refund of Trump tariffs, as trial continues in Supreme Court",0.35,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Costco', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米国土安全保障長官、入国禁止措置の拡大を要請　約30カ国が対象か,US Secretary of Homeland Security requests expansion of entry ban to approximately 30 countries,-0.4,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Homeland Security', 'ORG'), ('approximately 30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米国防長官、生存者は目にしていなかったと主張　「麻薬船」追撃で,US Secretary of Defense claims he didn't see any survivors in pursuit of 'drug ship',0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ドイツ軍に納入予定の弾薬、輸送車から盗まれる　約2万発分か,"Approximately 20,000 rounds of ammunition stolen from a transport vehicle scheduled to be delivered to the German military",-0.16666666666666666,"[('Approximately 20,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('German', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,マレーシア航空機の捜索再開へ、行方不明から10年超　当局が発表,Officials announce resumption of search for Malaysian Airlines plane more than 10 years after it went missing,0.15,"[('Malaysian Airlines', 'ORG'), ('more than 10 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港政府トップが独立調査を指示　高層住宅群火災で死者増えるなか,Hong Kong government top official orders independent investigation as death toll rises in high-rise residential fires,0.25,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mazungumzo ya Urusi na Marekani yashindwa kuleta maafikiano","Directly, the talks between Russia and the United States failed to reach an agreement",-0.2,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Serikali yamburuza Mahakamani mwanaharakati Mange Kimambi,Protests in Tanzania: The government drags activist Mange Kimambi to court,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Mange Kimambi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumatano: Vilabu vya Saudia vyaelekeza macho kwa Salah,Football rumors Wednesday: Saudi clubs are eyeing Salah,0.0,"[('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('Salah', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tanzania kwenye mzani wa nani 'beberu' nani mfadhili,Tanzania on the scale of who is the 'imperialist' who is the benefactor,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Samia -Nguvu Iliyotumika Oktoba 29 ilistahili,President Samia - The power used on October 29 was deserved,0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON'), ('October 29', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"""Sasa kuna fursa ya kumaliza vita kuliko wakati mwingine wowote"" - Zelensky","""Now there is an opportunity to end the war more than ever before"" - Zelensky",0.5,[]
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Simba yamtimua kocha wake,Simba fired his coach,0.0,[]
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Who are you?' na hoja 6 zilizotikisa hotuba ya Rais Samia,'Who are you?' and 6 arguments that shook President Samia's speech,0.0,"[('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kombe la Mataifa ya Afrika: Timu tano zinazopigiwa upatu kushinda AFCON 2025,Africa Cup of Nations: Five teams tipped to win AFCON 2025,0.8,"[('Africa Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('AFCON', 'ORG'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mtangazaji wa redio miongoni mwa walioshtakiwa kwa njama ya kusajili watu Urusi,A radio host among those accused of conspiracy to register people in Russia,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
