Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Hamás entrega a los 20 rehenes que mantenía con vida mientras Israel libera a los primeros presos palestinos como parte del acuerdo de cese el fuego,Hamas hands over 20 hostages it was keeping alive as Israel releases first Palestinian prisoners as part of ceasefire agreement,0.175,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('over 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Quiénes son los 20 rehenes liberados por Hamás como parte del acuerdo de cese al fuego con Israel,Who are the 20 hostages released by Hamas as part of the ceasefire agreement with Israel,0.0,"[('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"4 razones de la crisis de violencia que vive Perú, factor clave en la caída de la presidenta Dina Boluarte","4 reasons for the violence crisis that Peru is experiencing, a key factor in the fall of President Dina Boluarte",0.0,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Dina Boluarte', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""La IA está muy sobrevalorada: es mucho menos creativa que el peor de mis estudiantes"": el aclamado físico Carlo Rovelli a la BBC","""AI is very overrated: it is much less creative than the worst of my students"": acclaimed physicist Carlo Rovelli to the BBC",-0.11666666666666667,"[('Carlo Rovelli', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo el rechazo cambia el comportamiento de las personas y los consejos de un experto para superarlo,How rejection changes people's behavior and expert advice on overcoming it,0.0,[]
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इसराइली संसद में ट्रंप के भाषण के दौरान हंगामा, दो सांसदों को सदन से बाहर निकाला गया","Uproar during Trump's speech in Israeli Parliament, two MPs thrown out of the House",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Israeli Parliament', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('House', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,पीएम मोदी ने इसराइली बंधकों की रिहाई को लेकर ट्रंप की तारीफ़ की","Live, PM Modi praised Trump for the release of Israeli hostages",0.13636363636363635,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ग़ज़ा में युद्ध विराम समझौते और 20 बंधकों की रिहाई के बारे में अब तक क्या-क्या पता है?,What is known so far about the ceasefire agreement in Gaza and the release of 20 hostages?,0.1,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बैंकिंग सेक्टर में नौकरी कैसे मिलती है, ये है रास्ता","How to get a job in banking sector, this is the way",0.0,[]
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"कैंसर से जंग में नए शोध से बंधी आस, बिना सर्जरी के इलाज की कोशिश","New research brings hope in the fight against cancer, attempts at treatment without surgery",0.13636363636363635,[]
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मणिपुर में बँटी हुई बस्तियों के बीच बने 'बफ़र ज़ोन', आशंकाओं के बीच घर-वापसी की धुंधलाती उम्मीद: ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट","'Buffer zones' formed between divided settlements in Manipur, amid apprehensions, hope of returning home dims: Ground report",0.0,"[('Manipur', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान-अफ़ग़ानिस्तान सीमा पर हुए हालिया टकराव की क्या वजह है? जानिए विशेषज्ञों की राय,What is the reason for the recent conflict on the Pakistan-Afghanistan border? Know the opinion of experts,0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पीएम मोदी ग़ज़ा शांति सम्मेलन में शिरकत करने शर्म अल-शेख़ क्यों नहीं गए?,Why did PM Modi not go to Sharm el-Sheikh to attend the Gaza peace conference?,0.0,"[('PM Modi', 'GPE'), ('Sharm el-Sheikh', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार विधानसभा चुनाव के लिए एनडीए में सीटों का बँटवारा, महागठबंधन के लिए क्या हैं संकेत?","Seat distribution in NDA for Bihar assembly elections, what are the indications for the grand alliance?",0.5,"[('NDA', 'GPE'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Hamas solta todos os 20 reféns vivos em Gaza e Israel começa a libertar presos palestinos em 1ª fase de acordo de cessar-fogo,Hamas releases all 20 live hostages in Gaza and Israel begins releasing Palestinian prisoners in 1st phase of ceasefire agreement,0.13636363636363635,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('1st', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quem são os reféns em Gaza libertados pelo Hamas em acordo com Israel,Who are the hostages in Gaza released by Hamas in agreement with Israel,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Pesquisa sobre como inovação cria crescimento econômico sustentável rende Nobel de Economia a 3 pesquisadores,Research into how innovation creates sustainable economic growth wins Nobel Prize in Economics for 3 researchers,0.25,"[('Nobel Prize in Economics', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula se encontra com papa Leão 14 no Vaticano e diz que os dois 'já são amigos',Lula meets with Pope Leo 14 at the Vatican and says the two 'are already friends',0.0,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Em meio a soltura de reféns, embate interno entre Hamas e clã palestino deixa ao menos 27 mortos em Gaza","Amid the release of hostages, internal clash between Hamas and Palestinian clan leaves at least 27 dead in Gaza",-0.16666666666666666,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('at least 27', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como é para milhares de palestinos voltar para casa após cessar-fogo em Gaza: 'Eles destruíram tudo',What it's like for thousands of Palestinians to return home after ceasefire in Gaza: 'They destroyed everything',0.0,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Achava meio chato': brasileiro citado no Nobel de Física trabalhou por acaso na teoria que o transformou em referência internacional,'I thought it was kind of boring': Brazilian named in the Nobel Prize for Physics worked by chance on the theory that turned him into an international reference,-0.13333333333333333,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('the Nobel Prize for Physics', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula em Roma: Brasil tem desafios para reduzir desperdício de alimentos enquanto celebra saída do Mapa da Fome,Lula in Rome: Brazil faces challenges in reducing food waste while celebrating exit from the Hunger Map,-0.2,"[('Rome', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Posso matar e não vou ser condenado': os presos ucranianos que estão trocando a cadeia pelo campo de batalha na guerra com a Rússia,'I can kill and I won't be convicted': Ukrainian prisoners who are leaving prison for the battlefield in the war with Russia,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"ВСУ продвигаются в Запорожской области, российская армия нанесла контрудар в районе Доброполья. Что происходит на фронте?","The Ukrainian Armed Forces are advancing in the Zaporozhye region, the Russian army launched a counterattack in the Dobropillia area. What's happening at the front?",0.0,"[('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Dobropillia', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Последние живые израильские заложники вернулись из плена ХАМАС; Трамп выступил в Кнессете и отправился в Египет","LIVELive,The last living Israeli hostages returned from Hamas captivity; Trump spoke in the Knesset and went to Egypt",0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Knesset', 'ORG'), ('Egypt', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Последние 48 заложников ХАМАС: кто выжил и кто погиб,The last 48 Hamas hostages: who survived and who died,0.0,"[('48', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Трамп заявил, что может отправить Киеву ракеты Tomahawk, если Путин не прекратит войну","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Trump says he may send Tomahawk missiles to Kyiv if Putin doesn't stop war",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Tomahawk', 'PRODUCT'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ХАМАС освободил 20 израильских заложников. Главное,Hamas freed 20 Israeli hostages. Main,0.16666666666666666,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Инновации как двигатель прогресса. Нобель по экономике в 2025 году получили Мокир, Агион и Ховитт","Innovation as the engine of progress. Nobel in Economics in 2025 received by Mokyr, Aghion and Howitt",0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Mokyr', 'GPE'), ('Howitt', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"СМИ сообщают, что президент Мадагаскара покинул страну. Военные утверждают, что не собираются захватывать власть",Media reports that the President of Madagascar has left the country. The military says it has no intention of seizing power.,-0.05,"[('Media', 'ORG'), ('Madagascar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Когда вы испытываете стресс, ваш нос становится холоднее. Тепловизор это видит","When you are stressed, your nose becomes colder. The thermal imager sees this",0.0,[]
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«У них было такое в анализах крови, чего мы понять не могли». Где и как реабилитируют освобожденных израильских заложников",“They had things in their blood tests that we couldn’t figure out.” Where and how will freed Israeli hostages be rehabilitated?,0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Кажется, техномиллиардеры готовятся к концу света. Стоит ли нам всем беспокоиться?",It seems tech billionaires are preparing for the end of the world. Should we all be worried?,0.0,[]
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ハマス、生存の人質全員を解放　イスラエルで拘束のパレスチナ人らは西岸地区へ,Hamas releases all surviving hostages; Palestinians held in Israel are sent to the West Bank,0.0,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('the West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国、米関税の脅しを「二重基準」と非難　対抗措置を示唆,"China denounces US tariff threat as 'double standards', suggests countermeasures",0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ハマス治安部隊と有力氏族の武装メンバーが衝突、死者多数　ガザ市,Clashes between Hamas security forces and armed members of powerful clan leave many dead in Gaza City,0.20000000000000004,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza City', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タリバン政府、パキスタン軍に「報復」攻撃と発表　国境で緊張激化,Taliban government announces 'retaliatory' attack on Pakistani military; tensions intensify on border,-0.1,"[('Taliban', 'ORG'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,西アフリカのマリ、アメリカに仕返し　旅行者にビザ保証金1万ドル課す,"West Africa's Mali retaliates against US by imposing $10,000 visa deposit on travelers",0.0,"[(""West Africa's"", 'GPE'), ('Mali', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('10,000', 'MONEY')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ガザで停戦発効、イスラエル軍がガザの一部から撤退,"Ceasefire takes effect in Gaza, Israeli forces withdraw from part of Gaza",0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノーベル平和賞はヴェネズエラの野党指導者マリア・コリナ・マチャド氏に　「民主主義の核心」と委員会,"Nobel Peace Prize awarded to Venezuelan opposition leader Maria Colina Machado, committee says she is the ``core of democracy''",0.0,"[('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('Maria Colina Machado', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,マクロン仏大統領、ルコルニュ氏を首相に再任命　政治的混乱続く,French President Macron reappoints Le Cornu as prime minister; political turmoil continues,0.0,"[('French', 'NORP'), ('Macron', 'PERSON'), ('Le Cornu', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、中国に100％の追加関税を課すと脅す　レアアース輸出規制強化に反発,"Trump threatens to impose 100% additional tariffs on China, pushing back against tougher rare earth export regulations",0.15,"[('100%', 'PERCENT'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Rais Trump awasili Misri, akisema awamu ya pili ya mazungumzo kuhusu Gaza tayari imeanza","Directly, President Trump arrives in Egypt, saying the second phase of talks about Gaza has already begun",0.05,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, mateka wanaoachiliwa ni akina nani?",Who are the captives released?,0.0,[]
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, mabilionea wa teknolojia wanajiandaa na maangamizi ya akili mnemba (AI)?",Are technology billionaires preparing for the destruction of Mnemba (AI)?,0.0,"[('Mnemba', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ni mshambuliaji gani bora kati ya hawa watatu?,Which of the three attacker is the best of these three?,1.0,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mapigano yamezuka kati ya vikosi vya Hamas na wanaukoo wenye silaha katika mji wa Gaza,Fights have erupted between Hamas forces and armed militants in Gaza City,0.0,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza City', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi waganga Afrika Kusini wavyotumia waziwazi dawa haramu kutibu maradhi ya akili,How South African Physicians clearly use illegal drugs to treat mental illness,-0.125,"[('South African', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Machozi na furaha yashuhudiwa huko Tel Aviv kuachiliwa kwa mateka kulipoanza,Tears and joy are witnessed in Tel Aviv when the release of the captives began,0.8,"[('Tel Aviv', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Barcelona yagoma kumuongezea mkataba Robert Lewandowski,European football rumors Monday: Barcelona YAGOMA adds to the contract Robert Lewandowski,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Barcelona YAGOMA', 'ORG'), ('Robert Lewandowski', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ofisi ya rais wa Madagascar inasema jaribio la kunyakua mamlaka linaendelea,Madagascar's presidential office says an attempt to grab authority is underway,0.0,"[('Madagascar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, chapati, mkate na wali vinahatarisha vipi afya yako?","How do chapati, bread and rice risk your health?",0.0,[]
