Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los 5 de Ulm: el controvertido juicio en Alemania que cuestiona el fuerte vínculo del país con Israel y la respuesta a las protestas a favor de los palestinos,The Ulm 5: the controversial trial in Germany that questions the country's strong bond with Israel and the response to pro-Palestinian protests,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('pro-Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Mi hermano ahora es una persona completamente distinta"": la metamorfosis del mexicano Temach para convertirse en la mayor estrella de la machosfera en América Latina","""My brother is now a completely different person"": the metamorphosis of Mexican Temach to become the biggest star of the machosphere in Latin America",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Quiénes son los principales candidatos para presidir Colombia y suceder a Petro,Who are the main candidates to preside over Colombia and succeed Petro?,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Petro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Un golpe de suerte: cómo un desconocido farmacéutico británico inventó por casualidad los fósforos de madera hace 200 años,A stroke of luck: how an unknown British pharmacist accidentally invented wooden matches 200 years ago,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('200 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Quiénes fueron los herederos de Marilyn Monroe y cuánto dinero ganaron con los derechos de la imagen de la icónica actriz,Who were Marilyn Monroe's heirs and how much money did they earn from the rights to the iconic actress's image?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Marilyn Monroe's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El canadiense que se declaró culpable de vender en internet sustancias tóxicas a personas que se querían suicidar en 41 países,The Canadian who pleaded guilty to selling toxic substances online to people who wanted to commit suicide in 41 countries,0.0,neutral,"[('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('41', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La preocupante guerra invisible del GPS que está alterando el transporte aéreo,The worrying invisible GPS war that is disrupting air transport,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Cómo operan el Primer Comando de la Capital y el Comando Vermelho, los poderosos grupos criminales de Brasil designados como terroristas por EE.UU.","How the First Capital Command and the Red Command operate, the powerful criminal groups in Brazil designated as terrorists by the US.",-1.0,negative,"[('the First Capital Command', 'ORG'), ('the Red Command', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""¿Y si hacemos protagonista del Mundial al futbolista menos conocido?"": la campaña viral argentina que convirtió en estrella al jugador de Nueva Zelanda Tim Payne","""What if we make the least known footballer the protagonist of the World Cup?"": the Argentine viral campaign that made New Zealand player Tim Payne a star",0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Argentine', 'NORP'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE'), ('Tim Payne', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Nos estamos quedando sin oxígeno y hay pacientes que pueden morir"": la crítica situación de los hospitales en Bolivia por las protestas y bloqueos de carreteras","""We are running out of oxygen and there are patients who could die"": the critical situation of hospitals in Bolivia due to protests and road blockades",0.0,neutral,"[('Bolivia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सीयूईटी-यूजी परीक्षा पर विवाद, केजरीवाल ने कहा, 'देश को शिक्षित प्रधानमंत्री की ज़रूरत'","Controversy over CUET-UG exam, Kejriwal said, 'The country needs an educated Prime Minister'",0.0,neutral,"[('CUET', 'PERSON'), ('Kejriwal', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,वैभव सूर्यवंशी भारतीय टीम से खेलने के लिए कितने तैयार, राजस्थान के हेड कोच संगकारा ने बताया","Live, how ready Vaibhav Suryavanshi is to play for the Indian team, Rajasthan head coach Sangakkara told",0.0,neutral,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Rajasthan', 'PERSON'), ('Sangakkara', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ऋषभ पंत : लखनऊ सुपर जायंट्स में क्या सब कुछ ठीक नहीं था? कप्तानी छोड़ने के पीछे क्या है कहानी,Rishabh Pant: Was everything not well with Lucknow Supergiants? What is the story behind leaving the captaincy?,0.0,neutral,"[('Rishabh Pant', 'PERSON'), ('Lucknow Supergiants', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पांचवीं पीढ़ी के लड़ाकू विमान बनाने का दांव एचएएल की जगह निजी कंपनियों पर क्यों?,Why is the bet on private companies instead of HAL to make fifth generation fighter aircraft?,0.0,neutral,"[('fifth', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वैभव सूर्यवंशी क्यों टीम इंडिया की रेस में शुभमन गिल पर भारी पड़ रहे हैं,Why is Vaibhav Suryavanshi overshadowing Shubman Gill in the race for Team India?,1.0,positive,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Shubman Gill', 'PERSON'), ('Team India', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"जापान ने भारतीय आमों के आयात पर लगाई रोक, क्या है वजह और क्या होगा असर?","Japan bans import of Indian mangoes, what is the reason and what will be the effect?",0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पाकिस्तान और चीन के समझौते में कश्मीर का ज़िक्र, भारत के एतराज़ के पीछे 63 साल पुराना विवाद","Kashmir mentioned in the agreement between Pakistan and China, 63 year old dispute behind India's objection",0.0,neutral,"[('Kashmir', 'LOC'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('63 year old', 'DATE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सीबीएसई का नया सिस्टम क्या स्टूडेंट्स का सिरदर्द बढ़ा रहा है?,Is the new system of CBSE increasing the headache of students?,0.0,neutral,"[('CBSE', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,त्विषा शर्मा केसः सास गिरिबाला और पति समर्थ सिंह को पांच दिन की सीबीआई रिमांड,Tvisha Sharma case: Five days CBI remand to mother-in-law Giribala and husband Samarth Singh,0.0,neutral,"[('Tvisha Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Five days', 'DATE'), ('CBI', 'ORG'), ('Giribala', 'PERSON'), ('Samarth Singh', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"इंदिरा गांधी ने रुपए को जानबूझकर कमज़ोर क्यों किया था, सोवियत संघ हुआ था नाराज़","Why did Indira Gandhi deliberately weaken the rupee, the Soviet Union was angry",0.0,neutral,"[('Indira Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('the Soviet Union', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Governo Lula vê interferência dos EUA nas eleições e não descarta novas ações de Trump após medida sobre PCC e Comando Vermelho,Lula government sees US interference in the elections and does not rule out further actions by Trump after measure on PCC and Red Command,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('PCC', 'ORG'), ('Red Command', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A reação de Lula: 'Não aceitamos ser tratados como moleques',Lula's reaction: 'We don't accept being treated like kids',0.0,neutral,"[('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Os riscos econômicos para o Brasil após a medida americana,The economic risks for Brazil after the American measure,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Tiro pode sair pela culatra': impacto sobre políticos e Faria Lima pode prejudicar Flávio Bolsonaro, diz professor","'This could backfire': impact on politicians and Faria Lima could harm Flávio Bolsonaro, says professor",0.0,neutral,"[('Faria Lima', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como o governo Lula perdeu a batalha que fez Estados Unidos declararem Comando Vermelho e PCC como terroristas,How the Lula government lost the battle that made the United States declare Comando Vermelho and PCC terrorists,-1.0,negative,"[('United States', 'GPE'), ('Comando Vermelho', 'PERSON'), ('PCC', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O acidente que levou farmacêutico a inventar os palitos de fósforo,The accident that led a pharmacist to invent matchsticks,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O 'vendedor de venenos' que forneceu substâncias tóxicas para pessoas em todo o mundo,The 'Poison Seller' Who Provided Toxic Substances to People Around the World,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como as eleições podem ser impactadas por decisão da gestão Trump,How elections could be impacted by Trump administration decisions,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que pode acontecer após Trump declarar PCC e CV como organizações terroristas,What could happen after Trump declares PCC and CV as terrorist organizations,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Украина первой в мире запустила «частную ПВО»: кто ее придумал и  насколько она эффективна,Ukraine was the first in the world to launch “private air defense”: who invented it and how effective it is,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Хегсет: США не «отворачиваются» от союзников в Азии, но ждут от них увеличения оборонных расходов","Hegseth: The US is not “turning its back” on allies in Asia, but expects them to increase defense spending",0.0,neutral,"[('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Asia', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: видео подтверждают систематические удары дронов по российским грузовикам на трассе на Мариуполь","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: video confirms systematic drone strikes on Russian trucks on the highway to Mariupol",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Mariupol', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп пока не принял решение о сделке с Ираном,Trump has not yet decided on a deal with Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Почему у тираннозавра были такие короткие лапы? Британские ученые нашли ответ,Why did Tyrannosaurus rex have such short legs? British scientists have found the answer,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Взорвавшаяся ракета Blue Origin ставит под сомнение планы НАСА о возвращении на Луну,Blue Origin rocket explosion casts doubt on NASA's plans to return to the Moon,0.0,neutral,"[('Blue Origin', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG'), ('Moon', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зачем Путин ездил в Казахстан? Объясняет Темур Умаров в подкасте «Что это было?»,Why did Putin go to Kazakhstan? Temur Umarov explains in the podcast “What was that?”,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Kazakhstan', 'GPE'), ('Temur Umarov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В многоэтажку в Румынии попал российский дрон, МИД страны закрыл генконсульство РФ в Констанце","A Russian drone hit a high-rise building in Romania, the country's Foreign Ministry closed the Russian Consulate General in Constanta",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Romania', 'GPE'), ('Foreign Ministry', 'ORG'), ('the Russian Consulate General', 'ORG'), ('Constanta', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Карьера, полная боли. На Netflix вышел сериал о легендарном теннисисте Рафаэле Надале",A career full of pain. Netflix has released a series about the legendary tennis player Rafael Nadal,0.0,neutral,"[('Netflix', 'ORG'), ('Rafael Nadal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Новый скандал между Польшей и Украиной. Варшава возмущена решением назвать в честь «Героев УПА» спецподразделение ВСУ,A new scandal between Poland and Ukraine. Warsaw is outraged by the decision to name a special unit of the Ukrainian Armed Forces in honor of the “Heroes of the UPA”,-1.0,negative,"[('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Warsaw', 'GPE'), ('the Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Heroes of the UPA', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、イランとの合意に向けた「最終決定」のため側近と協議　しかし結論は出ず,"Trump talks with aides to make ``final decision'' on Iran deal, but no conclusion reached",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米ケネディ・センターからトランプ氏の名前削除、米連邦判事が命令,US federal judge orders Trump's name removed from Kennedy Center,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Kennedy Center', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ政権の2800億円超「反武器化」基金、米連邦地裁が一時差し止め　「政治的捜査」補償が目的の基金,"Trump administration's 280 billion yen ""anti-weaponization"" fund temporarily blocked by US federal court; fund intended to compensate for ""political investigation""",0.0,neutral,"[('280 billion yen', 'MONEY'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,EUがハンガリーの「変化の風」歓迎、164億ユーロの補助金凍結解除へ,"EU welcomes 'winds of change' in Hungary, lifts €16.4 billion subsidy freeze",1.0,positive,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('€16.4 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,NATOとEU、ロシアを非難　ロシアのドローンがルーマニアの集合住宅を直撃,NATO and EU condemn Russia: Russian drone hits apartment complex in Romania,0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Romania', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエルがレバノン首都を攻撃、停戦発効後で2回目,Israel attacks Lebanese capital for second time since ceasefire takes effect,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanese', 'NORP'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,欧州で熱波、ポルトガルは40.3度で5月の最高を更新　フランスでは休校も,"Heatwave in Europe, Portugal hits record high of 40.3 degrees in May; schools closed in France",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Portugal', 'GPE'), ('40.3 degrees', 'QUANTITY'), ('May', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 米国とイランは和平に近づいているのか、再び戦争へ向かっているのか,[Commentary] Are the US and Iran getting closer to peace or heading towards war again?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,EU、中国「Temu」に370億円の罰金　違法製品の販売めぐり,EU fines China's Temu 37 billion yen for selling illegal products,0.0,neutral,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Temu 37 billion yen', 'LAW')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,輸送コンテナをキッチン・バス完備の住居に　住宅価格が高騰するキューバ, 所要時間 1,07","Video, Turning a shipping container into a home with a kitchen and bath as housing prices soar in Cuba, Required time 1,07",0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani haijasema lolote baada ya mkutano wa kuamua 'hatma' ya Iran","Directly, the United States has not said anything after the meeting to decide the 'fate' of Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Marekani yaonyesha matumaini licha ya pingamizi la ujenzi wa kituo cha Ebola Kenya,The United States shows hope despite the opposition to the construction of an Ebola center in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ni sarafu gani zilifaidika na vita vya Iran na zipi zilitetereka?,Which currencies benefited from the Iran war and which ones suffered?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Maswali 5 magumu kuhusu moto katika bweni shuleni Kenya,5 difficult questions about a fire in a school dormitory in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tofauti ya dakika 7,000 - kwa nini PSG wanaweza kuwa na makali dhidi ya Arsenal","7,000 minute difference - why PSG may have the edge over Arsenal",0.0,neutral,"[('7,000 minute', 'TIME'), ('PSG', 'ORG'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mahakama yasitisha kwa muda kufunguliwa kwa hospitali ya ebola ya Marekani nchini Kenya,The court temporarily halts the opening of an American Ebola hospital in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('American Ebola', 'ORG'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Walimu walijua mpango wa kuchoma shule ulioua watoto 16 Kenya - Waziri,The teachers knew about the plan to burn the school that killed 16 children in Kenya - Minister,-1.0,negative,"[('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kauli tata za wanasiasa wanaohama vyama Tanzania,Controversial statements of politicians who change parties in Tanzania,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,AFCON U-17: Tanzania yatinga fainali na kufuzu kombe la dunia kwa mara ya kwanza,AFCON U-17: Tanzania reaches the final and qualify for the world cup for the first time,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, ni wachezaji gani matajiri zaidi wa soka duniani?",Who are the richest soccer players in the world?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Voting ongoing in snap elections in Malta, governing party expected to win","Voting ongoing in snap elections in Malta, governing party expected to win",1.0,positive,"[('Malta', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup dark horses: Talented Senegal looking to ‘achieve great things’,World Cup dark horses: Talented Senegal looking to ‘achieve great things’,1.0,positive,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war: What is happening on day 92 as Trump weighs Iran deal,Iran war: What is happening on day 92 as Trump weighs Iran deal,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('day 92', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Anthony Gordon completes ‘childhood dream’ move to Barcelona,Anthony Gordon completes ‘childhood dream’ move to Barcelona,0.0,neutral,"[('Anthony Gordon', 'PERSON'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Rwanda-Russia nuclear deal underscores Africa’s shifting power balance,Rwanda-Russia nuclear deal underscores Africa’s shifting power balance,0.0,neutral,"[('Rwanda', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Louisiana lawmakers pass congressional map favouring Republicans,Louisiana lawmakers pass congressional map favouring Republicans,0.0,neutral,"[('Louisiana', 'GPE'), ('Republicans', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Trump’s ‘final’ decision on Iran deal due; Israel deepens Lebanon invasion,Trump’s ‘final’ decision on Iran deal due; Israel deepens Lebanon invasion,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump’s', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Trump pledges to withdraw from Kennedy Center after court strikes his name,Trump pledges to withdraw from Kennedy Center after court strikes his name,0.0,neutral,"[('Kennedy Center', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,ICE agent arrested over shooting of Venezuelan man in US immigration raid,ICE agent arrested over shooting of Venezuelan man in US immigration raid,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Arbitrary measures’: Lula slams US ‘terror’ designation for Brazil gangs,‘Arbitrary measures’: Lula slams US ‘terror’ designation for Brazil gangs,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Tokyo Drift: The art of going sideways,Tokyo Drift: The art of going sideways,0.0,neutral,"[('Tokyo Drift', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Rashmika Mandanna interview: On the Crunchyroll Anime Awards 2026, growing up with Naruto and learning emotion through anime","Rashmika Mandanna interview: On the Crunchyroll Anime Awards 2026, growing up with Naruto and learning emotion through anime",0.0,neutral,"[('Rashmika', 'GPE'), ('Mandanna', 'PERSON'), ('the Crunchyroll Anime Awards 2026', 'ORG'), ('Naruto', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Breadcrumbed and burnt out: Inside India’s situationship era,Breadcrumbed and burnt out: Inside India’s situationship era,0.0,neutral,"[('Inside India’s', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Everest Day 2026: Living goddesses, TikTok and a new Prime Minister; explore Nepal beyond the mountains","Everest Day 2026: Living goddesses, TikTok and a new Prime Minister; explore Nepal beyond the mountains",0.0,neutral,"[('Everest Day 2026', 'DATE'), ('TikTok', 'ORG'), ('Nepal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,How Mohit Rai styled Aishwarya Rai Bachchan for Cannes 2026,How Mohit Rai styled Aishwarya Rai Bachchan for Cannes 2026,-1.0,negative,"[('Aishwarya Rai Bachchan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,D.K. Shivakumar to be sworn in as CM at Lok Bhavan's Glass House on June 3,D.K. Shivakumar to be sworn in as CM at Lok Bhavan's Glass House on June 3,0.0,neutral,"[('D.K.', 'GPE'), ('Shivakumar', 'PERSON'), ('CM', 'ORG'), (""Lok Bhavan's"", 'PERSON'), ('Glass House', 'ORG'), ('June 3', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Armed forces ready for ‘Operation Sindoor 2.0’ if needed: Army chief,Armed forces ready for ‘Operation Sindoor 2.0’ if needed: Army chief,0.0,neutral,"[('Army', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Claims of being vishwaguru but can't conduct single exam: Rahul's dig at PM,Claims of being vishwaguru but can't conduct single exam: Rahul's dig at PM,0.0,neutral,"[('Rahul', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Israel-Iran war LIVE: Israeli army issues evacuation orders for seven south Lebanon villages,Israel-Iran war LIVE: Israeli army issues evacuation orders for seven south Lebanon villages,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran war', 'EVENT'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,U.S. War Secretary Hegseth backs Trump’s India-Pak ceasefire claim; outlines Indo-Pacific strategy,U.S. War Secretary Hegseth backs Trump’s India-Pak ceasefire claim; outlines Indo-Pacific strategy,-1.0,negative,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('Trump’s India-Pak', 'ORG'), ('Indo-Pacific', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,No deal announced after Trump meeting to make 'final determination' on Iran,No deal announced after Trump meeting to make 'final determination' on Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US not 'turning back' on Asia allies, but expects them to boost defence - Hegseth","US not 'turning back' on Asia allies, but expects them to boost defence - Hegseth",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Asia', 'LOC'), ('defence - Hegseth', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'Poison seller' who sold toxic chemicals online to people across world admits aiding suicides,'Poison seller' who sold toxic chemicals online to people across world admits aiding suicides,0.0,neutral,"[('Poison', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nato and EU condemn Russia after drone hits Romanian residential block,Nato and EU condemn Russia after drone hits Romanian residential block,0.0,neutral,"[('Nato', 'ORG'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Romanian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,First of five men found alive in flooded Laos cave rescued,First of five men found alive in flooded Laos cave rescued,0.0,neutral,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Laos', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ghana parliament passes anti-LGBTQ+ bill,Ghana parliament passes anti-LGBTQ+ bill,0.0,neutral,"[('Ghana', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Spain's Sánchez digs in after eight years as PM as wave of scandals threatens survival,Spain's Sánchez digs in after eight years as PM as wave of scandals threatens survival,0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Sánchez', 'GPE'), ('eight years', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Israel put on UN sexual violence in warzones blacklist for first time,Israel put on UN sexual violence in warzones blacklist for first time,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Exploding rocket casts doubts over Nasa's Moon plans,Exploding rocket casts doubts over Nasa's Moon plans,0.0,neutral,"[('Nasa', 'ORG'), ('Moon', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Former US attorney general Pam Bondi defends her handling of Epstein files in congressional probe,Former US attorney general Pam Bondi defends her handling of Epstein files in congressional probe,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Pam Bondi', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Across the Middle East, Muslims Mark Eid Amid War and Crisis","Across the Middle East, Muslims Mark Eid Amid War and Crisis",-1.0,negative,"[('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('Muslims', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Russian Drone That Hit Romania Also Hit European Confidence,The Russian Drone That Hit Romania Also Hit European Confidence,0.0,neutral,"[('The Russian Drone That Hit Romania', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Lithuania, Once Occupied by Germany, Is Glad German Troops Are Back","Lithuania, Once Occupied by Germany, Is Glad German Troops Are Back",0.0,neutral,"[('Lithuania', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Glad German Troops Are Back', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Colombia’s Elections Are a Crucial Test for the Left in Latin America,Colombia’s Elections Are a Crucial Test for the Left in Latin America,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Curry Shops Got Caught in Japan’s Immigration Crackdown,How Curry Shops Got Caught in Japan’s Immigration Crackdown,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Who’s the Vegas Retiree With the Big Offer for Greenland?,Who’s the Vegas Retiree With the Big Offer for Greenland?,0.0,neutral,"[('Greenland', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Trump’s Boat Strikes Have Failed to Curb Cocaine Flow to U.S., Experts Say","Trump’s Boat Strikes Have Failed to Curb Cocaine Flow to U.S., Experts Say",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump’s Boat Strikes Have Failed', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,France’s Far Right Has 2 Leaders. They Don’t Always Have One Voice.,France’s Far Right Has 2 Leaders. They Don’t Always Have One Voice.,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('One', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"No, Not That Georgia. A.I. Compounds a Nation’s Identity Woes.","No, Not That Georgia. A.I. Compounds a Nation’s Identity Woes.",0.0,neutral,"[('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('A.I. Compounds a Nation’s Identity Woes', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Europe Is Edging Closer to a Trade War With China. Here’s Why.,Europe Is Edging Closer to a Trade War With China. Here’s Why.,-1.0,negative,"[('Europe Is Edging Closer', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
