Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La ""transformación milagrosa"" de Corea del Norte: cómo logró Kim Jong-un paliar la situación económica de su país y afianzar su poder","The ""miraculous transformation"" of North Korea: how Kim Jong-un managed to alleviate his country's economic situation and consolidate his power",0.0,neutral,"[('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué papel está teniendo EE.UU. en Venezuela tras los devastadores terremotos que dejaron miles de muertos y damnificados,What role is the US playing in Venezuela after the devastating earthquakes that left thousands of dead and homeless?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los palestinos lloran la muerte en un ataque israelí del hombre que organizaba proyecciones de los partidos del Mundial entre las ruinas de Gaza,Palestinians mourn the death in an Israeli attack of the man who organized screenings of World Cup matches among the ruins of Gaza,-1.0,negative,"[('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""En la reforma de mi casa encontré un cementerio con los restos de 40.000 personas esclavizadas""","""In the renovation of my house I found a cemetery with the remains of 40,000 enslaved people""",0.0,neutral,"[('40,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Es imbatible Francia? El veredicto de los expertos de la BBC sobre la gran favorita para ganar el Mundial,Is France unbeatable? The verdict of the BBC experts on the great favorite to win the World Cup,1.0,positive,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¡Francia imparable! Gana 2-0 frente a Marruecos y clasifica a semifinales por tercer Mundial consecutivo,Unstoppable France! Win 2-0 against Morocco and qualify for the semifinals for the third consecutive World Cup,1.0,positive,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Win 2-0', 'PERSON'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Está siendo este el mejor Mundial de la historia?,Is this being the best World Cup in history?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere a los 75 años Bonnie Tyler, la voz que cautivó al mundo con el éxito ""Total Eclipse of the Heart"" en los 80","Bonnie Tyler, the voice that captivated the world with the hit ""Total Eclipse of the Heart"" in the 80s, dies at 75",0.0,neutral,"[('Bonnie Tyler', 'PERSON'), ('Total Eclipse of the Heart', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('80s', 'DATE'), ('75', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Creo que esta será la última vez que nos veamos"": quién es el doctor Hussam Abu Safiya detenido por Israel en Gaza y por qué se teme por su vida","""I think this will be the last time we see each other"": who is Dr. Hussam Abu Safiya detained by Israel in Gaza and why there are fears for his life",0.0,neutral,"[('Hussam Abu Safiya', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere Bonnie Tyler: por qué su clásico de los 80 ""Total Eclipse of the Heart"" es ""la canción más épica de la historia""","Bonnie Tyler dies: why her '80s classic ""Total Eclipse of the Heart"" is ""the most epic song ever""",0.0,neutral,"[('Bonnie Tyler', 'PERSON'), ('80s', 'DATE'), ('Total Eclipse of the Heart', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भारत अपना अहम हथियार ब्रह्मोस कई देशों को क्यों बेच रहा है, रूस की परमिशन क्या ज़रूरी है?","Why is India selling its important weapon BrahMos to many countries, is Russia's permission necessary?",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('BrahMos', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अभिनेता राजेश शर्मा कैसे पड़े बीमार, अक्षय कुमार से लेकर शुभेंदु अधिकारी ने क्या कहा?","How did actor Rajesh Sharma fall ill, what did everyone from Akshay Kumar to Shubhendu Adhikari say?",0.0,neutral,"[('Rajesh Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Akshay Kumar', 'FAC'), ('Shubhendu Adhikari', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,एंडी बर्नम ने ग़ज़ा में इसराइली कार्रवाई पर क्यों मांगी माफ़ी?","Live, Why did Andy Bynum apologize for Israeli action in Gaza?",0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Bynum', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिकी हमलों में ईरान के चाबहार पोर्ट को भी नुक़सान, भारत से क्या है इसका संबंध","Iran's Chabahar port also damaged in American attacks, what is its relation with India?",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Chabahar', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"रूस में कितना गंभीर होता जा रहा है तेल संकट, पेट्रोल पंप पर लगती लंबी कतारें","How serious is the oil crisis becoming in Russia, long queues at petrol pumps",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वैभव सूर्यवंशी की इन कमियों की हो रही है बात, जोफ्रा आर्चर के पुराने कमेंट की चर्चा","These shortcomings of Vaibhav Suryavanshi are being talked about, Joffra Archer's old comment is being discussed",0.0,neutral,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), (""Joffra Archer's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका में पंजाब पुलिस का इंस्पेक्टर वॉन्टेड, पूरा मामला","Inspector of Punjab Police wanted in America, the whole matter",0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भारत को हराकर इंग्लैंड ने जीती सिरीज़, भारतीय बल्लेबाज़ों के प्रदर्शन पर आईपीएल शैली की चर्चा","England won the series by defeating India, IPL style discussion on the performance of Indian batsmen",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका के ताबड़तोड़ हमले, ईरान का दावा बुशहर का न्यूक्लियर पॉवर प्लांट भी निशाने पर","America's rapid attacks, Iran's claim that Bushehr's nuclear power plant is also on target.",-1.0,negative,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Bushehr', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारत में इस्लाम के आने में क्या काली मिर्च की भी भूमिका थी?,Did black pepper also play a role in the arrival of Islam in India?,0.0,neutral,"[('Islam', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Produtora de filme sobre Bolsonaro funcionava em casa de sócio em subúrbio dos Estados Unidos,Film production company about Bolsonaro operated out of a partner's house in a suburb of the United States,0.0,neutral,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Regina Casé volta ao teatro e revê carreira na TV: 'Como atriz, sou celebrada; como apresentadora, tenho haters'","Regina Casé returns to the theater and reviews her career on TV: 'As an actress, I am celebrated; As a presenter, I have haters'",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"BTS, Madonna, Shakira e Justin Bieber: como vai ser o 'show do intervalo' da final da Copa","BTS, Madonna, Shakira and Justin Bieber: what the 'halftime show' of the World Cup final will be like",0.0,neutral,"[('BTS', 'ORG'), ('Madonna', 'PERSON'), ('Shakira', 'PERSON'), ('Justin Bieber', 'PERSON'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Mãe, acho que vou morrer': o lado sombrio da febre do 'lifting de bumbum brasileiro' no Reino Unido","'Mum, I think I'm going to die': the dark side of the 'Brazilian butt lift' craze in the UK",0.0,neutral,"[('Mum', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Copa do Mundo de 2026 já é a melhor da história? O que dizem os números,Is the 2026 World Cup already the best in history? What the numbers say,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem são os indígenas que buscam regulamentar a mineração de ouro e diamante em suas terras,Who are the indigenous people seeking to regulate gold and diamond mining on their lands?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Bonnie Tyler, cantora de 'Total Eclipse of the Heart', morre aos 75 anos",'Total Eclipse of the Heart' Singer Bonnie Tyler Dies at 75,0.0,neutral,"[('Heart', 'ORG'), ('Bonnie Tyler Dies', 'PERSON'), ('75', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Governo Trump reage à decisão do Brasil que permite retorno de suposto espião à Rússia,Trump administration reacts to Brazil's decision allowing alleged spy to return to Russia,1.0,positive,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Análise: Trump não tem opção melhor do que negociar com o Irã,Analysis: Trump has no better option than negotiating with Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A sangrenta imagem de 1770 que alimentou a Independência dos EUA,The bloody image of 1770 that fueled US Independence,0.0,neutral,"[('1770', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Анализ: как долго Россия сможет обстреливать столицу Украины баллистическими ракетами?,Analysis: How long can Russia bombard the Ukrainian capital with ballistic missiles?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Таганроге эвакуируют район из-за атаки беспилотников","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: area in Taganrog evacuated due to drone attack",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Taganrog', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Из-за рубежа на фронт. Что известно о потерях иностранцев в составе российских сил в Украине,From abroad to the front. What is known about the losses of foreigners as part of Russian forces in Ukraine,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"У границы с Украиной проводятся военные сборы, Литва сбила дроны с сигаретами из Беларуси. Главное в Беларуси за неделю",Military training is taking place near the border with Ukraine; Lithuania shot down drones carrying cigarettes from Belarus. The main things in Belarus in a week,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Lithuania', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Иране похоронили аятоллу Хаменеи; КСИР заявил об ударе по американской базе в Иордании,Ayatollah Khamenei was buried in Iran; The IRGC announced a strike on an American base in Jordan,0.0,neutral,"[('Ayatollah Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('IRGC', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Jordan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Ариадна, ты меня бесишь!» Как семейный конфликт привел к депортации антивоенной активистки из Турции в Россию","""Ariadne, you're pissing me off!"" How a family conflict led to the deportation of an anti-war activist from Turkey to Russia",-1.0,negative,"[('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Разбитый автомобиль ТЦК и массовые беспорядки. Что известно о конфликте из-за мобилизации во Львове,A broken TCC car and riots. What is known about the conflict due to mobilization in Lviv,-1.0,negative,"[('Lviv', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Покушение на бизнесмена Ермолаева в Монако: суд в Киеве арестовал сотрудника ГУР, подозреваемого в убийстве Березовской",Attempt on businessman Ermolaev in Monaco: a court in Kyiv arrested a police officer suspected of murdering Berezovskaya,0.0,neutral,"[('Ermolaev', 'PERSON'), ('Monaco', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Berezovskaya', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Чет-нечет». В России придумывают все новые схемы продажи дефицитного бензина,"""Even-odd."" Russia is coming up with new schemes for selling scarce gasoline",0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,ВСУ заявили о поражении более 25 российских судов в Азовском море. Что известно,The Ukrainian Armed Forces announced the defeat of more than 25 Russian ships in the Sea of ​​Azov. What is known,0.0,neutral,"[('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('more than 25', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Sea of ​​Azov', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,スペイン、山火事で12人死亡　南欧で熱波続く,12 people killed in wildfires in Spain; heatwave continues in southern Europe,-1.0,negative,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、クリミア沖で燃料輸送中のロシア船を攻撃　燃料供給網への攻撃強化,"Ukraine attacks a Russian ship transporting fuel off the coast of Crimea, intensifying attacks on the fuel supply network",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Crimea', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,バーナム氏、次のイギリス首相になる見通し　労働党議員322人が党首指名投票で支持,Burnham expected to become the next British Prime Minister; 322 Labor Party MPs support him in leadership nomination vote,0.0,neutral,"[('Burnham', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('322', 'CARDINAL'), ('Labor Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカとイラン、攻撃の応酬続く　ハメネイ師の葬儀は最終日,US and Iran continue to exchange attacks; Khamenei's funeral is the last day,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('the last day', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ガザでW杯観戦会を開催の活動家、イスラエル軍に殺される　パレスチナ人から悼む声,Activist holding World Cup watching party in Gaza killed by Israeli army; voices of mourning from Palestinians,-1.0,negative,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 フランス、モロッコに勝ちベスト4　エムバペとデンベレが得点,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] France beats Morocco in top four, Mbappé and Dembele score",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mbappé', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英野党ファラージ党首の議員辞職に伴う補欠選挙の実施確定　主要政党はボイコット表明,By-election confirmed following UK opposition leader Farage's resignation as MP; major political parties announce boycott,1.0,positive,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Farage', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,イギリスの選挙常連候補「顔がごみ箱伯爵」とは？　補選でファラージ氏に挑戦, 所要時間 0,48","Video, Who is the regular British election candidate, ``The Count of the Garbage Can''? Challenging Mr. Farage in by-election, time required 0,48",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), (""The Count of the Garbage Can''"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Farage', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、ウクライナに「パトリオット」ミサイルのライセンス生産容認,Trump allows Ukraine to license production of Patriot missiles,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Patriot', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,中国のタピオカティー・チェーン、ルイ・ヴィトンの商標権侵害で2.4億円賠償命令　ネットで議論に,"Chinese bubble tea chain ordered to pay 240 million yen for infringement of Louis Vuitton's trademark rights, sparking debate online",0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('240 million yen', 'MONEY'), (""Louis Vuitton's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani na Iran zashambuliana wakati Khamenei akizikwa","Immediately, the United States and Iran attacked each other when Khamenei was buried",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Zifahamu tawala 10 za kimabavu Afrika,Know the 10 authoritarian regimes in Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Majengo 10 marefu zaidi Afrika Mashariki 2026,10 tallest buildings in East Africa 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('East Africa', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vita vya Ukraine vilivyobadili uhusiano kati ya Putin na matajiri wa Urusi,The war in Ukraine changed the relationship between Putin and Russia's wealthy,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Mbappe, Dembele waiongoza Ufaransa kwenye nusu fainali ya Kombe la Dunia","Mbappe, Dembele lead France to the semi-finals of the World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Hali iko vipi katika miji mitano yenye ubora wa juu wa maisha 2026?,How is the situation in the five cities with the highest quality of life in 2026?,0.0,neutral,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Tottenham yawasilisha ombi la kumsajili Randal Kolo Muani,European football rumors Friday: Tottenham submit a request to sign Randal Kolo Muani,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Tottenham', 'ORG'), ('Randal Kolo Muani', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Rais Samia awaonya wanaharakati dhidi ya kuchochea vurugu,President Samia warns activists against inciting violence,-1.0,negative,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Mashambulizi na cheche za maneno: Je, Trump ana chaguo jingine zaidi  ya kufanya mazungumzo na Iran?",Attacks and verbal sparks: Does Trump have any other option but to negotiate with Iran?,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,CCM na ACT Wazalendo kuanza mazungumzo ya Serikali ya Umoja wa Kitaifa Zanzibar,CCM and ACT Wazalendo to start talks on the Government of National Unity in Zanzibar,0.0,neutral,"[('CCM', 'ORG'), ('Wazalendo', 'GPE'), ('the Government of National Unity in', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Trump grants Kyiv Patriots licences: What’s next in the Russia-Ukraine war?,Trump grants Kyiv Patriots licences: What’s next in the Russia-Ukraine war?,-1.0,negative,"[('Kyiv Patriots', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Degree but no job: The battle against unemployment in Gaza,Degree but no job: The battle against unemployment in Gaza,0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Bayeux Tapestry smuggled into Britain for first visit in 1,000 years","Bayeux Tapestry smuggled into Britain for first visit in 1,000 years",0.0,neutral,"[('Bayeux Tapestry', 'ORG'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('1,000 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,England vs Norway: Key talking points ahead of World Cup quarterfinal,England vs Norway: Key talking points ahead of World Cup quarterfinal,0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Wildfires in southern Spain kill at least 12,Wildfires in southern Spain kill at least 12,-1.0,negative,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('at least 12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Unstoppable force’: Mbappe’s France crush Morocco’s World Cup dreams,‘Unstoppable force’: Mbappe’s France crush Morocco’s World Cup dreams,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Morocco’s World Cup', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Can Belgium’s roller-coaster campaign continue? Sturdy Spain are up next,Can Belgium’s roller-coaster campaign continue? Sturdy Spain are up next,0.0,neutral,"[('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Which records has Kylian Mbappe broken at the World Cup?,Which records has Kylian Mbappe broken at the World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('Kylian Mbappe', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Paris celebrates as France secures World Cup semi-final spot,Paris celebrates as France secures World Cup semi-final spot,0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US and Ukraine agree on patriot missile production deal,US and Ukraine agree on patriot missile production deal,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,When killer waves snuffed out six lives in Visakhapatnam,When killer waves snuffed out six lives in Visakhapatnam,-1.0,negative,"[('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Visakhapatnam', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Who is to mind the creche in Karnataka?,Who is to mind the creche in Karnataka?,0.0,neutral,"[('Karnataka', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Dwindling Fortunes: Quick-commerce platforms, large retailers threaten small businesses and neighbourhood shops in Kerala","Dwindling Fortunes: Quick-commerce platforms, large retailers threaten small businesses and neighbourhood shops in Kerala",1.0,positive,"[('Kerala', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Death of 14 Juang girls from Odisha in TN ammonia gas leak exposes tribe’s socio-economic struggle,Death of 14 Juang girls from Odisha in TN ammonia gas leak exposes tribe’s socio-economic struggle,-1.0,negative,"[('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('Odisha', 'GPE'), ('TN', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ranking the favourites in the FIFA World Cup,Ranking the favourites in the FIFA World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Vijay Karur visit LIVE: Chief Minister announces memorial to stampede victims on behalf of TVK,Vijay Karur visit LIVE: Chief Minister announces memorial to stampede victims on behalf of TVK,0.0,neutral,"[('Vijay Karur', 'PERSON'), ('TVK', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,India lays out tariffs and quotas for U.K. vehicles under trade deal,India lays out tariffs and quotas for U.K. vehicles under trade deal,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('U.K.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Prambanan Temple and Indonesia’s journey with Hinduism | Explained,Prambanan Temple and Indonesia’s journey with Hinduism | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Prambanan Temple', 'FAC'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE'), ('Hinduism', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Oman after Dubai: A new battle to bring Mahadev App kingpin back to India | Explained,Oman after Dubai: A new battle to bring Mahadev App kingpin back to India | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Oman', 'GPE'), ('Dubai', 'GPE'), ('Mahadev App', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Explained', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,SIR in Manipur: Data shows disproportionately high deletions in tribal constituencies,SIR in Manipur: Data shows disproportionately high deletions in tribal constituencies,0.0,neutral,"[('SIR', 'ORG'), ('Manipur', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Huge crowds in Mashhad as Iran's late supreme leader is buried,Huge crowds in Mashhad as Iran's late supreme leader is buried,0.0,neutral,"[('Mashhad', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ukrainian agent accused of murdering Monaco bomb suspect changes story,Ukrainian agent accused of murdering Monaco bomb suspect changes story,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Monaco', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Palestinians mourn Gaza World Cup screenings organiser killed in Israeli strike,Palestinians mourn Gaza World Cup screenings organiser killed in Israeli strike,-1.0,negative,"[('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Gaza World Cup', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"China lands reusable rocket for first time, state media says","China lands reusable rocket for first time, state media says",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Chip giant SK Hynix raises $26.5bn in mega US share sale,Chip giant SK Hynix raises $26.5bn in mega US share sale,0.0,neutral,"[('26.5bn', 'MONEY'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Big fall in oil, gas and cargo ships taking US-backed Hormuz route after new strikes","Big fall in oil, gas and cargo ships taking US-backed Hormuz route after new strikes",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Ukraine strikes Russian ships near Crimea, escalating attacks on fuel supplies","Ukraine strikes Russian ships near Crimea, escalating attacks on fuel supplies",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Crimea', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Democrat Graham Platner suspends campaign for key US Senate race after assault allegation,Democrat Graham Platner suspends campaign for key US Senate race after assault allegation,0.0,neutral,"[('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Graham Platner', 'PERSON'), ('US Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Greek F-16 fighter jet crash-lands at busy Zakynthos airport,Greek F-16 fighter jet crash-lands at busy Zakynthos airport,0.0,neutral,"[('Greek F-16', 'ORG'), ('Zakynthos', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ex-Olympian pleads not guilty to Reflecting Pool vandalism charges,Ex-Olympian pleads not guilty to Reflecting Pool vandalism charges,0.0,neutral,"[('Ex-Olympian', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Moscow Still Has Art and Culture. Just Don’t Say ‘Ukraine.’,Moscow Still Has Art and Culture. Just Don’t Say ‘Ukraine.’,0.0,neutral,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iran’s Supreme Leader Remains Absent, a Void at the Top of the Regime","Iran’s Supreme Leader Remains Absent, a Void at the Top of the Regime",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Remains Absent', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"After Venezuela Earthquakes, a Youth Baseball League Counts the Dead","After Venezuela Earthquakes, a Youth Baseball League Counts the Dead",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela Earthquakes', 'PERSON'), ('Youth Baseball League Counts the Dead', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,At Least 11 People Die in Southern Spain Wildfire,At Least 11 People Die in Southern Spain Wildfire,0.0,neutral,"[('At Least 11', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Fighting Fires With Figures, These Experts Are Trying to Stop Europe from Burning","Fighting Fires With Figures, These Experts Are Trying to Stop Europe from Burning",0.0,neutral,"[('These Experts Are Trying to Stop Europe', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Burning', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Can Hungarian Holocaust Survivors Find Justice in the U.S.?,Can Hungarian Holocaust Survivors Find Justice in the U.S.?,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"China Launches Reusable Rocket, Clearing a Key Hurdle in Race With SpaceX","China Launches Reusable Rocket, Clearing a Key Hurdle in Race With SpaceX",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Indian Diaspora, Now the Largest Foreign-Born Group in Australia, Welcomes Modi","Indian Diaspora, Now the Largest Foreign-Born Group in Australia, Welcomes Modi",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian Diaspora', 'PERSON'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Welcomes Modi', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Meet Neil, Australia’s Celebrity Seal","Meet Neil, Australia’s Celebrity Seal",0.0,neutral,"[('Meet Neil', 'PERSON'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Celebrity Seal', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Trump’s NATO Summit, and Everyone Else’s","Trump’s NATO Summit, and Everyone Else’s",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump’s NATO Summit', 'ORG')]"
