Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué Trump decidió bombardear a Estado Islámico en Nigeria,Why Trump decided to bomb Islamic State in Nigeria,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Invitamos a un hombre a casa para Navidad y se quedó con nosotros 45 años""","""We invited a man home for Christmas and he stayed with us for 45 years""",0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('45 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo el arresto de una mujer en Londres cambió la vida de los niños de todo el mundo,How a woman's arrest in London changed the lives of children around the world,-0.05,"[('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Miguel, Rafael y Gabriel, los ángeles venerados por tres religiones diferentes (y lo que revelan sobre el origen de los mensajeros divinos)","Michael, Raphael and Gabriel, the angels venerated by three different religions (and what they reveal about the origin of divine messengers)",0.0,"[('Michael', 'PERSON'), ('Raphael', 'PERSON'), ('Gabriel', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo un error tipográfico convirtió a una edición de la Biblia en 1631 en ""la Biblia Malvada"" (y otras erratas consideradas infames)","How a typographical error turned a 1631 edition of the Bible into ""the Evil Bible"" (and other infamous typos)",-0.5416666666666666,"[('1631', 'DATE'), ('Bible', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश में भारत क्या चूक गया? आईसीजी की रिपोर्ट और एक्सपर्ट्स से समझिए,What did India miss in Bangladesh? Understand from ICG report and experts,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('ICG', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,उन्नाव रेप केस: दिल्ली हाई कोर्ट के बाहर महिलाओं का प्रदर्शन, पुलिस ने दी चेतावनी","Live, Unnao rape case: Women protest outside Delhi High Court, police warns",0.0987878787878788,"[('Unnao', 'GPE'), ('Delhi High Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"तारिक़ रहमान को लेकर बांग्लादेश के मीडिया में पूछे जा रहे कई सवाल, जमात से कैसा होगा संबंध?","Many questions are being asked in the media of Bangladesh regarding Tariq Rehman, what will be his relation with the Jamaat?",0.5,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Tariq Rehman', 'PERSON'), ('Jamaat', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"जब पीएम मोदी ने लाहौर में कहा था, ""जंग को ज़ंग लग गया, अब जंग नहीं होगी""","When PM Modi said in Lahore, ""The war has become rusty, now there will be no war.""",0.0,"[('PM Modi', 'ORG'), ('Lahore', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"""हमने क्रिसमस पर एक शख़्स को अपने घर बुलाया- और वह 45 साल तक हमारे साथ रहा""","""We invited a man to our house for Christmas - and he stayed with us for 45 years""",0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('45 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वक़्त की धारा में हँसिए की धार, भारतीय कम्युनिस्ट पार्टी के 100 साल","The edge of the sickle in the stream of time, 100 years of the Communist Party of India",0.0,"[('100 years', 'DATE'), ('the Communist Party of India', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ट्रंप ने कहा- अमेरिका ने नाइजीरिया में इस्लामिक स्टेट के ख़िलाफ़ घातक हमला किया,Trump said- America carried out deadly attack against Islamic State in Nigeria,-0.2,"[('Trump said-', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Islamic State', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इंडिगो संकट के बाद अब तीन नई एयरलाइंस शुरू करने की मंज़ूरी, जानिए इनके बारे में","After Indigo crisis, now approval to start three new airlines, know about them",0.13636363636363635,"[('Indigo', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"व्हाट्सऐप में इस नए तरीक़े से हो रही है धोखाधड़ी, बचने के लिए ये करें","Fraud is happening in this new way in WhatsApp, do this to avoid it",0.13636363636363635,"[('Fraud', 'ORG'), ('WhatsApp', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como a prisão de uma mulher em Londres mudou a vida de crianças no mundo todo,How a woman's arrest in London changed the lives of children around the world,-0.05,"[('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Cirurgia de Bolsonaro: três pontos sobre oitava cirurgia do ex-presidente desde facada,Bolsonaro surgery: three points about the former president's eighth surgery since stabbing,-0.3,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('eighth', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Família de sangue nem sempre é o nosso lugar de apoio e confiança, diz Vera Iaconelli","Blood family is not always our place of support and trust, says Vera Iaconelli",0.0,"[('Vera Iaconelli', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Em carta, Bolsonaro confirma filho Flávio como pré-candidato a presidente","In letter, Bolsonaro confirms son Flávio as pre-candidate for president",0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O 'trem do amor', no qual ucranianas visitam seus maridos que lutam contra a Rússia",The 'love train' in which Ukrainian women visit their husbands who are fighting against Russia,0.5,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,7 ideias em alta para viajar mais e melhor em 2026,7 trending ideas to travel more and better in 2026,0.5,"[('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Convidamos um homem para passar o Natal em nossa casa. Ele ficou conosco por 45 anos','We invited a man to spend Christmas at our house. He stayed with us for 45 years',0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), (""45 years'"", 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Umas 50 brasileiras' estiveram na mansão de Epstein, diz vítima do bilionário à BBC","'About 50 Brazilian women' were at Epstein's mansion, the billionaire's victim tells the BBC",-0.07500000000000001,"[('About 50', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem era o Sol Invicto, deus pagão com festa que Igreja usou para celebrar o Natal","Who was the Undefeated Sun, a pagan god with a party that the Church used to celebrate Christmas",0.0,"[('the Undefeated Sun', 'PERSON'), ('Church', 'ORG'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что мы знаем о потерях России в Украине в 2025 году?,What do we know about Russian losses in Ukraine in 2025?,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Лицо, известное многим как ""Юра Унитаз""». Кто может возглавить российские беспилотные войска",“The face known to many as “Yura the Toilet”.” Who can lead Russian unmanned troops,0.15555555555555556,"[('Yura the Toilet', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Россия отдала Украину, Казахстан и Кавказ». В США рассекретили расшифровки переговоров Путина с Бушем","“Russia gave up Ukraine, Kazakhstan and the Caucasus.” Transcripts of Putin's talks with Bush have been declassified in the United States",0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kazakhstan', 'GPE'), ('Caucasus', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Bush', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский заявил, что вскоре встретится с Трампом; Россия ударила по Одессе","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky said he will soon meet with Trump; Russia hit Odessa",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Odessa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп заявил, что США нанесли удар по «Исламскому государству» в Нигерии",Trump says US has struck Islamic State in Nigeria,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В рождественском обращении король Карл призвал к миру и цифровому детоксу,King Charles calls for peace and digital detox in Christmas address,0.0,"[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Мы пригласили к себе домой на Рождество человека, и он остался с нами на 45 лет»","“We invited a man to our home for Christmas, and he stayed with us for 45 years.”",0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('45 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Умерла актриса Вера Алентова, звезда фильма «Москва слезам не верит»","Actress Vera Alentova, star of the film “Moscow Doesn’t Believe in Tears,” has died",0.0,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Tears', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В своем обращении «к городу и миру» папа римский призвал к прекращению всех войн,"In his address “to the city and the world,” the Pope called for an end to all wars",0.0,[]
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Аленький цветочек» на крови. В Мариуполе открывают театр, где погибли сотни людей","""The Scarlet Flower"" on blood. A theater is being opened in Mariupol where hundreds of people died",0.0,"[('The Scarlet Flower', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Mariupol', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍、ナイジェリアの「イスラム国」に「強力な」攻撃実施　トランプ氏が発表,"U.S. military launches ""strong"" attack on Islamic State in Nigeria, Trump announces",0.16666666666666663,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Islamic State', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナ和平の「新たな構想」、ゼレンスキー氏が称賛　米特使との協議受け,Zelenskiy praises “new concept” for peace in Ukraine after talks with US special envoy,0.24675324675324675,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トルコ、「イスラム国」メンバー115人を拘束　年末年始の攻撃を計画した疑い,Türkiye detains 115 Islamic State members suspected of planning year-end and New Year attacks,0.13636363636363635,"[('Türkiye', 'ORG'), ('115', 'CARDINAL'), ('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('year-end', 'DATE'), ('New Year', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,教皇レオ、ウクライナでの戦争を終わらせる「勇気」促す　初のクリスマス演説,Pope Leo urges “courage” to end war in Ukraine in first Christmas speech,0.25,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英国王、分断された世界での結束を呼びかける　クリスマス恒例メッセージ,British King's annual Christmas message calls for unity in a divided world,0.0,"[(""British King's"", 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 アメリカ人教皇とアメリカ政府、仲たがいしているのか,[Commentary] Are the American Pope and the US government at odds?,0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告の資料、さらに100万件超か　米当局が発見し精査中と,More than 1 million more documents belonging to former defendant Epstein have been discovered by US authorities and are under review.,0.3333333333333333,"[('More than 1 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「くまのプーさん」初登場から100年　イギリスの森に名声もたらす,"100 years since “Winnie the Pooh” first appeared, bringing fame to British forests",0.125,"[('100 years', 'DATE'), ('Winnie the Pooh', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,サンタクロース、スピード違反で取り締まり受ける　米オハイオ州, 所要時間 1,14","Video, Santa Claus gets arrested for speeding in Ohio, US, Duration 1,14",0.0,"[('Santa Claus', 'PERSON'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Marekani yafanya shambulizi Nigeria,  dhidi ya nani na kwa nini?","The United States is attacking Nigeria, against whom and why?",0.0,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Zelensky apongeza 'mawazo mapya' baada ya mazungumzo na wajumbe wa Marekani","Directly, Zelensky applauds the 'new ideas' after talks with the American delegation",0.07878787878787878,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ajali maarufu za ndege zilizowaua viongozi na watu mashuhuri duniani,Famous plane crashes that killed world leaders and celebrities,0.15,[]
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Habari 10 zilizosomwa sana BBC mwaka 2025,10 most read BBC news in 2025,0.5,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Semenyo kutua City, United au Liverpool?","European Football Rumors: Semenyo landing at City, United or Liverpool?",0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Semenyo', 'PERSON'), ('City', 'GPE'), ('United', 'ORG'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wakristo Tanzania wahimizwa kudai haki wakiadhimisha Krismasi,Christians in Tanzania are encouraged to demand justice while celebrating Christmas,0.0,"[('Christians', 'NORP'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watano wafariki helikopta ikianguka mlima Kilimanjaro,Five died when the helicopter crashed on Mount Kilimanjaro,0.0,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mount Kilimanjaro', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Krisimasi ni nini na ni kwanini Wakristo wanaisherehekea?,What is Christmas and why do Christians celebrate it?,0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('Christians', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Matukio 5 makubwa ya kukumbukwa duniani 2025,5 major events to remember in the world in 2025,0.0625,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Z﻿ingatia mambo haya matano kama hutaki kunenepa msimu wa Krismasi,Consider these five things if you don't want to gain weight during the Christmas season,0.0,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Christmas season', 'DATE')]"
