Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Vi cómo se llevaron a mi hijo a punta de pistola"": la desesperación de los familiares de los cientos de niños secuestrados en una escuela católica de Nigeria","""I saw how they took my son at gunpoint"": the despair of the relatives of the hundreds of children kidnapped from a Catholic school in Nigeria",0.0,"[('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué es Lev Tahor, la secta judía ultraortodoxa de la que rescataron a 17 menores en Colombia y a la que acusan de tráfico y abuso infantil","What is Lev Tahor, the ultra-Orthodox Jewish sect from which they rescued 17 minors in Colombia and from which they accuse of trafficking and child abuse",0.0,"[('Lev Tahor', 'PERSON'), ('ultra-Orthodox', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Lo que nos tiene fregados aquí es el aumento del dólar"": cómo viven los venezolanos la posibilidad de un ataque de EE.UU.","""What's bothering us here is the rise of the dollar"": how Venezuelans experience the possibility of a US attack.",0.0,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Nadie las va a apoyar"": la reacción de los soldados ucranianos en el frente a las propuestas del plan de paz de EE.UU.","""No one is going to support them"": the reaction of Ukrainian soldiers on the front to the proposals of the US peace plan.",0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Nos reencontramos después de 40 años y el amor aún estaba ahí"": la conmovedora historia de dos adolescentes que fueron separados cuando ella quedó embarazada","""We met again after 40 years and the love was still there"": the moving story of two teenagers who were separated when she became pregnant",0.41666666666666663,"[('40 years', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"रूस को फिर जी-8 में लाने की कोशिश, क्या यह पुतिन की जीत है?","Effort to bring Russia back into G-8, is this a victory for Putin?",0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('G-8', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,जंग ख़त्म करने के लिए जारी वार्ता के बीच रूस-यूक्रेन ने एक-दूसरे पर किए बड़े हमले","Live, amid ongoing talks to end the war, Russia-Ukraine launched major attacks on each other",0.024621212121212117,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार: नीतीश की नई सरकार पर क्या बीजेपी का अधिक असर दिखाई देगा,Bihar: Will BJP have more influence on Nitish's new government?,0.3181818181818182,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Nitish', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इथियोपिया में फटा ज्वालामुखी और असर भारत में, जानिए क्या-क्या होगा प्रभावित","Volcano erupts in Ethiopia and its impact in India, know what will be affected",0.0,"[('Ethiopia', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नरेंद्र मोदी ने अयोध्या के राम मंदिर में किया ध्वजारोहण, जानिए, क्या हैं इसकी विशेषताएं","Narendra Modi hoisted the flag in Ram temple of Ayodhya, know what are its features",0.0,"[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('Ram', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"धर्मेंद्र ने जब पूछा था, 'कैसे हो बेटे, कुछ खाया तुमने?'","When Dharmendra asked, 'How are you son, have you eaten anything?'",0.0,"[('Dharmendra', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"हुमा क़ुरैशी का सवाल- लड़कियां कैसी दिखें, कितना वज़न हो ये कोई और क्यों तय करे","Huma Qureshi's question - Why should anyone else decide how girls should look, how much they should weigh?",0.2,"[(""Huma Qureshi's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"धर्मेंद्र का निधन, अभिनय के अलावा जो उर्दू और शायरी से हमेशा करते रहे प्यार","Dharmendra passes away, apart from acting he always loved Urdu and poetry.",0.35,"[('Dharmendra', 'PERSON'), ('Urdu', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सिंध: पाकिस्तान में सबसे ज़्यादा हिंदू आबादी वाले इलाक़े का इतिहास,Sindh: History of the area with the highest Hindu population in Pakistan,0.0,"[('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O relato de mães brasileiras de crianças atacadas em Portugal: 'Atravessei um oceano pra dar vida melhor e me frustrei',The report of Brazilian mothers of children attacked in Portugal: 'I crossed an ocean to give a better life and I was frustrated',-0.09999999999999998,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Portugal', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,STF mantém Bolsonaro preso por unanimidade: o que esperar de semana decisiva para o ex-presidente,STF unanimously keeps Bolsonaro arrested: what to expect from a decisive week for the former president,0.0,"[('STF', 'ORG'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('a decisive week', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Bolsonaro dizer que teve surto não combina com imagem de homem forte que criou, diz analista","Bolsonaro saying he had an outbreak does not fit with the image of a strong man he created, says analyst",0.11666666666666664,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que a imprensa internacional falou sobre episódio com tornozeleira eletrônica de Bolsonaro,What the international press said about the episode with Bolsonaro's electronic ankle bracelet,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Sertralina e pregabalina: para que servem os medicamentos tomados por Bolsonaro,Sertraline and pregabalin: what are the drugs taken by Bolsonaro for,0.0,"[('Sertraline', 'PERSON'), ('pregabalin', 'GPE'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Lula sai do confronto com Trump mais forte do que entrou' em caso Bolsonaro, diz New York Times","'Lula leaves the confrontation with Trump stronger than he entered' in Bolsonaro case, says New York Times",0.13636363636363635,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('New York Times', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Baby Shark: como vídeo de 90 segundos gerou negócio de US$ 400 milhões,Baby Shark: how a 90-second video generated a business worth US$400 million,0.3,"[('Baby Shark', 'PERSON'), ('90-second', 'TIME'), ('US$400 million', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Fazer xixi sentado é melhor para os homens?,Is peeing sitting down better for men?,0.17222222222222222,[]
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A 'escola de astronautas' que fica escondida em montanha na Suíça,The 'astronaut school' hidden in a mountain in Switzerland,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: новый удар по Киеву и массированная атака на Новороссийск, Геленджик и Таганрог","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: a new blow to Kyiv and a massive attack on Novorossiysk, Gelendzhik and Taganrog",0.06818181818181818,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Novorossiysk', 'ORG'), ('Gelendzhik and Taganrog', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Возможно, наступает рассвет». Что пишет пресса о женевских переговорах по окончанию войны в Украине","""Perhaps dawn is coming."" What the press writes about the Geneva negotiations to end the war in Ukraine",0.0,"[('Geneva', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Триумф Аонисики. Беженец из Украины выиграл Императорский турнир по сумо в Японии,Triumph of Aonisiki. A refugee from Ukraine won the Imperial Sumo Tournament in Japan,0.0,"[('Triumph of Aonisiki', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('the Imperial Sumo Tournament', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Переговоры в Женеве, новые версии мирного плана и повсеместный хаос. «Контекст» от Би-би-си","Negotiations in Geneva, new versions of the peace plan and widespread chaos. ""Context"" from the BBC",0.13636363636363635,"[('Geneva', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Австралии детям до 16 запретили пользоваться соцсетями. Как это будет работать?,"In Australia, children under 16 are banned from using social media. How will it work?",0.03333333333333333,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('under 16', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Пробиться через «зону поражения»: как роботы спасают украинских военных на восточном фронте,Breaking through the “kill zone”: how robots save Ukrainian soldiers on the eastern front,0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Стойкий» снова в Ла-Манше. Британский ВМФ перехватил еще два российских корабля,The Steadfast is back in the English Channel. The British Navy intercepted two more Russian ships,0.15,"[('Steadfast', 'PERSON'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE'), ('The British Navy', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Взлет «Грипена». Вслед за Украиной шведские боевые самолеты купила Колумбия и захотела Канада,"Takeoff of the Gripen. Following Ukraine, Colombia bought Swedish combat aircraft and Canada wanted them",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Swedish', 'NORP'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Наемники для России? Дочь экс-президента ЮАР обвинила свою сестру в вербовке южноафриканцев для войны в Украине,Mercenaries for Russia? The daughter of the ex-president of South Africa accused her sister of recruiting South Africans for the war in Ukraine,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('South Africans', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Рубио покинул Женеву, заявив о значительном прогрессе в переговорах с Украиной. Главное",Rubio left Geneva announcing significant progress in negotiations with Ukraine. Main,0.18055555555555555,"[('Geneva', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、和平案の修正を前向きに評価　欧州側が変更か,Mr. Zelenskiy positively evaluates the revisions to the peace plan; will the European side make changes?,0.11363636363636363,"[('Zelenskiy', 'PERSON'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 修正された和平案、ウクライナがゆくゆくは受け入れるかもしれない内容に,"[Commentary] Revised peace plan, content that Ukraine may eventually accept",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ政権におけるコーミー元FBI長官やNY州司法長官の起訴無効　臨時検事の任命が違法と連邦地裁,Federal district judge invalidates indictment of former FBI Director Comey and New York State Attorney General during Trump administration; appoints temporary prosecutor illegal,-0.0784090909090909,"[('FBI', 'ORG'), ('Comey', 'PERSON'), ('New York State', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,コーミー元FBI長官、「トランプはおそらくまた私を狙う」「司法の独立信じる」　自分の起訴無効となり, 所要時間 1,25","Video, Former FBI Director Comey says, ``Trump will probably target me again'' ``I believe in the independence of the judiciary'' His indictment is invalidated, time required 1,25",0.0,"[('FBI', 'ORG'), ('Comey', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,韓国最大のオンライン性犯罪組織のトップに無期懲役判決　被害者260人超,"Head of South Korea's largest online sex crime organization sentenced to life in prison, with over 260 victims",0.0,"[(""South Korea's"", 'GPE'), ('260', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナ和平交渉で「和平の枠組み更新」と米・ウが共同声明,U.S. and U.S. jointly announce ``renewal of peace framework'' during Ukraine peace negotiations,0.0,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,COP30、化石燃料削減について新合意を確保できず,COP30 fails to secure new agreement on fossil fuel reduction,0.012121212121212125,[]
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヴェトナムの洪水による死者、少なくとも90人に　12人が行方不明,"At least 90 people killed in Vietnam floods, 12 missing",-0.2333333333333333,"[('At least 90', 'CARDINAL'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ナイジェリアのキリスト教系学校で生徒・教師300人以上誘拐　生徒50人が脱出,Over 300 students and teachers kidnapped at Christian school in Nigeria; 50 students escape,0.0,"[('Over 300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Christian', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('50', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Zelensky aunga mkono marekebisho ya mpango wa amani unaopendekezwa","Directly, Zelensky supports the amendment of the proposed peace plan",0.1,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Gen Z Tanzania wanavyozima udini kwa utani na ubunifu,Gen Z Tanzania extinguishes religion with jokes and creativity,0.0,"[('Gen Z', 'PERSON'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Cartel de los Soles: Lifahamu kundi linaloiumiza kichwa Marekani,Cartel de los Soles: Get to know the cartel that is hurting America,0.0,"[('Cartel de los Soles', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Machafuko yaliyoshuhudiwa Tanzania yalichochewa kutoka nje- Waziri Mkuu,The riots witnessed in Tanzania were provoked from outside - the Prime Minister,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Vinicius agoma kusaini mkataba mpya Madrid,European football rumors: Vinicius refuses to sign a new contract in Madrid,0.06818181818181818,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Madrid', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Kwanini vuguvugu la Gen Z si la Tanzania peke yake?,Protests in Tanzania: Why is the Gen Z movement not unique to Tanzania?,-0.1875,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini wanawake hawawaoneshi wapenzi wao kwenye mtandao?,Why don't women show their boyfriends on the internet?,0.0,[]
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kuwasaka wauaji na wauzaji wa viungo vya miili ya binadamu kwa ajili ya 'matambiko',Pursuing killers and sellers of human body parts for 'rituals',0.0,[]
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Choo hiki sawa na bodaboda 10,000 au nyumba 300 za kisasa","This toilet is equivalent to 10,000 bodabodas or 300 modern houses",0.08333333333333334,"[('10,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('300', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Mabosi' wa BBC kuhojiwa bungeni,BBC 'bosses' to be questioned in parliament,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
