Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"तेजस्वी यादव होंगे महागठबंधन के सीएम उम्मीदवार, विपक्ष ने पूछा- एनडीए का चेहरा कौन?","Tejashwi Yadav will be the CM candidate of Grand Alliance, opposition asked- Who is the face of NDA?",0.5,"[('Tejashwi Yadav', 'PERSON'), ('CM', 'ORG'), ('Grand Alliance', 'ORG'), ('NDA', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,डिप्रेशन की दवाइयों के साइड इफ़ेक्ट्स पर भी गौर करना क्यों ज़रूरी है?,Why is it important to consider the side effects of depression medications?,0.4,[]
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,जेएनयू छात्र संघ चुनाव 4 नवंबर को, 6 नवंबर को आएंगे नतीजे","Live, JNU Students Union elections on 4th November, results will come on 6th November",0.13636363636363635,"[('JNU Students Union', 'ORG'), ('4th', 'ORDINAL'), ('November', 'DATE'), ('6th', 'ORDINAL'), ('November', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मध्य प्रदेश: दलित युवक को पेशाब पिलाने का आरोप, राज्य में 15 दिनों के अंदर दलित उत्पीड़न के तीन बड़े मामले","Madhya Pradesh: Accused of making Dalit youth drink urine, three major cases of Dalit harassment in the state within 15 days",0.0625,"[('Dalit', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dalit', 'PERSON'), ('15 days', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पुतिन से नाराज़ ट्रंप ने रूसी तेल कंपनियों पर लगाए प्रतिबंध,भारत पर भी क्यों पड़ सकता है बुरा असर","Angry with Putin, Trump imposed sanctions on Russian oil companies, why it can have a bad effect on India too",-0.3999999999999999,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,महिला वर्ल्ड कप: सेमीफ़ाइनल में अब भी पहुंच सकती है भारतीय टीम,Women's World Cup: Indian team can still reach the semi-finals,0.0,"[(""Women's World Cup"", 'ORG'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप-पुतिन बातचीत 'टलते' ही रूस का यूक्रेन पर बड़ा हमला, बच्चों समेत सात लोगों की मौत","As soon as Trump-Putin talks were 'postponed', Russia attacked Ukraine, seven people including children died.",0.0,"[('Trump-Putin', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,सम्राट चौधरी ने बिहार विधानसभा चुनाव को लेकर किया ये दावा - देखिए इंटरव्यू, अवधि 2,59","Video, Samrat Chaudhary made this claim regarding Bihar assembly elections - watch interview, duration 2,59",0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('2,59', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार के इस ज़िले में 'चमत्कारी फल' ने बदली ज़िंदगियां, पर किसानों को अब भी है ये मलाल","'Miracle fruit' changed lives in this district of Bihar, but farmers still have this regret",0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que brasileiros estão buscando cidadania de país africano de onde saíram milhões de escravizados,Why Brazilians are seeking citizenship in an African country from which millions of slaves came,0.0,"[('Brazilians', 'NORP'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O homem com ELA que se tornou símbolo da lei de eutanásia aprovada no Uruguai,The man with ALS who became a symbol of the euthanasia law approved in Uruguay,0.0,"[('ALS', 'ORG'), ('Uruguay', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Efeito China': aproximação com o gigante asiático pode enfraquecer a indústria no Brasil?,'China effect': could rapprochement with the Asian giant weaken the industry in Brazil?,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Asian', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que se sabe sobre ataques do governo Trump a barcos no Pacífico que deixaram 5 mortos,What is known about Trump administration attacks on boats in the Pacific that left 5 dead,-0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Pacific', 'LOC'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que se sabe sobre prisão de Capitão Hunter, youtuber detido em São Paulo por suspeita de estupro de vulnerável","What is known about the arrest of Captain Hunter, a YouTuber detained in São Paulo on suspicion of rape of a vulnerable person",-0.275,"[('Hunter', 'PERSON'), ('YouTuber', 'GPE'), ('São Paulo', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Por que novo filme com Leonardo DiCaprio é sucesso de crítica, mas fracasso de bilheteria","Why new film with Leonardo DiCaprio is a critical success, but a box office failure",0.029924242424242423,"[('Leonardo DiCaprio', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Rei Charles será primeiro monarca britânico a rezar ao lado de um papa em 500 anos,King Charles will be first British monarch to pray alongside a pope in 500 years,0.125,"[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('500 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Por anos, só temíamos seres humanos': por que mulher russa viveu em caverna na Índia com filhas pequenas","'For years, we only feared human beings': why Russian woman lived in cave in India with young daughters",0.025,"[('years', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quanto podem valer as joias roubadas do Louvre?,How much could the jewels stolen from the Louvre be worth?,0.25,"[('Louvre', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Мы ждали. Время пришло». Трамп отменил встречу с Путиным в Венгрии, США ввели санкции против «Роснефти» и «Лукойла»","“We waited. The time has come."" Trump canceled a meeting with Putin in Hungary, the United States imposed sanctions against Rosneft and Lukoil",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Rosneft', 'ORG'), ('Lukoil', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Семь вопросов к примирению России и Азербайджана,Seven questions for reconciliation between Russia and Azerbaijan,0.0,"[('Seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Azerbaijan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Дублине второй день продолжаются антииммигрантские беспорядки. Что известно,Anti-immigrant riots continue for the second day in Dublin. What is known,0.0,"[('the second day', 'DATE'), ('Dublin', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что такое «теневой флот» и как Россия использует его против Запада,What is the “shadow fleet” and how Russia uses it against the West,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Евросоюз ужесточил санкции против России. Что попало в 19-й пакет?,The European Union has tightened sanctions against Russia. What was included in the 19th package?,0.0,"[('The European Union', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('19th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Трамп объявил об отмене встречи с Путиным в Будапеште","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Trump announces cancellation of meeting with Putin in Budapest",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Budapest', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ФИДЕ изучит обвинения в мошенничестве от экс-чемпиона мира Крамника в адрес гроссмейстера Народицкого,FIDE will look into allegations of fraud from ex-world champion Kramnik against grandmaster Naroditsky,0.0,"[('Kramnik', 'PERSON'), ('Naroditsky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ФБК потребовали признать террористической организацией в России,FBK demanded to recognize a terrorist organization in Russia,0.0,"[('FBK', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Премию Сахарова присудили белорусскому журналисту Анджею Почобуту и грузинской журналистке Мзие Амаглобели,The Sakharov Prize was awarded to Belarusian journalist Andrzej Poczobut and Georgian journalist Mzie Amaglobeli,0.0,"[('Belarusian', 'NORP'), ('Andrzej Poczobut', 'PERSON'), ('Georgian', 'NORP'), ('Mzie Amaglobeli', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,«Для кадыровцев не важно девушка ты, гей или критик». Что известно правозащитникам о смерти чеченки в Ереване?, Продолжительность 6,10","Video, “For Kadyrov’s men, it doesn’t matter whether you’re a girl, gay or a critic.” What do human rights activists know about the death of a Chechen woman in Yerevan?, Duration 6.10",0.20833333333333334,"[('Kadyrov', 'PERSON'), ('Chechen', 'NORP'), ('Yerevan', 'PERSON'), ('6.10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ガザ人道支援、イスラエルに「法的義務がある」　国際司法裁が勧告,"Israel has a legal obligation to provide humanitarian aid to Gaza, International Court of Justice recommends",0.1,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('International Court of Justice', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ガザの保健危機は「何世代にもわたって続く」　WHOトップがBBCに語る,"Gaza's health crisis will 'last for generations', WHO chief tells BBC",0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカが新たな対ロ制裁発表　トランプ氏、プーチン氏との対話は「何も進展がない」,"US announces new sanctions against Russia; Trump says talks with Putin ""no progress""",0.13636363636363635,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍、太平洋でも船を攻撃　「麻薬テロリスト」だと国防長官,U.S. military attacks ships in the Pacific; Defense Secretary calls them ``narco-terrorists'',-0.1,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Pacific', 'LOC'), ('Defense', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アイスランドで初めて蚊を確認、5月には過去最高気温を更新,"First mosquito found in Iceland, record high temperature in May",0.20500000000000002,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('Iceland', 'GPE'), ('May', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアがウクライナ首都など攻撃、子どもら死傷　米ロ首脳会談の棚上げ発表後,"Russia attacks Ukrainian capital, killing children and injuring others, after announcement of shelving of US-Russian summit",0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,仏ルーヴル美術館館長、強盗犯が侵入した窓を映す「監視カメラなかった」　察知に遅れ,Director of France's Louvre Museum was too late to realize that there was no surveillance camera showing the window where the robber entered.,-0.3,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Louvre Museum', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 初の女性首相誕生という歴史的瞬間、ただし高市氏の理念に懸念も,"[Commentary] Historic moment with the birth of the first female prime minister, but there are concerns about Takaichi's ideals",0.08333333333333333,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Takaichi', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】日本初の女性首相、高市早苗氏はどんな人か　「鉄の女」サッチャー元英首相を私淑,"[Commentary] What kind of person is Japan's first female prime minister, Sanae Takaichi? She is a personal admirer of the ""Iron Lady"" and former British Prime Minister Thatcher.",0.14166666666666666,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the ""Iron Lady', 'LAW'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Thatcher', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump anasema mazungumzo ya Putin 'hayaelekei popote' huku akiweka vikwazo vipya","Directly, Trump says Putin's talks are 'going nowhere' as he imposes new sanctions",0.11818181818181818,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Ahadi tano za urais zilizoibua mshangao Zanzibar,Tanzania 2025 election: Five presidential promises that surprised Zanzibar,0.1,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Zanzibar', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini sheria ya uhalifu wa mitandaoni inawatia wasiwasi Gen Z Kenya?,Why cybercrime law worries Gen Z Kenya?,0.0,"[('Gen Z', 'PERSON'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Alhamisi: Michael Olise kusalia Bayern Munich mpaka 2029?,European Football Rumors Thursday: Michael Olise to stay at Bayern Munich until 2029?,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Michael Olise', 'PERSON'), ('Bayern Munich', 'LOC'), ('2029', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Makamu Mwenyekiti wa CHADEMA, John Heche akamatwa na kupelekwa Tarime Tanzania","The Vice Chairman of CHADEMA, John Heche was arrested and sent to Tarime Tanzania",0.0,"[('CHADEMA', 'ORG'), ('John Heche', 'PERSON'), ('Tarime Tanzania', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Picha za wanawake wa Kisomali zinavyotumiwa kueneza taarifa ghushi mitandaoni,Photos of Somali women are being used to spread fake news on the internet,-0.5,"[('Somali', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini Trump alifanikiwa kusuluhisha vita vya Gaza lakini anashindwa na vita vya Ukraine?,Why did Trump succeed in resolving the Gaza war but is failing in the Ukraine war?,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, ndege ya Putin itavuka anga ya Umoja wa Ulaya kwenda Hungary?",Will Putin's plane cross EU airspace to Hungary?,0.0,"[(""Will Putin's"", 'PERSON'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Hungary', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Khamenei amtaja Trump kuwa muongo kuhusu mradi wa nyuklia,Khamenei called Trump a liar about the nuclear project,0.0,"[('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kizazi kipya cha 'Gen Z' kinavyotikisa siasa duniani kwa maandamano,The new generation of 'Gen Z' is shaking up world politics with protests,0.13636363636363635,"[(""'Gen Z'"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
