Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué medidas están tomando los gobiernos para aliviar el aumento de los precios de los combustibles en América Latina y el mundo,What measures are governments taking to alleviate the increase in fuel prices in Latin America and the world?,0.0,neutral,"[('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Trump dice que EE.UU. podría apoderarse ""fácilmente"" de la isla de Jark, el centro neurálgico de la industria petrolera de Irán","Trump says US could 'easily' seize Jark Island, nerve center of Iran's oil industry",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Jark Island', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Artemis II: cómo es la ambiciosa misión para regresar a la Luna después de 50 años,Artemis II: what the ambitious mission is like to return to the Moon after 50 years,0.0,neutral,"[('Artemis II', 'PRODUCT'), ('50 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los intrépidos ladrones que en apenas 3 minutos robaron pinturas valuadas en US$10 millones de un museo en Italia,The intrepid thieves who in just 3 minutes stole paintings valued at US$10 million from a museum in Italy,0.0,neutral,"[('just 3 minutes', 'TIME'), ('US$10 million', 'MONEY'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Las repartidoras de yogur que combaten la soledad en Japón, uno de los países más envejecidos del mundo","Yogurt delivery girls fighting loneliness in Japan, one of the oldest countries in the world",0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Un petrolero de Rusia llega a Cuba con el permiso de Trump en medio del bloqueo de EE.UU. a la isla,A Russian oil tanker arrives in Cuba with Trump's permission amid the US blockade of the island,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Impiden a la máxima autoridad católica en Jerusalén entrar al lugar más sagrado del cristianismo el Domingo de Ramos,The highest Catholic authority in Jerusalem is prevented from entering the most sacred place in Christianity on Palm Sunday,0.0,neutral,"[('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'), ('Christianity', 'NORP'), ('Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo fue la ""primera guerra de la historia"" en la región donde hoy se encuentra Irán","How was the ""first war in history"" in the region where Iran is today?",-1.0,negative,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""La riqueza de las naciones"": cómo un libro escrito hace 250 años aún influye en nuestras vidas","""The Wealth of Nations"": How a book written 250 years ago still influences our lives",0.0,neutral,"[('The Wealth of Nations', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('250 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La historia de la Monobloc, la humilde silla de plástico blanca que ha conquistado el mundo","The history of the Monobloc, the humble white plastic chair that has conquered the world",0.0,neutral,"[('Monobloc', 'PERSON')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप ने फिर बातचीत की कही बात, ईरान ने पाकिस्तान की भूमिका पर भी दिया जवाब","Trump again talked about talks, Iran also replied on Pakistan's role",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,होर्मुज़ में ईरान के 'नियंत्रण' से जुड़े प्रस्ताव पर बोले अमेरिकी विदेश मंत्री मार्को रुबियो","Live, US Secretary of State Marco Rubio speaks on the proposal related to Iran's 'control' in Hormuz",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Marco Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तानी क्रिकेट लीग में बॉल के साथ क्या हुआ जिस पर मचा हंगामा,What happened with the ball in Pakistani Cricket League that created an uproar?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistani Cricket League', 'ORG')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,लौट रही है लखनऊ की शाही रसोई की रौनक जहाँ 188 साल से परोसे जा रहे हैं लज़ीज़ पकवान,The glory of Lucknow's royal kitchen is returning where delicious dishes are being served for 188 years.,0.0,neutral,"[('Lucknow', 'ORG'), ('188 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ईरान युद्ध के कारण पैदा हुए तेल संकट से कैसे निपट रहे हैं ये देश,How are these countries dealing with the oil crisis caused by the Iran war?,-1.0,negative,"[('the Iran war', 'EVENT')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार बोर्ड के टॉपर्स की कहानी: किसी ने मज़दूरी करते हुए तो किसी ने यूट्यूब के ज़रिए की पढ़ाई,Story of Bihar Board toppers: Some studied while working and some through YouTube.,0.0,neutral,"[('Bihar Board', 'ORG'), ('YouTube', 'ORG')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सऊदी एयर बेस पर दो टुकड़ों में टूटे अमेरिकी  विमान की तस्वीर की सच्चाई क्या है,What is the truth behind the picture of an American plane broken into two pieces at a Saudi air base?,0.0,neutral,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Saudi', 'NORP')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"एक चींटी की कीमत 21 हज़ार रुपये, इन चींटियों का क्या करते हैं तस्कर","The price of one ant is Rs 21 thousand, what do smugglers do with these ants?",0.0,neutral,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('21 thousand', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप बोले- मैं ईरान का तेल अपने कब्ज़े में लेना चाहता हूं, खार्ग द्वीप पर भी नियंत्रण संभव","Trump said - I want to take control of Iran's oil, control over Kharg Island is also possible",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Kharg Island', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पायलट कैसे बनते हैं, ट्रेनिंग में कितना ख़र्च आता है, सैलरी कितनी मिलती है?","How to become a pilot, how much does training cost, how much is the salary?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Eleições 2026: tarifa zero no transporte público pode ser 'Bolsa Família sobre rodas' para Lula?,2026 elections: could zero fares on public transport be 'Bolsa Família on wheels' for Lula?,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bolsa Família', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump diz que está considerando anexar ilha iraniana, mas um acordo poderia ser fechado 'rapidamente'","Trump says he is considering annexing Iranian island, but deal could be reached 'quickly'",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os mistérios de uma antiga civilização avançada ainda pouco conhecida,The mysteries of an ancient advanced civilization still little known,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Propaganda nas escolas russas é tema de filme ganhador de Oscar — mas ela funciona?,Propaganda in Russian schools is the subject of an Oscar-winning film — but does it work?,1.0,positive,"[('Propaganda', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Oscar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As fotos que mostram avião espião dos EUA destruído por drone iraniano,Photos showing US spy plane destroyed by Iranian drone,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Por que a pequena ilha de Kharg, alvo de Trump no Irã, é estratégica na guerra","Why the small island of Kharg, Trump's target in Iran, is strategic in the war",-1.0,negative,"[('Kharg', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que o estresse faz com a sua pele — e como lidar com isso,What stress does to your skin — and how to deal with it,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Uma formiga por mais de R$ 1 mil: a nova fronteira do tráfico de vida selvagem,"An ant for more than R$1,000: the new frontier of wildlife trafficking",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Trump tem agora pouquíssimas opções na guerra no Irã,Why Trump now has very few options in the war in Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Guerra no Irã pode redefinir a aviação internacional?,Could war in Iran redefine international aviation?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Международный редактор Би-би-си: Трамп ведет войну в Иране, руководствуясь инстинктом, но это не работает","BBC International Editor: Trump is fighting war in Iran on instinct, but it's not working",-1.0,negative,"[('BBC International', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Следующая остановка — Марс? Почему лунная миссия «Артемида» настолько важна для NASA,Next stop: Mars? Why the Artemis lunar mission is so important to NASA,0.0,neutral,"[('Mars', 'LOC'), ('Artemis', 'ORG'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Пакистан анонсировал переговоры между Ираном и США «в ближайшие дни». Что об этом известно?,Pakistan announced talks between Iran and the United States “in the coming days.” What is known about this?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('the coming days', 'DATE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский сообщил, что «партнеры» просили не бить по российской нефтяной индустрии; массированная атака на Таганрог","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: Zelensky said that “partners” asked not to hit the Russian oil industry; massive attack on Taganrog",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Премьер Израиля распорядился не мешать патриарху Иерусалима служить в храме Гроба Господня на Страстной неделе. В Вербное воскресенье его остановила полиция,The Prime Minister of Israel ordered not to interfere with the Patriarch of Jerusalem serving in the Church of the Holy Sepulcher during Holy Week. On Palm Sunday he was stopped by the police,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE'), ('the Church of the Holy Sepulcher', 'ORG'), ('Holy Week', 'DATE'), ('Palm Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Из музея в Италии украли картины Ренуара, Сезанна и Матисса","Paintings by Renoir, Cezanne and Matisse were stolen from a museum in Italy",0.0,neutral,"[('Renoir', 'ORG'), ('Cezanne', 'PERSON'), ('Matisse', 'ORG'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп не возражает против поставок российской нефти на Кубу,Trump does not object to Russian oil supplies to Cuba,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Американский «летающий радар», судя по снимкам, разрушен в результате иранской атаки на базу в Саудовской Аравии","The American “flying radar”, judging by the pictures, was destroyed as a result of an Iranian attack on a base in Saudi Arabia",-1.0,negative,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Украина», «Киев» и «Зеленский». Репортаж с митинга Орбана, который показывает, чего ожидать от выборов","“Ukraine”, “Kyiv” and “Zelensky”. Report from Orbán's rally that shows what to expect from the elections",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Orbán', 'ORG')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как угроза со стороны России сделала Германию ведущей военной силой Европы,How the Russian threat made Germany Europe's leading military power,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、「体制転換は起きた」と主張　米国とイランが近く協議とパキスタン外相,"Trump claims that ``regime change has occurred''; US and Iran to hold talks soon, Pakistan's foreign minister",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,米・イスラエルの攻勢激化、イランも攻撃続ける　沈静化の兆し見えず, 所要時間 2,43","Video, US and Israeli offensives intensify, Iran continues to attack, with no signs of calming down, Required time: 2,43",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('2,43', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、空爆でレバノンのジャーナリスト3人を殺害　「テロリスト」だと主張,"Israel kills 3 Lebanese journalists in airstrike, claims they were 'terrorists'",-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、カトリック教会幹部が聖地に入るのを阻止　ネタニヤフ首相は一転許可,Israel blocks Catholic church officials from entering holy sites; Prime Minister Netanyahu gives permission,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「王はいらない」、アメリカ各地で反トランプ政権デモ　イランとの戦争や移民政策を非難,``We don't need a king'' - anti-Trump demonstrations across the US denounce war with Iran and immigration policy,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,トランプ政権に抗議する「王はいらない」デモ、米各地の様子, 所要時間 1,12","Video, ""We don't need a king"" demonstrations protesting the Trump administration in various parts of the United States, Duration 1,12",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,パリのバンク・オブ・アメリカ前で爆破未遂、3人逮捕　イラン戦争に関係との見方も,Three arrested after attempted bombing in front of Bank of America in Paris; some believe it may be related to the Iran war,-1.0,negative,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bank of America', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('the Iran war', 'EVENT')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英中部ダービーで乗用車が歩行者らに突入、7人負傷　男性を逮捕,"Man arrested after car plows into pedestrians in England's central derby, injuring 7 people",0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イランでの戦争、「数週間以内」に終える見通しと米国務長官　イスラエルはイラン核施設などを攻撃,"War in Iran expected to end 'within weeks', US Secretary of State says Israel attacks Iranian nuclear facilities, etc.",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('weeks', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イラン代表のサッカー選手たち、戦争初日に爆撃で死亡の生徒たちを追悼,Iranian national soccer players pay tribute to students killed in bombing on first day of war,-1.0,negative,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('first day', 'DATE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump atishia 'kuharibu kabisa' viwanda vya nishati Iran ikiwa makubaliano hayatafikiwa 'haraka'","Directly, Trump threatens to 'completely destroy' Iran's energy industries if an agreement is not reached 'quickly'",-0.3333,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Vita vya Marekani, Israel na Iran vinaonyesha kuwa sheria za kimataifa za vita zimekiukwa","The war between the US, Israel and Iran shows that the international laws of war have been violated",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, kuna uwezekano gani kwa Marekani kuanzisha operesheni ya kijeshi ya ardhini Iran?",How likely is it for the US to launch a ground military operation in Iran?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Trump adokeza mpango wa kukiteka Kisiwa cha Kharg nchini Iran, huku bei ya mafuta ikipanda","Trump hints at a plan to seize Kharg Island in Iran, as oil prices rise",0.0,neutral,"[('Kharg Island', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Israel inatambua vipi maeneo ya kushambulia nchini Iran?",How does Israel identify attack sites in Iran?,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"""Trump agundua Israel ilimdanganya "" - The Independent","""Trump discovers Israel lied to him"" - The Independent",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hatima ya kilo 440 za urani iliyorutubishwa ya Iran ni ipi? – Uchambuzi,What is the fate of Iran's 440 kg of enriched uranium? – Analysis,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('440 kg', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Wasiwasi waikumbuka Bayern Munich huku ligi ya Saudia ikijaribu kumshawishi Hary Kane,European football rumors Monday: Concerns over Bayern Munich as the Saudi league tries to lure Hary Kane,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Bayern Munich', 'PERSON'), ('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('Hary Kane', 'PERSON')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Katibu mkuu wa CAF ajiuzulu baada ya mzozo kuhusu fainali ya Afcon,CAF secretary general to resign after dispute over Afcon final,0.0,neutral,"[('CAF', 'ORG'), ('Afcon', 'ORG')]"
2026_03_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Iran inatoza ushuru meli kupita Mlango- Bahari wa Hormuz?,Why does Iran tax ships passing through the Strait of Hormuz?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
