Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Honduras declara ganador de las elecciones al conservador Nasry ""Tito"" Asfura tras semanas de incertidumbre mientras su rival denuncia fraude","Honduras declares conservative Nasry ""Tito"" Asfura the winner of the elections after weeks of uncertainty while his rival denounces fraud",0.0,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('Nasry', 'ORG'), ('weeks', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo el arresto de una mujer en Londres cambió la vida de los niños de todo el mundo,How a woman's arrest in London changed the lives of children around the world,-0.05,"[('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es Nasry Asfura, el candidato respaldado por Trump y declarado como ganador de las elecciones en Honduras tras un polémico escrutinio que duró semanas","Who is Nasry Asfura, the candidate supported by Trump and declared the winner of the elections in Honduras after a controversial scrutiny that lasted weeks",0.55,"[('Nasry Asfura', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('weeks', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Salí de Venezuela buscando el American Dream y acabé encontrando el sueño español en Madrid""","""I left Venezuela looking for the American Dream and ended up finding the Spanish dream in Madrid""",0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the American Dream', 'ORG'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Madrid', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La historia detrás de ""Feliz Navidad"" de José Feliciano, la canción festiva más exitosa escrita por un artista latino","The story behind José Feliciano's ""Feliz Navidad,"" the most successful holiday song written by a Latin artist",0.2833333333333333,"[(""José Feliciano's"", 'PERSON'), ('Feliz Navidad', 'PERSON'), ('Latin', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वक़्त की धारा में हँसिए की धार, भारतीय कम्युनिस्ट पार्टी के 100 साल","The edge of the sickle in the stream of time, 100 years of the Communist Party of India",0.0,"[('100 years', 'DATE'), ('the Communist Party of India', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अरावली पहाड़ियों के मुद्दे पर जयराम रमेश ने मोदी सरकार पर खड़े किए सवाल","Live, Jairam Ramesh raised questions on Modi government on the issue of Aravalli hills.",0.13636363636363635,"[('Jairam Ramesh', 'PERSON'), ('Modi', 'GPE'), ('Aravalli', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,उन्नाव बलात्‍कार केस: कुलदीप सिंह सेंगर को ज़मानत आख़ि‍र किस आधार पर मिली?,Unnao rape case: On what basis did Kuldeep Singh Sengar get bail?,0.0,"[('Kuldeep Singh Sengar', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"न्यूज़ीलैंड में भारत के साथ ट्रेड डील पर विवाद, विदेश मंत्री ने जताई आपत्ति, सरकार ने विपक्ष से मांगी मदद","Controversy over trade deal with India in New Zealand, Foreign Minister expressed objection, government sought help from opposition",0.005681818181818177,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"क्रिसमस: 'सैंटा क्लॉस' कहां पर दफ़्न हैं, क्या आयरलैंड में है उनकी क़ब्र?","Christmas: Where is 'Santa Claus' buried, is his grave in Ireland?",0.0,"[(""Santa Claus'"", 'PERSON'), ('Ireland', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बांग्लादेश: तारिक़ रहमान की 17 साल बाद वापसी, बीएनपी ने क्या-क्या बताया","Bangladesh: Tariq Rahman's return after 17 years, what did BNP tell?",0.0,"[(""Tariq Rahman's"", 'PERSON'), ('17 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अमेरिका की उस रिपोर्ट पर चीन हुआ नाराज़ जिसमें भारत और पाकिस्तान का भी है ज़िक्र,China angry over America's report in which India and Pakistan are also mentioned,-0.5,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,विराट कोहली और रोहित शर्मा के शतकों के आगे वैभव सूर्यवंशी और साकिबुल ग़नी की चर्चा क्यों?,Why is Vaibhav Suryavanshi and Sakibul Ghani discussed ahead of the centuries of Virat Kohli and Rohit Sharma?,0.0,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Sakibul Ghani', 'PERSON'), ('the centuries', 'DATE'), ('Virat Kohli', 'ORG'), ('Rohit Sharma', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अरावली: उत्तर भारत की प्राचीन 'ग्रीन वॉल' पर क्यों छिड़ा है आधुनिक संग्राम,Aravalli: Why is there a modern war on the ancient 'Green Wall' of North India?,0.0,"[('Aravalli', 'PERSON'), ('North India', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As brigas e disputas que dividem republicanos no coração do trumpismo,The fights and disputes that divide Republicans at the heart of Trumpism,0.0,"[('Republicans', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Candidato de Trump é eleito em Honduras após semanas de incertezas e acusação de fraude,Trump candidate is elected in Honduras after weeks of uncertainty and accusations of fraud,0.0,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('weeks', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Umas 50 brasileiras' estiveram na mansão de Epstein, diz vítima do bilionário à BBC","'About 50 Brazilian women' were at Epstein's mansion, the billionaire's victim tells the BBC",-0.07500000000000001,"[('About 50', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O bilionário que decidiu testar os limites da China — e acabou preso,The billionaire who decided to test China's limits — and ended up in prison,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As melhores fotografias da natureza de 2025,The best nature photographs of 2025,1.0,"[('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,80% dos países já dessalinizam água do mar para uso — inclusive o Brasil,80% of countries already desalinate seawater for use — including Brazil,0.0,"[('80%', 'PERCENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que 'Um Filme Minecraft' foi a produção mais importante do cinema em 2025,Why 'A Minecraft Movie' was the most important cinema production in 2025,0.45,"[('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A música de Natal que Chico Buarque fez para imobiliária dar de presente a clientes e virou raridade,The Christmas song that Chico Buarque made for a real estate agent to give as a gift to clients and became a rarity,0.2,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('Chico Buarque', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Stranger Things: as teorias sobre o que pode acontecer no final da série,Stranger Things: theories about what could happen at the end of the series,0.0,[]
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Аленький цветочек» на крови. В Мариуполе открывают театр, где погибли сотни людей","""The Scarlet Flower"" on blood. A theater is being opened in Mariupol where hundreds of people died",0.0,"[('The Scarlet Flower', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Mariupol', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Мир встречает Рождество: первая рождественская служба папы Льва, Трамп проверил, что Санта действительно хороший","The world welcomes Christmas: Papa Leo's first Christmas service, Trump verifies that Santa is really good",0.475,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), (""Papa Leo's"", 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Santa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: пожар в Темрюкском порту после удара украинских дронов; Зеленский рассказал о разногласиях с США по Донбассу и ЗАЭС","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: fire in the Temryuk port after a strike by Ukrainian drones; Zelensky spoke about disagreements with the United States over Donbass and Zaporozhye Nuclear Power Plant",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Temryuk', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Donbass', 'PERSON'), ('Zaporozhye Nuclear Power Plant', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Почему лидер Армении грустит под Земфиру и Леди Гагу? Разбираемся в новом образе Пашиняна,Why is the leader of Armenia sad when listening to Zemfira and Lady Gaga? Let's understand Pashinyan's new image,-0.18181818181818182,"[('Armenia', 'ORG'), ('Zemfira', 'PERSON'), ('Lady Gaga', 'PERSON'), ('Pashinyan', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Еще миллион документов. Власти США нашли множество новых материалов, потенциально связанных с делом Эпштейна",A million more documents. US authorities have found a trove of new materials potentially related to the Epstein case.,0.21212121212121213,"[('A million', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Умерла основательница российского телеканала РЕН ТВ Ирена Лесневская,"The founder of the Russian television channel REN TV, Irena Lesnevskaya, has died",0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Irena Lesnevskaya', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Президентом Гондураса избран политик, которого поддержал Трамп. Перевес составил менее 1%, голоса считали недели","A politician supported by Trump was elected president of Honduras. The margin was less than 1%, the votes were counted for weeks",-0.16666666666666666,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('less than 1%', 'PERCENT'), ('weeks', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Новый взрыв на юге Москвы — недалеко от места, где два дня назад уже погиб генерал. Что известно","A new explosion in the south of Moscow, not far from the place where the general had already died two days ago. What is known",0.04545454545454545,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('two days ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Зеленский рассказал о 20 пунктах мирного плана. Что в нем нового?,Zelensky spoke about 20 points of the peace plan. What's new in it?,0.13636363636363635,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('about 20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Прокормить машину. Как и зачем российские издательства придумывают несуществующих авторов нон-фикшна,Feed the car. How and why Russian publishing houses invent non-existent non-fiction authors,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告の資料、さらに100万件超か　米当局が発見し精査中と,More than 1 million more documents belonging to former defendant Epstein have been discovered by US authorities and are under review.,0.3333333333333333,"[('More than 1 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、非武装地帯の設置の可能性示す　最新の和平案を説明,Zelenskiy explains the latest peace plan showing the possibility of establishing a demilitarized zone,0.5,[]
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ホンジュラス大統領選、トランプ氏が支持したアスフラ氏が勝利,"Asufura, supported by Trump, wins Honduras presidential election",0.3,"[('Asufura', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Honduras', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,サンタクロース、スピード違反で取り締まり受ける　米オハイオ州, 所要時間 1,14","Video, Santa Claus gets arrested for speeding in Ohio, US, Duration 1,14",0.0,"[('Santa Claus', 'PERSON'), ('Ohio', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,フランスの植民地支配は「犯罪」、謝罪と賠償求める法案を可決　アルジェリア,"Algeria passes a bill calling for an apology and compensation, calling French colonial rule a “crime”",0.0,"[('Algeria', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,キリスト誕生を「K-POP風」に祝う、ペンライトやフォトブースも　韓国, 所要時間 1,21","Video, celebrating the birth of Christ in a ""K-POP style"" with penlights and a photo booth, South Korea, time required 1,21",0.0,"[('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英バルモラル城の人物、エプスティーン元被告の共犯者に「不適切な友人」の紹介を要求　追加公開資料で表面化,"A person at Britain's Balmoral Castle requests former defendant Epstein's accomplice to introduce him to ""inappropriate friends,"" surfaced in additional public documents",0.0,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Balmoral Castle', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、エプスティーン元被告の自家用機に考えられていたより多く搭乗　 検察メールに記述,"Trump flew on Epstein's private plane more often than expected, prosecutors' email says",0.13333333333333333,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トゥーンベリ氏、ロンドンで逮捕　「パレスチナ・アクション」支持の抗議に参加し,Thunberg arrested in London after participating in protest in support of Palestine Action,0.1,"[('Thunberg', 'ORG'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Palestine Action', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wakristo Tanzania wahimizwa kudai haki wakiadhimisha Krismasi,Christians in Tanzania are encouraged to demand justice while celebrating Christmas,0.0,"[('Christians', 'NORP'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watano wafariki helikopta ikianguka mlima Kilimanjaro,Five died when the helicopter crashed on Mount Kilimanjaro,0.0,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mount Kilimanjaro', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Maafisa wabaini nyaraka zaidi ya milioni moja zinazohusishwa na kesi ya Epstein","Directly, officials identified more than one million documents related to the Epstein case",0.19999999999999998,"[('more than one million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Krisimasi ni nini na ni kwanini Wakristo wanaisherehekea?,What is Christmas and why do Christians celebrate it?,0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('Christians', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Ligi Kuu England: Je, timu inayoongoza wakati wa Krismasi ndio hushinda taji?",Premier League England: Does the top team at Christmas win the title?,0.65,"[('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya:  Rashford hataki kurudi Man United,Football rumors in Europe: Rashford does not want to return to Man United,0.0,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Man United', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mlipuko wa bomu waua watu msikitini Nigeria,A bomb blast kills people in a mosque in Nigeria,0.0,"[('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Venezuela yaishutumu Marekani kwa 'unyang'anyi mkubwa',Venezuela accuses the US of 'massive extortion',0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Meli 5 zenye uwezo mkubwa wa kijeshi duniani,5 ships with the largest military capacity in the world,-0.1,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kwanini uchumi wa Afrika unakua lakini umasikini haupungui? Je, 2026 itakuwa tofauti?",Why is the African economy growing but poverty is not decreasing? Will 2026 be different?,0.0,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
