Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué China apoya de manera limitada a su aliada Cuba en medio de las presiones de Estados Unidos,Why China supports its ally Cuba in a limited way amid pressure from the United States,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo Petro logró aumentar su popularidad al término de su mandato y qué papel tiene el presidente en las elecciones de Colombia,How Petro managed to increase his popularity at the end of his term and what role the president has in the Colombian elections,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué el divorcio en Japón separa a padres e hijos y cómo una reforma podría cambiarlo,Why divorce in Japan separates parents and children and how reform could change it,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Lo que nuestras creencias sobre los senos revelan acerca de la vida, el amor, el sexo y la sociedad""","""What our beliefs about breasts reveal about life, love, sex and society""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo es Bután, el remoto reino del Himalaya que ahora se abre al mundo","What Bhutan is like, the remote Himalayan kingdom that is now opening up to the world",0.0,neutral,"[('Bhutan', 'GPE'), ('Himalayan', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué las ideas de un gran estratega de las Guerras Napoleónicas siguen vigentes para entender el actual conflicto en Irán,Why the ideas of a great strategist from the Napoleonic Wars are still valid to understand the current conflict in Iran,-0.3333,negative,"[('the Napoleonic Wars', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué es la Tarea de selección de Wason, uno de los problemas de lógica más investigados y desconcertantes de la historia","What is the Wason Selection Task, one of the most researched and puzzling logic problems in history",0.0,neutral,"[('the Wason Selection Task', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Todos los que se han ido están aquí"": por qué 1980 es un año clave para entender la crisis migratoria que conecta a Centroamérica y EE.UU.","""All those who have left are here"": why 1980 is a key year to understand the migration crisis that connects Central America and the United States.",-1.0,negative,"[('1980', 'DATE'), ('a key year', 'DATE'), ('Central America', 'LOC'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Vendí a mi hija de 5 años para que recibiera tratamiento médico"": las familias que se enfrentan a decisiones imposibles en Afganistán",'I sold my 5-year-old daughter for medical treatment': Families facing impossible decisions in Afghanistan,0.0,neutral,"[('5-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo la familia Andic construyó el imperio de la moda Mango y qué poder tiene Jonathan, el heredero acusado de la muerte de su padre","How the Andic family built the Mango fashion empire and what power Jonathan, the heir accused of his father's death, has",-1.0,negative,"[('Andic', 'PERSON'), ('Mango', 'LOC'), ('Jonathan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी' पर मुख्य न्यायाधीश जस्टिस सूर्यकांत ने ये कहा,Chief Justice Justice Surya Kant said this on 'Cockroach Janata Party',0.0,neutral,"[('Surya Kant', 'PERSON'), (""Cockroach Janata Party'"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,यूक्रेन ने रूसी ड्रोन हमलों से निपटने के लिए निकाला ये हाई-टेक तरीक़ा,Ukraine came up with this high-tech method to deal with Russian drone attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,राहुल गांधी ने नीट पेपर लीक मामले के बाद अब सीबीएसई बोर्ड परीक्षा पर उठाए सवाल","Live, Rahul Gandhi now raises questions on CBSE board exam after NEET paper leak case",0.0,neutral,"[('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('CBSE', 'ORG'), ('NEET', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"त्विषा शर्मा केस: सुप्रीम कोर्ट ने की सुनवाई, गवाहों और अभियुक्तों को लेकर क्या कहा","Tvisha Sharma case: What did the Supreme Court say about the hearing, witnesses and accused?",0.0,neutral,"[('Tvisha Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,फाल्टा सीट पर बीजेपी की भारी जीत के टीएमसी के लिए क्या मायने हैं?,What does BJP's massive victory in Falta seat mean for TMC?,1.0,positive,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Falta', 'GPE'), ('TMC', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ईरान से समझौते पर किन बातों को लेकर बंटे राष्ट्रपति ट्रंप की पार्टी के सांसद,On what issues are MPs of President Trump's party divided on the agreement with Iran?,1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पेट्रोल, डीज़ल के दाम फिर बढ़े, जानिए अब कितने रुपए लीटर मिलेगा","Petrol and diesel prices increased again, know how much you will get per liter now",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी: वो सोशल मीडिया आंदोलन जिन्होंने दुनियाभर में सत्ता को चुनौती दी,Cockroach Janata Party: The social media movement that challenged power around the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"रुबियो के सामने जयशंकर बोले- हमारे लिए 'इंडिया फ़र्स्ट', कई स्रोतों से सस्ती ऊर्जा आपूर्ति करेंगे सुनिश्चित","Jaishankar said in front of Rubio - 'India first' for us, will ensure supply of cheap energy from many sources",0.0,neutral,"[('Jaishankar', 'PERSON'), (""Rubio - '"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दिमागी उम्र बढ़ने की रफ़्तार कम करने के तीन दिलचस्प तरीक़े,Three interesting ways to slow down brain aging,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A viagem de Flávio Bolsonaro aos EUA em busca de Trump: classe executiva, steak de carne, fotos e sorvete","Flávio Bolsonaro's trip to the USA in search of Trump: business class, steak, photos and ice cream",0.0,neutral,"[(""Flávio Bolsonaro's"", 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que a disputa inesperada entre PCC e CV em São Paulo revela sobre a facção paulista,What the unexpected dispute between PCC and CV in São Paulo reveals about the São Paulo faction,0.0,neutral,"[('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON'), ('São Paulo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O recado do papa Leão 14 sobre a inteligência artificial em seu primeiro 'cartão de visitas' ao completar um ano de pontificado,Pope Leo 14's message about artificial intelligence in his first 'business card' upon completing one year of his pontificate,0.0,neutral,"[(""Leo 14's"", 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('one year', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"EUA dizem que acordo com Irã pode ser fechado nesta segunda com proposta 'sólida', mas Teerã nega","US says deal with Iran could be closed this Monday with 'solid' proposal, but Tehran denies",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('this Monday', 'DATE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Dark Horse' virou 'comédia de erros' que ameaça candidatura de Flávio Bolsonaro, diz Financial Times","'Dark Horse' became a 'comedy of errors' that threatens Flávio Bolsonaro's candidacy, says Financial Times",-1.0,negative,"[(""Dark Horse'"", 'PERSON'), (""Flávio Bolsonaro's"", 'PERSON'), ('Financial Times', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O Reino Unido está se tornando ingovernável?,Is the UK becoming ungovernable?,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Diretor-executivo de um banco pede desculpas após descrever seus funcionários como 'capital humano de menor valor',Bank CEO apologizes after describing his employees as 'less valuable human capital',0.0,neutral,"[('Bank', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A piloto de combate com 'nervos de aço' que salvou a vida de 148 passageiros,The combat pilot with 'nerves of steel' who saved the lives of 148 passengers,0.0,neutral,"[('148', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,3 exemplos de como presidente da Venezuela está desmantelando modelo econômico chavista,3 examples of how the president of Venezuela is dismantling the Chavista economic model,0.0,neutral,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Chavista', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: число пострадавших при массированном ударе по Киеву увеличилось до 87","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: the number of victims of a massive attack on Kyiv increased to 87",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('87', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Цены на нефть упали: трейдеры надеются на заключение соглашения между США и Ираном,Oil prices fell: traders hope for an agreement between the US and Iran,1.0,positive,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Самолет министра обороны Британии терял сигнал GPS рядом с границей России,British Defense Secretary's plane lost GPS signal near Russian border,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Число случаев гонореи и сифилиса в Европе достигло рекордно высокого уровня,Gonorrhea and syphilis cases in Europe reach record highs,0.0,neutral,"[('Gonorrhea', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Какие объекты пострадали от российского удара по Киеву: правительственные здания, музеи и опера","What objects were damaged by the Russian strike on Kyiv: government buildings, museums and the opera",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Удар «Орешником» по Украине: ответ за налет на Москву или угроза Европе?,The Oreshnik attack on Ukraine: a response to the raid on Moscow or a threat to Europe?,-1.0,negative,"[('Oreshnik', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Подземные учения в Лондоне. На заброшенной платформе метро репетировали отражение нападения России на страны Балтии,Underground exercises in London. On an abandoned metro platform they rehearsed for repelling a Russian attack on the Baltic countries,-1.0,negative,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('metro', 'FAC'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Baltic', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Время на нашей стороне». Трамп приказал не торопиться на переговорах с Ираном — что известно о возможной сделке?,"""Time is on our side."" Trump ordered no rush in negotiations with Iran - what is known about a possible deal?",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Александр Усик победил «короля кикбоксинга» Рико Верховена,Alexander Usyk defeated the “king of kickboxing” Rico Verhoeven,0.0,neutral,"[('Alexander Usyk', 'PERSON'), ('Rico Verhoeven', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Пакистане при подрыве поезда, который перевозил военных, погибли по меньшей мере 20 человек",At least 20 people were killed when a train carrying military was blown up in Pakistan.,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、イランとの合意を「急がないよう」米交渉団に指示したと,Trump tells US negotiators not to rush into deal with Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシア、ウクライナを攻撃し多数死傷させる　極超音速ミサイル使用と表明,Russia announces use of hypersonic missile to attack Ukraine and cause multiple casualties,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,パキスタンで列車を狙った爆発、少なくとも20人死亡　分離派組織が犯行声明,At least 20 killed in train explosion in Pakistan; separatist group claims responsibility,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日本で4月から離婚後の共同親権スタート、子の利益と安全への懸念のバランスに揺れる,"In Japan, joint custody after divorce will start from April, but the balance is wavering between the interests of the child and concerns for safety.",0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('April', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英国防相を乗せた空軍機に信号妨害、ロシア国境近くを飛行中,Signal jamming of Air Force plane carrying British Defense Minister while flying near Russian border,0.0,neutral,"[('Signal', 'ORG'), ('Air Force', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英で少女2人をレイプした少年3人、拘禁刑にならず　英首相は「言語道断」と批判,"Three boys who raped two girls in the UK were not jailed, criticized by British Prime Minister as ``outrageous''",0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,中国炭鉱のガス爆発で80人超死亡、過去17年で最悪規模　現地からBBC特派員が報告, 所要時間 1,07","Video, More than 80 people killed in gas explosion at Chinese coal mine, worst in 17 years; BBC correspondent reports from the scene, Required time 1,07",-1.0,negative,"[('More than 80', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('17 years', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ホワイトハウス近くで発砲、容疑者をシークレットサービスが射殺,Secret Service shoots suspect in shooting near White House,0.0,neutral,"[('White House', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米深夜番組「ザ・レイト・ショー」が終了　最後のゲストはマッカートニー氏,"US late-night show ""The Late Show"" ends with McCartney as the final guest",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('late-night', 'TIME'), ('The Late Show', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('McCartney', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ポーランドに米兵追加配備すると発表　NATO会合の最中に,Trump announces deployment of additional US troops to Poland during NATO meeting,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani, Iran huenda zikafikia makubaliano leo - Rubio","Directly, the United States, Iran may reach an agreement today - Rubio",1.0,positive,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini China imenyamaza wakati mshirika wake Cuba anakabiliwa na shinikizo la Marekani?,Why is China silent when its ally Cuba is facing pressure from the United States?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ndege za kivita za Marekani zilizoshambuliwa na Iran wakati wa Vita,American warplanes attacked by Iran during the War,-1.0,negative,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the War', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Lissu afika Mahakama Kuu kusikiliza shauri la kesi ya mali za CHADEMA,Lissu arrives at the High Court to hear the case of CHADEMA assets,0.0,neutral,"[('Lissu', 'ORG'), ('the High Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi 10 za Afrika zenye madeni ya kutisha 2026,10 African countries with terrible debts 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Rekodi 11 na historia zilizoandikwa EPL msimu huu, Arsenal ikitwaa ubingwa","11 records and history written in EPL this season, Arsenal taking the championship",0.0,neutral,"[('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('EPL', 'ORG'), ('this season', 'DATE'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tunachojua kuhusu uwezekano wa kufikiwa kwa makubaliano kati ya Iran na Marekani,What we know about the possibility of an agreement between Iran and the United States,1.0,positive,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nadharia tatu kuhusu uwezekano wa kutokea mwisho wa dunia,Three theories about the possibility of the end of the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"'Nilinusurika mashambulizi ya makombora Hormuz, lakini rafiki yangu hajapatikana'","'I survived the missile attacks in Hormuz, but my friend has not been found'",-1.0,negative,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_25,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, kutakuwa na uvamizi wa Marekani?: Hatima ya Cuba ni nini baada ya mashtaka dhidi ya Raúl Castro",Will there be an American invasion?: What is the fate of Cuba after the impeachment against Raúl Castro?,0.0,neutral,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON')]"
