Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""No colecciono horrores sino pruebas del espíritu humano"": Svetlana Alexievich, la Nobel de Literatura que contó como nadie el drama de Chernóbil","""I do not collect horrors but evidence of the human spirit"": Svetlana Alexievich, the Nobel Prize winner in Literature who told the Chernobyl drama like no one else",0.0,"[('Svetlana Alexievich', 'PERSON'), ('the Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Literature', 'GPE'), ('Chernobyl', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Quiénes aparecen y qué dicen los archivos de Epstein publicados por el Departamento de Justicia de EE.UU.,Who appears and what they say in the Epstein files published by the US Department of Justice.,0.0,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('the US Department of Justice', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Estados Unidos captura un segundo tanquero frente a las costas de Venezuela,The United States captures a second tanker off the coast of Venezuela,0.0,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El extraordinario hallazgo que revela que los humanos generamos fuego cientos de miles de años antes de lo que se pensaba,The extraordinary discovery that reveals that humans generated fire hundreds of thousands of years earlier than previously thought,0.05555555555555555,"[('hundreds of thousands', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El misterio de por qué miles de cartas escritas por Jane Austen fueron destruidas por su propia hermana,The mystery of why thousands of letters written by Jane Austen were destroyed by her own sister,0.6,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jane Austen', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बांग्लादेश: उस्मान हादी की अंत्येष्टि, विदेशी दूतावासों के ये संदेश और 24 घंटे का अल्टिमेटम","Bangladesh: Osman Hadi's funeral, these messages from foreign embassies and 24-hour ultimatum",-0.125,"[(""Osman Hadi's"", 'PERSON'), ('24-hour', 'TIME')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चंगेज़ ख़ाँ दुनिया के बड़े हिस्से को जीतने के बावजूद भारत से क्यों लौट गया था?,Why did Genghis Khan return from India despite conquering a large part of the world?,0.21428571428571427,"[('Genghis Khan', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,बांग्लादेश: चटगांव स्थित भारतीय वीज़ा केंद्र अनिश्चितकाल के लिए बंद","Live, Bangladesh: Indian Visa Center in Chittagong closed indefinitely",-0.02121212121212122,"[('Indian Visa Center', 'ORG'), ('Chittagong', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,टी20 वर्ल्ड कप से शुभमन गिल को बाहर रखने के हैं कई संदेश,There are many messages to keep Shubman Gill out of T20 World Cup.,0.5,"[('Shubman Gill', 'PERSON'), ('T20 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अनुराग द्विवेदी: साइकिल से सुपरकार तक पहुंचने वाला यूट्यूबर ईडी की जांच के घेरे में कैसे आया,Anurag Dwivedi: How the YouTuber who reached supercar from bicycle came under the scanner of ED,0.0,"[('Anurag Dwivedi', 'PERSON'), ('YouTuber', 'ORG'), ('ED', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नितिन नबीन और यूपी में पंकज चौधरी को कमान देने के पीछे बीजेपी की रणनीति- द लेंस,BJP's strategy behind giving command to Nitin Nabin and Pankaj Chaudhary in UP - The Lens,-0.4,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Nitin Nabin', 'PERSON'), ('Pankaj Chaudhary', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बीबीसी एक्सक्लूसिव: नए पीएम आवास की लागत बताने से सरकार का इनकार,BBC Exclusive: Government refuses to reveal cost of new PM residence,0.13636363636363635,"[('BBC Exclusive: Government', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'शांति': भारत में परमाणु ऊर्जा से जुड़े प्रस्तावित क़ानून पर इतना 'शोर' क्यों?,'Peace': Why so much 'noise' over the proposed law related to nuclear energy in India?,0.1,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बुर्क़ा न पहनने पर पत्नी और बेटियों को मारकर घर में दफ़नाने का आरोप, पुलिस और पड़ोसियों ने क्या बताया","Accused of killing wife and daughters and burying them at home for not wearing burqa, what did police and neighbors tell",0.0,[]
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Segundo navio com petróleo da Venezuela é interceptado pelos EUA; o que se sabe,Second ship with Venezuelan oil is intercepted by the US; what is known,0.0,"[('Second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como o bloqueio petrolífero 'total e completo' de Trump pode afetar a economia da Venezuela - e se voltar contra os EUA,How Trump's 'total and complete' oil blockade could affect Venezuela's economy - and backfire on the US,0.05,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula: 'Intervenção armada na Venezuela seria catástrofe humanitária e precedente perigoso',Lula: 'Armed intervention in Venezuela would be a humanitarian catastrophe and a dangerous precedent',-0.6,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As fábricas secretas onde a Ucrânia constrói seus novos mísseis de longo alcance,The secret factories where Ukraine builds its new long-range missiles,-0.13181818181818183,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Os tentáculos do Comando Vermelho na política do Rio de Janeiro, segundo as investigações","The tentacles of Comando Vermelho in Rio de Janeiro politics, according to investigations",0.0,"[('Comando Vermelho', 'ORG'), ('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Bill Clinton, Mick Jagger e Michael Jackson: as personalidades que aparecem nos 'arquivos de Epstein'","Bill Clinton, Mick Jagger and Michael Jackson: the personalities that appear in the 'Epstein files'",0.0,"[('Bill Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Mick Jagger', 'PERSON'), ('Michael Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O país onde os jovens são a geração mais afetada pela solidão,The country where young people are the generation most affected by loneliness,0.3,[]
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Homens armados mascarados e molho envenenado – como minha esposa planejou me matar,Masked Gunmen and Poisoned Sauce – How My Wife Planned to Kill Me,0.0,[]
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,EUA atacam Estado Islâmico na Síria; o que se sabe,US attacks Islamic State in Syria; what is known,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Islamic State', 'ORG'), ('Syria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Дружба против Москвы. Решил ли визит Зеленского в Варшаву проблемы в отношениях Украины и Польши?,Friendship against Moscow. Did Zelensky's visit to Warsaw solve the problems in relations between Ukraine and Poland?,0.0,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Warsaw', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Светлана Алексиевич о «комплексе Навального», новой книге и женском взгляде на войну, Продолжительность 36,20","Video, Svetlana Alexievich about the “Navalny complex”, a new book and a woman’s view of the war, Duration 36.20",-0.08181818181818182,"[('Svetlana Alexievich', 'PERSON'), ('36.20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Разногласия в мире Трампа — как они возникли в самом сердце движения МАГА?,Disagreement in Trump's World—How did it emerge from the heart of the MAGA movement?,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,США захватили еще один нефтяной танкер у берегов Венесуэлы,US seizes another oil tanker off the coast of Venezuela,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский заявил, что считает справедливой остановку войны «там, где стоим»; в СБУ утверждают, что поразили два Су-27 в Крыму","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: Zelensky said that he considers it fair to stop the war “where we stand”; The SBU claims that they hit two Su-27s in Crimea",0.7,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('SBU', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Crimea', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«США должны использовать свое огромное психологическое влияние на Россию». Что может заставить Путина прекратить войну в Украине?,“The US must use its enormous psychological influence on Russia.” What could force Putin to end the war in Ukraine?,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Blue Origin впервые отправила в космос человека в инвалидной коляске,Blue Origin sent a wheelchair user into space for the first time,0.125,"[('Blue Origin', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Билл Клинтон, Майкл Джексон и Мик Джаггер. Кого можно найти в новых документах из дела Джеффри Эпштейна","Bill Clinton, Michael Jackson and Mick Jagger. Who can be found in the new documents from the Jeffrey Epstein case",0.13636363636363635,"[('Bill Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Michael Jackson', 'PERSON'), ('Mick Jagger', 'PERSON'), ('Jeffrey Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Туристам придется платить сбор в €2, чтобы подойти к римскому фонтану Треви",Tourists will have to pay a fee of €2 to go to Rome's Trevi Fountain,0.0,"[('2', 'MONEY'), ('Rome', 'GPE'), ('Trevi Fountain', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Могут ли во Вселенной закончиться звезды? Старых хватит надолго, но новые рождаются все реже, говорят ученые","Could the universe run out of stars? The old ones will last a long time, but new ones are born less and less often, scientists say",-0.024494949494949497,[]
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン大統領、「西側がロシアを尊重」すれば戦争はないと　テレビ出演でBBCに回答,President Putin tells the BBC in a TV appearance that there will be no war if the West respects Russia,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('West', 'LOC'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,プーチン氏、西側首脳がロシアをだましたと　BBCロシア編集長の質問に答え, 所要時間 1,59","Video, Putin answers BBC Russia editor's question about Western leaders deceiving Russia, Duration 1,59",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('BBC Russia', 'ORG'), ('Western', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米司法省、エプスティーン元被告の捜査資料など公開　多くが黒塗りで民主党は批判,"US Department of Justice releases investigation materials on former defendant Epstein, much of it blacked out, criticized by Democrats",0.1,"[('US Department of Justice', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Democrats', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,台北の地下鉄駅で刃物襲撃、3人死亡　容疑者はビルから転落死,Three people killed in knife attack at Taipei subway station; suspect falls from building,-0.2,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Taipei', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,バングラデシュで新聞社に放火　青年活動家の死に対する抗議が激化,Newspaper office set on fire in Bangladesh; protests intensify over death of young activist,0.1,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU、ウクライナへ900億ユーロ融資で合意　凍結ロシア資産は使わず,EU agrees to loan 90 billion euros to Ukraine without using frozen Russian assets,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('90 billion', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,TikTokのアメリカ事業売却、オーナーが契約締結,Owner signs deal to sell TikTok's U.S. business,0.0,"[('TikTok', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日銀が利上げ決定、1995年以降で最高水準に　インフレ圧力の中,Bank of Japan decides to raise interest rates to highest level since 1995 amid inflationary pressures,0.0,"[('Bank of Japan', 'ORG'), ('1995', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ブラウン大学銃撃、容疑者を遺体で発見　MIT教授殺害にも関係か,Brown University shooting suspect found dead; may be related to MIT professor's murder,-0.1,"[('Brown University', 'ORG'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yakamata meli ya pili ya mafuta pwani ya Venezuela","Directly, the United States should send a second oil tanker off the coast of Venezuela",0.05,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"AFCON 2025: Pazia likifunguliwa leo, AFCON sasa ni kila baada ya miaka minne kuanzia 2028","AFCON 2025: Curtain opens today, AFCON now every four years from 2028",0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('AFCON', 'ORG'), ('every four years', 'DATE'), ('2028', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Bayern kutoa £43m kumsajili Bruno wa United,European football rumours: Bayern to offer £43m to sign United's Bruno,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('43', 'MONEY'), ('United', 'ORG'), ('Bruno', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nyaraka za siri za Jeffrey Epstein zatolewa hadharani: Nini kipya?,Jeffrey Epstein's secret files made public: What's new?,-0.08787878787878789,"[(""Jeffrey Epstein's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi wafusi wa Trump wa MAGA walivyogawanyika - na inamaanisha nini?,How Trump's MAGA supporters split — and what does it mean?,-0.3125,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nyota watano wakubwa Afrika ambao hawakuwahi kushinda AFCON,Five big stars in Africa who never won AFCON,0.0,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('AFCON', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mlipuko wa mafua ya ndege na namna unavyoweza kutokea miongoni mwa wanadamu,An outbreak of bird flu and how it can occur among humans,0.0,[]
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi mshahara wa Mkenya 'utakavyopigwa panga' ifikapo Februari 2026,How a Kenyan's salary will be 'sworded' by February 2026,0.0,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('February 2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Unyanyapaa wa wanajeshi wa Ukraine 'walikufa kwa njia mbaya',Stigma of Ukrainian soldiers 'died the wrong way',-0.5,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi ya kujilinda dhidi ya walaghai  mitandaoni msimu wa Krismasi,How to protect yourself from online fraudsters this Christmas season,0.0,"[('this Christmas season', 'DATE')]"
