Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La escasez de combustible en Rusia está causando estragos, pero ¿presionará a Putin para cambiar de estrategia en la guerra de Ucrania?","Russia's fuel shortage is wreaking havoc, but will it pressure Putin to change strategy in the Ukraine war?",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Trump da por terminada la tregua con Irán mientras Teherán advierte de una respuesta ""valiente"" a los ataques de EE.UU.",Trump ends truce with Iran as Tehran warns of 'brave' response to US attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cuántos miles de millones de dólares costará la reconstrucción en Venezuela tras los terremotos y con qué recursos cuenta el país para afrontarla,How many billions of dollars will reconstruction in Venezuela after the earthquakes cost and what resources does the country have to face it?,0.0,neutral,"[('billions of dollars', 'MONEY'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere a los 75 años Bonnie Tyler, la voz que cautivó al mundo con el éxito ""Total Eclipse of the Heart"" en la década de los 80","Bonnie Tyler, the voice that captivated the world with the hit ""Total Eclipse of the Heart"" in the 1980s, dies at 75",0.0,neutral,"[('Bonnie Tyler', 'PERSON'), ('Total Eclipse of the Heart', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the 1980s', 'DATE'), ('75', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Mundial 2026: quién inventó las tarjetas roja y amarilla del fútbol (y cómo se le ocurrió la idea),World Cup 2026: who invented the red and yellow cards in football (and how the idea came about),0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Creo que esta será la última vez que nos veamos"": quién es el doctor Hussam Abu Safiya detenido por Israel en Gaza y por qué se teme por su vida","""I think this will be the last time we see each other"": who is Dr. Hussam Abu Safiya detained by Israel in Gaza and why there are fears for his life",0.0,neutral,"[('Hussam Abu Safiya', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Arrancan los cuartos de final del Mundial: cómo llegan y qué posibilidades tienen Argentina, España y los otros 6 equipos que juegan","The quarterfinals of the World Cup begin: how they arrive and what possibilities do Argentina, Spain and the other 6 teams playing have?",0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El médico alemán condenado a cadena perpetua por el asesinato de 15 pacientes y sospechoso de más casos,German doctor sentenced to life in prison for murder of 15 patients and suspected of more cases,0.0,neutral,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Es una causa perdida, un socio terrible en la OTAN"": Trump carga contra España y amenaza con una ruptura comercial","""It is a lost cause, a terrible partner in NATO"": Trump charges against Spain and threatens a trade breakup",0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Los adolescentes que ensayaban su baile de fin de curso cuando ocurrieron los terremotos de Venezuela y a los que sus padres aún buscan entre los escombros casi ""sin ayuda""","The teenagers who were rehearsing their prom when the earthquakes in Venezuela occurred and for whom their parents are still searching through the rubble almost ""without help""",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पहले विश्व युद्ध के हज़ारों भूले-बिसरे पंजाबी सैनिकों को पहली बार मिल रही है पहचान,Thousands of forgotten Punjabi soldiers of the First World War are getting recognition for the first time.,-1.0,negative,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('the First World War', 'EVENT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,अमेरिकी हमलों को लेकर ईरान ने संयुक्त राष्ट्र को लिखी चिट्ठी","Live, Iran wrote a letter to the United Nations regarding American attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United Nations', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"क्या ओटीटी कंटेंट पर सेंसर बोर्ड की निगरानी होती है, फ़िल्म 'सतलुज' पर हुए विवाद से समझिए",Is OTT content monitored by the Censor Board? Understand from the controversy over the film 'Sutlej'.,0.0,neutral,"[('the Censor Board', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पंजाब के गांवों में बड़ी स्क्रीनों पर दिखाई जा रही फ़िल्म 'सतलुज', लोग क्या कह रहे हैं","The film 'Sutlej' is being shown on big screens in the villages of Punjab, what are people saying?",0.0,neutral,"[('Punjab', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका ने ईरान पर बरसाए बम, जवाब में ईरान का क़तर, कुवैत और बहरीन के अमेरिकी ठिकानों पर हमला","America rained bombs on Iran, in response Iran attacked American bases in Qatar, Kuwait and Bahrain",-1.0,negative,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Bahrain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"दलित युवक से शादी करने वाली महिला का घरवालों ने अपहरण किया, पुलिस ने ढाई घंटे में ऐसे बचाया","A woman who married a Dalit youth was kidnapped by her family, the police saved her in two and a half hours.",0.0,neutral,"[('Dalit', 'PERSON'), ('two and a half hours', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ट्रंप की तुर्की से नज़दीकी बढ़ने पर इसराइल क्यों हो रहा है परेशान?,Why is Israel worried as Trump grows closer to Türkiye?,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Türkiye', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"नाक के रास्ते दिमाग़ में घुसने वाला वो अमीबा जो है जानलेवा, कैसे होता है बचाव","The amoeba that enters the brain through the nose is fatal, how is it protected?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,आक्रामक बयानों के बावजूद ट्रंप के पास ईरान से बातचीत के अलावा कोई बेहतर विकल्प नहीं,"Despite aggressive statements, Trump has no better option than talks with Iran.",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,प्रशांत किशोर अगर बांकीपुर से हारे तो क्या होगा और जीते तो क्या असर पड़ेगा?,What will happen if Prashant Kishor loses from Bankipur and what will be the impact if he wins?,1.0,positive,"[('Bankipur', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem são os indígenas que buscam regulamentar a mineração de ouro e diamante em suas terras,Who are the indigenous people seeking to regulate gold and diamond mining on their lands?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Bonnie Tyler, cantora de 'Total Eclipse of the Heart', morre aos 75 anos",'Total Eclipse of the Heart' Singer Bonnie Tyler Dies at 75,0.0,neutral,"[('Heart', 'ORG'), ('Bonnie Tyler Dies', 'PERSON'), ('75', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Análise: Trump não tem opção melhor do que negociar com o Irã,Analysis: Trump has no better option than negotiating with Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Governo Trump reage à decisão do Brasil que permite retorno de suposto espião à Rússia,Trump administration reacts to Brazil's decision allowing alleged spy to return to Russia,1.0,positive,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A Argentina está sendo favorecida na Copa do Mundo 2026?,Is Argentina being favored in the 2026 World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Da euforia ao 'nunca mais vai ser campeão': o que a eliminação do Brasil da Copa pode nos ensinar sobre frustrações,From euphoria to 'you'll never be champion again': what Brazil's elimination from the World Cup can teach us about frustrations,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O funcionário público chinês condenado à morte por aceitar US$ 325 milhões em propina,Chinese civil servant sentenced to death for accepting $325 million in bribes,-1.0,negative,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('$325 million', 'MONEY')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Pode ou não pode missa em latim? A discussão após Vaticano excomungar grupo ultraconservador,Can or cannot mass in Latin? The discussion after the Vatican excommunicated ultraconservative group,0.0,neutral,"[('Latin', 'LANGUAGE'), ('Vatican', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump diz que cessar-fogo 'acabou' e EUA lançam novos ataques contra o Irã,Trump says ceasefire is 'over' and US launches new attacks on Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,9 de julho para além da Revolução Constitucionalista: data marca o confronto indígena que deu origem à cidade de São Paulo,July 9th beyond the Constitutionalist Revolution: date marks the indigenous confrontation that gave rise to the city of São Paulo,0.0,neutral,"[('July 9th', 'DATE'), ('the Constitutionalist Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('São Paulo', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,ВСУ заявили о поражении более 25 российских судов в Азовском море. Что известно,The Ukrainian Armed Forces announced the defeat of more than 25 Russian ships in the Sea of ​​Azov. What is known,0.0,neutral,"[('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('more than 25', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Sea of ​​Azov', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«ОКР отказался от части территорий страны». Почему z-блогеры не рады возвращению России в МОК,“The ROC abandoned part of the country’s territories.” Why z-bloggers are not happy about Russia's return to the IOC,0.0,neutral,"[('ROC', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('IOC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Певица Бонни Тайлер, знаменитая хитом Total Eclipse of the Heart, умерла в возрасте 75 лет после тяжелой болезни","Singer Bonnie Tyler, famous for the hit Total Eclipse of the Heart, has died at the age of 75 after a serious illness.",0.0,neutral,"[('Bonnie Tyler', 'PERSON'), ('Total Eclipse of the Heart', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the age of 75', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Кремле не согласились с позицией США, что удары Киева вглубь России могут способствовать завершению конфликта","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: the Kremlin did not agree with the US position that Kyiv’s strikes deep into Russia could help end the conflict",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Они не заслуживают сделки». США заявили о 170 ударах по Ирану за двое суток, Тегеран — об атаках на американские базы","""They don't deserve a deal."" The United States announced 170 strikes on Iran in two days, Tehran announced attacks on American bases",-1.0,negative,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('170', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('two days', 'DATE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Скандальный политик-демократ Грэм Платнер выбывает из гонки за место в Сенате после обвинений в сексуализированном насилии,Controversial Democratic politician Graham Platner drops out of Senate race after sexual assault allegations,0.0,neutral,"[('Controversial Democratic', 'ORG'), ('Graham Platner', 'PERSON'), ('Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Европа побила рекорд жары в июне. Почему раскачиваются погодные качели?,Europe broke its heat record in June. Why do the weather swings swing?,1.0,positive,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('June', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Саммит смешанных чувств. Чем закончилась встреча лидеров НАТО в Анкаре,Summit of mixed feelings. How did the meeting of NATO leaders in Ankara end?,0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Ankara', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Джереми Боуэн: несмотря на всю браваду Трампа, у него нет лучшего выхода, чем переговоры с Ираном","Jeremy Bowen: Despite all Trump's bravado, he has no better option than negotiations with Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('Jeremy Bowen', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Защитят ли вооруженные группы небо России? | Военное время, Продолжительность 10,00","Video, Will armed groups protect the skies of Russia? | Wartime, Duration 10.00",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('10.00', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米中央軍、イランを追加攻撃　「強力にたたいた」とトランプ氏,US Central Command launches additional attack on Iran; Trump says it was a ``strong strike'',-1.0,negative,"[('US Central Command', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、ウクライナに「パトリオット」ミサイルのライセンス生産容認,Trump allows Ukraine to license production of Patriot missiles,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Patriot', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、NATO首脳会議でスペインを「相手にするだけ無駄」と批判　グリーンランド領有めぐる主張も再燃,"Trump criticizes Spain at NATO summit, calling it ``a waste of time to deal with it'' Claims over Greenland are reignited",0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Greenland', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,患者15人を殺害した医師に終身刑、余罪あるとみて当局は捜査継続　ドイツ,"Doctor who murdered 15 patients sentenced to life in prison, authorities continue investigation as he may have additional charges in Germany",0.0,neutral,"[('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,中国のタピオカティー・チェーン、ルイ・ヴィトンの商標権侵害で2.4億円賠償命令　ネットで議論に,"Chinese bubble tea chain ordered to pay 240 million yen for infringement of Louis Vuitton's trademark rights, sparking debate online",0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('240 million yen', 'MONEY'), (""Louis Vuitton's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏の文句は「家族の口論」のようなもの　NATO事務総長がBBCに説明,"Trump's complaints are like 'family arguments', NATO Secretary General explains to BBC",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,溺死と宣告された幼児、病院の安置室で生きているのが発見される　米アリゾナ,"Infant declared drowned found alive in hospital morgue in Arizona, US",0.0,neutral,"[('Arizona', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,NATO首脳会議での結束に「暗雲」　トランプ氏の発言で, 所要時間 0,54","Video, Mr. Trump's remarks cast a ""dark cloud"" on unity at NATO summit, Duration 0,54",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Duration 0,54', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,NATOは本当に「団結」しているのか、ルッテ事務総長にBBC記者が聞く, 所要時間 1,21","Video, BBC reporter asks Secretary General Rutte if NATO is really ""united"", Duration 1,21",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Rutte', 'PERSON'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,右翼ル・ペン氏、仏大統領選への立候補を表明　有罪判決について上告の意向,"Right-wing Le Pen announces candidacy for French presidential election, intends to appeal conviction",1.0,positive,"[('Le Pen', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Rais Samia awaonya wanaharakati dhidi ya kuchochea vurugu","Directly, President Samia warns activists against inciting violence",-1.0,negative,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,CCM na ACT Wazalendo kuanza mazungumzo ya Serikali ya Umoja wa Kitaifa Zanzibar,CCM and ACT Wazalendo to start talks on the Government of National Unity in Zanzibar,0.0,neutral,"[('CCM', 'ORG'), ('Wazalendo', 'GPE'), ('the Government of National Unity in', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Kwa nini timu za Ulaya zinatawala?,World Cup 2026: Why are European teams dominating?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, sheria za Kiislamu zilifuatwa wakati wa mazishi ya Ali Khamenei?",Were Islamic laws followed during Ali Khamenei's funeral?,0.0,neutral,"[('Islamic', 'NORP'), (""Ali Khamenei's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Rais wa Nigeria ataka kujua jinsi taasisi feki ilivyoanzishwa ndani ya ofisi yake,The President of Nigeria will want to know how a fake institution was established within his office,0.0,neutral,"[('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vyuo 10 bora Afrika Mashariki 2026,Top 10 universities in East Africa 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('East Africa', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Uturuki ilikuwaje mshirika mkuu katika muungano wa NATO?,How did Turkey become a major partner in the NATO alliance?,0.0,neutral,"[('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya Alhamisi: Guimaraes, anayelengwa na Arsenal, aomba kuondoka Newcastle.","European football rumors Thursday: Guimaraes, target of Arsenal, asks to leave Newcastle.",0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Guimaraes', 'PERSON'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Newcastle', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Trump atishia Iran usitishaji mapigano ""umefutiliwa mbali""; Iran yaonya kuwa ""watajibu bila uwoga""","Trump threatens Iran ceasefire ""has been scrapped""; Iran warns they will ""retaliate without fear""",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nyuma ya pazia ya urembo unaokuwa wa kukuza makalio,Behind the scenes of hip-hugging beauty,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Who is Zeynep Sonmez, the Wimbledon with the ‘Palestine’ watermelon racket?","Who is Zeynep Sonmez, the Wimbledon with the ‘Palestine’ watermelon racket?",0.0,neutral,"[('Zeynep Sonmez', 'PERSON'), ('Wimbledon', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup: France face Morocco as quarterfinal showdown takes centre stage,World Cup: France face Morocco as quarterfinal showdown takes centre stage,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Australia, India strike deal on uranium exports during PM Modi’s visit","Australia, India strike deal on uranium exports during PM Modi’s visit",0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"US, Iran launch more attacks as mediators urge warring sides to uphold MoU","US, Iran launch more attacks as mediators urge warring sides to uphold MoU",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('MoU', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Hottest June on record in Western Europe as heatwaves hit continent,Hottest June on record in Western Europe as heatwaves hit continent,0.0,neutral,"[('Western Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Inside a UK university’s ‘disturbing’ crackdown on pro-Palestine students,Inside a UK university’s ‘disturbing’ crackdown on pro-Palestine students,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('pro-Palestine', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"‘Shoot me, Just let my son pass’: Final moments of Palestinian Ahmad Zaid","‘Shoot me, Just let my son pass’: Final moments of Palestinian Ahmad Zaid",0.0,neutral,"[('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Ahmad Zaid', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,In maps and charts: South Sudan’s 15 years of independence,In maps and charts: South Sudan’s 15 years of independence,0.0,neutral,"[('South Sudan’s', 'LOC'), ('15 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"‘If it’s fair, we’ll win’: Confident but wary Morocco fans paint Boston red","‘If it’s fair, we’ll win’: Confident but wary Morocco fans paint Boston red",0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('Boston', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"‘If it’s fair, we’ll win’: Confident but wary Morocco fans paint Boston red","‘If it’s fair, we’ll win’: Confident but wary Morocco fans paint Boston red",0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('Boston', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Income Tax Department opposes same-sex couple’s plea for tax exemption on gifts,Income Tax Department opposes same-sex couple’s plea for tax exemption on gifts,0.0,neutral,"[('Income Tax Department', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"India, Australia unveil new defence declaration to deepen Indo-Pacific cooperation | LIVE","India, Australia unveil new defence declaration to deepen Indo-Pacific cooperation | LIVE",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Indo-Pacific', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia war LIVE: Iran to bury Khamenei in culmination of mass funeral,West Asia war LIVE: Iran to bury Khamenei in culmination of mass funeral,-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,State Election Commissioners face controversy in Kerala and Tamil Nadu,State Election Commissioners face controversy in Kerala and Tamil Nadu,0.0,neutral,"[('State Election Commissioners', 'ORG'), ('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why is BrahMos emerging as India’s most sought-after defence export? | Explained,Why is BrahMos emerging as India’s most sought-after defence export? | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('BrahMos', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Madras High Court stays Look Out Circular issued against former DMK Minister E.V. Velu,Madras High Court stays Look Out Circular issued against former DMK Minister E.V. Velu,0.0,neutral,"[('Madras High Court', 'ORG'), ('Look Out Circular', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('DMK', 'ORG'), ('E.V. Velu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Nigel Farage: A persistent force in British politics,Nigel Farage: A persistent force in British politics,0.0,neutral,"[('Nigel Farage', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Calcutta HC appoints special officer for debit-frozen TMC bank accounts, to manage Mamata-led group's expenses","Calcutta HC appoints special officer for debit-frozen TMC bank accounts, to manage Mamata-led group's expenses",0.0,neutral,"[('Mamata', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Bonnie Tyler, who topped the charts with epic 'Total Eclipse of the Heart', has died at 75","Bonnie Tyler, who topped the charts with epic 'Total Eclipse of the Heart', has died at 75",0.0,neutral,"[('Bonnie Tyler', 'PERSON'), (""Total Eclipse of the Heart'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('75', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Checkbox caste: On the counting of caste, Census 2027","Checkbox caste: On the counting of caste, Census 2027",0.0,neutral,"[('Checkbox', 'ORG'), ('2027', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US and Iran trade strikes for second night in a row after Trump declares ceasefire 'over',US and Iran trade strikes for second night in a row after Trump declares ceasefire 'over',0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('second night', 'TIME'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Democrat Graham Platner suspends campaign for key US Senate race after assault allegation,Democrat Graham Platner suspends campaign for key US Senate race after assault allegation,0.0,neutral,"[('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Graham Platner', 'PERSON'), ('US Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Platner's disastrous candidacy exposes rifts that could dampen Democrats' Senate hopes,Platner's disastrous candidacy exposes rifts that could dampen Democrats' Senate hopes,0.0,neutral,"[('Platner', 'PERSON'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,It was 'love at first sight' with their adopted baby. Then they were told he may have been trafficked,It was 'love at first sight' with their adopted baby. Then they were told he may have been trafficked,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Watch: We're a step closer to finding out if bees have feelings, here's why","Watch: We're a step closer to finding out if bees have feelings, here's why",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,International court tells BBC of breakthrough in Sudan war crimes probe,International court tells BBC of breakthrough in Sudan war crimes probe,-1.0,negative,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Ukraine to get licence to produce Patriot missiles, Trump says","Ukraine to get licence to produce Patriot missiles, Trump says",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Patriot', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Starmer gifted gun and ammunition by Turkish president at Nato,Starmer gifted gun and ammunition by Turkish president at Nato,0.0,neutral,"[('Starmer', 'ORG'), ('Turkish', 'NORP'), ('Nato', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Wealthy AI workers send San Francisco house prices soaring,Wealthy AI workers send San Francisco house prices soaring,0.0,neutral,"[('San Francisco', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Arizona toddler found alive in hospital morgue after declared dead from drowning,Arizona toddler found alive in hospital morgue after declared dead from drowning,0.0,neutral,"[('Arizona', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"U.S. Launches New Strikes on Iran, Military Says","U.S. Launches New Strikes on Iran, Military Says",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Launches New Strikes', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Trump Praises NATO’s ‘Unity’ After Lashing Out at Allies,Trump Praises NATO’s ‘Unity’ After Lashing Out at Allies,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump Praises NATO’s ‘Unity’ After Lashing Out', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"At Iran’s Funeral for Ayatollah Khamenei, Mourners Bid an Emotional Farewell","At Iran’s Funeral for Ayatollah Khamenei, Mourners Bid an Emotional Farewell",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ayatollah Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Mourners Bid', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Le Pen Launches Presidential Campaign, in a Twist for French Politics","Le Pen Launches Presidential Campaign, in a Twist for French Politics",0.0,neutral,"[('Le Pen Launches Presidential Campaign', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Internal File Finds I.C.C. Prosecutor Engaged in Sexual Harassment,Internal File Finds I.C.C. Prosecutor Engaged in Sexual Harassment,0.0,neutral,"[('Internal File Finds I.C.C. Prosecutor Engaged', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Trump’s Arrival in Turkey for NATO Summit Adds Drama and Spectacle,Trump’s Arrival in Turkey for NATO Summit Adds Drama and Spectacle,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump’s Arrival', 'PERSON'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('NATO Summit', 'ORG'), ('Drama', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As More Remains Are Found in Rubble From Venezuela Earthquakes, Horror Becomes Routine","As More Remains Are Found in Rubble From Venezuela Earthquakes, Horror Becomes Routine",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Heartbreak and Anger in Egypt Over a Stinging World Cup Loss to Argentina,Heartbreak and Anger in Egypt Over a Stinging World Cup Loss to Argentina,0.0,neutral,"[('Anger', 'ORG'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Alluring Albanian Island Inspiring Ivanka’s Fantasy,The Alluring Albanian Island Inspiring Ivanka’s Fantasy,0.0,neutral,"[('The Alluring Albanian Island Inspiring Ivanka’s Fantasy', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Marine Le Pen’s Return Has Sidelined Her Protégé. Can They Join Forces?,Marine Le Pen’s Return Has Sidelined Her Protégé. Can They Join Forces?,0.0,neutral,"[('Marine Le Pen’s Return Has', 'PERSON')]"
