Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué los comunistas de India perdieron por completo el poder tras casi 70 años gobernando a millones de personas,Why India's communists completely lost power after almost 70 years ruling millions of people,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('communists', 'NORP'), ('almost 70 years', 'DATE'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Son los chequeos médicos de los presidentes de EE.UU. un mero ejercicio de relaciones públicas?,Are the medical checkups of US presidents a mere public relations exercise?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Quiénes son los principales candidatos para presidir Colombia y suceder a Petro,Who are the main candidates to preside over Colombia and succeed Petro?,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Petro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Creía que mi familia se había resistido a Hitler, hasta que descubrí que mi bisabuelo era nazi""","""I thought my family had resisted Hitler, until I discovered that my great-grandfather was a Nazi""",1.0,positive,"[('Hitler', 'PERSON'), ('Nazi', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Donald y Doris Fisher, la pareja que no pudo encontrar un talle de jeans y terminó creando el gigante de la moda Gap","Donald and Doris Fisher, the couple who couldn't find a size for jeans and ended up creating the fashion giant Gap",0.0,neutral,"[('Donald', 'PERSON'), ('Doris Fisher', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Lo que el precio de una sola taza de café dice sobre la agitación económica actual,What the price of a single cup of coffee says about the current economic turmoil,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Es como si la muerte viniera a buscarnos cada mes"": la pesadilla de vivir con el trastorno disfórico premenstrual","""It's like death comes looking for us every month"": the nightmare of living with premenstrual dysphoric disorder",-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere Edgar Morin, el filósofo francés que aportó ""una nota de esperanza frente a un mundo que se deteriora""","Edgar Morin, the French philosopher who provided ""a note of hope in the face of a deteriorating world,"" dies",0.0,neutral,"[('Edgar Morin', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Un golpe de suerte: cómo un desconocido farmacéutico británico inventó por casualidad los fósforos de madera hace 200 años,A stroke of luck: how an unknown British pharmacist accidentally invented wooden matches 200 years ago,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('200 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Mi hermano ahora es una persona completamente distinta"": la metamorfosis del mexicano Temach para convertirse en la mayor estrella de la machosfera en América Latina","""My brother is now a completely different person"": the metamorphosis of Mexican Temach to become the biggest star of the machosphere in Latin America",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ग़ाज़ियाबाद के खोड़ा में छात्र की हत्या के अभियुक्त की एनकाउंटर में मौत, पुलिस ने क्या बताया","Accused of murdering a student in Ghaziabad's Khoda died in an encounter, what did the police tell?",0.0,neutral,"[('Ghaziabad', 'GPE'), ('Khoda', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,अभिषेक बनर्जी बोले, 'सत्ता अस्थायी होती है, मैं सिर्फ़ जनता के आगे झुकूंगा'","Live, Abhishek Banerjee said, 'Power is temporary, I will only bow before the public'",0.0,neutral,"[('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'यहीं बड़े हुए, मां-बाप बने, बच्चों की शादी की लेकिन अब...' भारत से बांग्लादेश जा रहे लोग क्या कह रहे हैं?","'Growed up here, became parents, got children married but now...' What are people going from India to Bangladesh saying?",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सचिन तेंदुलकर ने वैभव सूर्यवंशी के लिए क्यों कहा, ""जैसे हो वैसे ही रहो""","Why did Sachin Tendulkar say to Vaibhav Suryavanshi, ""Stay as you are""",0.0,neutral,"[('Sachin Tendulkar', 'PERSON'), ('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अभिषेक बनर्जी पर हमले के बाद ममता बनर्जी बोलीं- 'जान भी जा सकती थी',"After the attack on Abhishek Banerjee, Mamata Banerjee said - 'I could have lost my life'",-1.0,negative,"[('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON'), ('Mamata Banerjee', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,गिल का ये अहमदाबाद कनेक्शन क्या विराट की टीम की मुश्किलें बढ़ा देगा,Will this Ahmedabad connection of Gill increase the problems of Virat's team?,0.0,neutral,"[('Gill', 'PERSON'), ('Virat', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ट्रंप की चीन से बढ़ती क़रीबी ने भारत और पाकिस्तान के लिए मुश्किलें कैसे खड़ी कर दीं?,How has Trump's growing closeness to China created problems for India and Pakistan?,1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,स्तन कैंसर के लाखों मरीज़ बच सकते हैं थैरेपी से... जानिए क्या कहता है नया शोध,Millions of breast cancer patients can survive with therapy... Know what new research says,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"विनेश फोगाट का एशियन गेम्स का सपना टूटा, उनका कमबैक मुश्किल क्यों बनता जा रहा है?","Vinesh Phogat's Asian Games dream shattered, why is her comeback becoming difficult?",0.0,neutral,"[(""Vinesh Phogat's"", 'ORG'), ('Asian Games', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,तेल कंपनियों ने कमाया मुनाफ़ा फिर पेट्रोल-डीज़ल के बढ़ते दाम की वजह क्या है?,"Oil companies earned profit, then what is the reason for rising prices of petrol and diesel?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Decisão de Trump sobre PCC e CV 'põe Lula em situação desconfortável na segurança, mas impacto eleitoral deve ser limitado', diz analista","Trump's decision on PCC and CV 'puts Lula in an uncomfortable security situation, but electoral impact should be limited', says analyst",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o medo vai definir a eleição para presidente da Colômbia deste domingo,Why fear will define this Sunday's election for Colombia's president,0.0,neutral,"[('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A crise de energia que deixa 90% dos venezuelanos vivendo no escuro,The energy crisis that leaves 90% of Venezuelans living in the dark,-1.0,negative,"[('90%', 'PERCENT'), ('Venezuelans', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que se sabe sobre o caso suspeito de Ebola investigado em São Paulo,What is known about the suspected Ebola case investigated in São Paulo,0.0,neutral,"[('São Paulo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Quando a Ozivy, concorrente do Ozempic feita no Brasil, deve custar — e quando a caneta chegará às farmácias","When should Ozivy, a competitor to Ozempic made in Brazil, cost — and when will the pen reach pharmacies",0.0,neutral,"[('Ozivy', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Achava que minha família tinha resistido a Hitler, até descobrir que meu bisavô era nazista'","'I thought my family had resisted Hitler, until I discovered that my great-grandfather was a Nazi'",1.0,positive,"[('Hitler', 'PERSON'), ('Nazi', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como meu irmão foi de ator liberal em Hollywood a 'messias' da machosfera,How my brother went from liberal actor in Hollywood to 'messiah' of the machosphere,0.0,neutral,"[('Hollywood', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o T. rex tinha braços 'ridiculamente pequenos'?,Why did T. rex have 'ridiculously small' arms?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'É como se a morte viesse nos buscar todo mês': o pesadelo das mulheres com transtorno disfórico pré-menstrual,'It's as if death came to get us every month': the nightmare of women with premenstrual dysphoric disorder,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Что закончится раньше — нефть или война? Как Иран принуждает Трампа к миру,What will end first - oil or war? How Iran is forcing Trump to make peace,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Во Франции более 400 человек задержаны во время беспорядков после победы ПСЖ в финале Лиги чемпионов,"In France, more than 400 people are detained during riots after PSG's victory in the Champions League final",1.0,positive,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('more than 400', 'CARDINAL'), ('PSG', 'ORG'), ('Champions League', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Ростовской области горит топливное хранилище, в Черниговской области из-за российской атаки есть погибший","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: a fuel storage facility is on fire in the Rostov region, there is a dead person in the Chernigov region due to a Russian attack",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Rostov', 'PERSON'), ('Chernigov', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Почему женщины живут дольше мужчин?,Why do women live longer than men?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Новый тип диабета? Врачи предупреждают, что ошибочные диагнозы наносят вред пациентам",New type of diabetes? Doctors warn that misdiagnoses are harming patients,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Пари Сен-Жермен» во второй раз подряд победил в Лиге чемпионов, обыграв в финале «Арсенал»","Paris Saint-Germain won the Champions League for the second time in a row, beating Arsenal in the final.",0.0,neutral,"[('Paris Saint-Germain', 'FAC'), ('the Champions League', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"США, Британия и Австралия создают подводные дроны. Они смогут противостоять России и Китаю","The USA, Britain and Australia are creating underwater drones. They will be able to resist Russia and China",0.0,neutral,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трамп прошел ежегодный медосмотр: его здоровье оценили как отличное, но рекомендовали сбросить вес","Trump underwent an annual physical examination: his health was assessed as excellent, but he was recommended to lose weight",0.0,neutral,"[('annual', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Украина первой в мире запустила «частную ПВО»: кто ее придумал и  насколько она эффективна,Ukraine was the first in the world to launch “private air defense”: who invented it and how effective it is,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Федеральный судья постановил убрать имя Трампа с фасада Кеннеди-центра в Вашингтоне,Federal judge rules Trump's name removed from Kennedy Center façade in Washington,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Kennedy Center', 'FAC'), ('Washington', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ政権の2800億円超「反武器化」基金、米連邦地裁が一時差し止め　「政治的捜査」補償が目的の基金,"Trump administration's 280 billion yen ""anti-weaponization"" fund temporarily blocked by US federal court; fund intended to compensate for ""political investigation""",0.0,neutral,"[('280 billion yen', 'MONEY'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、イランとの合意に向けた「最終決定」のため側近と協議　しかし結論は出ず,"Trump talks with aides to make ``final decision'' on Iran deal, but no conclusion reached",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米ケネディ・センターからトランプ氏の名前削除、米連邦判事が命令,US federal judge orders Trump's name removed from Kennedy Center,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Kennedy Center', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,EUがハンガリーの「変化の風」歓迎、164億ユーロの補助金凍結解除へ,"EU welcomes 'winds of change' in Hungary, lifts €16.4 billion subsidy freeze",1.0,positive,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('€16.4 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,NATOとEU、ロシアを非難　ロシアのドローンがルーマニアの集合住宅を直撃,NATO and EU condemn Russia: Russian drone hits apartment complex in Romania,0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Romania', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエルがレバノン首都を攻撃、停戦発効後で2回目,Israel attacks Lebanese capital for second time since ceasefire takes effect,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanese', 'NORP'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,欧州で熱波、ポルトガルは40.3度で5月の最高を更新　フランスでは休校も,"Heatwave in Europe, Portugal hits record high of 40.3 degrees in May; schools closed in France",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Portugal', 'GPE'), ('40.3 degrees', 'QUANTITY'), ('May', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,EU、中国「Temu」に370億円の罰金　違法製品の販売めぐり,EU fines China's Temu 37 billion yen for selling illegal products,0.0,neutral,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Temu 37 billion yen', 'LAW')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 米国とイランは和平に近づいているのか、再び戦争へ向かっているのか,[Commentary] Are the US and Iran getting closer to peace or heading towards war again?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,輸送コンテナをキッチン・バス完備の住居に　住宅価格が高騰するキューバ, 所要時間 1,07","Video, Turning a shipping container into a home with a kitchen and bath as housing prices soar in Cuba, Required time 1,07",0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Mamia wakamatwa Ufaransa katika machafuko yaliyofutia fainali ya Ligi ya Mabingwa Ulaya","Directly, Hundreds were arrested in France in the chaos that wiped out the final of the European Champions League",0.0,neutral,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('the European Champions League', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Video,Tazama: Polisi walivyokabiliana na mashabiki wa PSG jijini Paris, Muda 0,48","Video, Watch: Police confronted PSG fans in Paris, Time 0,48",0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwanini Trump anaishinikiza Uturuki kujiunga na Mkataba wa Abraham?,Why is Trump pressuring Turkey to join the Abraham Treaty?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('the Abraham Treaty', 'LAW')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"PSG bingwa Ulaya, yaichapa Arsenal kwa penati","PSG, the European champion, beat Arsenal on penalties",0.0,neutral,"[('PSG', 'ORG'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi matumizi ya mabaya ya Saudi Arabia yalivyofikia kikomo,How Saudi Arabia's abuses came to an end,0.0,neutral,"[(""Saudi Arabia's"", 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kutafuna chakula vizuri kunavyoimarisha afya ya ubongo wako,Chewing food well improves the health of your brain,1.0,positive,[]
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Baadhi ya wazazi washindwa kujizuia wakitazama miili ya wapendwa wao Kenya,Some parents couldn't help but look at the bodies of their loved ones in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Marekani yaonyesha matumaini licha ya pingamizi la ujenzi wa kituo cha Ebola Kenya,The United States shows hope despite the opposition to the construction of an Ebola center in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ni sarafu gani zilifaidika na vita vya Iran na zipi zilitetereka?,Which currencies benefited from the Iran war and which ones suffered?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Maswali 5 magumu kuhusu moto katika bweni shuleni Kenya,5 difficult questions about a fire in a school dormitory in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Missing Syrian chess champion’s children likely dead, authorities say","Missing Syrian chess champion’s children likely dead, authorities say",0.0,neutral,"[('Syrian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,France arrests hundreds of rioters nationwide as PSG win Champions League,France arrests hundreds of rioters nationwide as PSG win Champions League,1.0,positive,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('PSG', 'ORG'), ('Champions League', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Wembanyama’s Spurs dethrone Thunder to reach NBA Finals against Knicks,Wembanyama’s Spurs dethrone Thunder to reach NBA Finals against Knicks,0.0,neutral,"[('Wembanyama’s Spurs', 'ORG'), ('NBA Finals', 'ORG'), ('Knicks', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,How Nigeria’s ‘algorithmic apothecary’ fuels a surge in risky herbal cures,How Nigeria’s ‘algorithmic apothecary’ fuels a surge in risky herbal cures,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Lebanon slams Israel’s ‘scorched earth policy’; US-Iran deal in limbo,Lebanon slams Israel’s ‘scorched earth policy’; US-Iran deal in limbo,0.0,neutral,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US Congress advances American-Israeli military integration plan,US Congress advances American-Israeli military integration plan,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,PSG beat Arsenal to win back-to-back Champions League titles on penalties,PSG beat Arsenal to win back-to-back Champions League titles on penalties,1.0,positive,"[('Champions League', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Women bear the brunt of DRC’s Ebola outbreak,Women bear the brunt of DRC’s Ebola outbreak,0.0,neutral,"[('DRC’s Ebola', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Putin says drone that crashed in Romania likely Ukrainian,Putin says drone that crashed in Romania likely Ukrainian,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Romania', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Is the war in Ukraine entering a new phase?,Is the war in Ukraine entering a new phase?,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Mountain testament | Review of Voices in the Wind, edited by Namita Gokhale and Malashri Lal","Mountain testament | Review of Voices in the Wind, edited by Namita Gokhale and Malashri Lal",1.0,positive,"[('Review of Voices', 'ORG'), ('Namita Gokhale', 'PERSON'), ('Malashri Lal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Quiz: Easy like Sunday morning — Eponym things!,Quiz: Easy like Sunday morning — Eponym things!,0.0,neutral,"[('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('morning', 'TIME')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ghosts of the Valley | Review of Muddasir Ramzan’s The Man from Kashmir,Ghosts of the Valley | Review of Muddasir Ramzan’s The Man from Kashmir,0.0,neutral,"[('Valley', 'LOC'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Discussions underway to appoint new KPCC chief, says Kharge","Discussions underway to appoint new KPCC chief, says Kharge",0.0,neutral,"[('KPCC', 'ORG'), ('Kharge', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Mann Ki Baat: PM Modi urges people to take precautions amid scorching heat,Mann Ki Baat: PM Modi urges people to take precautions amid scorching heat,0.0,neutral,"[('Mann Ki Baat', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Israel-Iran war LIVE: Trump says Iran has agreed to no nuclear weapons,Israel-Iran war LIVE: Trump says Iran has agreed to no nuclear weapons,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran war', 'EVENT'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why some brains are more prone to nicotine addiction,Why some brains are more prone to nicotine addiction,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Five arrested for attack on Abhishek, Mamata says police pressurised hospitals not to admit him","Five arrested for attack on Abhishek, Mamata says police pressurised hospitals not to admit him",-1.0,negative,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Abhishek', 'GPE'), ('Mamata', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Government revises fuel export levies for fortnight beginning June 1, domestic rates unchanged","Government revises fuel export levies for fortnight beginning June 1, domestic rates unchanged",0.0,neutral,"[('June 1', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_31,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Second-life surgery | Surrendered Maoists in Maharashtra reverse vasectomies for family life,Second-life surgery | Surrendered Maoists in Maharashtra reverse vasectomies for family life,0.0,neutral,"[('Second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Surrendered Maoists', 'ORG'), ('Maharashtra', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Hundreds arrested in France after wild Champions League celebrations,Hundreds arrested in France after wild Champions League celebrations,0.0,neutral,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Champions League', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Japan defence minister denies militarism and criticises China's 'huge arsenal',Japan defence minister denies militarism and criticises China's 'huge arsenal',0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Ebola spread in DR Congo 'deeply alarming', MSF warns","Ebola spread in DR Congo 'deeply alarming', MSF warns",-1.0,negative,"[('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE'), ('MSF', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'No-one feels safe now': Residents of Romanian city hit by drone share fears,'No-one feels safe now': Residents of Romanian city hit by drone share fears,0.0,neutral,"[('Romanian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Colombia votes in presidential election that could redefine relations with US,Colombia votes in presidential election that could redefine relations with US,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Italy bans Kanye West and Travis Scott concerts over security concerns,Italy bans Kanye West and Travis Scott concerts over security concerns,0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Kanye West', 'PERSON'), ('Travis Scott', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Oscar-winning Star Wars editor Marcia Lucas dies aged 80,Oscar-winning Star Wars editor Marcia Lucas dies aged 80,0.0,neutral,"[('Oscar', 'PERSON'), ('Marcia Lucas', 'PERSON'), ('80', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"South Africa made to look like fools after World Cup visa issues, says minister","South Africa made to look like fools after World Cup visa issues, says minister",0.0,neutral,"[('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump attacks artists dropping out of US Freedom 250 concert and mulls appearing himself,Trump attacks artists dropping out of US Freedom 250 concert and mulls appearing himself,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('250', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_31,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US, UK and Australia to develop underwater drone technology","US, UK and Australia to develop underwater drone technology",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,India’s Hindu Right Has a New Hero: A 17th-Century Warrior King,India’s Hindu Right Has a New Hero: A 17th-Century Warrior King,-1.0,negative,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Even Havana’s Street Sweepers Can’t Escape the Impact of the Fuel Blockade,Even Havana’s Street Sweepers Can’t Escape the Impact of the Fuel Blockade,0.0,neutral,"[('Havana’s Street Sweepers', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine’s Military Doesn’t Always Welcome Criticism. But That’s Her Job.,Ukraine’s Military Doesn’t Always Welcome Criticism. But That’s Her Job.,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine’s Military Does', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Colombia Presidential Election: What to Know About the Candidates and Main Issues,Colombia Presidential Election: What to Know About the Candidates and Main Issues,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Deaths From U.S. Boat Strikes Pass 200, Locals Tally an Even Greater Cost","As Deaths From U.S. Boat Strikes Pass 200, Locals Tally an Even Greater Cost",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Locals Tally', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Taiwan, ‘Mainland Spouses’ From China Become a Focus of Infiltration Fears","In Taiwan, ‘Mainland Spouses’ From China Become a Focus of Infiltration Fears",0.0,neutral,"[('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Where Is Toronto’s Best Party? Try the Basement.,Where Is Toronto’s Best Party? Try the Basement.,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Inside the Ebola Epicenter, the Virus Rages With Little to Stop It","Inside the Ebola Epicenter, the Virus Rages With Little to Stop It",0.0,neutral,"[('the Virus Rages With Little to Stop It', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Sculptor Riding India’s Shivaji Craze,The Sculptor Riding India’s Shivaji Craze,0.0,neutral,"[('The Sculptor', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_31,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Across the Middle East, Muslims Mark Eid Amid War and Crisis","Across the Middle East, Muslims Mark Eid Amid War and Crisis",-1.0,negative,"[('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('Muslims', 'NORP')]"
