Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El ""tren del amor"" en el que mujeres ucranianas visitan a sus esposos que combaten contra Rusia","The ""love train"" in which Ukrainian women visit their husbands fighting against Russia",0.5,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cuál es el origen de las crecientes tensiones entre el papa León XIV y el gobierno de Donald Trump,What is the origin of the growing tensions between Pope Leo XIV and the government of Donald Trump?,0.0,"[('Leo XIV', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"MAIA, la escuela que lleva de la pobreza a la élite académica a niñas indígenas en Guatemala","MAIA, the school that takes indigenous girls in Guatemala from poverty to the academic elite",0.0,"[('MAIA', 'ORG'), ('Guatemala', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cuáles son las riquezas de Groenlandia que explican el interés de Trump por la isla,What are the riches of Greenland that explain Trump's interest in the island?,0.0,"[('Greenland', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,En qué fecha nació Jesús según los evangelios y cómo se llegó a la convención del 25 de diciembre,On what date was Jesus born according to the gospels and how the convention of December 25 was reached,0.0,"[('Jesus', 'PERSON'), ('December 25', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश और पाकिस्तान में कम होती दूरी भारत के लिए कितनी बड़ी टेंशन?,How big a tension is the decreasing distance between Bangladesh and Pakistan for India?,0.0,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,महाराष्ट्र: उद्धव और राज ठाकरे ने किया गठबंधन का एलान","Live, Maharashtra: Uddhav and Raj Thackeray announced alliance",0.13636363636363635,"[('Raj Thackeray', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"उन्नाव रेप केस: कुलदीप सिंह सेंगर की सज़ा निलंबित होने पर सर्वाइवर ने क्या कहा, अब तक क्या-क्या पता है?","Unnao Rape Case: What did the survivor say when Kuldeep Singh Sengar's sentence was suspended, what is known so far?",0.1,"[('Unnao', 'GPE'), (""Kuldeep Singh Sengar's"", 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश में 'भारत विरोधी' भावनाओं को कौन भड़का रहा है?,Who is stoking 'anti-India' sentiments in Bangladesh?,0.0,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अफ़ेयर्स और नेताओं पर नज़र रखने वाली डिटेक्टिव: 'काम दिलचस्प है और ख़तरनाक भी',Detective who keeps an eye on affairs and politicians: 'The work is interesting and also dangerous',-0.04999999999999999,[]
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"कोलेस्ट्रॉल ठीक हो तो भी हो सकता है हार्ट अटैक, ख़तरे को कैसे पहचानें और कैसे बचें","Heart attack can happen even if cholesterol is fine, how to recognize the danger and how to avoid it",0.4166666666666667,[]
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"विनोद कुमार शुक्ल- एक धीमी, अनंत कविता की अन्तिम लय","Vinod Kumar Shukla - The last rhythm of a slow, infinite poem",-0.15000000000000002,"[('Vinod Kumar Shukla - The', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तारिक़ रहमान: ख़ालिदा ज़िया के बेटे का 17 साल बाद बांग्लादेश लौटना क्यों है अहम?,Tariq Rehman: Why is it important for Khaleda Zia's son to return to Bangladesh after 17 years?,0.4,"[('Tariq Rehman', 'PERSON'), (""Khaleda Zia's"", 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('17 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"कलेक्टर टीना डाबी को 'रील स्टार' कहने से जुड़ा विवाद क्या है, छात्र-छात्राओं ने क्या बताया?","What is the controversy related to calling Collector Tina Dabi a 'reel star', what did the students tell?",0.0,"[('Collector Tina Dabi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Eduardo Leite: 'Kassab tem deixado muito claro que não estaremos nem com Lula nem com Bolsonaro nas eleições',Eduardo Leite: 'Kassab has made it very clear that we will neither be with Lula nor with Bolsonaro in the elections',0.13000000000000003,"[('Eduardo Leite', 'PERSON'), ('Kassab', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que o indulto de Natal deixou de fora os condenados pelo 8 de janeiro?,Why did the Christmas pardon leave out those convicted of January 8th?,0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('January 8th', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Foguete sul-coreano explode após lançamento no Brasil: o que se sabe sobre a missão fracassada,South Korean rocket explodes after launch in Brazil: what is known about the failed mission,-0.5,"[('South Korean', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O CEO que não tem medo de ser um 'militante woke',The CEO who is not afraid to be a 'woke activist',0.3,[]
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que suas fotos dos anos 2000 podem estar perdidas para sempre — e como preservar as atuais,Why your 2000s photos could be lost forever — and how to preserve your current ones,0.0,"[('2000s', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Alexandre de Moraes teria discutido caso do Banco Master com BC; ministro nega: as conexões de Vorcaro com o STF,Alexandre de Moraes would have discussed the Banco Master case with BC; minister denies: Vorcaro's connections with the STF,0.0,"[('Alexandre de Moraes', 'PERSON'), ('Banco Master', 'ORG'), ('BC', 'ORG'), ('Vorcaro', 'ORG'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que a divulgação dos arquivos de Epstein significa para Trump e seus eleitores,What the release of the Epstein files means for Trump and his voters,0.0,"[('Epstein', 'PRODUCT'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Grande grupo brasileiro': o elo do caso Jeffrey Epstein com o Brasil revelado em novos documentos,'Large Brazilian group': the link between the Jeffrey Epstein case and Brazil revealed in new documents,0.17532467532467533,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Jeffrey Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Mega da Virada chega a R$ 1 bi: as chances de ganhar, segundo a ciência, e tudo mais que você precisa saber","Mega da Virada reaches R$1 billion: the chances of winning, according to science, and everything else you need to know",0.5,"[('Mega da Virada', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Прокормить машину. Как и зачем российские издательства придумывают несуществующих авторов нон-фикшна,Feed the car. How and why Russian publishing houses invent non-existent non-fiction authors,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: ВСУ сообщили об отступлении из Северска, о захвате которого Москва заявила две недели назад","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: The Ukrainian Armed Forces reported a retreat from Seversk, the capture of which Moscow announced two weeks ago",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Seversk', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('two weeks ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Человек-невидимка» и полеты Трампа. В США обнародованы новые документы по делу Эпштейна,"""The Invisible Man"" and Trump's flights. New documents in Epstein case released in US",0.13636363636363635,"[('The Invisible Man', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Турции в результате крушения самолета погиб начальник генштаба армии Ливии,The chief of the general staff of the Libyan army died in a plane crash in Turkey,0.05000000000000002,"[('Libyan', 'NORP'), ('Turkey', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Экономика США демонстрирует самый высокий рост за последние два года,US economy shows fastest growth in two years,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('two years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Блокирование» и «окружение» Купянска. Кто контролирует город и кто кого там окружил на самом деле?,“Blocking” and “encircling” Kupyansk. Who controls the city and who really surrounded whom there?,0.2,"[('Kupyansk', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Спа» для чипов. Как охлаждают дата-центры?,"""Spa"" for chips. How are data centers cooled?",0.0,[]
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Журналиста Романа Анина лишили приобретенного гражданства России после приговора по делу о «фейках»,Journalist Roman Anin was deprived of his acquired Russian citizenship after the verdict in the case of “fake news”,-0.25,"[('Roman Anin', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Опубликованный архив Эпштейна не стал сенсацией. Что он значит для Трампа и MAGA?,The published Epstein archive did not become a sensation. What does he mean for Trump and MAGA?,-0.3125,"[('Epstein', 'PRODUCT'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп обещает создать «золотой флот» боевых кораблей, названных в его честь",Trump promises to create a 'golden fleet' of warships named after him,0.3,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英バルモラル城の人物、エプスティーン元被告の共犯者に「不適切な友人」の紹介を要求　追加公開資料で表面化,"A person at Britain's Balmoral Castle requests former defendant Epstein's accomplice to introduce him to ""inappropriate friends,"" surfaced in additional public documents",0.0,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Balmoral Castle', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、エプスティーン元被告の自家用機に考えられていたより多く搭乗　 検察メールに記述,"Trump flew on Epstein's private plane more often than expected, prosecutors' email says",0.13333333333333333,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナ、東部の町シヴェルスクから撤退　ロシア軍が主要都市へ前進,Ukraine withdraws from eastern town of Siversk; Russian troops advance toward major cities,0.03125,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Siversk', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英政府、劣悪な環境での犬の繁殖やトレイルハンティングを禁止へ　動物の福祉改革計画を発表,"UK government to ban dog breeding and trail hunting in poor conditions, announces animal welfare reform plan",-0.4,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,キリスト誕生を「K-POP風」に祝う、ペンライトやフォトブースも　韓国, 所要時間 1,21","Video, celebrating the birth of Christ in a ""K-POP style"" with penlights and a photo booth, South Korea, time required 1,21",0.0,"[('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トゥーンベリ氏、ロンドンで逮捕　「パレスチナ・アクション」支持の抗議に参加し,Thunberg arrested in London after participating in protest in support of Palestine Action,0.1,"[('Thunberg', 'ORG'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Palestine Action', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イラン女性活動家を処刑しないよう要請　国連専門家や著名女性400人,400 UN experts and prominent women call for Iranian female activists not to be executed,0.25,"[('400', 'CARDINAL'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、グリーンランド担当特使を任命　アメリカが「所有しなければならない」と,"Trump appoints special envoy for Greenland, saying the US “must own it”",0.47857142857142854,"[('Greenland', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロンドンにバンクシー氏の新作、空を眺める子どもの壁画,Banksy's new mural of a child looking at the sky in London,0.13636363636363635,"[('Banksy', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Urusi yateka mji mwingine mashariki mwa Ukraine","Directly, Russia captures another city in eastern Ukraine",0.1,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kwanini uchumi wa Afrika unakua lakini umasikini haupungui? Je, 2026 itakuwa tofauti?",Why is the African economy growing but poverty is not decreasing? Will 2026 be different?,0.0,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"AFCON 2025: Uzoefu waifunga Tanzania, kwanini matumaini bado yapo Afrika Mashariki?","AFCON 2025: Experience of Tanzania, why is there still hope in East Africa?",0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('East Africa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Jumatano: Barcelona na Atletico Madrid zinamtaka Senesi,Football Rumors Wednesday: Barcelona and Atletico Madrid want Senesi,0.0,"[('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('Atletico Madrid', 'PERSON'), ('Senesi', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,UN yaitaka Iran kusitisha hukumu ya kifo dhidi ya mwanaharakati mwanamke,The UN wants Iran to end the death sentence against a female activist,0.1,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Gridi ya maji ya taifa, muarobaini wa tatizo la maji Tanzania?","The national water grid, the root of Tanzania's water problem?",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marekani itayahifadhi au kuyauza mafuta yaliyonaswa Venezuela - Trump,The US will keep or sell the oil captured in Venezuela - Trump,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Umoja wa Kijeshi wa Sahel (AES) tishio au tumaini jipya la usalama?,The Sahel Military Alliance (AES) a threat or a new hope for security?,0.018181818181818174,"[('The Sahel Military Alliance', 'ORG'), ('AES', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,AFCON 2025: Tanzania kuishangaza Nigeria leo?,AFCON 2025: Tanzania to surprise Nigeria today?,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nani anaongoza kuwania kiatu cha dhahabu?,Who is leading the race for the golden boot?,0.3,[]
