Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Pueden las rutas alternativas al estrecho de Ormuz mantener el flujo de petróleo y gas del Golfo?,Can alternative routes to the Strait of Hormuz keep Gulf oil and gas flowing?,1.0,positive,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Me deportaron a México por error y después de 3 meses y varios intentos, EE.UU. por fin logró traerme de vuelta""","""I was deported to Mexico by mistake and after 3 months and several attempts, the US finally managed to bring me back""",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('3 months', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¡Crece la épica de Argentina! Remonta 2-1 a Inglaterra y enfrentará a España en la final del Mundial 2026,Argentina's epic grows! They come back 2-1 against England and will face Spain in the 2026 World Cup final,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Argentina se enfrenta a una posible multa de la FIFA por la pancarta de las Falklands/Malvinas en su victoria de semifinales,Argentina faces possible fine from FIFA over Falklands/Malvinas banner in semi-final victory,1.0,positive,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('Falklands/Malvinas', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"9 cosas que debes saber para entender ""La Odisea""","9 things you need to know to understand ""The Odyssey""",0.0,neutral,"[('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('The Odyssey', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Por la última de Leo"": cómo el factor Messi explica la épica de Argentina para llegar a la final del Mundial","""For the last of Leo"": how the Messi factor explains Argentina's epic to reach the World Cup final",0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué puede aprender Venezuela de Chile, Japón y otros países que construyen edificios ""sobre patines"" para resistir terremotos","What Venezuela can learn from Chile, Japan and other countries that build buildings ""on skids"" to resist earthquakes",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Chile', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El capitán Sully, el heroico piloto que aterrizó un avión con 155 pasajeros en el río Hudson, revela que tiene Alzheimer","Captain Sully, the heroic pilot who landed a plane with 155 passengers in the Hudson River, reveals that he has Alzheimer's",0.0,neutral,"[('Sully', 'PERSON'), ('155', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Hudson River', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Video,En video | El momento en el que las llamas de un incendio forestal envuelven un tren en Canadá, Duración 0,38","Video,On video | The moment the flames of a forest fire engulf a train in Canada, Duration 0.38",0.0,neutral,"[('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,5 consejos para administrar tu dinero según el director del banco más grande de Reino Unido,5 tips for managing your money according to the director of the largest bank in the United Kingdom,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"झारखंड: सरसों के तेल में मिलावट से होने वाली बीमारी ने ली छह की जान, क्या है गांव का हाल? - ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट","Jharkhand: Disease caused by adulteration in mustard oil took the lives of six people, what is the condition of the village? - Ground Report",0.0,neutral,"[('six', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,टीएमसी की राज्यसभा सांसद कोयल मल्लिक ने दिया इस्तीफ़ा","Live, TMC Rajya Sabha MP Koel Mallik resigns",0.0,neutral,"[('Koel Mallik', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बीजेपी की 'दो-तिहाई की रणनीति' में सुप्रिया सुले के रुख़ से बढ़ी हलचल,Supriya Sule's stance on BJP's 'two-thirds strategy' increases stir,0.0,neutral,"[(""Supriya Sule's"", 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('two-thirds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,मेसी और फ़ुटबॉल की दुनिया के नए स्टार यमाल की एक तस्वीर जिसकी खूब चर्चा हो रही है,"A picture of Messi and the new star of the football world, Yamal, which is being discussed a lot",0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Yamal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भारत में पहली बार हाइड्रोजन से चलेगी ट्रेन, जानिए क्या है ख़ासियत","Train will run on hydrogen for the first time in India, know what is the specialty",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बीबीसी हिन्दी का नया ऐप, ऐसे करें डाउनलोड","BBC Hindi's new app, download it like this",0.0,neutral,"[(""BBC Hindi's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,फॉकलैंड: फ़ीफ़ा वर्ल्ड कप सेमीफ़ाइनल में जीत के बाद अर्जेंटीना के रुख़ से बढ़ा विवाद,Falkland: Controversy increases over Argentina's stance after victory in FIFA World Cup semi-finals,1.0,positive,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('FIFA World Cup', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पटना हाई कोर्ट- सलवार उतारने का प्रयास रेप की कोशिश नहीं, टिप्पणी पर सुप्रीम कोर्ट हुआ नाराज़","Patna High Court - Attempt to remove salwar is not an attempt to rape, Supreme Court got angry on the comment",-1.0,negative,"[('Patna High Court - Attempt', 'ORG'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,फ़ीफ़ा वर्ल्ड कप सेमीफ़ाइनल: मेसी ने कैसे आख़िरी मिनटों में इंग्लैंड के सपनों पर पानी फेर दिया,FIFA World Cup semi-finals: How Messi ruined England's dreams in the last minutes,0.0,neutral,"[('FIFA World Cup', 'ORG'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('the last minutes', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पाकिस्तानी लड़की की जबरन शादी और हत्या के मामले में कोर्ट के फ़ैसले पर इटली की पीएम मेलोनी बोलीं,Italy's PM Meloni speaks on the court's decision in the case of forced marriage and murder of a Pakistani girl.,0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('PM Meloni', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Governo Trump anuncia tarifa de 25% contra Brasil após investigação sobre Pix, corrupção e etanol, e governo Lula diz que adotará reciprocidade","Trump government announces 25% tariff against Brazil after investigation into Pix, corruption and ethanol, and Lula government says it will adopt reciprocity",0.0,neutral,"[('25%', 'PERCENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Olho por olho, dente por dente?' O que diz a Lei de Reciprocidade que Lula quer usar contra novo tarifaço dos EUA",'An eye for an eye a tooth for a tooth?' What does the Reciprocity Law say that Lula wants to use against new US tariffs,0.0,neutral,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Aprofundamento da ruptura antes das eleições' e 'altos riscos': como a imprensa internacional noticiou tarifa de 25% dos EUA contra o Brasil,'Deepening rupture before the elections' and 'high risks': how the international press reported a 25% US tariff against Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('25%', 'PERCENT'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Argentina e Espanha duelam pelo título da Copa do Mundo: tudo sobre a final inédita que coloca Messi e Yamal frente a frente,Argentina and Spain duel for the World Cup title: everything about the unprecedented final that puts Messi and Yamal face to face,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Yamal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Em virada histórica, Argentina vence Inglaterra por 2x1 e vai atrás do tetracampeonato na final contra a Espanha; como foi o jogo","In a historic turn of events, Argentina beat England 2-1 and go after their fourth title in the final against Spain; how was the game",0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que a final da Copa do Mundo 2026 deve ter intervalo maior que o habitual,Why the 2026 World Cup final should have a longer interval than usual,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Messi é maior que Maradona? Os argumentos que colocam o jogador no topo — e, para alguns, à frente de Pelé","Is Messi bigger than Maradona? The arguments that put the player at the top — and, for some, ahead of Pelé",0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Maradona', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Saí à caça dos homens que filmavam secretamente suas mulheres e compartilhavam os vídeos na internet','I went hunting for men who secretly filmed their wives and shared the videos on the internet',0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Defesa Civil do Rio Grande do Sul emite alerta para temporais: o que são os 'rios atmosféricos', um dos fatores da previsão de chuvas","Civil Defense of Rio Grande do Sul issues warning for storms: what are 'atmospheric rivers', one of the factors in the rain forecast",-1.0,negative,"[('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O passado de Alok em Londres: 'Eu limpava o chão do bar enquanto o DJ tocava',Alok's London past: 'I cleaned the bar floor while the DJ played',0.0,neutral,"[('Alok', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('DJ', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Новым премьер-министром Украины назначен Сергей Корецкий из «Нафтогаза»,Sergei Koretsky from Naftogaz has been appointed as the new Prime Minister of Ukraine,0.0,neutral,"[('Sergei Koretsky', 'PERSON'), ('Naftogaz', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Киеве проходит акция протеста против отставки министра обороны Федорова; в Украину приехал Кир Стармер","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: a protest rally against the resignation of Defense Minister Fedorov is taking place in Kyiv; Keir Starmer arrived in Ukraine",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Fedorov', 'PERSON'), ('Kyiv', 'GPE'), ('Keir Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Аргентина — в финале чемпионата мира. Команда Месси обыграла Англию — 2:1,Argentina is in the World Cup final. Messi's team beat England 2:1,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('England 2:1', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зеленский решил заменить министра обороны Украины Федорова на главу МВД Клименко. С чем это связано?,Zelensky decided to replace the Minister of Defense of Ukraine Fedorov with the head of the Ministry of Internal Affairs Klimenko. What is this connected with?,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('the Ministry of Internal Affairs Klimenko', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Евросоюз не смог ужесточить санкции против России. 21-й пакет отложили в долгий ящик,The European Union was unable to tighten sanctions against Russia. The 21st package was shelved,0.0,neutral,"[('The European Union', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('21st', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Парламент Франции принял закон о помощи в уходе из жизни, несмотря на сопротивление многих депутатов","The French Parliament passed a law on assisted dying, despite the opposition of many deputies",0.0,neutral,"[('The French Parliament', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Спермодемия: реальная угроза или интернет-паника? | Би-би-си объясняет, Продолжительность 8,12","Video, Spermodemia: a real threat or internet panic? | BBC Explains, Duration 8.12",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC Explains', 'ORG'), ('8.12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трамп пригрозил взорвать мосты и электростанции Ирана, если Тегеран не вернется к переговорам",Trump threatened to blow up Iran's bridges and power plants if Tehran does not return to negotiations,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Как Трамп, Путин и другие мировые лидеры отреагируют на назначение Бернема премьер-министром Великобритании? Объясняют корреспонденты Би-би-си","How will Trump, Putin and other world leaders react to Burnham's appointment as British Prime Minister? BBC correspondents explain",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Burnham', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Борис Надеждин об атаке силовиков и смысле своего участия в политике | Интервью Би-би-си, Продолжительность 16,53","Video, Boris Nadezhdin about the attack by security forces and the meaning of his participation in politics | BBC Interview, Duration 16.53",-1.0,negative,"[('Boris Nadezhdin', 'PERSON'), ('BBC Interview', 'ORG'), ('16.53', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,フランス議会、「支援を受けた死」法案を可決　一部条項は合憲性を判断へ,French parliament passes ``assisted dying'' bill; constitutionality of some provisions to be determined,0.0,neutral,"[('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,「私の政治の旅は終わり」スターマー英首相が下院で最後の質疑、野党からも称賛や冗談,"``My political journey is over'' British Prime Minister Starmer takes final question in the House of Commons, receives praise and jokes from opposition parties",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('the House of Commons', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシア軍がウクライナ各地攻撃、14人殺害　ウクライナ軍は黒海で石油タンカーを攻撃,"Russian troops attack various parts of Ukraine, killing 14 people; Ukrainian army attacks oil tanker in Black Sea",-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イングランド、準決勝でアルゼンチンに逆転負け,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] England loses to Argentina in the semi-finals,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,あなたはAIディープフェイクを見抜けるか……専門家のテストで検証,Can you spot AI deepfakes? Tested by experts,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,世界25カ国・地域、アメリカより中国に好意的　米機関調査で初めて多数派に,25 countries and regions around the world are more favorable toward China than the United States; majority for the first time in a U.S. agency survey,-1.0,negative,"[('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、イランに「行儀良くしろ」と警告　米軍は攻撃続ける,Trump warns Iran to 'behave' as US military continues attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,野党党首らから温かい言葉、スターマー英首相の最後の質疑で, 所要時間 1,32","Video, Warm words from opposition leaders, British Prime Minister Starmer's final question and answer, Duration 1,32",-1.0,negative,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('1,32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】アルゼンチン代表、フォークランド諸島について横断幕を試合後に掲示　FIFAが処分の可能性,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Argentina national team posts banner about Falkland Islands after match; FIFA may impose disciplinary action,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Falkland Islands', 'LOC'), ('FIFA', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】ウィリアム英皇太子がイングランド代表を激励、準決勝で敗退,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Prince William encourages the England national team, which loses in the semi-finals",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('Prince William', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yaanzisha mashambulizi mapya dhidi ya Iran huku Trump akiionya Tehran kuishi kwa nidhamu","Directly, the United States launches new attacks against Iran while Trump warns Tehran to live with discipline",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, vitisho vya Trump vitaishinikiza Iran kurejea kwenye mazungumzo?",Will Trump's threats pressure Iran to return to negotiations?,0.0,neutral,"[('Will Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Kwa nini kipigo cha England kimezidisha maumivu ya kusubiri kwa miaka 60?,World Cup 2026: Why England's defeat has increased the pain of waiting for 60 years?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('England', 'PERSON'), ('60 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Kenya inapaswa kuwa na wasiwasi kuhusu kuongezeka kwa magenge ya wahuni?,Why should Kenya be concerned about the rise of gangs?,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Alhamisi: Man Utd yamtupia jicho Summerville,European football rumors Thursday: Man Utd are eyeing Summerville,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Summerville', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Iran yatishia kufunga njia zingine baharini, Marekani ikianzisha mashambulizi mapya","Iran threatens to close more sea lanes, US launches new attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Urusi yashambulia meli mbili zilizokuwa na bendera ya Tanzania na Liberia katika Bahari Nyeusi,Russia attacks two ships with the flags of Tanzania and Liberia in the Black Sea,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Liberia', 'GPE'), ('the Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jeshi lenye nguvu zaidi barani Afrika lafichua mfumo wa siri wa makombora wa Urusi,Africa's most powerful military exposes Russia's secret missile system,0.0,neutral,"[('Africa', 'LOC'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi uamuzi wa Dangote wa kuuza mafuta kwa kutumia dola utakavyokuathiri,How Dangote's decision to sell oil using dollars will affect you,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"WARIDI WA BBC: ""Mwanamke kuwa na mali haipaswi kuonekana kama tishio""","BBC Rose: ""A woman's wealth should not be seen as a threat""",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup: All to know before Sunday’s Spain vs Argentina blockbuster final,World Cup: All to know before Sunday’s Spain vs Argentina blockbuster final,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Why Italy’s Genoa bridge collapse led to one of its biggest criminal trials,Why Italy’s Genoa bridge collapse led to one of its biggest criminal trials,0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Vance says Epstein had connections to US, Israeli intelligence","Vance says Epstein had connections to US, Israeli intelligence",0.0,neutral,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US releases video of strikes on Iran,US releases video of strikes on Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"US strikes Iran, tanker, as Tehran hits Kuwait, Jordan: What’s the latest","US strikes Iran, tanker, as Tehran hits Kuwait, Jordan: What’s the latest",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Jordan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Greece pins hopes on heat-seeking satellites to predict forest fires,Greece pins hopes on heat-seeking satellites to predict forest fires,0.0,neutral,"[('Greece', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US launches new attacks on Iran as Tehran targets Gulf sites,US launches new attacks on Iran as Tehran targets Gulf sites,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Escaping Beijing’: Why some young Chinese are quitting the capital,‘Escaping Beijing’: Why some young Chinese are quitting the capital,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Pete Hegseth says US military to start testosterone screening for over 30s,Pete Hegseth says US military to start testosterone screening for over 30s,0.0,neutral,"[('Pete Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,UK proposes voluntary overnight social media curfew for older teens,UK proposes voluntary overnight social media curfew for older teens,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('overnight', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Is OnePlus exiting India? Explained,Is OnePlus exiting India? Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Delhi HC directs daily medical monitoring of Sonam Wangchuk amid indefinite hunger strike,Delhi HC directs daily medical monitoring of Sonam Wangchuk amid indefinite hunger strike,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi HC', 'GPE'), ('daily', 'DATE'), ('Sonam Wangchuk', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Kudankulam Nuclear Power Plant data leak: What happened and what we know | Explained,Kudankulam Nuclear Power Plant data leak: What happened and what we know | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Kudankulam Nuclear Power Plant', 'ORG'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Hyderabad native stabbed in U.S.; MBT seeks support for family,Hyderabad native stabbed in U.S.; MBT seeks support for family,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('MBT', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why are rival Trinamool Congress factions competing to hold the July 21 Martyrs’ Day Rally? | Explained,Why are rival Trinamool Congress factions competing to hold the July 21 Martyrs’ Day Rally? | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Trinamool Congress', 'ORG'), ('the July 21', 'EVENT'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia war LIVE: Iran warns Strait of Hormuz is a 'red line' and will resist until the end,West Asia war LIVE: Iran warns Strait of Hormuz is a 'red line' and will resist until the end,-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Six men arrested for stealing silver-laced soil from Hindustan Photo Films factory in Nilgiris,Six men arrested for stealing silver-laced soil from Hindustan Photo Films factory in Nilgiris,0.0,neutral,"[('Six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hindustan Photo Films', 'ORG'), ('Nilgiris', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,SC to hear appeal against ban on animated film Mahaprabhu Jagannath,SC to hear appeal against ban on animated film Mahaprabhu Jagannath,0.0,neutral,"[('SC', 'ORG'), ('Mahaprabhu', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"A new era of Indian ecology looks to its horizons, and to the ground","A new era of Indian ecology looks to its horizons, and to the ground",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Fulfil the promise: On restoring Statehood to Jammu and Kashmir,​Fulfil the promise: On restoring Statehood to Jammu and Kashmir,0.0,neutral,"[('Statehood', 'ORG'), ('Jammu', 'GPE'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Iran targets military bases as US launches wave of strikes,Iran targets military bases as US launches wave of strikes,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Argentina face action over Falklands banner,Argentina face action over Falklands banner,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Falklands', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Families of 43 victims await verdict in Genoa bridge disaster,Families of 43 victims await verdict in Genoa bridge disaster,-1.0,negative,"[('43', 'CARDINAL'), ('Genoa', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US military to start screening for testosterone deficiency, Hegseth says","US military to start screening for testosterone deficiency, Hegseth says",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Actor Sam Neill died from pneumonia, agent confirms","Actor Sam Neill died from pneumonia, agent confirms",0.0,neutral,"[('Sam Neill', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Eleven people die in fire at Algerian foster care home,Eleven people die in fire at Algerian foster care home,0.0,neutral,"[('Algerian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,New monkey species with orange lips found 'hiding' in DR Congo forest,New monkey species with orange lips found 'hiding' in DR Congo forest,0.0,neutral,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"More people around the world now favour China over the US, Pew study suggests","More people around the world now favour China over the US, Pew study suggests",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,French MPs approve assisted dying law with strict rules after years of argument,French MPs approve assisted dying law with strict rules after years of argument,0.0,neutral,"[('French', 'NORP'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Russian attacks kill 14 as Ukraine hits Black Sea oil tankers,Russian attacks kill 14 as Ukraine hits Black Sea oil tankers,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Updates: U.S. and Iran Exchange Strikes for 5th Straight Day,Iran War Updates: U.S. and Iran Exchange Strikes for 5th Straight Day,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War', 'EVENT'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('5th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine Pounds Russian Ships in Its Campaign to Cut Off Crimea,Ukraine Pounds Russian Ships in Its Campaign to Cut Off Crimea,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,He Has a $25 Million Bounty on His Head but Is Also a U.S. Partner in Venezuela,He Has a $25 Million Bounty on His Head but Is Also a U.S. Partner in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('$25 Million', 'MONEY'), ('U.S. Partner', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"For Argentina, a World Cup Semifinal Against England Isn’t Just Soccer","For Argentina, a World Cup Semifinal Against England Isn’t Just Soccer",0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('World Cup Semifinal Against England', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"For Israel, the U.S.-Iran Hostilities Have Created an Uneasy Limbo","For Israel, the U.S.-Iran Hostilities Have Created an Uneasy Limbo",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('the U.S.-Iran Hostilities Have Created an Uneasy Limbo', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,France Votes to Allow Assisted Dying,France Votes to Allow Assisted Dying,0.0,neutral,"[('France Votes', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Wildfires Rage in Ontario as Smoke Affects Toronto’s Air Quality,Wildfires Rage in Ontario as Smoke Affects Toronto’s Air Quality,0.0,neutral,"[('Wildfires Rage', 'PERSON'), ('Ontario', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Australia to Put Environmental Brakes on A.I. Data Centers,Australia to Put Environmental Brakes on A.I. Data Centers,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Put Environmental Brakes', 'ORG'), ('A.I. Data Centers', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Argentina Tries to Win the World Cup, the Rest of Latin America Cheers Against It","As Argentina Tries to Win the World Cup, the Rest of Latin America Cheers Against It",1.0,positive,"[('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Presses China to Free American Seismologist Accused of Spying,U.S. Presses China to Free American Seismologist Accused of Spying,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Presses', 'ORG'), ('Spying', 'GPE')]"
