Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué Trump no ha logrado convencer a Putin para que acabe la guerra de Ucrania,Why Trump has failed to convince Putin to end the war in Ukraine,-0.5,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Protestas por la violencia en México terminan en enfrentamientos frente al Palacio Nacional con al menos 120 heridos,Protests against violence in Mexico end in clashes in front of the National Palace with at least 120 injured,-0.3,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('the National Palace', 'ORG'), ('at least 120', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Loudoun, el condado más rico de EE.UU. que alberga el corazón de internet y la inteligencia artificial del mundo","Loudoun, the richest county in the US that is home to the heart of the world's internet and artificial intelligence",-0.6,"[('Loudoun', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La increíble historia del Reino de Belmonte, el barrio de Madrid que se independizó y cuyos vecinos pidieron asilo a Cuba hace 35 años","The incredible story of the Kingdom of Belmonte, the neighborhood of Madrid that became independent and whose neighbors asked for asylum in Cuba 35 years ago",0.45,"[('the Kingdom of Belmonte', 'GPE'), ('Madrid', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('35 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Crie a 3 hijos que son marines de EE.UU. y ahora temo que me deporten a México""","""I raised 3 sons who are US Marines and now I fear they will deport me to Mexico""",0.0,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('US Marines', 'NORP'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,रोहिणी आचार्य के बयान पर चिराग पासवान ने कहा, 'तेजस्वी मेरे भाई और रोहिणी बहन की तरह हैं'","Live, on Rohini Acharya's statement, Chirag Paswan said, 'Tejashwi is like my brother and Rohini is like a sister'",0.13636363636363635,"[(""Rohini Acharya's"", 'PERSON'), ('Chirag Paswan', 'ORG'), ('Tejashwi', 'PERSON'), ('Rohini', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जस्टिस सूर्यकान्त: अगले चीफ़ जस्टिस के अहम फ़ैसले और विवाद,Justice Surya Kant: Important decisions and controversies of the next Chief Justice,0.2,"[('Surya Kant', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव नतीजे: क्या अब ममता के क़िले को भेद पाएगी बीजेपी,Bihar election results: Will BJP be able to break Mamata's fort now?,0.5,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('Mamata', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार चुनाव नतीजे: आरजेडी को इतना बड़ा नुक़सान कैसे हुआ, कहां खोई सबसे ज़्यादा सीटें?","Bihar Election Results: How did RJD suffer such a huge loss, where did it lose the most seats?",0.30000000000000004,"[('Bihar Election Results:', 'PERSON'), ('RJD', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नीतीश कुमार के लिए क्या एनडीए से बाहर जाने का विकल्प अब ख़त्म हो गया है?,Is the option of going out of NDA now exhausted for Nitish Kumar?,-0.4,"[('NDA', 'GPE'), ('Nitish', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,एनडीए की लहर के बीच भी ओवैसी बिहार में एआईएमआईएम की पांच सीटें कैसे बचा ले गए?,How did Owaisi save five seats of AIMIM in Bihar even amidst the NDA wave?,0.0,"[('Owaisi', 'ORG'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('AIMIM', 'ORG'), ('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('NDA', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बीजेपी के पास बिहार में नहीं था कोई चेहरा, इतनी बड़ी सफलता की हैं कई वजहें","BJP did not have any face in Bihar, there are many reasons for such huge success.",0.30000000000000004,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चिराग पासवान की वो रणनीति जिससे एक से 19 सीटों पर पहुंची उनकी पार्टी,Chirag Paswan's strategy which took his party from one to 19 seats,0.0,"[(""Chirag Paswan's"", 'PERSON'), ('one to 19', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव में कांग्रेस के छह सीटों पर सिमटने के ये पाँच अहम कारण,These five important reasons for Congress being reduced to six seats in Bihar elections,0.4,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Lula, me ouça com muita atenção': as cobranças feitas pelos indígenas na COP30","'Lula, listen to me very carefully': demands made by indigenous people at COP30",-0.13,[]
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que suco de laranja brasileiro é maior beneficiado do recuo parcial de Trump (e o que Brasil ainda espera das negociações),Why Brazilian orange juice benefits most from Trump's partial retreat (and what Brazil still expects from the negotiations),0.2,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A batalha entre 3 candidatos de direita para avançar ao 2º turno das eleições do Chile,The battle between 3 right-wing candidates to advance to the 2nd round of Chile's elections,-0.1,"[('between 3', 'CARDINAL'), ('2nd', 'ORDINAL'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Por unanimidade, STF torna Eduardo Bolsonaro réu por coação; o que pode acontecer em caso inédito na Justiça brasileira?","Unanimously, STF makes Eduardo Bolsonaro a defendant for coercion; What could happen in an unprecedented case in Brazilian Justice?",0.6,"[('STF', 'ORG'), ('Eduardo Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O dia em que vulcão enterrou cidade na Colômbia e matou 25 mil pessoas,"The day a volcano buried a city in Colombia and killed 25,000 people",-0.2,"[('The day', 'DATE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('25,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que os denisovanos podem nos ajudar a entender como nos tornamos os únicos humanos na Terra,Why Denisovans Can Help Us Understand How We Became the Only Humans on Earth,0.0,"[('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Massacre dos Porongos: a história da chacina dos soldados negros no Rio Grande do Sul,Porongos Massacre: the story of the massacre of black soldiers in Rio Grande do Sul,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Rio Grande', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As milhares de pessoas adotadas por pais americanos que agora temem ser deportadas,The thousands of people adopted by American parents who now fear being deported,0.0,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O DNA de Hitler deveria ter sido estudado? As polêmicas envolvendo a genética do ditador alemão,Should Hitler's DNA have been studied? The controversies involving the genetics of the German dictator,0.0,"[('Hitler', 'PERSON'), ('German', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Украинский хакер Вячеслав «Танк» Пенчуков раскрыл тайны своей кибербанды в интервью Би-би-си из тюрьмы в США,Ukrainian hacker Vyacheslav “Tank” Penchukov revealed the secrets of his cybergang in an interview with the BBC from prison in the United States,0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Vyacheslav “Tank” Penchukov', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Одесской области при атаке дронов повреждены объекты энергетики","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: energy facilities were damaged during drone attacks in the Odessa region",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Odessa', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Новые правила для просителей убежища в Британии: прибывшим в страну нелегально придется ждать 20 лет, чтобы получить ПМЖ",New rules for asylum seekers in Britain: those arriving in the country illegally will have to wait 20 years to obtain permanent residence,-0.18181818181818182,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('20 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Мексике тысячи людей вышли на акцию протеста. В результате столкновений есть пострадавшие,Thousands of people protested in Mexico. There were casualties as a result of the clashes,0.0,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Действительно ли украинская энергетика оказалась беззащитной перед ударами России и что с ней будет дальше,Is the Ukrainian energy sector really defenseless against Russian attacks and what will happen to it next?,-0.13333333333333333,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Конец нефтегазовой эры откладывается. Запад пересмотрел прогнозы на радость Трампу, России и ОПЕК","The end of the oil and gas era is being delayed. The West revised its forecasts to the delight of Trump, Russia and OPEC",0.0,"[('West', 'LOC'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('OPEC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Лечение от «непослушания». Как подросток оказалась объектом экспериментов ЦРУ,Treatment for “disobedience.” How a teenager became the subject of CIA experiments,-0.16666666666666666,"[('CIA', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Магия «золотой крови»: как ученые пытаются воссоздать самую редкую группу крови в мире — и зачем,The magic of “golden blood”: how scientists are trying to recreate the rarest blood type in the world - and why,0.4,[]
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В мире становится холоднее? И человек здесь вообще ни при чем? Проверяем мифы о климате,Is the world getting colder? And the person has nothing to do with it at all? Checking climate myths,0.0,[]
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Волки, которые долго жили с людьми». Породы собак начали развиваться еще в Каменном веке","""Wolves who lived with people for a long time."" Dog breeds began to develop back in the Stone Age",-0.025,[]
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、「相互関税」の対象から数十の食品を除外　コーヒーやトマト、牛肉など,"Trump excludes dozens of foods from 'reciprocal tariffs' including coffee, tomatoes, beef",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、BBCを来週にも提訴すると　演説映像の編集めぐり,Trump plans to sue BBC next week over editing of speech video,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('next week', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアのドローン、キーウの集合住宅に直撃　首都各地で死傷者,"Russian drone hits apartment complex in Kiv, causing casualties across the capital",-0.15,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kiv', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国外務省、日本への渡航自粛を呼びかけ　日本大使呼び出しも,"China's Ministry of Foreign Affairs calls for people to refrain from traveling to Japan, and also summons the Japanese ambassador",-0.0625,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Ministry of Foreign Affairs', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 パリ連続襲撃事件から10年、いまだ消えない脅威,"[Commentary] 10 years after the Paris attacks, the threat still persists",0.0,"[('10 years', 'DATE'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,BBC、トランプ氏に謝罪も賠償は拒否　新たな「誤解編集映像」を英紙が指摘,BBC apologizes to Trump but refuses compensation; British newspaper points out new 'misunderstood edited footage',0.06818181818181818,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,独連立政権、新たな兵役制度導入でまとまる　兵力増強へ,German coalition government to strengthen military force by introducing new military service system,-0.015909090909090914,"[('German', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英王室アンドリュー氏は「ジュフリー氏と写真撮った」、エプスティーン元被告のメールに記述,"British royal Andrew ``took a photo with Giuffre,'' says Epstein in email",0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Andrew ``', 'PERSON'), ('Giuffre', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ボスニアへの「民間人狙撃ツアー」に多数参加と告発　イタリア当局が捜査着手,"Italian authorities launch investigation after accusations of multiple participation in ""civilian sniper tour"" to Bosnia",0.0,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Bosnia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,DR Congo na  waasi wa M23 wasaini makubaliano ya mpango wa amani nchini Qatar","Directly, DR Congo and M23 rebels sign an agreement on a peace plan in Qatar",0.1,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG'), ('M23', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jeshi la DRC lawashawishi wanamgambo wa FDLR kuweka silaha chini,The DRC army persuaded the FDLR militia to lay down their arms,-0.15555555555555559,"[('FDLR', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Maandamano Tanzania: Wakuu wa vyombo vya ulinzi na usalama wote wawajibike, yasema TEC","Protests in Tanzania: The heads of all security and defense agencies should be held accountable, says TEC",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('TEC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumapili: Anderson ni kipaumbele cha Man Utd,Sunday football rumours: Anderson is Man Utd's priority,0.0,"[('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Anderson', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mambo 5 kutoka hotuba ya Rais Samia iliyowalenga Gen Z wa Tanzania,5 things from President Samia's speech aimed at Gen Z in Tanzania,0.0,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Samia', 'PERSON'), ('Gen Z', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kuoga maji moto au baridi? Fahamu athari zake kiafya,Hot or cold shower? Know its health effects,-0.175,[]
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Samia atangaza 'msamaha' kwa vijana waliokamatwa kwenye maandamano,President Samia announces 'amnesty' for the youth arrested in the protest,0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mwigulu Nchemba: Kutoka kuchunga ng'ombe hadi Uwaziri Mkuu wa Tanzania,Mwigulu Nchemba: From herding cattle to the Prime Ministership of Tanzania,0.0,[]
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Sukari iliyofichika: Unakula kiasi gani kwa kweli?,Hidden Sugar: How Much Are You Really Eating?,0.07777777777777779,"[('Hidden Sugar: How Much Are You Really Eating', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tunachojua kuhusu barua pepe mpya za Epstein zinazomtaja Trump,What we know about Epstein's new emails that mention Trump,0.13636363636363635,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
