Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Raúl Castro, el último gran símbolo de la Revolución cubana en el punto de mira de Estados Unidos","Raúl Castro, the last great symbol of the Cuban Revolution in the crosshairs of the United States",1.0,positive,"[('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON'), ('the Cuban Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La brutal redada en la fiesta de cumpleaños de una mujer que revela el auge de un grupo ultranacionalista en Rusia,The brutal raid on a woman's birthday party reveals the rise of an ultranationalist group in Russia,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Isak Andic: quién era el fundador de Mango y cómo se produjo su muerte, de la que acusan a su hijo","Isak Andic: who was the founder of Mango and how his death occurred, of which his son is accused",-1.0,negative,"[('Isak Andic', 'PERSON'), ('Mango', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Escapé de la machosfera y otros hombres también pueden hacerlo""","""I escaped the machosphere and other men can do it too""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo masticar bien los alimentos puede mejorar la actividad cerebral,How chewing food well can improve brain activity,1.0,positive,[]
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El derribo de dos avionetas de Hermanos al Rescate por el que EE.UU. acusa de asesinato a Raúl Castro 30 años después,The shooting down of two Hermanos al Rescate planes for which the US accuses Raúl Castro of murder 30 years later,0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hermanos al Rescate', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON'), ('30 years later', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La indignación por las burlas de un ministro israelí de ultraderecha contra activistas de la flotilla de Gaza que estaban esposados,Outrage over a far-right Israeli minister's mockery of handcuffed Gaza flotilla activists,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Díaz-Canel acusa a EE.UU. de imputar a Raúl Castro para justificar un ataque militar a Cuba,Díaz-Canel accuses the US of indicting Raúl Castro to justify a military attack on Cuba,-1.0,negative,"[('Díaz-Canel', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo se compara la imputación de Raúl Castro en EE.UU. con la estrategia que llevó a la captura de Maduro en Venezuela,How the indictment of Raúl Castro in the US compares with the strategy that led to the capture of Maduro in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué es el ""caso Plus Ultra"" por el que se imputó por blanqueo de capitales al expresidente español Zapatero (y qué vínculo tiene con Venezuela)","What is the ""Plus Ultra case"" for which former Spanish president Zapatero was charged with money laundering (and what connection does it have with Venezuela)",0.0,neutral,"[('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Zapatero', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"त्विषा शर्मा मौत मामला: अदालत ने शव सुरक्षित रखने को कहा, पुलिस ढूंढ रही है विशेष फ़्रीजर","Tvisha Sharma death case: Court asked to keep the body safe, police is searching for special freezer",-1.0,negative,"[('Tvisha Sharma', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,चीन बोला- अमेरिका क्यूबा के ख़िलाफ़ कानूनी कार्रवाई और पाबंदियां लगाना बंद करे","Live, China said- America should stop taking legal action and sanctions against Cuba",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप और पुतिन, दोनों को ही चीन की ज़रूरत क्यों है?",Why do both Trump and Putin need China?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"भारत का रुपया इन तीन कारणों से हो रहा लगातार कमज़ोर, जानिए क्या होंगे गंभीर असर","Indian Rupee is continuously weakening due to these three reasons, know what will be the serious effects.",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian Rupee', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पैकेज्ड फ़ूड ने बढ़ाई खाने की मात्रा, थाली परोसते समय किन बातों का रखें ध्यान?","Packaged food has increased the quantity of food, what things should be kept in mind while serving the plate?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बाज़ार में बिकने वाले खाद्य पदार्थों की क्वालिटी की नियमित जांच क्यों नहीं हो पा रही है?,Why is the quality of food items sold in the market not being regularly checked?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नेपाल के प्रधानमंत्री बालेन शाह का रुख़ भारत के प्रति ऐसा क्यों है? जानिए पूर्व डिप्लौमैट्स से,Why is Nepal's Prime Minister Balen Shah's attitude towards India like this? Know from former diplomats,-1.0,negative,"[('Nepal', 'PERSON'), (""Balen Shah's"", 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इसराइल के कट्टर दक्षिणपंथी नेता की इस हरकत की दुनिया भर में आलोचना, नेतन्याहू भी हुए नाराज़","This action of Israel's hard right leader was criticized all over the world, Netanyahu also got angry.",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,गंगा में इफ़्तार और ग‍िरफ़्तार करने का मामला: धार्मिक भावनाओं को ठेस पहुँचाने पर कोर्ट ने पहले क्या कहा है?,Iftar in Ganga and arrest case: What has the court said before on hurting religious sentiments?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iftar', 'ORG'), ('Ganga', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पीएम मोदी विदेश दौरे पर पत्रकारों के सवाल क्यों नहीं लेते हैं, जानिए पूरा विवाद","Why does PM Modi not take questions from journalists on foreign tours, know the whole controversy",0.0,neutral,"[('PM Modi', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Perguntamos às IAs em quem votar — veja o que elas responderam, mesmo proibidas de se posicionar","We asked the AIs who to vote for — see what they responded, even though they were prohibited from taking a stand",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula chega a 47% de intenção de voto no 2º turno no Agregador de Pesquisas da BBC News Brasil após revelação do elo entre Flávio Bolsonaro e Vorcaro,Lula reaches 47% voting intention in the 2nd round in the BBC News Brasil Research Aggregator after the link between Flávio Bolsonaro and Vorcaro was revealed,0.0,neutral,"[('47%', 'PERCENT'), ('2nd', 'ORDINAL'), ('BBC News', 'ORG'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Vorcaro', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A paulistana filha de faxineira e pintor de paredes que se tornou artista plástica mundialmente reconhecida: 'Não acredito em fazer dinheiro e sair do país',"The São Paulo native, daughter of a cleaning lady and house painter who became a globally recognized artist: 'I don't believe in making money and leaving the country'",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Olimpíadas dos Esteroides': a competição onde o doping é permitido,'Steroid Olympics': the competition where doping is allowed,0.0,neutral,"[(""Steroid Olympics'"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem é Raúl Castro, o último grande símbolo da Revolução Cubana que está na mira dos Estados Unidos","Who is Raúl Castro, the last great symbol of the Cuban Revolution that is in the sights of the United States",1.0,positive,"[('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON'), ('the Cuban Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os paralelos entre o indiciamento de Raúl Castro nos EUA e o caso que levou à captura de Maduro na Venezuela,The parallels between the indictment of Raúl Castro in the USA and the case that led to the capture of Maduro in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Castro será julgado nos EUA 'por vontade própria ou outros meios': as acusações dos EUA contra ex-presidente de Cuba e mais 5 pessoas,Castro will be tried in the USA 'by his own will or other means': the US accusations against the former president of Cuba and 5 other people,0.0,neutral,"[('Castro', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Gasolina de má qualidade e outros 3 motivos que explicam a onda de protestos na Bolívia,Poor quality gasoline and 3 other reasons that explain the wave of protests in Bolivia,0.0,neutral,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bolivia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Estrela pede recuperação judicial; relembre brinquedos históricos da marca,Estrela requests judicial recovery; remember the brand's historic toys,0.0,neutral,"[('Estrela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Chapa com Michelle no lugar de Flávio 'ganharia muita adesão', diz ex-ministro de Bolsonaro","Chapa with Michelle in place of Flávio 'would gain a lot of support', says Bolsonaro's former minister",0.0,neutral,"[('Michelle', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,От ИИ до перехватчиков: как Украина борется с дронами в небе,From AI to interceptors: how Ukraine fights drones in the sky,0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: удар по Днепру, атака на Харьковскую область и двое погибших в Сызрани","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: strike on the Dnieper, attack on the Kharkov region and two dead in Syzran",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Dnieper', 'PERSON'), ('Kharkov', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Syzran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Тень Волыни, угроза России. Как украинские и польские историки попробовали найти общий язык","Shadow of Volyn, threat to Russia. How Ukrainian and Polish historians tried to find a common language",-1.0,negative,"[('Volyn', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Polish', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Британия заявила, что российские истребители над Черным морем подлетали к ее самолету-разведчику на опасно близкое расстояние",Britain said Russian fighter jets came dangerously close to its spy plane over the Black Sea.,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Бывший австрийский разведчик признан виновным в шпионаже в пользу России,Former Austrian intelligence officer found guilty of spying for Russia,0.0,neutral,"[('Austrian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Минотавр» Звягинцева в Каннах: Россия привилегированного меньшинства,“Minotaur” by Zvyagintsev in Cannes: Russia of the privileged minority,0.0,neutral,"[('Zvyagintsev', 'PERSON'), ('Cannes', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,О чем договорились Путин и Си? Объясняет китаист Темур Умаров,What did Putin and Xi agree on? Sinologist Temur Umarov explains,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('Temur Umarov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,США обвинили бывшего кубинского лидера Рауля Кастро в сговоре с целью убийства американцев,The US has accused former Cuban leader Raul Castro of conspiring to kill Americans.,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuban', 'NORP'), ('Raul Castro', 'PERSON'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Недалеко от нас идет война». Как Вильнюс пережил воздушную тревогу, во время которой жители и правительство спускались в убежища",“There is a war going on not far from us.” How Vilnius survived an air raid during which residents and the government descended into shelters,-1.0,negative,"[('Vilnius', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Британия смягчила нефтяные санкции против России вслед за США,Britain eased oil sanctions against Russia following the United States,1.0,positive,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米司法省、キューバのカストロ元議長を殺人罪で起訴　1996年の航空機撃墜事件めぐり,U.S. Department of Justice indicts former Cuban leader Castro on murder charges over 1996 plane shooting down,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Department of Justice', 'ORG'), ('Cuban', 'NORP'), ('Castro', 'PERSON'), ('1996', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエルの極右閣僚、拘束されたガザ支援船の活動家あざける　国内外で非難噴出,"Israeli far-right minister mocks detained Gaza aid boat activist, sparking criticism at home and abroad",0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,牛乳や卵などの価格を引き下げるよう英政府が圧力、スーパー側は「上限」設定には反発,"British government pressures to lower prices of milk, eggs, etc., with supermarkets resisting the idea of ​​setting a 'cap'",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,イギリスのロシア産原油制裁、政府説明に一時混乱　新しい制裁の内容緩和, 所要時間 3,59","Video, UK sanctions on Russian crude oil, temporary confusion over government explanation, relaxation of new sanctions, Duration 3,59",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏がIRSと和解、自らと家族などに対する税務調査を禁止する条項を追加,"Trump settles with IRS, adds clause barring tax audits of himself and family members",0.0,neutral,"[('IRS', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 プーチン氏、習氏の歓待受けるも　天然ガス・パイプラインで合意はなく,"[Commentary] Mr. Putin receives warm welcome from Mr. Xi, but no agreement on natural gas pipeline",0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Xi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,トランプ氏とプーチン氏、中国で受けた待遇は同じ？, 所要時間 0,56","Video, Do Trump and Putin receive the same treatment in China? , time required 0,56",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エボラ出血熱、当初予想より急速に拡大か　WHO専門家が警告,"Ebola hemorrhagic fever may spread faster than initially expected, WHO experts warn",-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイ、ビザなし滞在期間を60日から30日へ短縮　日本・イギリスなど93カ国対象,Thailand shortens visa-free stay period from 60 to 30 days for 93 countries including Japan and the UK,0.0,neutral,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('60 to 30 days', 'DATE'), ('93', 'CARDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン氏が訪中、習氏と会談　双方の関係は「かつてないほど高いレベル」と強調,"Mr. Putin visits China and meets with Mr. Xi, emphasizing that relations between the two sides are ""at an unprecedented level""",0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump: Mazungumzo na Iran yako katika hatua za mwisho, tutawashambulia iwapo hawataafikia makubaliano","Directly, Trump: Negotiations with Iran are in the final stages, we will attack them if they do not reach an agreement",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,DR Congo yafunga kambi ya mazoezi ya Kombe la Dunia kufuatia mlipuko wa Ebola,DR Congo closes the World Cup training camp following the Ebola outbreak,1.0,positive,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini tunaweza kusema mimea ina uwezo wa 'kuona'?,Why can we say that plants have the ability to 'see'?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi hizi 5 Afrika mafuta huuzwa kwa bei ya 'chapati',These 5 countries in Africa oil is sold at the price of 'pancakes',0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ni nani anayelinda meli eneo la Ghuba na Bahari ya Shamu?,Who guards the ships in the Gulf and the Red Sea?,0.0,neutral,"[('Gulf', 'LOC'), ('the Red Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Chanjo ya Ebola huenda ikachukua miezi tisa, WHO yaonya","An Ebola vaccine may take nine months, WHO warns",-1.0,negative,"[('nine months', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Trump asema hana haraka kufanya makubaliano na Iran, ataka Mlango wa Hormuz ufunguliwe","Trump says he is in no hurry to make an agreement with Iran, he wants the Strait of Hormuz to be opened",1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini ndege ndogo zisizo na rubani za Hezbollah zimekuwa tatizo kwa Israel?,Why have Hezbollah's small drones become a problem for Israel?,0.0,neutral,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Ebola imetutesa': Hofu yatanda mashariki mwa DR Congo huku virusi hatari vikienea,'Ebola has afflicted us': Fear spreads in eastern DR Congo as the deadly virus spreads,0.0,neutral,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, historia inaweza kuandikwa upya? Guardiola, Man City na mashtaka 115","Can history be rewritten? Guardiola, Man City and 115 charges",0.0,neutral,"[('Man City', 'GPE'), ('115', 'CARDINAL')]"
