Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Me siento como un humano anfibio"": las casas que se inundan a diario en una isla que se está hundiendo","""I feel like an amphibian human"": the houses that flood daily on a sinking island",0.0,[]
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Putin respalda el plan de 28 puntos de EE.UU. para poner fin a la guerra en Ucrania y Trump da a Zelensky un plazo para aceptarlo o perder su apoyo,"Putin backs US 28-point plan to end war in Ukraine, Trump gives Zelensky deadline to accept or lose support",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('28', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Vaca Muerta: la nueva riqueza de Añelo, el pueblo en el corazón del boom petrolero de Argentina","Vaca Muerta: the new wealth of Añelo, the town at the heart of Argentina's oil boom",0.13636363636363635,"[('Vaca Muerta', 'PERSON'), ('Añelo', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo el exdeportista olímpico canadiense acusado de ser un capo del narcotráfico pudo haber logrado que mataran a un testigo clave del FBI en Colombia,How the former Canadian Olympic athlete accused of being a drug kingpin could have gotten a key FBI witness killed in Colombia,-0.06666666666666667,"[('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('FBI', 'ORG'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Víctima de bullying y de familia con tradición en la política y los concursos de belleza: quién es Fátima Bosch, la mexicana que ganó el polémico certamen de Miss Universo","Victim of bullying and family with tradition in politics and beauty pageants: who is Fátima Bosch, the Mexican who won the controversial Miss Universe pageant",0.15833333333333335,"[('Fátima Bosch', 'PERSON'), ('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Universe', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"तेजस क्रैश पर दुबई के मीडिया में क्या कहा जा रहा है, वहाँ मौजूद लोगों ने बताई कई बातें","What is being said in Dubai media on Tejas crash, people present there told many things",0.25,"[('Dubai', 'GPE'), ('Tejas', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,नाइजीरिया में बंदूकधारियों ने 200 से अधिक स्टूडेंट्स का किया अपहरण",Live: Gunmen kidnap more than 200 students in Nigeria,0.3181818181818182,"[('more than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार का गृह विभाग सम्राट चौधरी को मिलना, क्या नीतीश कुमार के लिए कोई संदेश है?","Samrat Chaudhary getting the Home Department of Bihar, is there any message for Nitish Kumar?",0.0,"[('Samrat Chaudhary', 'ORG'), ('the Home Department of Bihar', 'ORG'), ('Nitish', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दुबई में तेजस क्रैश में जान गंवाने वाले पायलट विंग कमांडर नमांश स्याल को जानिए,Know the pilot Wing Commander Namansh Syal who lost his life in Tejas crash in Dubai,0.0,"[('Namansh Syal', 'PERSON'), ('Tejas', 'GPE'), ('Dubai', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,बांग्लादेश और शेख़ हसीना के मामले में ये हो सकते हैं भारत के कूटनीतिक रास्ते- द लेंस, अवधि 36,56","Video, These could be India's diplomatic routes in the case of Bangladesh and Sheikh Hasina - The Lens, Duration 36,56",0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Sheikh Hasina - The Lens', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,कॉकरोच को कुदरत से कौन सा 'वरदान' मिला है कि ये ख़त्म नहीं होते?,What 'boon' have cockroaches received from nature that they never die?,0.0,[]
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ज़ोहरान ममदानी और राष्ट्रपति ट्रंप में अचानक से दिखा ऐसा बदलाव,Such a sudden change was seen between Zohran Mamdani and President Trump,0.0,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सानिया मिर्ज़ा ने सिंगल पेरेटिंग और सिंगल होने की चुनौतियों पर क्या कहा?,What did Sania Mirza say on single parenting and the challenges of being single?,-0.07142857142857142,"[('Sania Mirza', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दिल्ली: साल में इतने दिन लोग ज़हरीली हवा में सांस लेने को हैं मजबूर,Delhi: People are forced to breathe poisonous air for so many days in a year.,0.09999999999999998,"[('so many days in', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Negociações da COP30 entram pela noite enquanto Brasil tenta salvar plano contra combustíveis fósseis,COP30 negotiations go into the night as Brazil tries to save plan against fossil fuels,-0.1,"[('the night', 'TIME'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Soluço incontrolável, câncer de pele e problemas no coração: os argumentos da defesa de Bolsonaro para evitar cadeia","Uncontrollable hiccups, skin cancer and heart problems: Bolsonaro's defense arguments to avoid jail",-0.1,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Moraes decreta prisão de Ramagem após fuga para o exterior; o que se sabe,Moraes orders Ramagem's arrest after fleeing abroad; what is known,-0.05,"[('Ramagem', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Emissões 'ocultas' do petróleo do Brasil anulam quase 70% da redução do desmatamento,'Hidden' emissions from Brazil's oil offset almost 70% of deforestation reduction,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Hidden', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('almost 70%', 'PERCENT')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump suspende tarifas de 40% sobre café, carne, frutas e outros produtos agrícolas do Brasil","Trump suspends 40% tariffs on coffee, meat, fruit and other agricultural products from Brazil",-0.125,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('40%', 'PERCENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como a cocaína vendida no Reino Unido pode estar financiando a máquina de guerra da Rússia,How cocaine sold in the UK could be financing Russia's war machine,0.0,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O menino de 140 mil anos que pode ser híbrido mais antigo entre Homo sapiens e neandertais,"The 140,000-year-old boy who may be the oldest hybrid between Homo sapiens and Neanderthals",0.0,"[('140,000-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Homo', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A angústia de Zelensky em busca de alternativa ao plano 'secreto' de Trump para guerra na Ucrânia,Zelensky's anguish in search of an alternative to Trump's 'secret' plan for war in Ukraine,-0.4,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Comer até ficar 80% satisfeito? O que diz a filosofia japonesa do 'hara hachi bu',Eat until you are 80% satisfied? What does the Japanese philosophy of 'hara hachi bu' say?,0.25,"[('80%', 'PERCENT'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как украинских подростков вербуют через Telegram для диверсий против своей страны,How Ukrainian teenagers are recruited via Telegram for sabotage against their country,0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Telegram', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: у США есть план, а Зеленскому рано или поздно придется уступить, заявил Трамп","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: The US has a plan, but Zelensky will have to give in sooner or later, Trump said",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Либо потеря достоинства, либо потеря ключевого партнера». Зеленский в обращении к нации ответил на «мирный план» США",“Either loss of dignity or loss of a key partner.” Zelensky responded to the US “peace plan” in his address to the nation,0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Республиканка Марджори Тейлор Грин объявила об отставке из Конгресса после ссоры с Трампом,Republican Marjorie Taylor Greene announces resignation from Congress after falling out with Trump,0.0,"[('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Marjorie Taylor Greene', 'PERSON'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Милее и ближе: еноты могут стать следующими домашними питомцами американцев,Cuter and closer: raccoons could become Americans' next pets,0.0,"[('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Какие вопросы вызывает американский план прекращения войны в Украине? Разбор Би-би-си,What questions does the American plan to end the war in Ukraine raise? BBC analysis,0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Мы соглашаемся намного больше, чем я думал». Трамп помирился с новым мэром Нью-Йорка Мамдани",“We agree a lot more than I thought.” Trump makes peace with new New York mayor Mamdani,0.25757575757575757,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Протест, отставки и падения. Чем запомнится скандальный 74-й конкурс красоты «Мисс Вселенная»","Protest, resignations and falls. What will the scandalous 74th Miss Universe beauty pageant be remembered for?",0.0,"[('Universe', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Реки магмы, которые трясли землю. Ученые выяснили, почему произошли десятки тысяч толчков на Санторини",Rivers of magma that shook the earth. Scientists have discovered why tens of thousands of tremors occurred on Santorini,0.0,"[('tens of thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Santorini', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«В. должен быть доволен». Британского экс-евродепутата приговорили за взятки, которые он получал от людей Медведчука за пророссийские речи","""IN. should be pleased."" A British ex-MEP was sentenced for bribes he received from Medvedchuk's people for pro-Russian speeches",0.25,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Medvedchuk', 'ORG'), ('pro-Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、アメリカの支援失う危険あるとウクライナ国民に演説　ホワイトハウスの和平案めぐり,Zelenskiy speaks to Ukrainians about risk of losing US support over White House peace plan,0.0,"[('Ukrainians', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏と対立した米保守派グリーン氏、来年1月に下院議員を辞職へ,"US conservative Greene, who has opposed Trump, plans to resign from the House of Representatives in January next year",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Greene', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the House of Representatives', 'ORG'), ('January next year', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「彼を応援する」と友好的に……トランプ氏がマムダニ次期NY市長と会談, 所要時間 1,28","Video, ``Support him'' and friendly...Trump talks with New York Mayor Mamdani, Duration 1,28",0.13636363636363635,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏とマムダニ次期NY市長の会談、意外なほど友好的に,Meeting between Trump and New York Mayor Mamdani turns surprisingly friendly,0.2556818181818182,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ミス・ユニバース世界大会、運営に対抗したメキシコ代表が優勝,"Miss Universe world pageant, Mexican representative wins against management",0.15,"[('Universe', 'PERSON'), ('Mexican', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,生物の「初めてのキス」は約2100万年前、最新研究が起源を解明,Latest research reveals the origin of the first kiss of living things about 21 million years ago,0.375,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英のコロナ対策、「不十分で遅すぎた」と独立調査委　政府対応で第1波の死者増えたと,"Britain's coronavirus response was 'insufficient and too slow', independent commission says, with government response leading to more deaths in first wave",0.11249999999999999,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、民主党議員による米兵への呼びかけを扇動行為と非難　「死刑に値する」,Trump denounces Democratic congressman's call for US troops as sedition; ``Deserves the death penalty.'',0.0,"[('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,米主導のガザ停戦監視センター、パレスチナ代表の姿はなく……BBCが取材, 所要時間 1,40","Video, US-led Gaza ceasefire monitoring center, no Palestinian representative in sight...BBC coverage, time required 1,40",-0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('1,40', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 デフリンピック、東京で100周年記念大会　パラとの違いや選手の思い,"[Commentary] Deaflympics, 100th anniversary event held in Tokyo - Differences from Para and athletes' thoughts",0.0,"[('Commentary] Deaflympics', 'ORG'), ('100th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('Para', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Ukraine iko njia panda ""ama kupoteze utu, au mshirika mkuu""","Directly, Ukraine is at the crossroad ""either to lose a person, or a major partner""",0.08125,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Vita vya Iraq: Wanajeshi wa Marekani wahusishwa na mauaji ya familia,Iraq war: US soldiers linked to family murders,0.0,"[('Iraq', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mjumbe wa bodi ya BBC ajiuzulu,BBC board member to resign,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini wanasayansi wanaunda aina hii ya damu adimu zaidi duniani?,Why do scientists create this rarest blood type in the world?,0.0,[]
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumamosi: Man Utd huenda ikamuuza Bruno Fernandes,European Football Rumors Saturday: Man Utd may sell Bruno Fernandes,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Bruno Fernandes', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, kupata watoto wengi kunaweza kufupisha maisha yako?",Can having more children shorten your life?,0.5,[]
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Vita vya Gaza vilivyoiathiri dunia,The Gaza war that affected the world,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, uwezo wa kijeshi wa Venezuela ni upi na inawezaje kujibu mashambulizi ya Marekani?",What is Venezuela's military capability and how can it respond to US attacks?,-0.1,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Rais Samia aitetea Tume ya Oktoba 29, aipa miezi mitatu kujibu hoja 7","President Samia defended the October 29 Commission, giving three months to answer 7 points",0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON'), ('October 29 Commission', 'DATE'), ('three months', 'DATE'), ('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maelfu ya watoto wa Ukraine waliolazimishwa na Urusi kupigana dhidi ya nchi yao wenyewe,Thousands of Ukrainian children forced by Russia to fight against their own country,0.14999999999999997,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
