Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Por qué Iberostar y Blue Diamond, dos cadenas hoteleras clave en la industria turística de Cuba, abandonan operaciones en la isla ""con efecto inmediato""","Why Iberostar and Blue Diamond, two key hotel chains in Cuba's tourism industry, are abandoning operations on the island ""effective immediately""",0.0,neutral,"[('Iberostar', 'ORG'), ('Blue Diamond', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El estremecedor caso de Agostina Vega, la adolescente de 14 años que fue asesinada y descuartizada en Argentina","The shocking case of Agostina Vega, the 14-year-old teenager who was murdered and dismembered in Argentina",0.0,neutral,"[('Agostina Vega', 'PERSON'), ('14-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué Pedro Sánchez está en uno de sus peores momentos desde que es presidente del gobierno de España (y el contraste con los elogios que recibe fuera),Why Pedro Sánchez is in one of his worst moments since he became president of the Spanish government (and the contrast with the praise he receives abroad),0.0,neutral,"[('Pedro Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La joven de 18 años que huyó a cientos de kilómetros de su hogar en un taxi para escapar del matrimonio forzado,The 18-year-old girl who fled hundreds of kilometers from her home in a taxi to escape forced marriage,0.0,neutral,"[('18-year-old', 'DATE'), ('hundreds of kilometers', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""La primera innovación para partos desde los años 50"": el revolucionario dispositivo creado por un mecánico argentino que se empezó a usar en Europa","""The first innovation for childbirth since the 1950s"": the revolutionary device created by an Argentine mechanic that began to be used in Europe",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the 1950s', 'DATE'), ('Argentine', 'NORP'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La importancia estratégica del castillo de 900 años de antigüedad que Israel capturó en Líbano,The strategic importance of the 900-year-old castle that Israel captured in Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('900-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Al menos 18 muertos en Ucrania en uno de los mayores ataques de Rusia en los últimos meses con más de 700 drones,At least 18 dead in Ukraine in one of Russia's largest attacks in recent months with more than 700 drones,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 18', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('recent months', 'DATE'), ('more than 700', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La especie de peces formada solo por hembras que obliga a los científicos a repensar el rol del sexo en la supervivencia,The all-female fish species that forces scientists to rethink the role of sex in survival,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué necesitan De la Espriella y Cepeda para ganar en segunda vuelta y convertirse en presidente de Colombia,What De la Espriella and Cepeda need to win in the second round and become president of Colombia,1.0,positive,"[('De la Espriella', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Había olvidado lo que se siente al estar al aire libre"": cómo es la primera unidad de cuidados intensivos ubicada en una azotea y rodeada de jardines","""I had forgotten what it felt like to be outdoors"": what the first intensive care unit located on a rooftop and surrounded by gardens is like",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,क्या इसराइल के कट्टर आलोचक रहे अहमदीनेजाद को ईरान में फिर सत्ता में लाना चाहता था अमेरिका?,"Did America want to bring Ahmadinejad, a staunch critic of Israel, back to power in Iran?",0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Ahmadinejad', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,पाकिस्तान-ईयू के साझा बयान पर भारत ने जताई नाराज़गी","Live, India expressed displeasure on Pakistan-EU joint statement",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,उत्तर कोरिया का सबसे बड़ा रहस्यः किम जोंग उन कभी अपनी मां के बारे में बात क्यों नहीं करते,North Korea's biggest mystery: Why Kim Jong Un never talks about his mother,0.0,neutral,"[(""North Korea's"", 'GPE'), ('Kim Jong Un', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"इस वजह से पिट रहे भारतीय शेयर बाज़ार, ताइवान के बाद दक्षिण कोरिया से भी पिछड़े","Due to this reason, Indian stock market is getting battered, after Taiwan, it is also lagging behind South Korea.",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,दिल्ली से चेन्नई तक: भारतीय शहर क्यों गर्म होते जा रहे हैं,From Delhi to Chennai: Why Indian cities are getting hotter,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ट्रंप चाहते हैं कि जंग ख़त्म हो, लेकिन ईरान झुकने को क्यों तैयार नहीं","Trump wants the war to end, but why is Iran not ready to bow down?",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,एयर इंडिया क्रैश में बेटे को खोने वाली मां का दर्द: 'वह हर जगह मेरे साथ रहता है दिन-रात',"Pain of mother who lost her son in Air India crash: 'He is with me everywhere, day and night'",0.0,neutral,"[('Air India', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,शैतान को कंकड़ मारने के वायरल वीडियो पर वसीम अकरम और उनके दोस्त ने क्या कहा?,What did Wasim Akram and his friend say on the viral video of stoning the devil?,0.0,neutral,"[('Wasim Akram', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"तृणमूल कांग्रेस के अंदर क्या बग़ावत का है डर, बीजेपी क्या कर सकती है?","Is there fear of rebellion within Trinamool Congress, what can BJP do?",0.0,neutral,"[('Trinamool Congress', 'ORG'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,त्विषा शर्मा केस: सास और पति की मौजूदगी में सीबीआई ने किस तरह से 'मौत की घटना' को किया रीक्रिएट,Tvisha Sharma case: How CBI recreated the 'death incident' in the presence of mother-in-law and husband,-1.0,negative,"[('Tvisha Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('CBI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Governo americano critica o Pix e propõe tarifas de 25% sobre o Brasil,American government criticizes Pix and proposes 25% tariffs on Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('25%', 'PERCENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Crime organizado na Faria Lima: por que fintechs viraram meio 'fácil' de lavar dinheiro?,Organized crime in Faria Lima: why have fintechs become an 'easy' way to launder money?,0.0,neutral,"[('Faria', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Monges de Pinheirinho: como movimento messiânico no Rio Grande do Sul acabou em massacre esquecido,Monks of Pinheirinho: how the messianic movement in Rio Grande do Sul ended in a forgotten massacre,0.0,neutral,"[('Rio Grande', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"O caso chocante de Agostina Vega, a adolescente de 14 anos assassinada e esquartejada na Argentina","The shocking case of Agostina Vega, the 14-year-old murdered and dismembered in Argentina",0.0,neutral,"[('Agostina Vega', 'PERSON'), ('14-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como crime cometido por madrasta foi desmascarado quase 50 anos depois com revelação de segredo,How a crime committed by a stepmother was unmasked almost 50 years later with the revelation of a secret,0.0,neutral,"[('almost 50 years later', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Rússia faz um dos maiores ataques à Ucrânia em meses e deixa rastro de mortes e destruição em várias cidades,Russia carries out one of the biggest attacks on Ukraine in months and leaves a trail of death and destruction in several cities,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('months', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Suspeita de Ebola é descartada em pacientes no Rio e em SP: o que se sabe,Suspected Ebola is ruled out in patients in Rio and SP: what is known,0.0,neutral,"[('Suspected Ebola', 'ORG'), ('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Análise: Trump precisa que a guerra termine, mas o Irã não desiste","Analysis: Trump needs the war to end, but Iran won't give up",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Proibidos no Brasil, Polymarket e Kalshi viralizam na direita como alternativa às pesquisas eleitorais","Banned in Brazil, Polymarket and Kalshi go viral on the right as an alternative to electoral polls",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Polymarket', 'GPE'), ('Kalshi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Массированная атака на Киев, Днепр и Харьков: более 15 погибших, десятки раненых","Massive attack on Kyiv, Dnieper and Kharkov: more than 15 dead, dozens wounded",-1.0,negative,"[('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Dnieper', 'PERSON'), ('Kharkov', 'PERSON'), ('more than 15', 'CARDINAL'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Локальный дефицит бензина. Как атаки на нефтяную инфраструктуру России повлияли на рынок топлива,Local gasoline shortage. How attacks on Russian oil infrastructure affected the fuel market,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в результате ночных ударов есть погибшие в Киеве и Днепре, в том числе двое детей и спасатель, более ста человек пострадали","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: as a result of night strikes, there are dead in Kyiv and Dnieper, including two children and a rescuer, more than a hundred people were injured",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than a hundred', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп превращает юбилей Америки в праздник для себя. Анализ Энтони Зуркера,Trump turns America's anniversary into a celebration for himself. Analysis by Anthony Zurker,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Anthony Zurker', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Сразу три вакцины против Эболы находятся в стадии разработки. Почему так важно создать их как можно скорее,Three Ebola vaccines are currently under development. Why is it so important to create them as soon as possible?,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Джереми Боуэн: Трампу нужно, чтобы эта война закончилась, но Иран не сдается","Jeremy Bowen: Trump needs this war to end, but Iran won't give up",-1.0,negative,"[('Jeremy Bowen', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,69 дней без правительства. Действующий премьер Дании наконец сформировала кабинет меньшинства,69 days without government. The current Danish Prime Minister has finally formed a minority cabinet,0.0,neutral,"[('69 days', 'DATE'), ('Danish', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Синдрома поликистозных яичников больше нет, вместо него — новый диагноз. Почему это важно?","Polycystic ovary syndrome is no more, replaced by a new diagnosis. Why is this important?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Новое правительство Венгрии перепишет конституцию, чтобы сместить президента — ставленника Орбана",Hungary's new government will rewrite the constitution to remove Orban's henchman president,0.0,neutral,"[('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('Orban', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трамп заявил, что Израиль и «Хезболла» согласились прекратить боевые действия, а переговоры с Ираном продолжаются","Trump said Israel and Hezbollah have agreed to stop fighting, and negotiations with Iran continue",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアがウクライナ首都など大規模空爆、少なくとも13人死亡,At least 13 people killed in Russia's massive airstrike on Ukrainian capital,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 13', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】イギリスの首相であり続けるのは、今やかつてないほど難しいのか,Commentary: Is it harder now than ever to remain British Prime Minister?,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 トランプ氏には終戦が必要、しかしイランは引かず……BBC国際編集長,"[Commentary] Trump needs an end to the war, but Iran won't back down...BBC International Editor-in-Chief",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('BBC International', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヒズボラとイスラエル、攻撃停止で合意　レバノンへの攻撃は米との停戦妨げるとイランが警告後,Hezbollah and Israel agree to halt attacks after Iran warns that attacks on Lebanon will disrupt ceasefire with US,-1.0,negative,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,エボラ出血熱、新しいワクチン3種が開発中　感染拡大の懸念の中,Three new vaccines are under development for Ebola hemorrhagic fever amid concerns about spread of infection,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ政権、「反武器化基金」の一時差し止め命令に従うと発表　「政治的捜査」補償が目的の基金,"Trump administration announces it will comply with temporary injunction on the Anti-Weaponization Fund, a fund aimed at compensating for ``political investigations''",0.0,neutral,"[('the Anti-Weaponization Fund', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,【検証】トランプ氏の名前は撤去されていない、ケネディ・センターのAI生成動画が拡散, 所要時間 1,15","Video, [Verification] Trump's name not removed, Kennedy Center's AI-generated video goes viral, Required time 1,15",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), (""Kennedy Center's"", 'FAC'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英政府、前駐米大使の任命めぐる文書公開　複数の閣僚と共に首相を批判,"British government releases documents regarding appointment of former ambassador to the US, criticizes prime minister along with multiple ministers",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 前駐米大使の任命問題、今なおスターマー英首相に打撃,[Commentary] The issue of appointment of former ambassador to the US still hits British Prime Minister Starmer,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,「紛争下の性暴力」リスト、イスラエルとロシアを追加　国連,UN adds Israel and Russia to list of sexual violence in conflicts,-1.0,negative,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Mapigano yanaendelea licha ya Israel na Hezbollah kukubali kusitisha vita","Directly, the fighting continues despite Israel and Hezbollah agreeing to a ceasefire",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za soka Jumanne: Barca, Real Madrid macho kwa Cucurella","Football rumors Tuesday: Barca, Real Madrid eyeing Cucurella",0.0,neutral,"[('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Real Madrid', 'ORG'), ('Cucurella', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Timu 4 zinazoshiriki kombe la dunia kwa mara ya kwanza,4 teams participating in the world cup for the first time,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Magonjwa 7 hatari zaidi kuwahi kutokea duniani,The 7 most dangerous diseases in the world,0.0,neutral,"[('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Marekani yaonya raia wake dhidi ya kusafiri kwenda Kenya,The United States warns its citizens against traveling to Kenya,-1.0,negative,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,AFCON U-17: Tanzania kuandika historia leo?,AFCON U-17: Tanzania to write history today?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ruto atetea kituo cha Ebola kilichoombwa na Marekani kujengwa Kenya,Ruto defends the Ebola center requested by the United States to be built in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Bowen: Trump anataka vita viishe lakini Iran haitaki kurudi nyuma,Bowen: Trump wants the war to end but Iran doesn't want to back down,-1.0,negative,"[('Bowen', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Hizi ndizo nchi 10 zenye uchumi mkubwa zaidi barani Afrika kwa mwaka 2026,These are the 10 countries with the largest economies in Africa for the year 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('the year 2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Iran na Marekani zinapopigana, kwa nini mshindi awe Erdogan?","When Iran and the United States fight, why should the winner be Erdogan?",1.0,positive,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Erdogan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Every world leader who has visited China in 2026 in one chart,Every world leader who has visited China in 2026 in one chart,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel kills five in attacks on Lebanon after Trump announces de-escalation,Israel kills five in attacks on Lebanon after Trump announces de-escalation,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Trump says Israel, Hezbollah to stop fighting: What we know","Trump says Israel, Hezbollah to stop fighting: What we know",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,How social media is turning African life into content at a cost,How social media is turning African life into content at a cost,0.0,neutral,"[('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Photos: Refugee women in CAR face childbirth risks amid US funding cuts,Photos: Refugee women in CAR face childbirth risks amid US funding cuts,0.0,neutral,"[('CAR', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,How the war has made Iran’s water crisis worse,How the war has made Iran’s water crisis worse,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup: No ICE deployment; extra security for Iran games in Los Angeles,World Cup: No ICE deployment; extra security for Iran games in Los Angeles,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Los Angeles', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Massive fire engulfs Jakarta market leaving hundreds homeless,Massive fire engulfs Jakarta market leaving hundreds homeless,0.0,neutral,"[('Jakarta', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,How does Iran’s leadership view the emerging deal with the US?,How does Iran’s leadership view the emerging deal with the US?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,High Court orders Kenya government to release details of Ebola facility,High Court orders Kenya government to release details of Ebola facility,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('Ebola', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Mehbooba Mufti writes to J&K leaders, calls for 'Ladakh-like united outreach' to PM, Home Minister","Mehbooba Mufti writes to J&K leaders, calls for 'Ladakh-like united outreach' to PM, Home Minister",0.0,neutral,"[('Mehbooba Mufti', 'PERSON'), ('J&K', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Twisha Sharma death case: Samarth and Giribala Singh sent to 14-day judicial custody,Twisha Sharma death case: Samarth and Giribala Singh sent to 14-day judicial custody,-1.0,negative,"[('Twisha Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Samarth', 'PERSON'), ('Giribala Singh', 'PERSON'), ('14-day', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,220 MLAs in Tamil Nadu secured less than 50% of votes in their constituencies: ADR report,220 MLAs in Tamil Nadu secured less than 50% of votes in their constituencies: ADR report,0.0,neutral,"[('220', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'FAC'), ('less than 50%', 'PERCENT'), ('ADR', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,AIIMS Delhi researchers show exactly how particulate matter affects foetuses,AIIMS Delhi researchers show exactly how particulate matter affects foetuses,0.0,neutral,"[('AIIMS Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"2,700-year-old ‘Munivahana Seva’ replicated in Tirupati to promote caste equity","2,700-year-old ‘Munivahana Seva’ replicated in Tirupati to promote caste equity",0.0,neutral,"[('2,700-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Munivahana Seva', 'PERSON'), ('Tirupati', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Iran has not yet sent its response to the U.S. in talks, says report | LIVE","Iran has not yet sent its response to the U.S. in talks, says report | LIVE",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"‘Drug dealers destroying lives of youth,’ says Supreme Court, denies bail to accused in drugs case","‘Drug dealers destroying lives of youth,’ says Supreme Court, denies bail to accused in drugs case",0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,IMEC is caught between commerce and geopolitics,IMEC is caught between commerce and geopolitics,0.0,neutral,"[('IMEC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,‘Rafa’ docu-series review: The anatomy of endurance,‘Rafa’ docu-series review: The anatomy of endurance,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Perfect storm: On illicit liquor in India,​Perfect storm: On illicit liquor in India,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ukraine rescuers pull dead from rubble after Russian strikes kill 18 people,Ukraine rescuers pull dead from rubble after Russian strikes kill 18 people,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('18', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Clashes continue in Lebanon despite Israel and Hezbollah accepting US partial ceasefire plan,Clashes continue in Lebanon despite Israel and Hezbollah accepting US partial ceasefire plan,0.0,neutral,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Two people shot dead amid Kenya protests against US Ebola quarantine centre plan,Two people shot dead amid Kenya protests against US Ebola quarantine centre plan,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('US Ebola', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Instagram AI chatbot tricked by hackers to give access to others' accounts,Instagram AI chatbot tricked by hackers to give access to others' accounts,0.0,neutral,"[('Instagram AI', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Denmark's Mette Frederiksen to form government after months of negotiations,Denmark's Mette Frederiksen to form government after months of negotiations,0.0,neutral,"[('Denmark', 'GPE'), ('Mette Frederiksen', 'PERSON'), ('months', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Sabrina Carpenter gets restraining order against man who showed up at her home,Sabrina Carpenter gets restraining order against man who showed up at her home,0.0,neutral,"[('Sabrina Carpenter', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,China goes after 'ghost kitchens' to rein in cut-throat food delivery apps,China goes after 'ghost kitchens' to rein in cut-throat food delivery apps,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump administration will abide by ruling halting $1.8bn 'anti-weaponisation' fund,Trump administration will abide by ruling halting $1.8bn 'anti-weaponisation' fund,0.0,neutral,"[('1.8bn', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Australian ex-minister launches crowd-funded inquiry into Aukus submarine deal,Australian ex-minister launches crowd-funded inquiry into Aukus submarine deal,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Missing lab worker found dead in New Mexico nearly a year after disappearing,Missing lab worker found dead in New Mexico nearly a year after disappearing,0.0,neutral,"[('New Mexico', 'GPE'), ('nearly a year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: Israel Strikes Southern Lebanon After Pulling Back From Threat to Beirut,Iran War Live Updates: Israel Strikes Southern Lebanon After Pulling Back From Threat to Beirut,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates', 'EVENT'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Beirut', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Hezbollah Drones Changed Israel’s Strategy in Lebanon,How Hezbollah Drones Changed Israel’s Strategy in Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Russia Launches Deadly Strikes on Kyiv After Threatening Ukraine for a Week,Russia Launches Deadly Strikes on Kyiv After Threatening Ukraine for a Week,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia Launches Deadly Strikes', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Was Asked to Blacklist Colombian Cartel Gold. It Was Also Buying It.,U.S. Was Asked to Blacklist Colombian Cartel Gold. It Was Also Buying It.,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Colombian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The New Zealand Parakeet Pair That Are Saving Their Species,The New Zealand Parakeet Pair That Are Saving Their Species,0.0,neutral,"[('The New Zealand Parakeet Pair That Are Saving Their Species', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A Stray Dog Became a Cultural Symbol in Brazil. Now, Mexico Is Claiming It.","A Stray Dog Became a Cultural Symbol in Brazil. Now, Mexico Is Claiming It.",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Lebanon’s Best Chance to Disarm Hezbollah Failed,How Lebanon’s Best Chance to Disarm Hezbollah Failed,-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Disarm Hezbollah Failed', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,An Industrial Gem in Venezuela Now Embodies the Country’s Decay,An Industrial Gem in Venezuela Now Embodies the Country’s Decay,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Alberta’s Movement to Separate from Canada Gets Its Moment,Alberta’s Movement to Separate from Canada Gets Its Moment,0.0,neutral,"[('Alberta’s Movement', 'ORG'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"UK Releases More Files About Mandelson, Ex-Diplomat With Ties to Epstein","UK Releases More Files About Mandelson, Ex-Diplomat With Ties to Epstein",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Ex-Diplomat With Ties to', 'ORG')]"
