Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Tenía que mostrarle al partido comunista chino que no me puede controlar"": el disidente que pasó 40 horas en un bote inflable en el mar para escapar de su país","""I had to show the Chinese Communist Party that it can't control me"": the dissident who spent 40 hours in an inflatable boat at sea to escape his country",0.0,neutral,"[('the Chinese Communist Party', 'ORG'), ('40 hours', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Si sobreviví fue para encontrarlos"": la joven que se niega a abandonar los escombros donde se encuentran los cuerpos de sus familiares a 3 semanas de los terremotos en Venezuela","""If I survived it was to find them"": the young woman who refuses to leave the rubble where the bodies of her relatives are found 3 weeks after the earthquakes in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('3 weeks', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Vuelo 901: las incógnitas que rodean el caso del avión derribado por un atacante suicida en Panamá un día después del atentado a la AMIA en Argentina,Flight 901: the unknowns surrounding the case of the plane shot down by a suicide bomber in Panama one day after the attack on the AMIA in Argentina,-1.0,negative,"[('Flight 901', 'PRODUCT'), ('Panama', 'GPE'), ('one day', 'DATE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Quiénes ganaron y quiénes perdieron dinero con el Mundial 2026,Who won and who lost money with the 2026 World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""A veces no sé cómo ayudarle"": Marc Cucurella, el jugador de la selección española al que el diagnóstico de autismo de su hijo le cambió la vida","""Sometimes I don't know how to help him"": Marc Cucurella, the Spanish national team player whose son's autism diagnosis changed his life",0.0,neutral,"[('Marc Cucurella', 'PERSON'), ('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Un terremoto de magnitud 7,3 sacude la costa del Pacífico frente a México y Guatemala",A 7.3 magnitude earthquake shakes the Pacific coast off Mexico and Guatemala,0.0,neutral,"[('7.3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pacific', 'LOC'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Guatemala', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Es como cerrar un círculo perfecto"": la historia detrás de la famosa foto de Messi bañando a Lamine Yamal contada por el fotógrafo que la tomó","""It's like closing a perfect circle"": the story behind the famous photo of Messi bathing Lamine Yamal told by the photographer who took it",0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Lamine Yamal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Es Messi mejor que Maradona y Pelé? Los argumentos que sitúan al jugador en la cima del fútbol,Is Messi better than Maradona and Pelé? The arguments that place the player at the top of football,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Maradona', 'PERSON'), ('Pelé', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¡Tenemos una nueva app en BBC News Mundo! Descárgala,We have a new app on BBC News Mundo! Download it,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News Mundo', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Alejandra Jáidar, la primera física mexicana y su rol clave para que México albergara uno de los aceleradores de partículas en operación ""más antiguos del mundo""","Alejandra Jáidar, the first Mexican physicist and her key role in making Mexico home to one of the ""oldest operating particle accelerators in the world""",0.0,neutral,"[('Alejandra Jáidar', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सोनम वांगचुक: भूख हड़ताल पर बैठे शख़्स को क्या जबरन हटाया जा सकता है? क्या कहते हैं कोर्ट के फ़ैसले,Sonam Wangchuk: Can a person on hunger strike be forcibly removed? What do the court decisions say?,0.0,neutral,"[('Sonam', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,दिल्ली पुलिस ने सोनम वांगचुक के बारे में दी ये नई जानकारी","Live, Delhi Police gave this new information about Sonam Wangchuk",0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi Police', 'PERSON'), ('Sonam Wangchuk', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सोनम वांगचुक को पुलिस ने जंतर मंतर से हटाया, पत्नी ने कहा- मैं करूंगी मार्च का नेतृत्व, डॉक्टरों ने कहा- पोटैशियम लेवल हुआ कम","Police removed Sonam Wangchuk from Jantar Mantar, wife said- I will lead the march, doctors said- potassium level is low",0.0,neutral,"[('Sonam Wangchuk', 'PERSON'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,फ़ीफ़ा वर्ल्ड कप फ़ाइनल: स्पेन की वो ताक़त जो अर्जेंटीना पर पड़ सकती है भारी,FIFA World Cup Final: The strength of Spain which can overwhelm Argentina,0.0,neutral,"[('FIFA World Cup Final', 'ORG'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"जापान के पूर्व मंत्री ने भारत सरकार के रुख़ को कहा- लापरवाह, बढ़ा विवाद","Former Japanese minister called Indian government's attitude careless, controversy increased",0.0,neutral,"[('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,आज़म ख़ान: जौहर यूनिवर्सिटी को गिराने के फ़ैसले के पीछे प्रशासन क्या कारण बता रहा है?,Azam Khan: What reason is the administration giving behind the decision to demolish Johar University?,0.0,neutral,"[('Azam Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Johar University', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"गैरी सोबर्स: 12 उंगलियां, एक ओवर में छह छक्के और 365 रन की पारी को कौन भूल सकता है","Gary Sobers: Who can forget 12 fingers, six sixes in an over and an inning of 365 runs",0.0,neutral,"[('Gary Sobers', 'PERSON'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('365', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"विक्रम वन: भारत का पहला प्राइवेट ऑर्बिटल रॉकेट की लॉन्चिंग सफल, क्या है ख़ासियत","Vikram One: Launch of India's first private orbital rocket successful, what is the specialty",1.0,positive,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"मेसी, माराडोना या पेले: आख़िर कौन है फ़ुटबॉल का सबसे महान खिलाड़ी","Messi, Maradona or Pele: Who is the greatest football player?",1.0,positive,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Maradona', 'PERSON'), ('Pele', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बीबीसी हिन्दी का नया ऐप, ऐसे करें डाउनलोड","BBC Hindi's new app, download it like this",0.0,neutral,"[(""BBC Hindi's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"A religião por trás da Korin, pioneira na produção de frango orgânico no Brasil","The religion behind Korin, a pioneer in organic chicken production in Brazil",0.0,neutral,"[('Korin', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Brasil tem de parar de se gabar' no futebol e 'descer do salto', diz biógrafo escocês de Pelé","'Brazil has to stop boasting' about football and 'get off the ground', says Pelé's Scottish biographer",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Pelé', 'PERSON'), ('Scottish', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As polêmicas do árbitro que vai apitar a final da Copa do Mundo 2026,The controversies of the referee who will referee the 2026 World Cup final,0.0,neutral,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Às vezes não sei como ajudá-lo': como diagnóstico de autismo do filho mudou a vida de Cucurella, da seleção espanhola","'Sometimes I don't know how to help him': how his son's autism diagnosis changed the life of Cucurella, from the Spanish national team",0.0,neutral,"[('Cucurella', 'PERSON'), ('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A história por trás da famosa foto de Messi banhando Lamine Yamal contada pelo fotógrafo que a fez: 'É como fechar um círculo perfeito',The story behind the famous photo of Messi bathing Lamine Yamal told by the photographer who took it: 'It's like closing a perfect circle',0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Lamine Yamal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O ranking das melhores finais da Copa do Mundo de todos os tempos,Ranking the best World Cup finals of all time,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Espanha x Argentina: data, horário, estádio e tudo sobre o jogo da final da Copa do Mundo 2026","Spain x Argentina: date, time, stadium and everything about the 2026 World Cup final game",0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As pessoas com tipo raro de nanismo que podem guardar 'segredo' contra câncer e diabetes: 'Vivemos em um mundo de gigantes',People with a rare type of dwarfism who can keep a 'secret' against cancer and diabetes: 'We live in a world of giants',-1.0,negative,"[('giants', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Literatura é também uma forma de vingança', diz Milton Hatoum sobre trilogia ambientada na ditadura","'Literature is also a form of revenge', says Milton Hatoum about the trilogy set during the dictatorship",0.0,neutral,"[('Milton Hatoum', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Com novo tarifaço de Trump e déficit fiscal crescente, Brasil chega à eleição mais importante do mundo em 2026 sem margem para erro, diz analista","With Trump's new tariff and growing fiscal deficit, Brazil reaches the most important election in the world in 2026 with no margin for error, says analyst",1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Дроны атаковали склады Wildberries в Тамбовской и Московской областях. Семь человек погибли, почти 50 пострадали","Drones attacked Wildberries warehouses in the Tambov and Moscow regions. Seven people died, almost 50 were injured",-1.0,negative,"[('Tambov', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('almost 50', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: беспилотники атаковали склады Wildberries в Тамбовской и Московской областях, погибли семь человек","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: drones attacked Wildberries warehouses in the Tambov and Moscow regions, killing seven people",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Tambov', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Обнуление срока Токаева: зачем Казахстану новая конституция и вице-президент,Resetting Tokayev's term: why does Kazakhstan need a new constitution and vice president,0.0,neutral,"[(""Resetting Tokayev's"", 'PERSON'), ('Kazakhstan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,США и Иран снова обменялись ударами. Это уже седьмая подряд ночь атак,The US and Iran exchanged blows again. This is the seventh consecutive night of attacks.,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('seventh', 'ORDINAL'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Китайский стартап Moonshot выпускает новую ИИ-модель. Он утверждает, что Kimi K3 не уступает американским аналогам",Chinese startup Moonshot releases a new AI model. He claims that the Kimi K3 is not inferior to its American counterparts,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Moonshot', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Ученые впервые обнаружили похожую на Землю планету с атмосферой. Это дает надежду на существование внеземной жизни,Scientists have discovered for the first time an Earth-like planet with an atmosphere. This gives hope for the existence of extraterrestrial life,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Суд арестовал провластного блогера Илью Ремесло по делу о «фейках» после «манифеста» против Путина,The court arrested pro-government blogger Ilya Remeslo in the case of “fake news” after the “manifesto” against Putin,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Депутата Бундестага призывают уйти в отставку из-за рождения сына с помощью суррогатной матери,Bundestag member called on to resign over son's birth via surrogate,0.0,neutral,"[('Bundestag', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зеленский назначает нового секретаря СНБО — Клименко из МВД. Что будет с Умеровым?,Zelensky appoints a new secretary of the National Security and Defense Council - Klimenko from the Ministry of Internal Affairs. What will happen to Umerov?,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('the National Security and Defense Council - Klimenko', 'ORG'), ('the Ministry of Internal Affairs', 'ORG'), ('Umerov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Финансовые итоги чемпионата мира по футболу: кто выиграл и кто в минусе,Financial results of the World Cup: who won and who lost,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,カナダの大規模な山火事でアメリカにも煙、トランプ氏は追加関税を主張,"Massive wildfires in Canada cause smoke in the US, Trump calls for additional tariffs",0.0,neutral,"[('Canada', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,遠い恒星の地球型惑星で大気を初確認、生命居住可能領域の内側,"Atmosphere detected for the first time on a terrestrial planet from a distant star, inside the habitable zone",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏のSNS運営会社、「市場を動かす」投稿への高速アクセスを有料販売へ,Trump's social media company to sell high-speed access to 'market-moving' posts for a fee,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英労働党、新党首にバーナム氏を任命　週明けに首相に就任し政権発足へ,British Labor Party appoints Burnham as new leader; Prime Minister to take office at the beginning of next week and form government,0.0,neutral,"[('British Labor Party', 'ORG'), ('Burnham', 'GPE'), ('the beginning of next week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 バーナム氏の政策について分かっていること　週明けに新たな英首相に,[Commentary] What we know about Mr. Burnham's policies: The new British Prime Minister will be appointed at the beginning of this week,0.0,neutral,"[('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('the beginning of this week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,メキシコ沖でM7.3の地震、一時津波警報も,"M7.3 earthquake off the coast of Mexico, temporary tsunami warning issued",-1.0,negative,"[('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,日本、皇位継承の規定を緩める　女性天皇を認めないことは変わらず,Japan loosens rules on succession to the imperial throne; continues to not allow female emperors,1.0,positive,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、米選挙システムに「衝撃的な脆弱性」あると主張　中間選挙を控え,Trump claims 'shocking vulnerabilities' in US election system ahead of midterm elections,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 FIFA、アルゼンチン代表の横断幕について「報告書を精査中」　フォークランド諸島領有権を主張,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] FIFA is ``examining the report'' regarding Argentina national team's banner, claiming sovereignty over the Falkland Islands",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the Falkland Islands', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゼレンスキー氏、ウクライナで高い支持のフェドロフ国防相を更迭　各地で抗議広がる,"Zelenskiy dismisses Defense Minister Fedorov, who has high support in Ukraine, sparking protests across the country",0.0,neutral,"[('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Fedorov', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yaishambulia Iran kwa usiku wa saba mfululizo","Directly, the United States attacked Iran for the seventh night in a row",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the seventh night', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Faida sita za swala kwa afya ya binadamu,Six benefits of antelope for human health,0.0,neutral,"[('Six', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Nyambizi ya nyuklia iliyozama 1989, ni bomu linalosubiri kulipuka",The nuclear submarine sunk in 1989 is a bomb waiting to explode,0.0,neutral,"[('1989', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nani mkali kati ya Messi na Maradona?,Who is stronger between Messi and Maradona?,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Maradona', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Jumamosi: Arsenal wanamtaka Rogers wa Villa,Saturday Football Rumours: Arsenal want Villa's Rogers,0.0,neutral,"[(""Villa's Rogers"", 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Freemasons waelezea taratibu zao na faida za kuwa mwanachama,The Freemasons explain their procedures and the benefits of being a member,0.0,neutral,"[('Freemasons', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwanini homoni ya testosterone ni kigezo cha kuwa mwanajeshi Marekani?,Why testosterone hormone is a criterion to be a soldier in the United States?,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ni klabu zipi za Ligi Kuu zimeathiriwa zaidi na Kombe la Dunia?,Which Premier League clubs have been most affected by the World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Dhana potofu wanazouziwa wanaume wanaojaribu kuongeza idadi ya mbegu za kiume,Misconceptions sold to men trying to increase their sperm count,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini dunia inazidi kupendelea China kuliko Marekani?,Why is the world increasingly favoring China over the United States?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Does Spain or Argentina’s form guide point to World Cup final glory?,Does Spain or Argentina’s form guide point to World Cup final glory?,0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,From France vs England to Messi vs Yamal: World Cup final weekend,From France vs England to Messi vs Yamal: World Cup final weekend,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel’s ‘Crimson Thread’ military barrier is strangling the West Bank,Israel’s ‘Crimson Thread’ military barrier is strangling the West Bank,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Crimson Thread', 'PERSON'), ('the West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Tuchel: England carry ‘scars’ of World Cup heartbreak,Tuchel: England carry ‘scars’ of World Cup heartbreak,0.0,neutral,"[('Tuchel', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Messi reflects on pressure and competition ahead of World Cup final,Messi reflects on pressure and competition ahead of World Cup final,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Mandela Day: What his legacy means in today’s South Africa,Mandela Day: What his legacy means in today’s South Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('Mandela Day', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Manila protests ‘racist’ portrayal of Filipinos in China Daily videos,Manila protests ‘racist’ portrayal of Filipinos in China Daily videos,0.0,neutral,"[('Manila', 'GPE'), ('Filipinos', 'NORP'), ('China Daily', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,At least 14 dead after minibus rolls off mountain road in Peru,At least 14 dead after minibus rolls off mountain road in Peru,0.0,neutral,"[('At least 14', 'CARDINAL'), ('minibus', 'ORG'), ('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"In New York’s ‘Little Palestine’, fans cheer for Spain in World Cup final","In New York’s ‘Little Palestine’, fans cheer for Spain in World Cup final",0.0,neutral,"[('New York’s ‘', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Israeli army destroys three schools in southern Lebanon, minister says","Israeli army destroys three schools in southern Lebanon, minister says",0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"New Delhi DCP’s office on Saturday (July 18, 2026) said that Sonam Wangchuk has been shifted to the hospital for ‘essential medical care’ as per the orders of the Delhi High Court and on expert medical advice due to his deteriorating health condition.","New Delhi DCP’s office on Saturday (July 18, 2026) said that Sonam Wangchuk has been shifted to the hospital for ‘essential medical care’ as per the orders of the Delhi High Court and on expert medical advice due to his deteriorating health condition.",0.0,neutral,"[('New Delhi', 'GPE'), ('DCP', 'ORG'), ('Saturday (July 18, 2026', 'DATE'), ('Sonam Wangchuk', 'PERSON'), ('the Delhi High Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,What prolonged fasting can do to the human body | Explained,What prolonged fasting can do to the human body | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Nothing should be administered to Sonam Wangchuk without my consent, says wife Gitanjali Angmo","Nothing should be administered to Sonam Wangchuk without my consent, says wife Gitanjali Angmo",0.0,neutral,"[('Sonam Wangchuk', 'LOC'), ('Gitanjali Angmo', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,M.A. Baby condemns removal of activist Sonam Wangchuk from Jantar Mantar protest site,M.A. Baby condemns removal of activist Sonam Wangchuk from Jantar Mantar protest site,0.0,neutral,"[('M.A. Baby', 'PERSON'), ('Sonam Wangchuk', 'PERSON'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Delimitation not just an INDIA bloc issue, concerns our Constitutional framework: Venugopal","Delimitation not just an INDIA bloc issue, concerns our Constitutional framework: Venugopal",0.0,neutral,"[('Constitutional', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Vikram-1, country’s first private orbital-class rocket, successfully places tech payloads, postcards into orbit","Vikram-1, country’s first private orbital-class rocket, successfully places tech payloads, postcards into orbit",1.0,positive,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia war LIVE: Iran claims strikes on U.S. targets in Kuwait, Jordan","West Asia war LIVE: Iran claims strikes on U.S. targets in Kuwait, Jordan",-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Jordan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why is ISRO making it harder for scientists to resign? | Explained,Why is ISRO making it harder for scientists to resign? | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Ram temple donation theft: Police take custody of Tinnu, nephew Manish Yadav","Ram temple donation theft: Police take custody of Tinnu, nephew Manish Yadav",0.0,neutral,"[('Tinnu', 'ORG'), ('Manish Yadav', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"CJP protesters claim police crackdown, say they are denied access to activist Sonam Wangchuk","CJP protesters claim police crackdown, say they are denied access to activist Sonam Wangchuk",0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Sonam Wangchuk', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US strikes hit Iran for seventh consecutive night,US strikes hit Iran for seventh consecutive night,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('seventh', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump threatens new Canada tariffs over fires sending 'filthy' air into US cities,Trump threatens new Canada tariffs over fires sending 'filthy' air into US cities,0.0,neutral,"[('Canada', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Many Ukrainian soldiers outraged over removal of defence minister, troops tell BBC","Many Ukrainian soldiers outraged over removal of defence minister, troops tell BBC",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Space start-up launches India’s first commercial rocket designed for orbit,Space start-up launches India’s first commercial rocket designed for orbit,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,White House defends Argentina team over Falklands banner,White House defends Argentina team over Falklands banner,0.0,neutral,"[('White House', 'ORG'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Falklands', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"One anti-war critic fined, another held as Russia clamps down on dissent","One anti-war critic fined, another held as Russia clamps down on dissent",-1.0,negative,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Indian activist on hunger strike for 20 days forcibly taken to hospital,Indian activist on hunger strike for 20 days forcibly taken to hospital,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('20 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,EU proposes slowing down cuts to carbon emissions for businesses,EU proposes slowing down cuts to carbon emissions for businesses,1.0,positive,"[('EU', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Magnitude 7.3 earthquake quake strikes off Mexico coast,Magnitude 7.3 earthquake quake strikes off Mexico coast,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Air conditioner sparked deadly blaze at children's orphanage - police,Air conditioner sparked deadly blaze at children's orphanage - police,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Trump Scraps With Meloni, His Envoy to Italy Is at Sea","As Trump Scraps With Meloni, His Envoy to Italy Is at Sea",0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,They Called Sam Neill ‘Skux.’ (It Was a Compliment.),They Called Sam Neill ‘Skux.’ (It Was a Compliment.),0.0,neutral,"[('Sam Neill ‘Skux', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Updates: Bridges and Water Plants Hit as Strikes Stretch to 7th Straight Day,Iran War Updates: Bridges and Water Plants Hit as Strikes Stretch to 7th Straight Day,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Updates', 'EVENT'), ('Bridges', 'PERSON'), ('Strikes Stretch', 'PERSON'), ('7th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Straight Day', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Burnham Becomes Labour Leader and Britain’s Incoming Prime Minister,Burnham Becomes Labour Leader and Britain’s Incoming Prime Minister,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The 20-Somethings Running Ukraine’s War Machine,The 20-Somethings Running Ukraine’s War Machine,-1.0,negative,"[('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"‘Suddenly, I Was Free’: A Chinese Pastor’s Journey From Jail to the U.S.","‘Suddenly, I Was Free’: A Chinese Pastor’s Journey From Jail to the U.S.",0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Israeli Strike in Gaza Kills Seven People, Health Officials Say","Israeli Strike in Gaza Kills Seven People, Health Officials Say",-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Seven', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Prominent Cuban Artist Will Go Into Exile After 5-Year Prison Term,Prominent Cuban Artist Will Go Into Exile After 5-Year Prison Term,0.0,neutral,"[('Cuban', 'NORP'), ('5-Year', 'DATE'), ('Prison Term', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"How Andy Burnham, ‘King of the North,’ Conquered U.K. Politics","How Andy Burnham, ‘King of the North,’ Conquered U.K. Politics",0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Beijing Rejects Trump’s Claim of Meddling, but Avoids a Fight","Beijing Rejects Trump’s Claim of Meddling, but Avoids a Fight",0.0,neutral,"[('Beijing Rejects Trump’s Claim of Meddling', 'ORG')]"
