Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El Mundial ""más caro y más politizado"": 4 claves del conflictivo megatorneo en Norteamérica","The ""most expensive and most politicized"" World Cup: 4 keys to the conflictive megatournament in North America",-1.0,negative,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('North America', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Estados Unidos e Irán intercambian ataques en Medio Oriente por segundo día consecutivo,The United States and Iran exchange attacks in the Middle East for the second day in a row,-1.0,negative,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('the second day in a row', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Han hecho lo que han querido con nosotros porque somos pobres"": el pueblo de Perú al que el Vaticano pidió perdón de rodillas por el despojo de tierras atribuido al Sodalicio","""They have done what they wanted with us because we are poor"": the people of Peru to whom the Vatican asked for forgiveness on their knees for the dispossession of land attributed to the Sodalicio",0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('Sodalicio', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Un escenario apocalíptico"": el brutal ataque con cuchillo a un hombre que desató violentas protestas en Belfast","""An apocalyptic scenario"": the brutal knife attack on a man that sparked violent protests in Belfast",-1.0,negative,"[('Belfast', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Tinder para esperma"": cómo funciona el mercado ilegal de semen en el que se engaña a mujeres vulnerables que desean quedar embarazadas","""Tinder for sperm"": how the illegal semen market works in which vulnerable women who want to get pregnant are deceived",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo los manglares en el mundo se están recuperando luego de décadas de destrucción por parte de los humanos,How the world's mangroves are recovering after decades of destruction by humans,0.0,neutral,"[('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Matan a 5 policías en Michoacán en vísperas de la inauguración del Mundial en México,They kill 5 police officers in Michoacán on the eve of the opening of the World Cup in Mexico,-1.0,negative,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Michoacán', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Bill Gates dice que Epstein intentó utilizar sus relaciones extramaritales para presionarlo, pero que no lo permitió","Bill Gates says Epstein tried to use extramarital affairs to pressure him, but he wouldn't let it",0.0,neutral,"[('Bill Gates', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Como un episodio sin gracia de Expedientes Secretos X"": la dura crítica de la BBC de ""El día de la revelación"", la nueva película de Steven Spielberg","""Like an unfunny episode of The X-Files"": the BBC's harsh criticism of ""The Day of Revelation"", Steven Spielberg's new film",0.0,neutral,"[('The X-Files', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('The Day of Revelation', 'WORK_OF_ART'), (""Steven Spielberg's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo gana la FIFA miles de millones de dólares con cada Mundial y por qué las entradas son cada vez más importantes para sus ingresos,How FIFA makes billions of dollars with each World Cup and why tickets are increasingly important to its income,0.0,neutral,"[('billions of dollars', 'MONEY'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,12 साल की बच्ची बनकर 14 महीने तक 37 साल की महिला ने कैसे दिया सबको धोखा,How a 37 year old woman deceived everyone by pretending to be a 12 year old girl for 14 months,0.0,neutral,"[('37 year old', 'DATE'), ('12 year old', 'DATE'), ('14 months', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"न्यूज़क्लिक मामले में एफ़आईआर और ईडी जांच रद्द, दिल्ली हाई कोर्ट ने अपने आदेश में और क्या-क्या कहा","FIR and ED investigation canceled in Newsclick case, what else did Delhi High Court say in its order",0.0,neutral,"[('FIR', 'ORG'), ('ED', 'ORG'), ('Newsclick', 'GPE'), ('Delhi High Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,टीएमसी छोड़ने की चर्चाओं पर क्या बोले राज्यसभा सांसद बाबुल सुप्रियो?","Live, what did Rajya Sabha MP Babul Supriyo say on the discussions of leaving TMC?",0.0,neutral,"[('Rajya Sabha', 'ORG'), ('Babul Supriyo', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"जब भारतीय फ़ुटबॉल टीम को मिला था वर्ल्ड कप में हिस्सा लेने का मौक़ा, लेकिन क्यों नहीं खेली टीम","When the Indian football team got a chance to participate in the World Cup, but why did the team not play?",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ओमान के निकट अमेरिकी मिसाइल हमले में तीन भारतीय नाविकों की मौत,Three Indian sailors killed in US missile attack near Oman,-1.0,negative,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Oman', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,कांग्रेस और टीएमसी के विलय की चर्चाओं पर क्या कह रहे हैं राजनीतिक विश्लेषक,What are political analysts saying on the discussions of merger of Congress and TMC?,0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('TMC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"तुर्की के गृह मंत्री ने कहा था- इंशाअल्लाह  यरूशलम भी मुक्त होगा, अब भिड़े अर्दोआन और नेतन्याहू","Türkiye's Home Minister had said - Inshallah Jerusalem will also be free, now Erdogan and Netanyahu clash",0.0,neutral,"[('Türkiye', 'GPE'), ('Inshallah Jerusalem', 'PERSON'), ('Erdogan', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,तृणमूल कांग्रेस और उसके चुनाव चिह्न से ममता बनर्जी क्या नियंत्रण खो सकती हैं? जानिए वजहें,Can Mamata Banerjee lose control over Trinamool Congress and its election symbol? Know the reasons,0.0,neutral,"[('Trinamool Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका ने कहा- ईरान पर जवाबी हमला पूरा हुआ, तेहरान ने कहा, होर्मुज़ स्ट्रेट सभी के लिए बंद","America said- retaliatory attack on Iran completed, Tehran said, Hormuz Strait closed for all",-1.0,negative,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz Strait', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान पर ट्रंप और नेतन्याहू की रणनीति क्यों नाकाम होती दिख रही है?,Why does Trump and Netanyahu's strategy on Iran seem to be failing?,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Desserviço ao feminismo': criadora da Lei Maria da Penha critica 'perdão' à mãe de Henry Borel,'Disservice to feminism': creator of the Maria da Penha Law criticizes 'forgiveness' to Henry Borel's mother,0.0,neutral,"[('Disservice', 'ORG'), (""Henry Borel's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Tudo que você precisa saber para conversar sobre a Copa do Mundo – mesmo sem gostar de futebol,Everything you need to know to talk about the World Cup – even if you don't like football,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Eleições no Peru: com mais de 98% de urnas apuradas, Keiko Fujimori volta a liderar por menos de mil votos","Elections in Peru: with more than 98% of ballots counted, Keiko Fujimori leads again by less than a thousand votes",0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('more than 98%', 'PERCENT'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('less than a thousand', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que Bill Gates disse sobre relação com Jeffrey Epstein em investigação do Congresso dos EUA,What Bill Gates said about his relationship with Jeffrey Epstein in an investigation by the US Congress,0.0,neutral,"[('Bill Gates', 'PERSON'), ('Jeffrey Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Eu amo a inflação', diz Trump, enquanto preços nos EUA sobem no ritmo mais acelerado em 3 anos","'I love inflation,' says Trump, as US prices rise at fastest pace in 3 years",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('3 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,EUA e Irã trocam ataques pelo 2º dia seguido em meio a frágil cessar-fogo,US and Iran exchange attacks for the second day in a row amid fragile ceasefire,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the second day in a row', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"De Pelé à 'Mão de Deus': a história do Azteca, o único estádio a sediar três Copas do Mundo","From Pelé to the 'Hand of God': the story of Azteca, the only stadium to host three World Cups",0.0,neutral,"[('Azteca', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cups', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Com Anitta e Shakira, como serão as três cerimônias de abertura da Copa — e os detalhes dos jogos do maior Mundial da história","With Anitta and Shakira, what the three opening ceremonies of the World Cup will be like — and the details of the games of the biggest World Cup in history",0.0,neutral,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Formato de ferradura, 'Estrela da Morte' e cachorro-quente a R$ 10: os segredos dos 16 estádios da Copa do Mundo","Horseshoe shape, 'Death Star' and R$10 hot dog: the secrets of the 16 World Cup stadiums",-1.0,negative,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Министр обороны Великобритании Джон Хили ушел в отставку из‑за недовольства военным бюджетом,British Defense Secretary John Healey resigned due to dissatisfaction with the military budget,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('John Healey', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: дроны атаковали Афипский НПЗ, при атаке беспилотников в Краснодаре пострадали два человека","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: drones attacked the Afipsky oil refinery; two people were injured in a drone attack in Krasnodar",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Afipsky', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Krasnodar', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Во вторую ночь беспорядков в Северной Ирландии пострадали 12 полицейских,12 police officers injured on second night of riots in Northern Ireland,0.0,neutral,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('second night', 'TIME'), ('Northern Ireland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Смертный приговор за самое кровавое нападение в истории Таиланда. Виновными признаны уйгуры, в деле было множество нестыковок","Death sentence for the deadliest attack in Thai history. Uighurs were found guilty, there were many inconsistencies in the case",-1.0,negative,"[('Thai', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Война в Иране: военные США обстреляли танкер, погибли три моряка из Индии; Вашингтон и Тегеран снова обменялись ударами","War in Iran: US military fired at a tanker, killing three sailors from India; Washington and Tehran exchange blows again",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Но что, если выиграем?!» Журналисты Би-би-си — об ожиданиях от чемпионата мира по футболу в своих странах",“But what if we win?!” BBC journalists talk about expectations from the World Cup in their countries,1.0,positive,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Бензин по QR-коду, гречка про запас. Как аннексированный Крым переживает блокаду?","Gasoline by QR code, buckwheat in reserve. How is annexed Crimea surviving the blockade?",0.0,neutral,"[('Crimea', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Папа Лев освятил башню Иисуса Христа в барселонском храме Святого Семейства ровно через 100 лет после смерти Гауди — фотографии,Pope Leo consecrated the Tower of Jesus Christ in Barcelona's Sagrada Familia exactly 100 years after Gaudi's death - photos,-1.0,negative,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('the Tower of Jesus Christ', 'FAC'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('Sagrada Familia', 'GPE'), ('100 years', 'DATE'), ('Gaudi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Поклонники Пикачу и Наруто против Трампа. Японцев возмутила эксплуатация президентом США образов из анимэ,Pikachu and Naruto fans against Trump. The Japanese were outraged by the US President's exploitation of images from anime,0.0,neutral,"[('Pikachu', 'GPE'), ('Naruto', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Почему у Венесуэлы был обогащенный уран — и зачем его тайно перевезли в США этой весной?,Why did Venezuela have enriched uranium - and why was it secretly transported to the US this spring?,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('this spring', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米国がイランに新たな攻撃　イランはホルムズ海峡で船舶を攻撃と発表,US launches new attack on Iran; Iran announces attack on ship in Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,【検証】 北アイルランドで暴力と混乱　ベルファストでの刺傷事件きっかけに, 所要時間 2,15","Video, [Verification] Violence and chaos in Northern Ireland triggered by stabbing incident in Belfast, Duration 2.15",0.0,neutral,"[('Northern Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Belfast', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米軍、オマーン湾でタンカーを攻撃と発表　インド人船員3人が行方不明,US military announces attack on tanker in Gulf of Oman; 3 Indian sailors missing,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC'), ('Oman', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏「インフレが大好きだ」と発言　米消費者物価は3年ぶりの高い伸び,"Trump says, ``I love inflation'' US consumer prices rise at the highest rate in three years",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('three years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 優勝候補は？　興味深い対戦は？　今大会の特色を解説,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Who are the winning candidates? Any interesting matchups? Explaining the characteristics of this tournament,1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 FIFAは主導権を失ったのか　ソマリア人審判の入国拒否で浮かび上がる問題,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Has FIFA lost its initiative? Issues raised by Somali referee's immigration refusal,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('Somali', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、ロシア深部の軍需工場をミサイル攻撃,Ukraine launches missile attack on military factory deep in Russia,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 誰のためのW杯か……米政府の入国禁止とビザ制限にファンの怒り,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Who is the World Cup for? Fans angered by US government's entry ban and visa restrictions,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゲイツ氏、エプスティーン元被告から個人的な交流を求められるも「決して応じなかった」　米下院監視委で証言,"Gates ``never responded'' to Epstein's request for personal contact, testifies before U.S. House Oversight Committee",0.0,neutral,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('U.S. House Oversight Committee', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,「ナルト」や「遊戯王」、「ポケモン」も……日本発のキャラクターをトランプ氏がSNS投稿に使用、反発高まる,"``Naruto'', ``Yu-Gi-Oh'', and ``Pokemon''... Trump uses characters from Japan in SNS posts, causing backlash",0.0,neutral,"[('Naruto', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Pokemon', 'PRODUCT'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('SNS', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Meli ya tatu ya mafuta yashambuliwa karibu na Oman","Directly, a third oil tanker was attacked near Oman",-1.0,negative,"[('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Oman', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Wachezaji 10 wenye asili ya Afrika wanaopeperusha bendera za Ulaya,World Cup 2026: 10 players of African origin flying European flags,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Bowen: Trump na Netanyahu walitaka kubadilisha mwelekeo wa Mashariki ya Kati - sasa wanakabiliwa na tishio,Bowen: Trump and Netanyahu wanted to change the direction of the Middle East - now they face a threat,0.0,neutral,"[('Bowen', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"'Ndoa ya pamoja' ilivyotibuka: Mabwana harusi 42 walifika, mabibi harusi hawakujitokeza","The 'joint marriage' was cured: 42 grooms showed up, the brides didn't show up",0.0,neutral,"[('42', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Siku ya Bajeti Afrika Mashariki: Bajeti ‘ya kipekee’ Tanzania,East Africa Budget Day: Tanzania's 'unique' budget,0.0,neutral,"[('East Africa Budget Day', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tikiti maji lina nguvu sawa na Viagra - Utafiti,Watermelon Is As Powerful As Viagra - Research,0.0,neutral,"[('Viagra - Research', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Alhamisi:Arsenal yamuwinda Williams,Football rumors Thursday: Arsenal chasing Williams,0.0,neutral,"[('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Williams', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Mwanasesere Natasha afufua mjadala wa dhulma mitandaoni, ni ubaguzi au burudani?","The doll Natasha revives the discussion of injustice on the internet, is it discrimination or entertainment?",0.0,neutral,"[('Natasha', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Trump: Tuliwashambulia Iran vikali na tutawashambulia tena leo,Trump: We attacked Iran very hard and we will attack them again today,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia kuanza leo, lini nchi ya Afrika itaibuka mshindi?","The World Cup starts today, when will an African country emerge victorious?",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Britain’s defence ⁠minister Healey quits over defence spending,Britain’s defence ⁠minister Healey quits over defence spending,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Healey', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Detained Gaza doctor Hussam Abu Safia shows signs of torture, family says","Detained Gaza doctor Hussam Abu Safia shows signs of torture, family says",0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Hussam Abu Safia', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Azteca: The World Cup’s most storied stadium prepares for latest chapter,Azteca: The World Cup’s most storied stadium prepares for latest chapter,0.0,neutral,"[('The World Cup’s', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Three Indian sailors killed in US strike on oil tanker,Three Indian sailors killed in US strike on oil tanker,-1.0,negative,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World celebrates, but Gaza watches the World Cup from a distance","World celebrates, but Gaza watches the World Cup from a distance",0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup Day 1: The games, predictions, stories shaping the tournament","World Cup Day 1: The games, predictions, stories shaping the tournament",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day 1', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"UK, Australia, Canada launch $4m peace fund for Israel-Palestine conflict","UK, Australia, Canada launch $4m peace fund for Israel-Palestine conflict",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('4', 'MONEY'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Czechia look to upset Son Heung-min’s South Korea in tough World Cup opener,Czechia look to upset Son Heung-min’s South Korea in tough World Cup opener,0.0,neutral,"[('Son Heung-min’s', 'PERSON'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Photos: Belfast police fire water cannon at anti-immigration protests,Photos: Belfast police fire water cannon at anti-immigration protests,0.0,neutral,"[('Belfast', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Thousands of Malawians flee homes in South Africa amid xenophobic threats,Thousands of Malawians flee homes in South Africa amid xenophobic threats,0.0,neutral,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Malawians', 'NORP'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"CPI not part of DMK alliance in Tamil Nadu, says Veerapandian","CPI not part of DMK alliance in Tamil Nadu, says Veerapandian",0.0,neutral,"[('DMK', 'ORG'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'FAC'), ('Veerapandian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Shatrughan Sinha vouches support for Mamata Banerjee amid allegations of joining rebel group of TMC,Shatrughan Sinha vouches support for Mamata Banerjee amid allegations of joining rebel group of TMC,0.0,neutral,"[('Shatrughan Sinha vouches', 'ORG'), ('Mamata Banerjee', 'ORG'), ('TMC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Canada introduces Bill to restrict social media access for under-16s,Canada introduces Bill to restrict social media access for under-16s,0.0,neutral,"[('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Bill', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Delhi High Court quashes Newsclick FIR, ED money laundering case","Delhi High Court quashes Newsclick FIR, ED money laundering case",0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi High Court', 'PERSON'), ('Newsclick FIR', 'PERSON'), ('ED', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Higher ethanol blended petrol between 22-30% exempted from central excise duty,Higher ethanol blended petrol between 22-30% exempted from central excise duty,0.0,neutral,"[('22-30%', 'PERCENT')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why TVK is eager to woo AIADMK cadre,Why TVK is eager to woo AIADMK cadre,0.0,neutral,"[('TVK', 'ORG'), ('AIADMK', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Signature forgery case: Court directs Abhishek Banerjee to appear before CID,Signature forgery case: Court directs Abhishek Banerjee to appear before CID,0.0,neutral,"[('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON'), ('CID', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"First in six decades, India-born Nikhil Chaudhary added to Australia's T20 squad","First in six decades, India-born Nikhil Chaudhary added to Australia's T20 squad",0.0,neutral,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('six decades', 'DATE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Nikhil Chaudhary', 'ORG'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('T20', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Foreseeable accidents: On the recent industrial accidents in India,​Foreseeable accidents: On the recent industrial accidents in India,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Sport during a war: On the FIFA World Cup 2026,​Sport during a war: On the FIFA World Cup 2026,-1.0,negative,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US and Iran exchange strikes across Middle East for second day in a row,US and Iran exchange strikes across Middle East for second day in a row,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Middle East', 'LOC'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump says 'I love the inflation' as US prices rise at fastest rate in three years,Trump says 'I love the inflation' as US prices rise at fastest rate in three years,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('three years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,The furious dispute over what caused Air India flight 171 to crash,The furious dispute over what caused Air India flight 171 to crash,0.0,neutral,"[('Air India', 'ORG'), ('171', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Thai court sentences two men to death over Bangkok shrine bombing,Thai court sentences two men to death over Bangkok shrine bombing,-1.0,negative,"[('Thai', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bangkok', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Vance says Israeli PM Netanyahu 'has got some things wrong',Vance says Israeli PM Netanyahu 'has got some things wrong',0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Four days of extreme rain killed 7% of world's rarest orangutans, study says","Four days of extreme rain killed 7% of world's rarest orangutans, study says",-1.0,negative,"[('Four days', 'DATE'), ('7%', 'PERCENT')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Knicks fans go wild as New York team makes biggest comeback in NBA Finals history,Knicks fans go wild as New York team makes biggest comeback in NBA Finals history,0.0,neutral,"[('Knicks', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Pope Leo visits Canary Islands to highlight perilous journeys of migrants,Pope Leo visits Canary Islands to highlight perilous journeys of migrants,0.0,neutral,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Canary Islands', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Olivia Rodrigo sings about heartbreak but she's already chosen her wedding song,Olivia Rodrigo sings about heartbreak but she's already chosen her wedding song,0.0,neutral,"[('Olivia Rodrigo', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nigeria evacuates citizens from South Africa as anti-migrant sentiment rises,Nigeria evacuates citizens from South Africa as anti-migrant sentiment rises,0.0,neutral,"[('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: U.S.-Iran Strikes Risk Dangerous New Phase,Iran War Live Updates: U.S.-Iran Strikes Risk Dangerous New Phase,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Women Who Fled Iran Are to Be Deported to Central African Republic, Lawyers Say","Women Who Fled Iran Are to Be Deported to Central African Republic, Lawyers Say",0.0,neutral,"[('Central African', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"U.K. Defense Secretary Resigns, in a Blow to Starmer","U.K. Defense Secretary Resigns, in a Blow to Starmer",0.0,neutral,"[('U.K.', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Resigns', 'PERSON'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Fractured North America Begins a Historic World Cup,A Fractured North America Begins a Historic World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Fractured North America Begins', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The War in Ukraine Has Now Gone On Longer Than World War I,The War in Ukraine Has Now Gone On Longer Than World War I,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Protests Threaten to Disrupt Mexico City’s World Cup Opening Ceremony,Protests Threaten to Disrupt Mexico City’s World Cup Opening Ceremony,0.0,neutral,"[('Threaten', 'PERSON'), ('Disrupt Mexico City’s', 'GPE'), ('World Cup Opening Ceremony', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Why Mexico’s President Will Not Attend the World Cup Opening Match,Why Mexico’s President Will Not Attend the World Cup Opening Match,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Will Not', 'PERSON'), ('the World Cup Opening Match', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In a Trump-Endorsed Presidential Candidate, Colombia’s Women See a Familiar Far-Right Playbook","In a Trump-Endorsed Presidential Candidate, Colombia’s Women See a Familiar Far-Right Playbook",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump-Endorsed Presidential Candidate', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A.I. and the Chip Boom: Take a Quiz on New Korean Slang and Memes,A.I. and the Chip Boom: Take a Quiz on New Korean Slang and Memes,0.0,neutral,"[('A.I.', 'ORG'), ('the Chip Boom: Take a Quiz', 'ORG'), ('New Korean Slang', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘Amazon.com of South Korea’ Is Fined a Record $409 Million,‘Amazon.com of South Korea’ Is Fined a Record $409 Million,0.0,neutral,"[('Amazon.com', 'ORG'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
