Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las personas que se mudan de Occidente a Rusia en busca de valores tradicionales (y la realidad que encuentran),People who move from the West to Russia in search of traditional values ​​(and the reality they find),0.0,neutral,"[('West', 'LOC'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere a los 78 años Sam Neill, el actor que protagonizó ""Jurassic Park""","Sam Neill, the actor who starred in ""Jurassic Park,"" dies at 78",0.0,neutral,"[('Sam Neill', 'PERSON'), ('Jurassic Park', 'FAC'), ('78', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El auge de la femosfera: las mujeres que renuncian al romance y buscan hombres de ""alto valor""",The Rise of the Phemosphere: Women Giving Up Romance and Seeking 'High Value' Men,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Sintieron ""amor a primera vista"" con su bebé adoptado, pero luego les dijeron que podía ser víctima de trata de personas","They felt ""love at first sight"" with their adopted baby, but were then told he could be a victim of human trafficking",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Pasé de vivir en la calle a ser un experto en finanzas en el banco más grande de Reino Unido,I went from living on the streets to being a financial expert at the largest bank in the United Kingdom,0.0,neutral,"[('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las cosas más extrañas que interfieren con el Wi-Fi y cómo mejorar la señal,The strangest things that interfere with Wi-Fi and how to improve the signal,1.0,positive,[]
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La erupción volcánica que produjo el sonido más fuerte que se haya registrado en la historia,The volcanic eruption that produced the loudest sound ever recorded in history,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere el senador estadounidense Lindsey Graham, estrecho aliado de Trump, tras una ""breve y repentina enfermedad""","US Senator Lindsey Graham, a close ally of Trump, dies after a ""brief and sudden illness""",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La legión de latinoamericanos que reclutó Mussolini para ganar el ""Mundial del fascismo"" en 1934","The legion of Latin Americans that Mussolini recruited to win the ""World Cup of Fascism"" in 1934",1.0,positive,"[('Latin Americans', 'NORP'), ('Mussolini', 'PERSON'), ('the ""World Cup of Fascism', 'EVENT'), ('1934', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Rivales encarnizados: el esperado partido en el que Messi enfrentará por primera vez a Inglaterra,Fierce rivals: the long-awaited match in which Messi will face England for the first time,0.0,neutral,"[('Fierce', 'ORG'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पाकिस्तान के मुफ़्ती का क्रिप्टोकरेंसी के ख़िलाफ़ फ़तवा, इस एक वजह से बताया हराम","Pakistan's Mufti's fatwa against cryptocurrency, called it haram for this one reason",0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Mufti', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,चलती ट्रेन में धार्मिक अनुष्ठान का वीडियो वायरल, रेलवे ने क्या बताया","Live video of religious ritual in a moving train goes viral, what did Railways tell?",0.0,neutral,"[('Railways', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'ट्रंप को मारने' की ईरान में लगातार उठती मांग किस तरह का संकेत है?,What kind of signal is the continuously rising demand in Iran to 'kill Trump'?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वैभव सूर्यवंशी ने बताया विंबलडन फ़ाइनल देखने के लिए किसने उन्हें कपड़े दिलाए?,Vaibhav Suryavanshi told who gave him clothes to watch Wimbledon final?,0.0,neutral,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Wimbledon', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'सतलुज' की कहानी कितनी जसवंत सिंह खालड़ा की और कितनी पंजाब की?,How much of the story of 'Sutlej' is of Jaswant Singh Khalda and how much of Punjab?,0.0,neutral,"[('Jaswant Singh Khalda', 'ORG'), ('Punjab', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,यास्तिका भाटिया ने लॉर्ड्स में वो कर दिखाया जो अब तक नहीं हुआ था,Yastika Bhatia did something at Lord's which had not been done till now,0.0,neutral,"[('Yastika Bhatia', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,मुस्लिम जज को क्यों मिल रहीं जान से मारने और रेप की धमकियां?,Why is a Muslim judge receiving death and rape threats?,-1.0,negative,"[('Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिकी सीनेटर लिंडसे ग्राहम की मौत: ईरानी मीडिया क्यों मना रहा है जश्न?,Death of US Senator Lindsey Graham: Why is Iranian media celebrating?,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वैभव सूर्यवंशी और भारतीय क्रिकेट को लेकर पाकिस्तान में क्या कहा जा रहा,What is being said in Pakistan about Vaibhav Suryavanshi and Indian cricket?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भारत के कई इलाक़ों से क्यों ग़ायब हुए बादल, क्या होता है 'मानसून ब्रेक'","Why did clouds disappear from many areas of India, what is 'monsoon break'?",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Os brasileiros que processam as bets para conseguir receber seus prêmios,Brazilians who process bets to receive their prizes,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Sam Neill, ator de 'Jurassic Park', morre aos 78 anos",'Jurassic Park' actor Sam Neill dies at 78,0.0,neutral,"[('Sam Neill', 'PERSON'), ('78', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A ascensão da 'femosfera': mulheres que renunciam ao romance e buscam homens de 'alto valor',The rise of the 'femosphere': women who forgo romance and seek 'high-value' men,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o novo regime do Irã é totalmente diferente do anterior,Why Iran's new regime is totally different from the previous one,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Carta de Bolsonaro é tentativa de desviar atenção de denúncia contra Valdemar e possível vídeo de Flávio, diz cientista político","Bolsonaro's letter is an attempt to divert attention from the complaint against Valdemar and a possible video of Flávio, says political scientist",0.0,neutral,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Valdemar', 'GPE'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Fifa avalia possibilidade de Copa do Mundo com 64 seleções,FIFA evaluates the possibility of a World Cup with 64 teams,0.0,neutral,"[('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('64', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Esqueça as promessas de Ano Novo: você pode 'recomeçar' a vida a qualquer momento e mudar seus hábitos de vez,Forget about New Year's resolutions: you can 'start over' your life at any time and change your habits for good,1.0,positive,"[(""New Year's"", 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A ascensão de Bellingham: feitos do 'maestro' da Inglaterra na Copa podem torná-lo uma lenda do futebol?,The rise of Bellingham: can the achievements of England's 'maestro' in the World Cup make him a football legend?,0.0,neutral,"[('Bellingham', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Os países da África que recusam ajuda financeira de Trump,African countries that refuse financial aid from Trump,0.0,neutral,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Levamos marmita para o trabalho por 10 anos e conseguimos nos aposentar aos 35 e 40 anos','We took lunch to work for 10 years and managed to retire at 35 and 40',0.0,neutral,"[('10 years', 'DATE'), (""35 and 40'"", 'DATE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: три человека погибли в Подмосковье в результате массированной атаки дронов","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: three people died in the Moscow region as a result of a massive drone attack",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Пожар в опасной близости от Парижа: на тушение леса Фонтенбло отправлены самолеты,Fire dangerously close to Paris: planes sent to extinguish Fontainebleau forest,0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE'), ('Fontainebleau', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В результате пожара в баре в Бангкоке погибли по меньшей мере 27 человек,At least 27 people are killed in a bar fire in Bangkok.,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 27', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bangkok', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Чемпионат для всего мира». Глава ФИФА рассматривает увеличение числа участников ЧМ по футболу до 64,"""Championship for the whole world."" FIFA head is considering increasing the number of World Cup participants to 64",0.0,neutral,"[('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('64', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Очень страшно». Как Запорожье живет под ежедневными атаками России, которые резко усилились","""Very scary."" How Zaporozhye lives under daily Russian attacks, which have sharply intensified",-1.0,negative,"[('daily', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Умер сенатор Линдси Грэм, выступавший за «адские санкции» против России. За день до смерти он был в Киеве","Senator Lindsey Graham, who advocated “hellish sanctions” against Russia, has died. The day before his death he was in Kyiv",-1.0,negative,"[('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('The day', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Тираннозавр по кличке Гас может стать самым дорогим в истории. И это проблема для ученых,Tyrannosaurus named Gus may become the most expensive in history. And this is a problem for scientists,0.0,neutral,"[('Gus', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Британская полиция: ничто не указывает на политический мотив убийства Энн Уидеком,British police: nothing indicates a political motive for the murder of Ann Widecombe,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Ann Widecombe', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зеленский анонсировал отставку премьер-министра. Кто заменит Юлию Свириденко?,Zelensky announced the resignation of the prime minister. Who will replace Yulia Sviridenko?,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Yulia Sviridenko', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Почему женщины переносят жару хуже мужчин?,Why do women tolerate heat worse than men?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ軍、イラン攻撃続ける　ホルムズ海峡は開かれていると主張,"US military continues to attack Iran, insists Strait of Hormuz is open",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリス猛暑、5月と6月の熱波で2700人以上死亡の可能性　研究チームが推定,"More than 2,700 people likely to die from heatwave in May and June in UK, research team estimates",0.0,neutral,"[('More than 2,700', 'CARDINAL'), ('May and June', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,タイ首都のバーで火災、少なくとも27人死亡　重体22人含む60人超負傷,"Fire at bar in Thailand's capital kills at least 27 people and injures over 60, including 22 in critical condition",-1.0,negative,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('at least 27', 'CARDINAL'), ('60', 'CARDINAL'), ('22', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米共和党重鎮のリンジー・グレアム上院議員、急病で死去と発表　トランプ氏の盟友,"US Republican Sen. Lindsey Graham, an ally of Mr. Trump, announces death due to sudden illness",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 ノルウェーにくすぶる「イングランド同点ゴールは無効」の声　ボールが頭上ワイヤに触れていたと,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Voices smoldering in Norway that ``England's equalizer was invalid'' - the ball had touched the overhead wire,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('Norway', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ロシアの爆弾がカフェの近くに落下、店内にも爆風　ウクライナ北東部スーミ, 所要時間 0,52","Video, Russian bomb falls near cafe, blast hits inside Sumy, northeastern Ukraine, Duration 0,52",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('cafe', 'GPE'), ('Sumy', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,﻿黒く焼け焦げた海のよう……スペイン山火事で焼かれた村でBBC記者, 所要時間 1,33","Video, Black sea... BBC reporter in village burnt out by Spanish bushfires, Duration 1,33",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 アルゼンチン、スイス下す　ベスト4が出そろう,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Argentina defeats Switzerland - Top 4 will emerge,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年ウィンブルドン】 車いす男子で小田が2連覇　女子は上地が初優勝し「生涯グランドスラム」達成,"[2026 Wimbledon] Oda wins second consecutive victory in men's wheelchair; Kamiji wins first in women's race, achieving ""Lifetime Grand Slam""",1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Kamiji', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Lifetime Grand Slam', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,モナコの爆発事件とウクライナでの容疑者射殺事件、関連と最新の展開をBBC記者が説明, 所要時間 1,08","Video, BBC reporter explains the connection and latest developments between the Monaco explosion and the shooting of a suspect in Ukraine, Duration 1,08",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Monaco', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Sina ujasiri alio nao Lissu': Mke wa Lissu aelezea gharama ya mapambano ya kisiasa ya Tanzania kwa familia,'I don't have the courage that Lissu has': Lissu's wife explains the cost of Tanzania's political struggle to the family,0.0,neutral,"[('Lissu', 'PERSON'), ('Lissu', 'PERSON'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Iran yashambulia mataifa ya Ghuba huku Marekani ikidai imekamilisha mashambulizi mapya","Directly, Iran attacks the Gulf states while the United States claims it has completed new attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Mama mkatili: ""Alinilazimisha kuishi kama mgonjwa kwa miaka mingi""","Cruel mother: ""She forced me to live as a patient for many years""",0.0,neutral,"[('many years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini makubaliano ya kusitisha mapigano kati ya Iran  na Marekani yamevunjika?,Why is the cease-fire agreement between Iran and the United States broken?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Arsenal inamuwania Álvarez wa Argentina,Monday European football rumours: Arsenal are in the running for Argentine Álvarez,0.0,neutral,"[('Monday', 'DATE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Argentine', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,ODM haitasimamisha mgombea urais katika uchaguzi wa Kenya wa 2027,ODM will not field a presidential candidate in the 2027 Kenyan elections,0.0,neutral,"[('2027', 'DATE'), ('Kenyan', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Mlo ulioniacha na vimelea 38 kwenye ubongo','The diet that left me with 38 parasites in my brain',0.0,neutral,"[('38', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Raia wa Marekani agundulika na Ebola baada ya kurejea kutoka DRC,An American citizen was diagnosed with Ebola after returning from the DRC,0.0,neutral,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('DRC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Marekani yasema Mlango Bahari wa Hormuz uko wazi huku ikiendelea kushambuliana na Iran,The United States says the Strait of Hormuz is open as it continues to attack Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,“Sijafurahishwa na Mchezo Wetu – Kwa Kila Kitu” - Kocha wa England,"""I'm not happy with our game - for everything"" - England coach",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,EU countries consider sanctions on trade from illegal Israeli settlements,EU countries consider sanctions on trade from illegal Israeli settlements,0.0,neutral,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup Preview: France and Spain clash in all-European blockbuster semi,World Cup Preview: France and Spain clash in all-European blockbuster semi,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Preview', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Wildfires near Paris force evacuations, disrupt train lines and motorway","Wildfires near Paris force evacuations, disrupt train lines and motorway",0.0,neutral,"[('Wildfires', 'PERSON'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,New Iran strikes on Gulf as US attacks escalate: What we know,New Iran strikes on Gulf as US attacks escalate: What we know,-1.0,negative,"[('New Iran', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"In Wales, an artist sews names of Gaza’s infant victims on christening gown","In Wales, an artist sews names of Gaza’s infant victims on christening gown",0.0,neutral,"[('Wales', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US and Iran trade strikes as ceasefire comes under growing strain,US and Iran trade strikes as ceasefire comes under growing strain,1.0,positive,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"More than 2,700 deaths linked to heatwaves in UK","More than 2,700 deaths linked to heatwaves in UK",-1.0,negative,"[('More than 2,700', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,FIFA World Cup: Which semifinalist has best chance to win the trophy?,FIFA World Cup: Which semifinalist has best chance to win the trophy?,1.0,positive,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Jurassic Park actor Sam Neill dies aged 78,Jurassic Park actor Sam Neill dies aged 78,0.0,neutral,"[('Jurassic Park', 'FAC'), ('Sam Neill', 'PERSON'), ('78', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Sheikh Hamad: The Arab leader who broke Israel’s siege on Gaza,Sheikh Hamad: The Arab leader who broke Israel’s siege on Gaza,0.0,neutral,"[('Hamad', 'PERSON'), ('Arab', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Centre to review messaging platforms’ response on notice over username feature,Centre to review messaging platforms’ response on notice over username feature,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Weather or human error? What led to Vietnam boat tragedy? | Explained,Weather or human error? What led to Vietnam boat tragedy? | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,SC stays Madras HC order directing ban on cow slaughter in T.N.,SC stays Madras HC order directing ban on cow slaughter in T.N.,0.0,neutral,"[('SC', 'ORG'), ('Madras HC', 'GPE'), ('T.N.', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Kaleshwaram row intensifies as Congress, BRS trade charges over lifting floodwaters amid dry spell","Kaleshwaram row intensifies as Congress, BRS trade charges over lifting floodwaters amid dry spell",-1.0,negative,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('BRS', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Interview | Shubhanshu Shukla on his new book, ‘The Second Orbit’","Interview | Shubhanshu Shukla on his new book, ‘The Second Orbit’",0.0,neutral,"[('Shubhanshu Shukla', 'PERSON'), ('Second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,CSK parts ways with head coach Stephen Fleming,CSK parts ways with head coach Stephen Fleming,0.0,neutral,"[('Stephen Fleming', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Controversial Kerala YouTuber Thoppi’s channel shut down over malicious content,Controversial Kerala YouTuber Thoppi’s channel shut down over malicious content,0.0,neutral,"[('Controversial Kerala', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,India-Australia ‘administrative arrangements’ for uranium supplies,India-Australia ‘administrative arrangements’ for uranium supplies,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"‘Jurassic Park’ star Sam Neill dies at 78, months after becoming cancer-free","‘Jurassic Park’ star Sam Neill dies at 78, months after becoming cancer-free",0.0,neutral,"[('Sam Neill', 'PERSON'), ('78, months', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Oil conundrum: On India’s energy imports from Russia,Oil conundrum: On India’s energy imports from Russia,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"At least 27 killed, 25 critically injured after fire engulfs Bangkok bar","At least 27 killed, 25 critically injured after fire engulfs Bangkok bar",-1.0,negative,"[('At least 27', 'CARDINAL'), ('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bangkok', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US senator and close Trump ally Lindsey Graham dies after 'brief and sudden illness',US senator and close Trump ally Lindsey Graham dies after 'brief and sudden illness',0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,British couple return to village at heart of deadly Spanish wildfire,British couple return to village at heart of deadly Spanish wildfire,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Wildfire raging south of Paris could have been set deliberately, says minister","Wildfire raging south of Paris could have been set deliberately, says minister",0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US Senator Mitch McConnell says absence due to fall and pneumonia,US Senator Mitch McConnell says absence due to fall and pneumonia,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Mitch McConnell', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Anthony Zurcher: From Trump critic to ally, Lindsey Graham was a political survivor of the Maga era","Anthony Zurcher: From Trump critic to ally, Lindsey Graham was a political survivor of the Maga era",0.0,neutral,"[('Anthony Zurcher', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('Maga', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,China evacuates nearly two million people as powerful typhoon makes landfall,China evacuates nearly two million people as powerful typhoon makes landfall,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('nearly two million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,T. rex could become most expensive fossil ever - but it's a ​problem for scientists,T. rex could become most expensive fossil ever - but it's a ​problem for scientists,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Former Emir of Qatar Sheikh Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani dies aged 74,Former Emir of Qatar Sheikh Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani dies aged 74,0.0,neutral,"[('Emir', 'PERSON'), ('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani', 'PERSON'), ('74', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"David Willey, esteemed BBC Vatican correspondent, dies aged 93","David Willey, esteemed BBC Vatican correspondent, dies aged 93",0.0,neutral,"[('David Willey', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Vatican', 'PRODUCT'), ('93', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Lebanese Hold Fast to Their Land Despite Threat of Long Israeli Occupation,Lebanese Hold Fast to Their Land Despite Threat of Long Israeli Occupation,0.0,neutral,"[('Lebanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Live Updates: Iran Ramps Up Threats as It Retaliates Against U.S. Strikes,Live Updates: Iran Ramps Up Threats as It Retaliates Against U.S. Strikes,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Japan Is Building a New Intelligence Agency With Help From the West,Japan Is Building a New Intelligence Agency With Help From the West,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Robot Army Remakes Ground Warfare in Ukraine,A Robot Army Remakes Ground Warfare in Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Ground Warfare', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Next Phase in Ukraine’s War With Russia: The Battle for Minds,The Next Phase in Ukraine’s War With Russia: The Battle for Minds,-1.0,negative,"[('The Next Phase', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('The Battle for Minds', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"It’s the Scent of Manure to Most, but ‘the Smell of Money’ to Them","It’s the Scent of Manure to Most, but ‘the Smell of Money’ to Them",0.0,neutral,"[('Them', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Residents of Spanish Towns Caught in Fierce Blazes Recount Harrowing Escapes,Residents of Spanish Towns Caught in Fierce Blazes Recount Harrowing Escapes,1.0,positive,"[('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Hard-Liners in Iran Want to Keep Fighting America,Hard-Liners in Iran Want to Keep Fighting America,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Keep Fighting America', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Trump Failed to Secure the Strait of Hormuz in His Iran Deal,How Trump Failed to Secure the Strait of Hormuz in His Iran Deal,-1.0,negative,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Zelensky Announces Leadership Shuffle as War Turns in Ukraine’s Favor,Zelensky Announces Leadership Shuffle as War Turns in Ukraine’s Favor,-1.0,negative,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
