Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Las mañanas y las noches ya no existen"": así es la vida en uno de los lugares más húmedos y calurosos del planeta","""Mornings and nights no longer exist"": this is life in one of the most humid and hottest places on the planet",0.0,neutral,"[('Mornings', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Comiendo chocolate y masticando hielo: el guía dado por muerto en el Everest relató a la BBC cómo sobrevivió 6 días en la montaña más alta del mundo,Eating chocolate and chewing ice: the guide presumed dead on Everest told the BBC how he survived 6 days on the highest mountain in the world,1.0,positive,"[('Everest', 'LOC'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('6 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Ucrania lanza un ataque ""sin precedentes"" en San Petersburgo con más de 140 drones en el último día del ""Davos de Rusia""","Ukraine launches ""unprecedented"" attack on St. Petersburg with more than 140 drones on the last day of ""Russia's Davos""",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('more than 140', 'CARDINAL'), ('the last day', 'DATE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Bishkek, la moderna capital de Kirguistán que está demoliendo su imponente arquitectura soviética","Bishkek, the modern capital of Kyrgyzstan that is demolishing its imposing Soviet architecture",0.0,neutral,"[('Bishkek', 'ORG'), ('Kyrgyzstan', 'GPE'), ('Soviet', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Las 10 camisetas más icónicas de la historia de los Mundiales, según la BBC","The 10 most iconic shirts in World Cup history, according to the BBC",0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué Henry Ford creó la semana laboral de 5 días hace 100 años y cómo la medida impactó al mundo,Why Henry Ford created the 5-day work week 100 years ago and how the move impacted the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Henry Ford', 'PERSON'), ('5-day', 'DATE'), ('100 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo la luz está empezando a invadir uno de los lugares más oscuros de la Tierra,How light is starting to invade one of the darkest places on Earth,0.0,neutral,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué pasó en la guerra de Biafra, el primer desastre humanitario televisado en el mundo cuyas heridas siguen abiertas","What happened in the Biafra war, the first televised humanitarian disaster in the world whose wounds remain open",-1.0,negative,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La ciencia (y psicología) detrás de la ola, el fenómeno que el público mexicano universalizó hace 40 años","The science (and psychology) behind the wave, the phenomenon that the Mexican public universalized 40 years ago",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('40 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Backrooms: cómo surgió la idea de la perturbadora película que se convirtió en uno de los mayores éxitos de 2026,Backrooms: how the idea for the disturbing film that became one of the biggest hits of 2026 came about,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ममता बनर्जी के सामने टीएमसी को टूट से बचाने के लिए अब क्या हैं विकल्प, आगे क्या करेंगी?","What are Mamata Banerjee's options now to save TMC from disintegration, what will she do next?",0.0,neutral,"[('TMC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारत की टी-20 क्रिकेट टीम के सिलेक्शन को लेकर किस तरह के उठ रहे हैं सवाल,What kind of questions are being raised regarding the selection of India's T-20 cricket team?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('T-20', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,कांग्रेस ने बताया 'इंडिया' गठबंधन की बैठक में 23 राजनीतिक दल होंगे शामिल","Live, Congress told that 23 political parties will participate in the meeting of 'India' alliance.",0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('23', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वीडियो,राकेश बेदी इंटरव्यू: 'श्रीमान श्रीमती' से लेकर 'धुरंधर' तक का सफ़र, अवधि 23,45","Video, Rakesh Bedi Interview: The journey from 'Shriman Shrimati' to 'Dhurandhar', duration 23,45",0.0,neutral,"[(""Shriman Shrimati'"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी की अंतरराष्ट्रीय मीडिया में कैसी चर्चा,How is Cockroach Janata Party discussed in the international media?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'बर्फ़ चबाकर जिंदा रहा', ऑक्सीज़न ख़त्म होने के छह दिन बाद ज़िंदा मिले शेरपा की कहानी","'Stayed alive by chewing snow', story of Sherpa found alive six days after oxygen ran out",1.0,positive,"[('Sherpa', 'ORG'), ('six days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"घरेलू गैस के दाम में 29 रुपये की बढ़ोतरी, कांग्रेस ने क्या कहा","Domestic gas price increased by Rs 29, what did Congress say?",0.0,neutral,"[('29', 'DATE'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वैभव सूर्यवंशी को अनदेखा कर पाना सेलेक्टर्स के लिए नामुमकिन क्यों था,Why was it impossible for the selectors to ignore Vaibhav Suryavanshi,0.0,neutral,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी क्या बड़े आंदोलन का रूप ले पाएगी, क्या कहते हैं विशेषज्ञ","Will Cockroach Janata Party be able to take the form of a big movement, what do experts say",0.0,neutral,"[('Will Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी को जंतर-मंतर पर एक दिन के विरोध प्रदर्शन से क्या हुआ हासिल,What did the Cockroach Janata Party achieve from the one day protest at Jantar Mantar?,0.0,neutral,"[('the Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Quem são Roberto Sánchez e Keiko Fujimori, e o que poderá ser decisivo na eleição no Peru, um país 'ingovernável'","Who are Roberto Sánchez and Keiko Fujimori, and what could be decisive in the election in Peru, an 'ungovernable' country",0.0,neutral,"[('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Super El Niño: os gráficos que mostram por que ele pode ser o fenômeno mais extremo em décadas — e quais seus efeitos,Super El Niño: the graphics that show why it could be the most extreme phenomenon in decades — and what its effects are,0.0,neutral,"[('Super El Niño', 'PERSON'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As duas eleições que podem consolidar 'círculo de fogo' pró-Trump em torno do Brasil,The two elections that could consolidate the pro-Trump 'ring of fire' around Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O sofrimento silencioso das crianças de Gaza que perderam capacidade de falar,The silent suffering of Gaza children who lost the ability to speak,0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Backrooms: como surgiu a ideia para o perturbador filme que se tornou um dos maiores sucessos de 2026,Backrooms: how the idea for the disturbing film that became one of the biggest hits of 2026 came about,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Os megabanquetes 'patrióticos' no centro de disputa entre direita e esquerda na França,The 'patriotic' megabanquets at the center of dispute between right and left in France,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Guia do Everest dado como morto conta como sobreviveu 6 dias sozinho na montanha: 'Quando o oxigênio acabou, eu não conseguia andar'","Everest guide presumed dead tells how he survived 6 days alone on the mountain: 'When the oxygen ran out, I couldn't walk'",0.0,neutral,"[('Everest', 'LOC'), ('6 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que representa para Cuba a saída das principais multinacionais hoteleiras que operavam no país,What does the departure of the main hotel multinationals that operated in the country mean for Cuba?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Marjane Satrapi faleceu 'de tristeza': é possível morrer pela perda da pessoa amada?,Marjane Satrapi passed away 'of sadness': is it possible to die from the loss of a loved one?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский едет в Лондон; Киев обвинил Москву в ударе по хранилищу отработанного ядерного топлива","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: Zelensky goes to London; Kyiv accused Moscow of attacking a spent nuclear fuel storage facility",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Армении проходят парламентские выборы. Главным вопросом на них стали отношения с Россией,Parliamentary elections are taking place in Armenia. The main issue at the meeting was relations with Russia.,0.0,neutral,"[('Armenia', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп готовит новую торговую войну со всем миром. На этот раз предлог — защита трудящихся,Trump is preparing a new trade war with the whole world. This time the pretext is the protection of workers,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Сложное соседство. Смогут ли США, Канада и Мексика отложить разногласия на время чемпионата мира по футболу?","Difficult neighborhood. Will the US, Canada and Mexico be able to put aside their differences during the World Cup?",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Утро и ночь больше не существуют, когда на улице 47°C: один день в самом жарком месте Индии",Morning and night no longer exist when it's 47°C outside: one day in India's hottest place,0.0,neutral,"[('47', 'CARDINAL'), ('one day', 'DATE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В годовщину высадки в Нормандии Хегсет заявил о «вторжении» мигрантов в Европу,"On the anniversary of the Normandy landings, Hegseth spoke of a migrant “invasion” of Europe",0.0,neutral,"[('Normandy', 'PERSON'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Чемпионат мира по футболу: США разрешили въезд сборной Ирана, но не пустили 15 членов делегации","FIFA World Cup: The United States allowed the entry of the Iranian national team, but did not allow 15 members of the delegation to enter",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Теннисистка из России Мирра Андреева победила  в финале «Ролан Гарроса»,Russian tennis player Mirra Andreeva won the Roland Garros final,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Mirra Andreeva', 'PERSON'), ('Roland Garros', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Украинские дроны атаковали Петербург и Ленинградскую область в заключительный день ПМЭФ. Что известно,Ukrainian drones attacked St. Petersburg and the Leningrad region on the final day of SPIEF. What is known,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('Leningrad', 'GPE'), ('the final day', 'DATE'), ('SPIEF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Развод с Россией, помолвка с Европой? Чего ждать от выборов в Армении: анализ Би-би-си","Divorce from Russia, engagement to Europe? What to expect from the elections in Armenia: BBC analysis",0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Armenia', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,プーチン氏、ゼレンスキー氏との会談は「意味がない」　戦争終結のための対面協議を拒否,"Putin's meeting with Zelensky is 'meaningless', rejects face-to-face talks to end war",-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米軍、イランのドローンとレーダー施設を攻撃と発表,US military announces attack on Iranian drone and radar facilities,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,習氏、7年ぶりに北朝鮮を訪れ金氏と会談へ　どんなことが話し合われるのか,Mr. Xi visits North Korea for the first time in 7 years to meet with Mr. Kim. What will be discussed?,0.0,neutral,"[('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('7 years', 'DATE'), ('Kim', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゼレンスキー氏、プーチン氏に直接会談を提案　公開書簡で,Zelensky proposes direct talks with Putin in open letter,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヒズボラ、イスラエルとレバノンが合意した停戦を拒否,Hezbollah rejects ceasefire agreed by Israel and Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,AIの進化、遅らせる策が必要　米アンソロピック共同創業者がBBC番組で主張,"We need measures to slow down the evolution of AI, co-founder of Anthropic argues on BBC program",0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ストレスと疲労、食料や水の問題も……ホルムズ海峡で足止めされている船員たち,"Stress and fatigue, food and water problems... Sailors stranded in the Strait of Hormuz",0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 アメリカ、メキシコ、カナダは相違を乗り越えられるのか　初の3カ国共催,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Can the United States, Mexico, and Canada overcome their differences? First three countries to co-host",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,マスク氏のAI「Grok」にビキニ写真生成された英下院議員が提訴　スターマー首相も訴えを支持,"British House of Commons member files suit after Musk's AI ""Grok"" generated bikini photo; Prime Minister Starmer supports the lawsuit",0.0,neutral,"[('British House of Commons', 'ORG'), ('Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Grok', 'PERSON'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英首相、マスク氏やファラージ氏が「分断をあおっている」と非難　ノヴァクさん殺害事件めぐり,British Prime Minister slams Musk and Farage for ``stoking division'' over Novak murder case,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Novak', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Jeshi la Marekani lasema limedungua ndege mbili zisizo na rubani za Iran katika Mlango wa Hormuz","Directly, the US military says it has shot down two Iranian drones in the Strait of Hormuz",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini uhusiano kati ya Iran na UAE unaelekea kuwa mgogoro mkali?,Why does the relationship between Iran and the UAE tend to be a bitter conflict?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, wanawake huwa na huruma kuliko wanaume?",Are women more compassionate than men?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Msichana mwenye umri wa miaka 16 alivyokuwa sehemu ya majaribio ya siri ya CIA,A 16-year-old girl who was part of a secret CIA experiment,0.0,neutral,"[('16-year-old', 'DATE'), ('CIA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: PSG yajiunga na Arsenal kumwinda Gibbs-White,European football rumours: PSG join Arsenal in pursuit of Gibbs-White,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Gibbs-White', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nini siri ya mwanga mwekundu katika kuboresha ngozi?,What is the secret of red light in improving the skin?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wachezaji 7 wa Afrika wa kutazamwa katika Kombe la Dunia,7 African players to watch in the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kipi kitaanza kumalizika, akiba za mafuta au vita Iran?","Which will begin to end, oil reserves or the war in Iran?",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Iran yaruhusiwa kuingia Marekani kwa ajili ya kombe la dunia,Iran is allowed to enter the United States for the world cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Madrid kutoa ofa ya dunia kwa Oliseh,European Football Rumors: Madrid to make a world offer for Oliseh,0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Madrid', 'GPE'), ('Oliseh', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Kosovo votes again amid political deadlock, seeking EU and NATO progress","Kosovo votes again amid political deadlock, seeking EU and NATO progress",1.0,positive,"[('Kosovo', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Photos: 100 days of the US–Israel war on Iran,Photos: 100 days of the US–Israel war on Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('100 days', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,From Messi to Yamal: Top 10 superstars to watch at FIFA World Cup 2026,From Messi to Yamal: Top 10 superstars to watch at FIFA World Cup 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Yamal', 'PERSON'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('FIFA World Cup 2026', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Massive human wave in Mexico ahead of World Cup 2026,Massive human wave in Mexico ahead of World Cup 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Pakistan official visits Iran with ‘special letter’ for supreme leader,Pakistan official visits Iran with ‘special letter’ for supreme leader,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('supreme', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Lebanon army chief in Pakistan, funeral plans for soldiers killed by Israel","Lebanon army chief in Pakistan, funeral plans for soldiers killed by Israel",-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran war day 100: US, Iran trade attacks again, raising tensions","Iran war day 100: US, Iran trade attacks again, raising tensions",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran war day', 'EVENT'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,By the numbers: 100 days of the US-Israel war on Iran,By the numbers: 100 days of the US-Israel war on Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('100 days', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,By the numbers: 100 days of the US-Israel war on Iran,By the numbers: 100 days of the US-Israel war on Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('100 days', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"No place to rest | In sweltering Indian cities, relief is unevenly distributed","No place to rest | In sweltering Indian cities, relief is unevenly distributed",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ruskin Bond at 92 | What is it like to be one of India’s most beloved writers?,Ruskin Bond at 92 | What is it like to be one of India’s most beloved writers?,0.0,neutral,"[('Ruskin Bond', 'PERSON'), ('92', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Indira Jaising: ‘Now is the time to reclaim the Constitution’,Indira Jaising: ‘Now is the time to reclaim the Constitution’,0.0,neutral,"[('Indira Jaising', 'PERSON'), ('the Constitution’', 'LAW')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Our agitation will continue until Union Minister Pradhan resigns: Cockroach Janta Party founder Dipke,Our agitation will continue until Union Minister Pradhan resigns: Cockroach Janta Party founder Dipke,0.0,neutral,"[('Union', 'ORG'), ('Pradhan', 'PERSON'), ('Cockroach Janta Party', 'ORG'), ('Dipke', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,LPG price hike: Government says rates in India among world's lowest despite 46% jump in global benchmark,LPG price hike: Government says rates in India among world's lowest despite 46% jump in global benchmark,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('46%', 'PERCENT')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Nepal wants to resolve boundary row with India through diplomacy, open heart: Khanal","Nepal wants to resolve boundary row with India through diplomacy, open heart: Khanal",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"TVK Government drawing criticism well before six months, says Stalin","TVK Government drawing criticism well before six months, says Stalin",1.0,positive,"[('TVK Government', 'ORG'), ('six months', 'DATE'), ('Stalin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Digvijaya Singh urges PM Modi to put three-language policy implementation on hold,Digvijaya Singh urges PM Modi to put three-language policy implementation on hold,0.0,neutral,"[('Digvijaya Singh', 'PERSON'), ('three-language', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why did Supreme Court back curbs on online gaming?,Why did Supreme Court back curbs on online gaming?,0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia war LIVE: U.S. says it destroyed two Iran drones targeting Hormuz shipping,West Asia war LIVE: U.S. says it destroyed two Iran drones targeting Hormuz shipping,-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Hegseth attacks Europe over migration with beach 'invasion' D-Day speech,Hegseth attacks Europe over migration with beach 'invasion' D-Day speech,-1.0,negative,"[('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Steve Rosenberg: Russia's economic forum overshadowed by drone attacks on St Petersburg,Steve Rosenberg: Russia's economic forum overshadowed by drone attacks on St Petersburg,-1.0,negative,"[('Steve Rosenberg', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('St Petersburg', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Huge crowds throng Madrid streets for Pope's open-air mass,Huge crowds throng Madrid streets for Pope's open-air mass,0.0,neutral,"[('Madrid', 'GPE'), ('Pope', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Iran says staff blocked from entering US after players given World Cup visas,Iran says staff blocked from entering US after players given World Cup visas,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Insecurity and instability drive voters in Peru's tight presidential race,Insecurity and instability drive voters in Peru's tight presidential race,0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Funeral held for baby shot dead by Israeli troops in occupied West Bank,Funeral held for baby shot dead by Israeli troops in occupied West Bank,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ragas and symphonies: Indian maestro Ilaiyaraaja is still reshaping music 50 years on,Ragas and symphonies: Indian maestro Ilaiyaraaja is still reshaping music 50 years on,0.0,neutral,"[('Ragas', 'PERSON'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Ilaiyaraaja', 'GPE'), ('50 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'It was either killed or be killed' - ongoing nightmares of an ex-child soldier in Somalia,'It was either killed or be killed' - ongoing nightmares of an ex-child soldier in Somalia,-1.0,negative,"[('Somalia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US and Iran exchange strikes in Gulf in latest test of ceasefire,US and Iran exchange strikes in Gulf in latest test of ceasefire,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_07,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Lebanese general among three soldiers killed in Israeli attack on car,Lebanese general among three soldiers killed in Israeli attack on car,-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanese', 'NORP'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Member of Neo-Nazi Party Reaches Mayoral Runoff in German Town,Member of Neo-Nazi Party Reaches Mayoral Runoff in German Town,0.0,neutral,"[('Neo-Nazi Party Reaches Mayoral Runoff', 'ORG'), ('German', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Peru’s Presidential Runoff Could Swing the Country to the Right: What to Know,Peru’s Presidential Runoff Could Swing the Country to the Right: What to Know,1.0,positive,"[('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mexico City’s Airport Got a $500 Million Renovation for the 2026 World Cup. Was It Enough?,Mexico City’s Airport Got a $500 Million Renovation for the 2026 World Cup. Was It Enough?,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico City’s', 'GPE'), ('$500 Million', 'MONEY'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Can the N.F.L. Win Fans in South Korea With Flag Football?,Can the N.F.L. Win Fans in South Korea With Flag Football?,1.0,positive,"[('the N.F.L. Win Fans', 'ORG'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A President, His Prime Minister and the Bitter Rift Dividing Senegal","A President, His Prime Minister and the Bitter Rift Dividing Senegal",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Venezuela, the Debt Collector Is the Devil","In Venezuela, the Debt Collector Is the Devil",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the Debt Collector Is the Devil', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Pope Leo, After Taking on Trump and A.I., Prepares for New Duels in Spain","Pope Leo, After Taking on Trump and A.I., Prepares for New Duels in Spain",0.0,neutral,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('A.I.', 'ORG'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine Strikes St. Petersburg in Long-Range Drone Attack,Ukraine Strikes St. Petersburg in Long-Range Drone Attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Infant Killed as Israeli Military Fires on Car in West Bank, Palestinian Officials Say","Infant Killed as Israeli Military Fires on Car in West Bank, Palestinian Officials Say",-1.0,negative,"[('Infant Killed', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('West Bank', 'GPE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_07,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Viral Gen-Z Protest Movement Draws Thousands to India’s Capital,A Viral Gen-Z Protest Movement Draws Thousands to India’s Capital,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
