Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Les dispararon a mis hijos delante de mis ojos"": los testimonios desgarradores de quienes huyen de la ciudad sudanesa de El Fasher","""They shot my children before my eyes"": the heartbreaking testimonies of those fleeing the Sudanese city of El Fasher",0.0,"[('Sudanese', 'NORP'), ('El Fasher', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Comando Vermelho: cómo drones y fusiles importados acaban en manos del crimen organizado en Brasil y están transformando el conflicto urbano,Comando Vermelho: how imported drones and rifles end up in the hands of organized crime in Brazil and are transforming the urban conflict,0.0,"[('Comando Vermelho:', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El rey Carlos le quita el título de príncipe a su hermano Andrés, que tiene que abandonar su mansión de Windsor","King Charles removes the title of prince from his brother Andrew, who has to leave his Windsor mansion",0.0,"[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('Windsor mansion', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La familia de la mujer que murió tras ser abandonada por un crucero en una isla remota denuncia la ""falta de cuidado"" de la empresa responsable del viaje","The family of the woman who died after being abandoned by a cruise ship on a remote island denounces the ""lack of care"" of the company responsible for the trip",0.05,[]
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Bohemian Rhapsody"": cómo Queen creó su mítica canción hace 50 años","""Bohemian Rhapsody"": how Queen created their legendary song 50 years ago",1.0,"[('50 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्या किसी प्रेग्नेंट महिला के लिए 145 किलो वज़न उठाना सुरक्षित है? दिल्ली पुलिस की सोनिका यादव के वायरल वीडियो पर बहस,Is it safe for a pregnant woman to lift 145 kg? Debate on Delhi Police's viral video of Sonika Yadav,0.41666666666666663,"[('145 kg', 'QUANTITY'), (""Delhi Police's"", 'ORG'), ('Sonika Yadav', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"किंग चार्ल्स ने अपने भाई एंड्रयू से छीनी 'प्रिंस' की उपाधि, शाही महल से भी होंगे बाहर","King Charles snatches the title of 'Prince' from his brother Andrew, will also be out of the royal palace",0.0,"[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,विराट कोहली ने भारतीय महिला क्रिकेट टीम को बधाई दी, ये कहा","Live, Virat Kohli congratulated the Indian women's cricket team, said this",0.13636363636363635,"[('Virat Kohli', 'ORG'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सरदार पटेल पर मुस्लिम विरोधी होने के आरोपों में कितना दम?,How much truth is there in the allegations against Sardar Patel of being anti-Muslim?,0.2,"[('Sardar Patel', 'PERSON'), ('anti-Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"महिला वर्ल्ड कप: भारतीय टीम की मुरीद हुई दुनिया, किसने क्या कहा","Women's World Cup: The world admired the Indian team, who said what?",0.0,"[(""Women's World Cup"", 'ORG'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जेमिमा और हरमनप्रीत की पार्टनरशिप कैसे सात बार की चैंपियन ऑस्ट्रेलिया पर पड़ी भारी,How Jemima and Harmanpreet's partnership cost seven-time champions Australia,0.0,"[('Jemima', 'PERSON'), ('Harmanpreet', 'ORG'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"महिला वर्ल्ड कप: जेमिमा की करिश्माई पारी से फ़ाइनल में भारत, ऑस्ट्रेलिया को पांच विकेट से हराया",Women's World Cup: Jemima's charismatic innings helped India defeat Australia by five wickets in the final.,0.25,"[(""Women's World Cup"", 'ORG'), ('Jemima', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मुंबई: कई घंटों तक बच्चों को बंधक बनाने वाले किडनैपर की मौत, अब तक क्या-क्या पता चला?","Mumbai: Kidnapper who held children hostage for several hours dies, what is known so far?",0.05,"[('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('several hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"भोपाल: सीनियर पुलिस अधिकारी पर चोरी का आरोप, सीसीटीवी में कैद हुई घटना","Bhopal: Senior police officer accused of theft, incident captured in CCTV",0.0,"[('CCTV', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que polícia do Rio ainda não divulgou lista de mortos e presos na operação contra o CV,Why the Rio police have not yet released a list of those killed and arrested in the operation against the CV,-0.2,"[('Rio', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Operação foi atuação do governador do Rio para preencher vazio na política da direita', diz professor de Cambridge","'The operation was an action by the governor of Rio to fill a void in right-wing politics', says Cambridge professor",0.1,"[('Rio', 'ORG'), ('Cambridge', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Doca, o número 2 do CV que driblou a maior e mais letal operação policial da história do Brasil","Doca, CV's number 2 who circumvented the largest and most lethal police operation in the history of Brazil",0.5,"[('CV', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump elogia encontro 'incrível' com Xi Jinping, mas termina sem acordo comercial formal","Trump praises 'incredible' meeting with Xi Jinping, but ends without formal trade agreement",0.9,"[('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Não se destrói uma lenda com ciência': a centenária busca pelo Monstro do Lago Ness,'You can't destroy a legend with science': the century-old search for the Loch Ness Monster,-0.2,"[('century-old', 'DATE'), ('the Loch Ness Monster', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Trump decidiu retomar testes de armas nucleares após 30 anos,Why Trump decided to resume nuclear weapons testing after 30 years,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('30 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Uso de drones por facções pode transformar conflito urbano em batalha aérea, diz pesquisador","Use of drones by factions could transform urban conflict into aerial battle, says researcher",0.0,[]
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Vi corpo sem cabeça, corpos totalmente desfigurados': o fotógrafo que acompanhou por 24 horas a operação policial que deixou 121 mortos no Rio","'I saw a headless body, totally disfigured bodies': the photographer who followed the police operation for 24 hours that left 121 people dead in Rio",-0.06666666666666667,"[('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('121', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Como o filme 'A Rede Social', sobre nascimento do Facebook, 'profetizou' problemas com tecnologia há 15 anos","How the film 'The Social Network', about the birth of Facebook, 'prophesied' problems with technology 15 years ago",0.03333333333333333,"[(""'The Social Network'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('15 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Из пропавших — в погибшие: что  известно о потерях России в Украине к ноябрю,From missing to dead: what is known about Russia’s losses in Ukraine by November,-0.2,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('November', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Дональд Трамп хочет возобновить «испытания ядерного оружия». Что это значит и к чему может привести?,"Donald Trump wants to resume ""nuclear weapons testing."" What does this mean and what can it lead to?",-0.056249999999999994,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в результате удара по жилой многоэтажке и инфраструктуре в Сумах пострадали 11 человек","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: 11 people were injured as a result of a strike on a residential high-rise building and infrastructure in Sumy",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sumy', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Брат короля Карла III принц Эндрю лишится титула «принц» и покинет резиденцию Royal Lodge в Виндзоре,"King Charles III's brother Prince Andrew will lose his title ""prince"" and leave the Royal Lodge in Windsor",0.0,"[(""Charles III's"", 'PERSON'), ('Prince Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('the Royal Lodge', 'ORG'), ('Windsor', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Германии вынесен приговор по делу о шпионаже в пользу России,"In Germany, a verdict was handed down in the case of espionage in favor of Russia",-0.15555555555555559,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Сотни тысяч ортодоксальных евреев перекрыли въезды в Иерусалим, протестуя против службы в армии. Есть погибший",Hundreds of thousands of Orthodox Jews blocked entrances to Jerusalem to protest against military service. There is a dead person,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Hundreds of thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Orthodox', 'NORP'), ('Jews', 'NORP'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Покровск и Мирноград на грани падения: насколько критическая ситуация сложилась там для Украины?,Pokrovsk and Mirnograd are on the verge of falling: how critical is the situation there for Ukraine?,0.0,"[('Pokrovsk', 'GPE'), ('Mirnograd', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп после встречи с лидером Китая: оценка «12 из 10», тарифы снизят, по войне в Украине будут «работать вместе»","Trump after a meeting with the leader of China: rating “12 out of 10”, tariffs will be reduced, they will “work together” on the war in Ukraine",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Лукойл» решил продать свои зарубежные активы нефтетрейдеру Gunvor из-за санкций,Lukoil decided to sell its foreign assets to oil trader Gunvor due to sanctions,-0.125,"[('Gunvor', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Во Франции задержали еще пятерых подозреваемых в ограблении Лувра. Украденные ценности пока не нашли,Five more suspects in the Louvre robbery were detained in France. The stolen valuables have not yet been found,0.5,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,チャールズ英国王、弟アンドリュー氏から「王子」の称号はく奪,King Charles strips his younger brother Andrew of the title 'Prince',0.0,"[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】　米中貿易戦争、「休戦」で合意も中国は長期戦の構え,"[Commentary] U.S.-China trade war, “truce” agreed, but China is poised for a long-term war",0.0,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,握手とささやき……トランプ氏と習氏の会談を73秒で, 所要時間 1,13","Video, handshakes and whispers...Trump-Xi meeting in 73 seconds, duration 1,13",0.0,"[('Trump-Xi', 'PERSON'), ('73 seconds', 'TIME'), ('1,13', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,アンドリュー英王子が王子でなくなる……BBC速報の瞬間, 所要時間 1,09","Video, The moment Prince Andrew ceases to be a prince...BBC news, Duration 1,09",0.0,"[('Prince Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('1,09', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,BBC番組収録中にアンドリュー氏の「王子」剝奪速報、観客や出演中の閣僚の反応は, 所要時間 1,44","Video, during the recording of a BBC program, Mr. Andrew's breaking news about the removal of the Prince, and the reaction of the audience and the ministers appearing, Duration 1,44",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米中首脳、約6年ぶりに直接会談　レアアースめぐる「障壁なくなった」とトランプ氏,US and Chinese leaders meet directly for first time in six years; Trump says ``barriers have disappeared'' regarding rare earths,0.16249999999999998,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('six years', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、核兵器の試験再開を指示　過去30年ほど行われず,"Trump orders resumption of nuclear weapons testing, something that hasn't happened in the past 30 years",-0.25,"[('the past 30 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ブラジル・リオデジャネイロで警察がギャング掃討作戦、少なくとも132人死亡と当局,"At least 132 people killed in police operation to wipe out gangs in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, authorities say",-0.25,"[('At least 132', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スーダンの準軍事組織、病院で民間人460人を殺害か　WHOトップが懸念表明,WHO chief expresses concern over Sudanese paramilitary group killing 460 civilians at hospital,0.0,"[('Sudanese', 'NORP'), ('460', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Matokeo ya uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Tume ya Uchaguzi NEC yaendelea kutoa matokeo,Tanzania 2025 election results: The NEC Electoral Commission continues to release results,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('The NEC Electoral Commission', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mkuu wa jeshi Tanzania alaani vurugu zinazoendelea","Directly, the Tanzanian army chief condemned the ongoing violence",0.1,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi  Tanzania 2025: Maandamano ya siku ya uchaguzi yana maanisha nini?,Tanzania Election 2025: What does the election day protest mean?,-0.3125,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE'), ('the election day', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Man City, Man United na Arsenal zamwania Carl Etta Eyong","Football rumors in Europe Friday: Man City, Man United and Arsenal for Carl Etta Eyong",0.0,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Man City', 'GPE'), ('Carl Etta', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ghasia zazuka  Namanga mpaka wa Kenya na Tanzania,"Riots broke out in Namanga, the border between Kenya and Tanzania",0.0,"[('Namanga', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Tunachojua kufikia sasa,Tanzania 2025 Election: What we know so far,0.1,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Bunge la Ulaya lasema uchaguzi wa Tanzania 'haukuwa huru na wa haki',The European Parliament says the Tanzanian elections were 'not free and fair',0.16666666666666666,"[('The European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Trump aiomba Idara ya Ulinzi Marekani kuanza tena majaribio ya silaha za nyuklia,Trump asked the US Department of Defense to resume nuclear weapons tests,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the US Department of Defense', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Polisi warusha mabomu ya machozi baada ya maandamano kuzuka Tanzania,Police throw tear gas after protests erupted in Tanzania,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Mkuu Tanzania 2025: Kura au maandamano? mizani ya haki za kikatiba inavyopimwa,Tanzania General Election 2025: Vote or protest? the balance of constitutional rights is measured,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzania General', 'ORG'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE')]"
