Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""En la ruina y profundamente endeudado"": así murió, hace 100 años, Mehmed VI, el último sultán del Imperio otomano","""In ruin and deeply in debt"": this is how Mehmed VI, the last sultan of the Ottoman Empire, died 100 years ago",0.0,neutral,"[('Mehmed VI', 'PERSON'), ('the Ottoman Empire', 'GPE'), ('100 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Trump advierte a Taiwán en contra de declarar su independencia horas después de reunirse con Xi Jinping en Pekín,Trump warns Taiwan against declaring independence hours after meeting Xi Jinping in Beijing,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('hours', 'TIME'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Suiza abrirá sus archivos secretos sobre Joseph Mengele, pero ¿cuál es la relación del ""Ángel de la muerte nazi"" con ese país?","Switzerland will open its secret files on Joseph Mengele, but what is the relationship of the ""Nazi Angel of Death"" with that country?",-1.0,negative,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Joseph Mengele', 'PERSON'), ('the ""Nazi Angel of Death', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué Italia se está convirtiendo en un refugio para los ultrarricos,Why Italy is becoming a haven for the ultra-rich,0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Muere un buzo que intentaba rescatar los cuerpos de los 5 italianos que se ahogaron en las Maldivas,A diver dies who was trying to rescue the bodies of the 5 Italians who drowned in the Maldives,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italians', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La trágica muerte de 5 buceadores italianos mientras exploraban unas cuevas en Maldivas,The tragic death of 5 Italian divers while exploring caves in the Maldives,-1.0,negative,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué opinan los críticos de China dentro del movimiento MAGA sobre el viaje de Trump a Pekín,What China critics within the MAGA movement think about Trump's trip to Beijing,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Con el 100% de las actas escrutadas, Keiko Fujimori y Roberto Sánchez se disputarán la presidencia de Perú el 7 de junio","With 100% of the minutes scrutinized, Keiko Fujimori and Roberto Sánchez will compete for the presidency of Peru on June 7",0.0,neutral,"[('100%', 'PERCENT'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'ORG'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('Peru', 'GPE'), ('June 7', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Un verdadero milagro"": rescatan a 11 personas con vida después de que su avión se estrellara en el Atlántico","""A true miracle"": 11 people rescued alive after their plane crashed in the Atlantic",0.0,neutral,"[('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('Atlantic', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las hermanas adolescentes de Gaza que ganaron un premio por convertir escombros de la guerra en ladrillos,The teenage sisters from Gaza who won an award for turning war debris into bricks,-1.0,negative,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,क्या अमेरिका और इसराइल फिर से कर रहे हैं ईरान पर हमले की तैयारी?,Are America and Israel preparing to attack Iran again?,-1.0,negative,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,सीबीएसई के विद्यार्थियों के लिए अब 9वीं क्लास से तीन भाषाएं पढ़ना ज़रूरी","LIVE, It is now mandatory for CBSE students to study three languages ​​from 9th class.",0.0,neutral,"[('CBSE', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('9th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,नीट पेपर लीक से चर्चा में आया राजस्थान का सीकर कोचिंग का नया हब कैसे बन गया?,How did Rajasthan's Sikar become the new coaching hub due to NEET paper leak?,0.0,neutral,"[('Sikar', 'NORP'), ('NEET', 'LAW')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,शी जिनपिंग से मुलाक़ात के बाद ट्रंप ने अमेरिका के दोस्त ताइवान को किस बात के लिए चेताया?,What did Trump warn America's friend Taiwan about after meeting Xi Jinping?,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"देहरादून में टंकी पर चढ़कर क्या मांग कर रहे थे नर्सिंग अफ़सर, महिला कांग्रेस नेता ने जान देने की कोशिश की",What were the nursing officers demanding by climbing on the tank in Dehradun? Woman Congress leader tried to commit suicide.,0.0,neutral,"[('Dehradun', 'GPE'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"जस्टिस सूर्यकांत ने 'कॉकरोच' वाले बयान पर दी सफ़ाई, बोले- 'मीडिया ने ग़लत ढंग से पेश किया'","Justice Surya Kant gave clarification on 'cockroach' statement, said - 'Media has presented it wrongly'",0.0,neutral,"[('Surya Kant', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"जब भारत को ज़्यादा विदेशी मुद्रा की ज़रूरत है, तब उसने चीनी के निर्यात पर प्रतिबंध क्यों लगाया?","When India needs more foreign exchange, why did it ban the export of sugar?",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,विराट कोहली ने कहा-  या तो पहले दिन ही बता दीजिए कि मेरी ज़रूरत नहीं है,Virat Kohli said- Either tell me on the first day itself that I am not needed.,0.0,neutral,"[('Virat Kohli said-', 'PERSON'), ('the first day', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,साँप अगर आपकी वॉशिंग मशीन या गाड़ी में घुस जाए तो जानिए क्या करना चाहिए,"If a snake enters your washing machine or car, then know what to do.",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_16,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बिहार: विक्रमशिला सेतु टूटने से भारी मुश्किल में आसपास की आबादी,  रोज़गार और कारोबार ठप","Bihar: Due to breakage of Vikramshila bridge, nearby population is in great trouble, employment and business came to a standstill.",1.0,positive,"[('Vikramshila', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Havengate: o fundo na mira da PF que conecta Vorcaro, Flávio e Eduardo Bolsonaro","Havengate: the fund in the PF's sights that connects Vorcaro, Flávio and Eduardo Bolsonaro",0.0,neutral,"[('Havengate', 'ORG'), ('Vorcaro', 'ORG'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Eduardo Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Após visita à China, Trump alerta Taiwan contra independência","After visit to China, Trump warns Taiwan against independence",-1.0,negative,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"O que é a Armadilha de Tucídides, conceito que Xi Jinping usa para definir relação entre EUA e China","What is the Thucydides Trap, a concept that Xi Jinping uses to define the relationship between the USA and China",0.0,neutral,"[('the Thucydides Trap', 'ORG'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Suíça vai divulgar arquivos secretos sobre Mengele, o 'Anjo da Morte' nazista que morreu no Brasil","Switzerland will release secret files on Mengele, the Nazi 'Angel of Death' who died in Brazil",-1.0,negative,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Mengele', 'GPE'), ('Nazi', 'NORP'), (""Angel of Death'"", 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Cientistas alertam para calor na Copa do Mundo e dizem que Fifa coloca jogadores em risco,Scientists warn of heat at the World Cup and say FIFA puts players at risk,-1.0,negative,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('FIFA', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Após negar, Eduardo confirma ter assinado contrato de gestão financeira de filme de Bolsonaro; entenda","After denying, Eduardo confirms that he signed a financial management contract for Bolsonaro's film; understand",0.0,neutral,"[('Eduardo', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Suspeito de elo com PCC e maior sonegador do Brasil: quem é o empresário Ricardo Magro, que está na lista vermelha da Interpol?","Suspected of links to the PCC and biggest tax evader in Brazil: who is businessman Ricardo Magro, who is on Interpol's red list?",0.0,neutral,"[('PCC', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Ricardo Magro', 'PERSON'), ('Interpol', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A incomum visita do diretor da CIA a Cuba em meio ao agravamento da crise na ilha,The unusual visit of the CIA director to Cuba amid the worsening crisis on the island,-1.0,negative,"[('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News Brasil', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Gravação de Flávio Bolsonaro com Vorcaro impulsiona Caiado e Zema, mas não beneficia Lula: 'Eleitor olhou para o lado'","Recording of Flávio Bolsonaro with Vorcaro boosts Caiado and Zema, but does not benefit Lula: 'Voter looked the other way'",0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Vorcaro', 'ORG'), ('Caiado', 'GPE'), ('Zema', 'PERSON'), ('Voter', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: утренние удары по Харькову и ночная атака на Одесскую область","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: morning attacks on Kharkov and night attack on the Odessa region",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('morning', 'TIME'), ('Kharkov', 'GPE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Odessa', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп призвал Тайвань не стремиться к независимости и не стал говорить о поставке оружия,Trump called on Taiwan not to seek independence and did not talk about arms supplies,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Убит «второй по значимости в мире» командир ИГИЛ,'World's second most powerful' ISIS commander killed,-1.0,negative,"[('World', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('ISIS', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Ищем еду по домам, мы здесь в ловушке». Как живут оккупированные Алешки в Херсонской области","“We’re looking for food in our houses, we’re trapped here.” How do occupied Aleshki live in the Kherson region?",0.0,neutral,"[('Aleshki', 'PERSON'), ('Kherson', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,60 лет «культурной революции» в Китае: ее история в шести предметах,60 years of the “cultural revolution” in China: its history in six subjects,0.0,neutral,"[('60 years', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('six', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Стартовал поиск нового агента 007: начались кастинги на роль Джеймса Бонда. Кого считают фаворитами?,The search for a new agent 007 has begun: castings for the role of James Bond have begun. Who are considered the favorites?,0.0,neutral,"[('007', 'CARDINAL'), ('James Bond', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Си Цзиньпин проводил Трампа, следующий — Путин. Чем закончился визит президента США в Китай","Xi Jinping saw off Trump, Putin next. How did the US President's visit to China end?",0.0,neutral,"[('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Чудовищная ложь». Израиль грозит New York Times иском о клевете за статью о насилии над палестинскими заключенными, издание защищает автора","""Monstrous lie."" Israel threatens New York Times with libel suit for article on abuse of Palestinian prisoners, publication defends author",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('New York Times', 'ORG'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Африке новая вспышка лихорадки Эбола: 80 умерших в ДР Конго, один смертельный случай в Уганде","In Africa, a new outbreak of Ebola fever: 80 deaths in DR Congo, one death in Uganda",-1.0,negative,"[('Africa', 'LOC'), ('80', 'CARDINAL'), ('DR Congo', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uganda', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Король севера». Кто такой Энди Бёрнем — политик, который хочет стать премьер-министром Великобритании","""King of the North"". Who is Andy Burnham - a politician who wants to become Prime Minister of Great Britain",1.0,positive,"[('North', 'LOC'), ('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('Great Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、イランの核開発停止「20年間で十分」　履行の保証があればと,"Trump says ``20 years is enough'' to halt Iran's nuclear program, as long as there is a guarantee that it will be implemented.",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,習氏との会談終えたトランプ氏、台湾の独立望んでいないと発言　合意の詳細は明かされず,"After meeting with Xi, Trump says he does not want independence for Taiwan, details of agreement not disclosed",0.0,neutral,"[('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英与党、下院補選についてバーナム市長の出馬届を受理　党首選への道開く,"UK ruling party accepts Mayor Burnham's candidacy for House of Commons by-election, paving the way for leadership election",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('House of Commons', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,レバノン、南部でイスラエルが救急隊員など6人殺害と発表　米はイスラエルとレバノンの停戦延長を発表,Israel announces killing of 6 people including emergency workers in southern Lebanon; US announces extension of ceasefire between Israel and Lebanon,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 暑さが「選手を危険にさらす」　科学者らFIFAに対策見直し要求,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Heat 'puts players at risk', scientists urge FIFA to review measures",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup] Heat', 'EVENT'), ('FIFA', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英労働党で党首選への動き加速　ストリーティング保健相が辞任、　バーナム市長は補選出馬へ,"Movement towards leadership election accelerates in UK Labor Party - Health Minister Streeting resigns, Mayor Burnham to run for election",-1.0,negative,"[('UK Labor Party - Health', 'ORG'), ('Streeting', 'PERSON'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イラン、ホルムズ海峡近くで「浮体式武器庫」の船舶を拿捕か,Iran seizes 'floating weapons storage' ship near Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait of', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、習氏と2日目の会談を終える　北京から帰国の途に,"Mr. Trump finishes his second day of talks with Mr. Xi, on his way back from Beijing",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、習氏がホルムズ海峡開放への協力申し出たと　会談初日について米メディアに説明,Trump explains to US media about the first day of talks that Xi offered to cooperate in opening the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the first day', 'DATE'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,キーウの集合住宅にドローン攻撃、ロシアが攻撃強化, 所要時間 1,26","Video, Russia intensifies drone attack on Kiiv apartment complex, Duration 1,26",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Kiiv', 'PERSON'), ('1,26', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Dangote: Wataalamu kuamua kiwanda kijengwe Tanzania au Kenya,Dangote: Experts decide whether the factory should be built in Tanzania or Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Mmoja wa viongozi wakuu wa ISIS auawa na majeshi ya Marekani na Nigeria","Directly, one of the main leaders of ISIS was killed by the American and Nigerian forces",-1.0,negative,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('ISIS', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Nigerian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Njia tatu za kupunguza kasi ya kuzeeka kwa ubongo,Three ways to slow down brain aging,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumamosi: Liverpool yawalenga Diomande, Nusa na Barcola msimu ujao","European football rumors on Saturday: Liverpool target Diomande, Nusa and Barcola next season",0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool target Diomande, Nusa and Barcola', 'ORG'), ('next season', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini baadhi ya majengo huegama bila kuanguka?,Why do some buildings stand without falling?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nani aliyejenga Al-Kaaba?,Who built Al-Kaaba?,0.0,neutral,"[('Al-Kaaba', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Dunia inazidi kutajirika, lakini kwa nini vijana hawana furaha?","The world is getting richer, but why are young people unhappy?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Uingereza yaunga mkono mpango wa haki za binadamu unaolenga kuondolewa kwa wahamiaji haramu,The UK supports a human rights initiative aimed at removing illegal immigrants,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kuanzia kwa makaribisho makubwa hadi mazungumzo magumu: China inataka nini kutoka kwa Trump?,From warm welcome to tough talks: What does China want from Trump?,-1.0,negative,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nchi gani za kiarabu zina uhusiano wa karibu na Israel?,Which Arab countries have a close relationship with Israel?,0.0,neutral,"[('Arab', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ultra-Orthodox conscription dispute pushes Israeli government to brink,Ultra-Orthodox conscription dispute pushes Israeli government to brink,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Robert Lewandowski to leave Barcelona with his ‘mission complete’,Robert Lewandowski to leave Barcelona with his ‘mission complete’,0.0,neutral,"[('Robert Lewandowski', 'PERSON'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,LIVE: Chelsea vs Manchester City – FA Cup final,LIVE: Chelsea vs Manchester City – FA Cup final,0.0,neutral,"[('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('FA Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"At least eight killed, 35 injured as train hits bus in Bangkok","At least eight killed, 35 injured as train hits bus in Bangkok",-1.0,negative,"[('At least eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('35', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bangkok', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘We just wanted it more’: How Kansas City became unlikely World Cup hosts,‘We just wanted it more’: How Kansas City became unlikely World Cup hosts,0.0,neutral,"[('Kansas City', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israeli strikes on southern Lebanon continue despite ‘ceasefire’ extension,Israeli strikes on southern Lebanon continue despite ‘ceasefire’ extension,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israeli settler blindfolds and detains Palestinian in occupied West Bank,Israeli settler blindfolds and detains Palestinian in occupied West Bank,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,From the Nakba to Gaza’s ruins: One man’s lifetime of displacement,From the Nakba to Gaza’s ruins: One man’s lifetime of displacement,0.0,neutral,"[('Nakba', 'PERSON'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('One', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Russia’s Putin to visit China following Trump’s trip,Russia’s Putin to visit China following Trump’s trip,1.0,positive,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Russia’s Putin to visit China following Trump’s trip,Russia’s Putin to visit China following Trump’s trip,1.0,positive,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Finding spiritual renewal and fellow Indians in Bali,Finding spiritual renewal and fellow Indians in Bali,0.0,neutral,"[('Indians', 'NORP'), ('Bali', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Is there a 'cobra effect' in India’s higher education system?,Is there a 'cobra effect' in India’s higher education system?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The day World War II reached Andhra Pradesh: echoes of forgotten battle still linger across Vizag,The day World War II reached Andhra Pradesh: echoes of forgotten battle still linger across Vizag,-1.0,negative,"[('World War II', 'EVENT'), ('Andhra', 'PERSON'), ('Vizag', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Why Indian chess needs more big-ticket, Super GM tournaments","Why Indian chess needs more big-ticket, Super GM tournaments",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Super GM', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Inside Neytt Homes in Delhi: Kerala brand behind the MET Gala carpet,Inside Neytt Homes in Delhi: Kerala brand behind the MET Gala carpet,0.0,neutral,"[('Neytt Homes', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Kerala', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Govt imposes import curbs on silver,Govt imposes import curbs on silver,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,A reality check on govt.’s claim of 45 days of LPG ‘rolling stock’,A reality check on govt.’s claim of 45 days of LPG ‘rolling stock’,0.0,neutral,"[('45 days', 'DATE'), ('LPG', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"CJI Surya Kant clarifies ‘parasites’ remarks, says youth are pillars of country","CJI Surya Kant clarifies ‘parasites’ remarks, says youth are pillars of country",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,T.N. Cabinet portfolios: CM Vijay to hold Home; Finance for Sengottaiyan; Aadhav Arjuna gets PWD,T.N. Cabinet portfolios: CM Vijay to hold Home; Finance for Sengottaiyan; Aadhav Arjuna gets PWD,0.0,neutral,"[('T.N. Cabinet', 'ORG'), ('CM Vijay', 'ORG'), ('Sengottaiyan', 'NORP'), ('Aadhav Arjuna', 'PERSON'), ('PWD', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,NEET paper leak row: Rahul Gandhi demands Dharmendra Pradhan’s removal,NEET paper leak row: Rahul Gandhi demands Dharmendra Pradhan’s removal,0.0,neutral,"[('NEET', 'LAW'), ('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('Dharmendra Pradhan’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Senior IS leader killed in joint operation, US and Nigeria say","Senior IS leader killed in joint operation, US and Nigeria say",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Rescue diver dies during search for bodies of Italians who drowned in Maldives caves,Rescue diver dies during search for bodies of Italians who drowned in Maldives caves,0.0,neutral,"[('Italians', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US planning to charge ex-Cuban leader Raúl Castro,US planning to charge ex-Cuban leader Raúl Castro,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('ex-Cuban', 'NORP'), ('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Toddlers among more than 50 schoolchildren kidnapped in Nigeria,Toddlers among more than 50 schoolchildren kidnapped in Nigeria,0.0,neutral,"[('more than 50', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Trump warns Taiwan against declaring independence, hours after summit with China's Xi","Trump warns Taiwan against declaring independence, hours after summit with China's Xi",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('hours', 'TIME'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Man killed by 13ft great white shark in Western Australia,Man killed by 13ft great white shark in Western Australia,0.0,neutral,"[('13ft great', 'QUANTITY'), ('Western Australia', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Switzerland to open secret files on Auschwitz 'Angel of Death' Mengele,Switzerland to open secret files on Auschwitz 'Angel of Death' Mengele,-1.0,negative,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Auschwitz', 'ORG'), (""Angel of Death'"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Lebanon says six killed in Israeli strike as US announces ceasefire extension,Lebanon says six killed in Israeli strike as US announces ceasefire extension,-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Freight train and bus crash kills at least eight in Bangkok,Freight train and bus crash kills at least eight in Bangkok,-1.0,negative,"[('at least eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bangkok', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,New outbreak of Ebola kills 80 in eastern DR Congo,New outbreak of Ebola kills 80 in eastern DR Congo,-1.0,negative,"[('80', 'CARDINAL'), ('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How a Nature Cruise Turned Into a Nightmare,How a Nature Cruise Turned Into a Nightmare,0.0,neutral,"[('Nightmare', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Rival Protests Begin in London, With a Major Security Effort","Rival Protests Begin in London, With a Major Security Effort",0.0,neutral,"[('London', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Trump Uses Taiwan Arms Sales as Bargaining Chip With China, in a Risky Move","Trump Uses Taiwan Arms Sales as Bargaining Chip With China, in a Risky Move",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump Uses Taiwan Arms Sales', 'ORG'), ('Bargaining Chip With China', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"They Fled to Safety in Palestinian Territory, Then Settlers Attacked Again","They Fled to Safety in Palestinian Territory, Then Settlers Attacked Again",-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Hamas’s Top Leader in Gaza Is Killed in Israeli Strike,Hamas’s Top Leader in Gaza Is Killed in Israeli Strike,-1.0,negative,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"China Will Host Putin, Days After Trump’s Visit","China Will Host Putin, Days After Trump’s Visit",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Days', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Trump Says a Top ISIS Leader Was Killed in a U.S.-Nigerian Mission,Trump Says a Top ISIS Leader Was Killed in a U.S.-Nigerian Mission,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Was Killed', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.-Nigerian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,It’s Been a Wild Week in British Politics. What Happens Next?,It’s Been a Wild Week in British Politics. What Happens Next?,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How a Drug Cartel Made a Mexican State Its Tool,How a Drug Cartel Made a Mexican State Its Tool,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_16,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Inside the Congolese Hotel Where Trump Deported 15 U.S. Migrants,Inside the Congolese Hotel Where Trump Deported 15 U.S. Migrants,0.0,neutral,"[('the Congolese Hotel Where Trump Deported', 'ORG'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
