Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Todos los migrantes tienen que pagarles a los traficantes de personas, pero de las mujeres se espera que también paguen con sexo""","""All migrants have to pay human traffickers, but women are also expected to pay with sex""",-0.05,[]
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Luis Magallanes, de pasar hambre en Venezuela a cantar en la Ópera de Zúrich gracias a un video casero","Luis Magallanes, from going hungry in Venezuela to singing at the Zurich Opera thanks to a home video",0.2,"[('Luis Magallanes', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the Zurich Opera', 'FAC')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Sólo queremos que salgan a la luz todas las pruebas de estos crímenes"": el escepticismo de las víctimas de Epstein ante la publicación de los archivos restantes del caso","""We just want all the evidence of these crimes to come to light"": the skepticism of Epstein's victims regarding the publication of the remaining files of the case",0.4,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"EE.UU. persigue ""activamente"" un tercer petrolero vinculado a Venezuela","The US ""actively"" pursues a third oil tanker linked to Venezuela",-0.06666666666666667,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Las 25 mejores películas de 2025, según los críticos de la BBC","The 25 best films of 2025, according to BBC critics",1.0,"[('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जेईई मेन और जेईई एडवांस्ड में क्या फ़र्क है?,What is the difference between JEE Main and JEE Advanced?,0.2833333333333333,"[('JEE Main', 'PERSON'), ('JEE Advanced', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,मॉस्को में हुए धमाके में सेना के एक जनरल की मौत, रूसी अधिकारियों ने बताया","Live, an army general died in a blast in Moscow, Russian officials said",0.062121212121212126,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"एक लाख का कर्ज़ हो गया 50 लाख, ज़मीन-जेवर बिके और किडनी भी बेचनी पड़ी","Loan of Rs 1 lakh became Rs 50 lakh, land, jewelery sold and kidney also had to be sold.",0.0,"[('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('50', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,समीर मिन्हास कौन हैं जिन्होंने एशिया कप में भारत के ख़िलाफ़ खेली 172 रनों की पारी,Who is Sameer Minhas who played an inning of 172 runs against India in Asia Cup?,0.0,"[('Sameer Minhas', 'PERSON'), ('172', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Asia Cup', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश: उस्मान हादी के हत्यारे क्या देश से फ़रार हो गए?,Bangladesh: Have Osman Hadi's killers absconded from the country?,0.0,"[(""Osman Hadi's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'विकसित भारत- जी राम जी' बिल बना क़ानून, मनरेगा से कितना अलग और विपक्ष क्यों है इसे लेकर हमलावर","'Developed India - Ji Ram Ji' bill becomes law, attackers on how different it is from MNREGA and why there is opposition",0.05,"[(""Developed India - Ji Ram Ji'"", 'FAC')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश: हिंसा की आग में झुलस रहे देश से कैसे बढ़ रही हैं भारत के लिए चुनौतियां,Bangladesh: How the challenges for India are increasing due to the country burning in the fire of violence.,-0.125,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,उस्मान हादी और हिंदू युवक की हत्या के बाद भारत और बांग्लादेश इस मुद्दे पर आए आमने-सामने,"After the murder of Osman Hadi and Hindu youth, India and Bangladesh came face to face on this issue.",0.0,"[('Osman Hadi', 'PERSON'), ('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चंगेज़ ख़ाँ दुनिया के बड़े हिस्से को जीतने के बावजूद भारत से क्यों लौट गया था?,Why did Genghis Khan return from India despite conquering a large part of the world?,0.21428571428571427,"[('Genghis Khan', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Terceiro navio ligado à Venezuela é alvo de ação dos EUA em meio à escalada de tensões,Third ship linked to Venezuela is target of US action amid escalating tensions,0.05,"[('Third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como foi a última grande intervenção militar dos EUA na América Latina - e como se compara à situação atual na Venezuela,What the last major US military intervention in Latin America was like - and how it compares to the current situation in Venezuela,-0.009375000000000001,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Latin America', 'LOC'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como o bloqueio petrolífero 'total e completo' de Trump pode afetar a economia da Venezuela - e se voltar contra os EUA,How Trump's 'total and complete' oil blockade could affect Venezuela's economy - and backfire on the US,0.05,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os disquetes esquecidos de Stephen Hawking por trás da corrida para evitar 'Idade das Trevas' digital,Stephen Hawking's forgotten floppy disks behind the race to avoid digital 'Dark Ages',-0.18333333333333335,"[(""Stephen Hawking's"", 'PERSON'), (""Dark Ages'"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Fui escravizada pela família do meu marido': os abusos sofridos por milhões de mulheres submetidas a casamentos forçados,'I was enslaved by my husband's family': the abuse suffered by millions of women subjected to forced marriages,-0.30000000000000004,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Rede criminosa desviou milhões arrecadados para crianças com câncer, revela investigação da BBC","Criminal network diverted millions raised for children with cancer, BBC investigation reveals",-0.4,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Canetas emagrecedoras: o que acontece quando você para de usar?,Slimming pens: what happens when you stop using them?,0.0,[]
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Meu pai abusou de 130 crianças, e descobrir a verdade foi horrível': o relato da filha do maior abusador da Igreja da Inglaterra","'My father abused 130 children, and finding out the truth was horrible': the account of the daughter of the Church of England's biggest abuser",-1.0,"[('130', 'CARDINAL'), (""the Church of England's"", 'ORG')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,CZT: o incrível material que está gerando uma revolução tecnológica (e por que é tão difícil de obter),CZT: The Amazing Material That's Driving a Technological Revolution (and Why It's So Hard to Get),0.1541666666666667,"[('CZT', 'NORP'), (""The Amazing Material That's Driving a Technological Revolution"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Москве в результате подрыва автомобиля погиб начальник управления Генштаба,"In Moscow, the head of the General Staff department died as a result of a car explosion",0.05000000000000002,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('General Staff', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: ночные атаки на Одесскую область; в Житомирской области грузовой поезд сошел с рельсов","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: night attacks on the Odessa region; a freight train derailed in the Zhytomyr region",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Odessa', 'GPE'), ('Zhytomyr', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Мы добьемся его избрания 48-м президентом США». Вдова и сторонники Чарли Кирка поддержали Джей Ди Вэнса,“We will get him elected as the 48th President of the United States.” Charlie Kirk's widow and supporters support J.D. Vance,0.0,"[('48th', 'ORDINAL'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), (""Charlie Kirk's"", 'PERSON'), ('J.D. Vance', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Гонконгский миллиардер Джимми Лай бросил вызов силе Китая. Это стоило ему свободы,Hong Kong billionaire Jimmy Lai has challenged China's power. It cost him his freedom,0.0,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('Jimmy Lai', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Саудовская Аравия снова казнила рекордное число людей за год. Большинство приговоров — за наркотики,Saudi Arabia has again executed a record number of people in a year. Most convictions are for drugs,0.5,"[('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('a year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Современные друиды пришли в Стоунхендж, чтобы отметить день зимнего солнцестояния. Фотографии",Modern Druids came to Stonehenge to celebrate the winter solstice. Photos,0.2,"[('Stonehenge', 'LOC'), ('winter', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,США захватили второй нефтяной танкер у берегов Венесуэлы и преследуют третий,The US has seized a second oil tanker off the coast of Venezuela and is pursuing a third.,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Украина заявила, что российские военные вошли в село Грабовское в Сумской области и вывезли все население. Что известно",Ukraine said that Russian troops entered the village of Grabovskoye in the Sumy region and took out the entire population. What is known,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Grabovskoye', 'PERSON'), ('Sumy', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Путешествие Томаса Стивенса: что увидел человек, первым объехавший мир на велосипеде?",The journey of Thomas Stevens: what did the man who was the first to travel around the world on a bicycle see?,0.25,"[('Thomas Stevens', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Администрация Трампа раскрыла материалы дела Эпштейна, но не все и с купюрами. Многие недовольны","The Trump administration has released the Epstein case file, but not all of it, and not all of it. Many are unhappy",-0.04999999999999999,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカがヴェネズエラ沖で石油タンカーを拿捕、今月2度目　3隻目を追跡中と当局者,"The US has seized an oil tanker off the coast of Venezuela for the second time this month, officials say they are tracking a third tanker.",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('this month', 'DATE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカとウクライナ、マイアミでの協議を「生産的」と評価　突破口はなく,U.S. and Ukraine call talks in Miami “productive”; no breakthrough,0.0,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Miami', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,バーボン「ジム・ビーム」、米主力製造拠点が来年1年閉鎖へ,Jim Beam bourbon's main manufacturing base in the US to close next year,-0.21111111111111114,"[('Jim Beam', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('next year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,サウジアラビアの死刑執行が過去最多、昨年の345人を超える　人権団体が非難,"Saudi Arabia executes the most people ever, surpassing 345 people last year, human rights group condemns",0.16666666666666666,"[('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('345', 'CARDINAL'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、ヨルダン川西岸の入植地19カ所を承認,Israel approves 19 West Bank settlements,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米司法省、「エプスティーン・ファイル」から一部資料を削除　写真少なくとも13点,U.S. Department of Justice deletes some documents from 'Epstein File' - at least 13 photos,-0.3,"[('U.S. Department of Justice', 'ORG'), (""Epstein File'"", 'PERSON'), ('at least 13', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英仏海峡を渡る移民、1日だけで800人超　12月の最多を記録,"More than 800 migrants cross the English Channel in one day alone, record high for December",0.165,"[('More than 800', 'CARDINAL'), ('the English Channel', 'ORG'), ('one day', 'DATE'), ('December', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヨハネスブルグ近郊のバーで銃撃事件、9人死亡　南アフリカ,"9 people killed in shooting incident at bar near Johannesburg, South Africa",-0.05,"[('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Johannesburg', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,プーチン氏、西側首脳がロシアをだましたと　BBCロシア編集長の質問に答え, 所要時間 1,59","Video, Putin answers BBC Russia editor's question about Western leaders deceiving Russia, Duration 1,59",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('BBC Russia', 'ORG'), ('Western', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, M23 wamejiondoa Uvira kweli? Hali ilivyo sasa Mashariki mwa DRC",Have M23 really pulled out of Uvira? The current situation in Eastern DRC,0.1,"[('M23', 'GPE'), ('Uvira', 'GPE'), ('Eastern DRC', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Wanafunzi wengine 130 waliotekwa nyara Nigeria waachiwa huru","Directly, 130 other kidnapped students in Nigeria have been released",-0.012499999999999997,"[('130', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi 10 za Afrika ambazo hazijawahi kushiriki fainali za AFCON,10 African countries that have never participated in the AFCON finals,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('AFCON', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Semenyo kumrithi Isak Liverpool?,Football rumors in Europe: Semenyo to succeed Isak Liverpool?,0.0,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Semenyo', 'PERSON'), ('Isak Liverpool', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,AFCON 2025: Morocco yawabwaga Comoros kwa tabu,AFCON 2025: Morocco beat Comoros with difficulty,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Faili za Epstein: Waathirika na mashaka kuhusu kutolewa kwa nyaraka zilizobaki za Epstein,Epstein files: Victims and doubts about release of remaining Epstein documents,0.0,"[('Epstein', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Aliyekuwa dereva Marekani: Sasa anaogopa wapiganaji baada ya kurudishwa Somalia,Former driver in the United States: Now he is afraid of fighters after being sent back to Somalia,-0.19999999999999998,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Somalia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini Wayahudi wa Uingereza wanakabiliwa na mabadiliko makubwa zaidi katika miaka 60?,Why are British Jews facing the biggest change in 60 years?,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Jews', 'NORP'), ('60 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Benin yamuweka kizuizini kiongozi wa upinzani kwa tuhuma za mapinduzi,Benin detains an opposition leader on suspicion of coup,0.0,"[('Benin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nyaraka za siri za Jeffrey Epstein zatolewa hadharani: Nini kipya?,Jeffrey Epstein's secret files made public: What's new?,-0.08787878787878789,"[(""Jeffrey Epstein's"", 'PERSON')]"
