Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,“Cuando me giré ya no quedaba nada”: el fulminante colapso del Ritasol Palace por los terremotos que sacudieron Venezuela,“When I turned around there was nothing left”: the sudden collapse of the Ritasol Palace due to the earthquakes that shook Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('the Ritasol Palace', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Los terremotos marcan a los países durante décadas y las consecuencias emocionales se llevan para siempre""","""Earthquakes mark countries for decades and the emotional consequences are carried forever""",0.0,neutral,"[('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Me da miedo lo que voy a ver allá dentro"": BBC Mundo visita la morgue improvisada de Los Silos, donde los cadáveres se acumulan al aire libre tras los terremotos en Venezuela","""I'm afraid of what I'm going to see in there"": BBC Mundo visits the improvised morgue of Los Silos, where corpses accumulate in the open air after the earthquakes in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC Mundo', 'ORG'), ('Los Silos', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué EE.UU. se llama Estados Unidos de América y quién le dio el nombre,Why is the USA called the United States of America and who gave it the name?,0.0,neutral,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('the United States of America', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quiénes fueron las ""madres fundadoras"", clave en la formación de Estados Unidos hace 250 años","Who were the ""founding mothers"", key in the formation of the United States 250 years ago",0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('250 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¡A octavos de final! Colombia se permite soñar en el Mundial tras una corta pero merecida victoria ante Ghana en que remató 20 veces,To the round of 16! Colombia allows itself to dream about the World Cup after a short but deserved victory against Ghana in which it finished 20 times,1.0,positive,"[('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Ghana', 'GPE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Argentina sobrevive en el Mundial ante un valiente Cabo Verde que llevó el partido a la prórroga e hizo sufrir a los de Messi hasta el último minuto,Argentina survives in the World Cup against a brave Cape Verde team that took the game to extra time and made Messi's team suffer until the last minute,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Cape Verde', 'PRODUCT'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('the last minute', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Hallan el cuerpo de la periodista mexicana Roxana Guzmán, cuyo secuestro quedó grabado y se hizo viral","They find the body of Mexican journalist Roxana Guzmán, whose kidnapping was recorded and went viral",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Roxana Guzmán', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Si De la Espriella intenta acabar con conquistas sociales, vendrá una reacción de la población en Colombia y se hará sentir la oposición política"": entrevista a Iván Cepeda, excandidato presidencial","""If De la Espriella tries to end social achievements, there will be a reaction from the population in Colombia and the political opposition will be felt"": interview with Iván Cepeda, former presidential candidate",0.0,neutral,"[('De la Espriella', 'PERSON'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Iván Cepeda', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Una mujer ""disfrazada de hombre"" con un tatuaje de serpiente: la sospechosa del atentado con bomba contra un millonario ucraniano en Mónaco","A woman ""disguised as a man"" with a snake tattoo: the suspect in the bomb attack against a Ukrainian millionaire in Monaco",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Monaco', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'हम साफ़ पानी मांग रहे थे, हम पर एफ़आईआर हो गई': हरियाणा के इस गांव में डेढ़ महीने से धरने पर हैं लोग","'We were demanding clean water, FIR lodged against us': People have been on strike in this village of Haryana for one and a half month",0.0,neutral,"[('FIR', 'ORG'), ('Haryana', 'PERSON'), ('one and a half month', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,टीएमसी की पश्चिम बंगाल अध्यक्ष ने दिया इस्तीफ़ा, बाग़ी विधायक संदीपन साहा ने कहा, 'ये तो होना ही था'","Live, TMC West Bengal President resigns, rebel MLA Sandipan Saha said, 'This was bound to happen'",0.0,neutral,"[('MLA', 'PERSON'), ('Saha', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"दिलजीत दोसांझ की 'पंजाब 95' 'सतलुज' नाम से रिलीज़, फ़िल्म के किरदार जसवंत सिंह खालड़ा कौन थे?","Diljit Dosanjh's 'Punjab 95' released with the name 'Sutlej', who was the film's character Jaswant Singh Khalda?",0.0,neutral,"[(""Diljit Dosanjh's '"", 'PERSON'), ('95', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sutlej', 'PERSON'), ('Jaswant Singh Khalda', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पाकिस्तान प्रशासित कश्मीर के चुनावों का बहिष्कार क्यों कर रही इमरान ख़ान की पार्टी?,Why is Imran Khan's party boycotting the elections in Pakistan-administered Kashmir?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Imran Khan's"", 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,केप वर्डे: अर्जेंटीना के फ़ैंस की सांसें रोक देने वाले इस छोटे से मुल्क की ये हैं 6 ख़ासियतें,Cape Verde: These are the 6 specialties of this small country that takes the breath away of Argentina fans.,0.0,neutral,"[('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"250 साल बाद भी 'अमेरिकन ड्रीम' ज़िंदा है, लेकिन मुश्किल से","250 years later, the 'American Dream' is still alive, but barely",0.0,neutral,"[('250 years later', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"होर्मुज़ स्ट्रेट: तनाव कम होने के बाद इलाक़े में कितनी सामान्य हुई ज़िंदगी, लोगों ने क्या बताया","Hormuz Strait: After the tension subsided, how normal life became in the area, what people said",0.0,neutral,"[('Hormuz Strait:', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"महाराष्ट्र में गाय-बैल खरीदना आसान पर घर ले जाना बना चुनौती, क़ानून और गोरक्षकों का डर","In Maharashtra, buying cows and bulls is easy but taking them home becomes a challenge, fear of law and cow protectors.",0.0,neutral,"[('Maharashtra', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इंस्टाग्राम पर बच्चों के यौन शोषण से जुड़े विज्ञापनों के मामले में केंद्रीय मंत्री ने मेटा को तलब किया,Union Minister summons Meta in case of advertisements related to sexual exploitation of children on Instagram,0.0,neutral,"[('Meta', 'PERSON'), ('Instagram', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इंस्टाग्राम में छिपी एक भयानक दुनिया का पर्दाफ़ाश- बीबीसी पड़ताल,A terrifying world hidden in Instagram exposed - BBC investigation,0.0,neutral,"[('Instagram', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"No aniversário de 250 anos, Trump reacende o debate: quais os limites do poder nos EUA?","On the 250th anniversary, Trump reignites the debate: what are the limits of power in the USA?",0.0,neutral,"[('250th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Viagem de Flávio aos EUA é tentativa de se livrar de responsabilidade por tarifaço, diz ministro de Lula","Flávio's trip to the USA is an attempt to avoid responsibility for tariffs, says Lula's minister",0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Prejudicou operação': PF reclama de sanção dos EUA que associou brasileiro foragido ao PCC,'It harmed the operation': PF complains about US sanction that associated fugitive Brazilian with the PCC,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('PCC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Argentina leva susto de Cabo Verde, mas vence na prorrogação e avança às oitavas da Copa","Argentina is scared by Cape Verde, but wins in extra time and advances to the round of 16 of the World Cup",1.0,positive,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Cape Verde', 'PRODUCT'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"6 fatos para conhecer Cabo Verde, o país por trás da seleção mais apaixonante da Copa","6 facts to know about Cape Verde, the country behind the World Cup's most exciting team",0.0,neutral,"[('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cape Verde', 'LOC'), (""the World Cup's"", 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Qual deve ser a escalação do Brasil contra a Noruega? As opções de Ancelloti, e os vantagens de cada cenário","What should Brazil's lineup be against Norway? Ancelloti's options, and the advantages of each scenario",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Ancelloti', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que São Paulo é a 2ª cidade do mundo que mais ouve Taylor Swift no Spotify — e como casamento pode impulsionar ainda mais suas músicas,Why São Paulo is the 2nd city in the world that listens to Taylor Swift the most on Spotify — and how marriage can boost your music even further,0.0,neutral,"[('2nd', 'ORDINAL'), ('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Spotify', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'VAR está indo longe demais': gol anulado da Croácia reacende debate na Copa do Mundo,'VAR is going too far': Croatia's disallowed goal reignites World Cup debate,0.0,neutral,"[('Croatia', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Qual a distância entre Lula e Flávio Bolsonaro nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,What is the distance between Lula and Flávio Bolsonaro in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"O mapa de satélite que mostra a extensão da destruição em La Guaira, a área mais atingida pelos terremotos na Venezuela","The satellite map showing the extent of destruction in La Guaira, the area hardest hit by earthquakes in Venezuela",1.0,positive,"[('La Guaira', 'FAC'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: при ударе по Сумам погибли четыре человека, украинские дроны атаковали Петербург","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: four people were killed in the strike on Sumy, Ukrainian drones attacked St. Petersburg",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sumy', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,От Оренбурга до Ташкента: как удары по российской энергетике отзываются в Центральной Азии,From Orenburg to Tashkent: how blows to the Russian energy sector are echoing in Central Asia,0.0,neutral,"[('Orenburg', 'GPE'), ('Tashkent', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Central Asia', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"ЧМ-2026: исторические достижения, VAR-драмы и отставки. Итоги первого раунда плей-офф","World Cup 2026: historical achievements, VAR dramas and resignations. Results of the first round of the playoffs",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Каким будет внешний вид человека в будущем? Возможно, нам самим предстоит сделать выбор",What will a person's appearance be like in the future? We may have to make our own choices.,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Рейтинг Путина снова упал — до довоенных значений. Что происходит,Putin's rating has fallen again - to pre-war levels. What's happening,-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В нападении на бизнесмена Ермолаева в Монако подозревают  гражданку Украины. Что известно,A Ukrainian citizen is suspected of attacking businessman Ermolaev in Monaco. What is known,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Ermolaev', 'PERSON'), ('Monaco', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"НАСА запустило робота, чтобы попробовать отодвинуть ценную космическую обсерваторию подальше от Земли",NASA has launched a robot to try to move a valuable space observatory further away from Earth.,0.0,neutral,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,День независимости или День Трампа? Как юбилей Америки превратился в спор о президентской власти. Рассылка «Контекст»,"Independence Day or Trump Day? How America's Jubilee Became a Debate over Presidential Power. Newsletter ""Context""",0.0,neutral,"[('Independence Day', 'EVENT'), ('Trump Day', 'EVENT'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Jubilee Became', 'PERSON'), ('Debate', 'ORG'), ('Presidential Power', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Каждая ночь в Украине похожа на игру в русскую рулетку». В Киеве — день траура после удара, при котором погибли 30 человек","“Every night in Ukraine is like playing Russian roulette.” In Kyiv there is a day of mourning after the attack, which killed 30 people",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Нормализует советскую военную эстетику»: британские политики призывают убрать «Машу и Медведя» со стриминговых сервисов,“Normalizes Soviet military aesthetics”: British politicians call for Masha and the Bear to be removed from streaming services,0.0,neutral,"[('Soviet', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Masha', 'PERSON'), ('Bear', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ポーランド首相、ロシアの脅威を念頭に警告　「今後数カ月が極めて重要」になり得ると,Polish Prime Minister warns of Russian threat: 'coming months could be crucial',-1.0,negative,"[('Polish', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), (""'coming months"", 'DATE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,イラン前最高指導者ハメネイ師の遺体を安置、アメリカとの不安定な停戦の中, 所要時間 0,41","Video, Iran's former supreme leader Ayatollah Khamenei's body laid to rest amid unstable ceasefire with US, Duration 0,41",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('supreme', 'ORG'), (""Ayatollah Khamenei's"", 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英で少女2人をレイプした少年2人に控訴審で拘禁刑　第一審の量刑が軽すぎると首相も批判,Two boys who raped two girls in the UK are sentenced to imprisonment by appeal court; the prime minister also criticizes the first trial's sentence as too lenient,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴェネズエラ地震発生から8日、生存者を倒壊した建物から救出,"8 days after Venezuela earthquake, survivors rescued from collapsed building",0.0,neutral,"[('8 days', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアのキーウ空爆、死者少なくとも30人に　「最大規模の攻撃」と市長,At least 30 killed in Russia's airstrike on KiV; mayor calls it 'largest attack',-1.0,negative,"[('At least 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('KiV', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ロシアの攻撃、キーウの集合住宅を破壊　BBCが現地報告, 所要時間 1,27","Video, Russian attack destroys apartment complex in Kiv, BBC reports on the ground, Duration 1,27",-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kiv', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴァチカン、世界的なカトリック教会分派の信者らを破門　異例の厳しい対応,Vatican excommunicates members of a worldwide sect of the Catholic Church in an unusually harsh response,0.0,neutral,"[('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('the Catholic Church', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イングランドとウェールズのパブ、午前5時まで営業可能に　イングランド対メキシコ戦に合わせ,[2026 Men's World Cup] Pubs in England and Wales to be open until 5am for England vs. Mexico match,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Wales', 'GPE'), ('5am', 'TIME'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,北京・最高層ビルの小型機衝突、操縦者の「個人的理由」が原因と　中国当局が発表,Chinese authorities say pilot's ``personal reasons'' were the cause of small plane crash into Beijing's tallest building,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,コウモリに顔に乗られ、狂犬病で死亡　カナダの11歳少年,11-year-old boy in Canada dies of rabies after getting hit in the face by a bat,0.0,neutral,"[('11-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Mazishi ya Ali Khamenei yaanza rasmi kwa kufunguliwa kwa msikiti wa Tehran","Immediately, Ali Khamenei's funeral officially begins with the opening of the mosque in Tehran",0.0,neutral,"[(""Ali Khamenei's"", 'PERSON'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Lissu ataka kulipwa fidia kwa kesi yake ‘kucheleweshwa’,Lissu wants to be compensated for his case being 'delayed',0.0,neutral,"[('Lissu', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, msimamo wa Democrats kuhusu Israel ni upi?",What is the position of the Democrats on Israel?,0.0,neutral,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, shampoo hurekebisha nywele? Wataalamu waeleza hila 4 muhimu",Does shampoo repair hair? Experts explain 4 important tricks,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwanini vita vijavyo dhidi ya Iran vinaweza kutokea mapema kuliko inavyofikiriwa - Reuters,Why the next war with Iran could happen sooner than thought - Reuters,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Reuters', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Majaribio ya tiba ya Ebola yaanza nchini DR Congo,Ebola treatment trials begin in DR Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Binadamu wa siku zijazo watakuwa na muonekano na sura gani?,What will the human of the future look like?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Marekani bado inaitumia ndege hii ya kivita ya B-52 miaka 70 baadaye?,Why is the US still using this B-52 fighter jet 70 years later?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('B-52', 'PRODUCT'), ('70 years later', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ifahamu teknolojia mpya inatoa matumaini kwa wanaume walioambiwa hawana uwezo wa kuzalisha,Know that new technology gives hope to men who were told they were unable to produce,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi makubaliano ya sekta ya afya kati ya Marekani na nchi za Afrika yalivyozua maoni yanayokinzana,How the health sector agreement between the United States and African countries created conflicting opinions,-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Armed fighters attack multiple towns across Mali,Armed fighters attack multiple towns across Mali,-1.0,negative,"[('Mali', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Saudi-led coalition pledges ‘unprecedented’ force against Houthi threats,Saudi-led coalition pledges ‘unprecedented’ force against Houthi threats,0.0,neutral,"[('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('Houthi', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Les Blues lead the way: Key takeaways from World Cup Round of 32,Les Blues lead the way: Key takeaways from World Cup Round of 32,0.0,neutral,"[('Les Blues', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup Round', 'EVENT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Cape Verde fans celebrate history despite loss,Cape Verde fans celebrate history despite loss,0.0,neutral,"[('Cape Verde', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Taylor Swift and Travis Kelce marry at NYC’s Madison Square Garden,Taylor Swift and Travis Kelce marry at NYC’s Madison Square Garden,0.0,neutral,"[('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Travis Kelce', 'PERSON'), ('NYC’s Madison Square Garden', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Trump praises army, rails against communism on eve of US 250th anniversary","Trump praises army, rails against communism on eve of US 250th anniversary",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,In form France meet giant killers Paraguay in World Cup last-16 clash,In form France meet giant killers Paraguay in World Cup last-16 clash,-1.0,negative,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('World Cup last-16', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Could Israel really build settlements in Gaza?,Could Israel really build settlements in Gaza?,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Trump calls communism a ‘mortal threat’ at US 250th birthday event,Trump calls communism a ‘mortal threat’ at US 250th birthday event,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('250th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Which teams are in the FIFA World Cup Round of 16, and what’s the schedule?","Which teams are in the FIFA World Cup Round of 16, and what’s the schedule?",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Round', 'EVENT'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,From Aldur to orbit: The remarkable journey of Chikkamagaluru boy-turned-Pixxel CEO,From Aldur to orbit: The remarkable journey of Chikkamagaluru boy-turned-Pixxel CEO,0.0,neutral,"[('Aldur', 'PERSON'), ('Chikkamagaluru', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Chandannagar’s jalbhara gets GI tag: The 220-year-old Bengali sweet that began as a wedding prank,Chandannagar’s jalbhara gets GI tag: The 220-year-old Bengali sweet that began as a wedding prank,0.0,neutral,"[('Chandannagar', 'ORG'), ('GI', 'ORG'), ('220-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Bengali', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,From ‘Legally Blonde’ to ‘Elle’: The fashion evolution of Elle Woods,From ‘Legally Blonde’ to ‘Elle’: The fashion evolution of Elle Woods,0.0,neutral,"[('Elle Woods', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Spin cycle: assessing India’s portfolio of Test tweakers,Spin cycle: assessing India’s portfolio of Test tweakers,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,This picture book raises awareness about adoption,This picture book raises awareness about adoption,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,MIB steps up pressure on Telegram; seeks proactive action against piracy,MIB steps up pressure on Telegram; seeks proactive action against piracy,0.0,neutral,"[('MIB', 'ORG'), ('Telegram', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Mamata Banerjee faces fresh jolt as TMC Bengal chief Chandrima Bhattacharya resigns,Mamata Banerjee faces fresh jolt as TMC Bengal chief Chandrima Bhattacharya resigns,0.0,neutral,"[('Mamata Banerjee', 'ORG'), ('Chandrima Bhattacharya', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"More Chinese investment good for larger relationship, says India’s envoy to China","More Chinese investment good for larger relationship, says India’s envoy to China",1.0,positive,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,MHA designates 23 Pakistan-based individuals as ‘terrorists’ under UAPA,MHA designates 23 Pakistan-based individuals as ‘terrorists’ under UAPA,-1.0,negative,"[('23', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Battery apps taken down in India after stalled e-rickshaw rides,Battery apps taken down in India after stalled e-rickshaw rides,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Taylor Swift marries Travis Kelce in NYC ceremony officiated by Adam Sandler,Taylor Swift marries Travis Kelce in NYC ceremony officiated by Adam Sandler,0.0,neutral,"[('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Travis Kelce', 'PERSON'), ('NYC', 'LOC'), ('Adam Sandler', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Brutal heat cancels Fourth of July events, from DC to Philadelphia","Brutal heat cancels Fourth of July events, from DC to Philadelphia",0.0,neutral,"[('Fourth of July', 'DATE'), ('DC', 'GPE'), ('Philadelphia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Keiko Fujimori declared winner of Peru's presidential election weeks after vote,Keiko Fujimori declared winner of Peru's presidential election weeks after vote,1.0,positive,"[('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Peru', 'GPE'), ('presidential election weeks', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Large crowds gather in Tehran on first day of Ayatollah Khamenei's funeral,Large crowds gather in Tehran on first day of Ayatollah Khamenei's funeral,0.0,neutral,"[('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('first day', 'DATE'), (""Ayatollah Khamenei's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ukrainian suspect hunted by police after Monaco bomb attack was 'disguised as a man',Ukrainian suspect hunted by police after Monaco bomb attack was 'disguised as a man',-1.0,negative,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Monaco', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Anguished families left to identify Venezuela quake victims at makeshift morgue,Anguished families left to identify Venezuela quake victims at makeshift morgue,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'Flamingo Revolution' takes off as thousands demand Albanian PM's resignation,'Flamingo Revolution' takes off as thousands demand Albanian PM's resignation,0.0,neutral,"[(""Albanian PM's"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"France records 2,025 excess deaths at peak of heatwave as Europe braces for more extreme weather","France records 2,025 excess deaths at peak of heatwave as Europe braces for more extreme weather",-1.0,negative,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('2,025', 'CARDINAL'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Row after Indian state drops eggs from school lunch menu,Row after Indian state drops eggs from school lunch menu,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nasa launches mission to save falling space telescope,Nasa launches mission to save falling space telescope,0.0,neutral,"[('Nasa', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Momentary Unity at a Funeral Masks Deep Divisions Among Iran’s Leaders,Momentary Unity at a Funeral Masks Deep Divisions Among Iran’s Leaders,0.0,neutral,"[('Momentary Unity', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Rwanda, July 4 Is Liberation Day From Genocide","In Rwanda, July 4 Is Liberation Day From Genocide",0.0,neutral,"[('Rwanda', 'GPE'), ('July 4 Is Liberation Day', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Trump’s Travel Crackdown Has a Winner: Mexican Tourism,Trump’s Travel Crackdown Has a Winner: Mexican Tourism,1.0,positive,"[('Trump’s Travel Crackdown', 'ORG'), ('Mexican', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Australia Tried to Push Back on China. China Pushed Harder.,Australia Tried to Push Back on China. China Pushed Harder.,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia Tried', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Long Lines for Gas Shatter the Illusion of Normalcy in Wartime Russia,Long Lines for Gas Shatter the Illusion of Normalcy in Wartime Russia,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,China Defends Widely Criticized ‘Ethnic Unity’ Law,China Defends Widely Criticized ‘Ethnic Unity’ Law,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A U.S. Independence Celebration Damaged a Museum in Belgium,A U.S. Independence Celebration Damaged a Museum in Belgium,0.0,neutral,"[('Belgium', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Officials Believed Israel Was Plotting to Kill Iranian Negotiators,U.S. Officials Believed Israel Was Plotting to Kill Iranian Negotiators,-1.0,negative,"[('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Can the World’s Largest Stadium Explain the Global Economy?,Can the World’s Largest Stadium Explain the Global Economy?,0.0,neutral,"[('the World’s Largest Stadium Explain', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Hopes for Investment in Iran Would Break With Decades of History,U.S. Hopes for Investment in Iran Would Break With Decades of History,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Decades', 'DATE')]"
