Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El niño que pasó 2 años escondido en un bosque para escapar de los nazis,The boy who spent 2 years hiding in a forest to escape the Nazis,-0.1,"[('2 years', 'DATE'), ('Nazis', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Somalilandia, el territorio que declaró su independencia hace más de 30 años y que solo Israel reconoce como nación soberana","Somaliland, the territory that declared its independence more than 30 years ago and that only Israel recognizes as a sovereign nation",0.25,"[('more than 30 years ago', 'DATE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La mujer que luchó por resolver el secuestro de su esposo en un caso que se convirtió en un misterio nacional,The woman who fought to solve the kidnapping of her husband in a case that became a national mystery,0.0,[]
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La Estación Espacial Internacional cumple 25 años en órbita: la historia en números del objeto más caro jamás construido,The International Space Station celebrates 25 years in orbit: the story in numbers of the most expensive object ever built,0.0,"[('The International Space Station', 'ORG'), ('25 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Invitamos a un hombre a casa para Navidad y se quedó con nosotros 45 años""","""We invited a man home for Christmas and he stayed with us for 45 years""",0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('45 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ढाका पुलिस का दावा, 'उस्मान हादी की हत्या के मुख्य अभियुक्त भारत भाग गए'","Dhaka Police claims, 'The main accused in the murder of Osman Hadi fled to India'",0.16666666666666666,"[('Dhaka Police', 'ORG'), ('Osman Hadi', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नेपाल में प्रधानमंत्री पद के उम्मीदवार बने बालेन शाह को जानिए, महज़ तीन सालों में कैसे राजनीति में छाए","Know Balen Shah, who became the Prime Ministerial candidate in Nepal, how he became famous in politics in just three years.",0.5,"[('Know Balen Shah', 'PERSON'), ('Nepal', 'GPE'), ('just three years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,आरएसएस-बीजेपी को लेकर दिग्विजय सिंह के बयान पर सुप्रिया श्रीनेत ने क्या कहा?","Live, what did Supriya Srinet say on Digvijay Singh's statement regarding RSS-BJP?",0.13636363636363635,"[('Supriya Srinet', 'PERSON'), (""Digvijay Singh's"", 'PERSON'), ('RSS-BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,आसमान में सुराख़ करने का हुनर बताने वाले शायर दुष्यंत कुमार - विवेचना,"Poet Dushyant Kumar, who showed the skill of making holes in the sky - Discussion",0.0,"[('Kumar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मध्य प्रदेश: बीजेपी नेता पर महिला के साथ रेप का आरोप, सोशल मीडिया पर धमकी देने का वीडियो वायरल","Madhya Pradesh: BJP leader accused of raping woman, video of threat goes viral on social media",0.03333333333333333,"[('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पीएम नरेंद्र मोदी और राहुल गांधी, साल 2025 ने इन पर कैसा असर डाला और आगे की राह क्या होगी?","PM Narendra Modi and Rahul Gandhi, how did the year 2025 affect them and what will be the way forward?",0.0,"[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('the year 2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,केरल के पुलिसकर्मी ने ऐसा क्या किया कि झारखंड के मज़दूर ने कहा- 'मिलेगा तो थैंक्यू बोलेगा',"What did the policeman from Kerala do that the laborer from Jharkhand said - 'If he gets it, he will say thank you'",0.0,"[('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('Jharkhand', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तीन करोड़ की बीमा राशि के लिए पिता को सांप से कटवाने का मामला,Case of father getting bitten by a snake for insurance amount of three crores,0.0,"[('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दिग्विजय सिंह ने आरएसएस-बीजेपी की क्यों की तारीफ़, कांग्रेस में सुधार की बात भी कही","Why did Digvijay Singh praise RSS-BJP, also talked about reform in Congress?",0.0,"[('Digvijay Singh', 'PERSON'), ('RSS-BJP', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como Colômbia se tornou uma das melhores economias de 2025 e quais desafios enfrenta?,How did Colombia become one of the best economies of 2025 and what challenges does it face?,1.0,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Após fuga de ex-diretor da PRF, Moraes ordena prisão domiciliar de outros 10 condenados por golpe: o que se sabe","After the escape of a former PRF director, Moraes orders house arrest for another 10 people convicted of a coup: what is known",-0.025,"[('PRF', 'ORG'), ('Moraes', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Os 20 melhores lugares para uma viagem internacional em 2026, segundo a BBC","The 20 best places for an international trip in 2026, according to the BBC",0.5,"[('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O povoado russo criado no Uruguai para ser 'paraíso na Terra' — mas que viveu um inferno,The Russian village created in Uruguay to be 'paradise on Earth' - but lived through hell,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Uruguay', 'GPE'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Cristãos estão sendo perseguidos na Nigéria, como diz Trump?","Are Christians being persecuted in Nigeria, as Trump says?",0.0,"[('Christians', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Este calor não é normal': como é a vida em cidades onde os termômetros chegam a 50ºC,'This heat is not normal': what life is like in cities where thermometers reach 50ºC,-0.075,[]
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como nosso corpo sofre (e se adapta) em uma onda de calor,How our bodies suffer (and adapt) in a heat wave,0.0,[]
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O Universo está ficando sem novas estrelas?,Is the Universe running out of new stars?,0.13636363636363635,"[('Universe', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Por que zebras, pandas e outros animais são pretos e brancos?","Why are zebras, pandas and other animals black and white?",-0.09722222222222221,"[('pandas', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Всплеск антисемитизма и отношение к Израилю. Почему евреи Британии переживают самые серьезные перемены за 60 лет,A surge of anti-Semitism and attitudes towards Israel. Why Britain's Jews are experiencing their biggest changes in 60 years,0.0,"[('anti-Semitism', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Jews', 'NORP'), ('60 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский встретился с Карни; российская армия заявила о контроле над Мирноградом, в ВСУ это не подтверждают","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: Zelensky met with Carney; The Russian army announced control over Mirnograd, the Ukrainian Armed Forces do not confirm this",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Carney', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Mirnograd', 'GPE'), ('the Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Италии арестованы девять обвиняемых в сборе миллионов евро для боевиков ХАМАС,Nine accused of raising millions of euros for Hamas militants arrested in Italy,0.0,"[('Nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Британии выпускникам предложат сделать «год перерыва» и попробовать послужить в армии,"In Britain, graduates will be offered to take a “gap year” and try to serve in the army",0.0,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('a “gap year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"НАБУ заявило, что выявило крупную схему подкупа депутатов украинского парламента. Что об этом известно?",NABU said it had identified a major bribery scheme against members of the Ukrainian parliament. What is known about this?,0.0625,"[('NABU', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Твардовский, память и правда в СССР и в современной России","Tvardovsky, memory and truth in the USSR and in modern Russia",0.2,"[('Tvardovsky', 'PERSON'), ('USSR', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Сначала K-поп, теперь K-еда. Как корейская кухня завоевывает Британию","First K-pop, now K-food. How Korean cuisine is conquering Britain",0.25,"[('First K-pop', 'ORG'), ('Korean', 'NORP'), ('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Израиль первым в мире признал независимость Сомалиленда, отколовшегося от Сомали","Israel was the first in the world to recognize the independence of Somaliland, which broke away from Somalia.",0.25,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Somaliland', 'PRODUCT'), ('Somalia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трое братьев из Дагестана в «Манчестер Юнайтед» и один в MMA: история семьи Ибрагимовых,Three brothers from Dagestan to Manchester United and one to MMA: the story of the Ibragimov family,0.0,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dagestan', 'GPE'), ('Manchester United', 'PERSON'), ('Ibragimov', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Лицо, известное многим как „Юра Унитаз“». Кто может возглавить российские беспилотные войска","""The face known to many as 'Yura Toilet'."" Who can lead Russian unmanned troops",0.15555555555555556,"[(""Yura Toilet'"", 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、トランプ氏と近くフロリダで会談予定と表明　戦争終結に向け,Zelenskiy announces plans to meet with Trump in Florida soon to end the war,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエルがソマリランドを承認、世界初　ソマリアや近隣国は非難,"Israel recognizes Somaliland, world's first, Somalia and neighboring countries condemn",0.25,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Somaliland', 'PRODUCT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Somalia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,シリアのモスクで金曜礼拝中に爆発、少なくとも8人死亡,Explosion at Syrian mosque during Friday prayers kills at least 8 people,-0.3,"[('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('at least 8', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル北部で襲撃事件、2人死亡　容疑者はパレスチナ人と当局,Two killed in attack in northern Israel; suspects are Palestinians and authorities,-0.2,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍、ナイジェリアの「イスラム国」に「強力な」攻撃実施　トランプ氏が発表,"U.S. military launches ""strong"" attack on Islamic State in Nigeria, Trump announces",0.16666666666666663,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Islamic State', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トルコ、「イスラム国」メンバー115人を拘束　年末年始の攻撃を計画した疑い,Türkiye detains 115 Islamic State members suspected of planning year-end and New Year attacks,0.13636363636363635,"[('Türkiye', 'ORG'), ('115', 'CARDINAL'), ('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('year-end', 'DATE'), ('New Year', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,教皇レオ、ウクライナでの戦争を終わらせる「勇気」促す　初のクリスマス演説,Pope Leo urges “courage” to end war in Ukraine in first Christmas speech,0.25,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英国王、分断された世界での結束を呼びかける　クリスマス恒例メッセージ,British King's annual Christmas message calls for unity in a divided world,0.0,"[(""British King's"", 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 アメリカ人教皇とアメリカ政府、仲たがいしているのか,[Commentary] Are the American Pope and the US government at odds?,0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Shambulizi dhidi ya Ukraine linaonyesha 'mtazamo wa kweli' wa Putin, Zelensky asema","Attack on Ukraine shows Putin's 'true attitude', Zelensky says",0.35,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"AFCON 2025: Uganda, Tanzania zatoshana nguvu, hatima ya 16 bora shakani","AFCON 2025: Uganda, Tanzania are strong, the fate of the best 16 in doubt",0.7166666666666667,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Uganda', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Trump apinga uwezekano wa Marekani kuitambua rasmi Somaliland,Trump opposes the possibility of the United States officially recognizing Somaliland,0.0,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Somaliland', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumapili: Chelsea na Leeds zinamfuatilia McAtee,European Football Rumors Sunday: Chelsea and Leeds are tracking McAtee,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Chelsea', 'PERSON'), ('Leeds', 'GPE'), ('McAtee', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini awamu ya pili ya usitishaji mapigano Gaza imekwama?,Why is the second phase of the cease-fire in Gaza stalled?,0.0,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nani anaweza kumrithi kocha wa Man City Guardiola?,Who can succeed Man City coach Guardiola?,0.0,"[('Man City', 'GPE'), ('Guardiola', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mzaha kuhusu upara wangu ulivyobadilisha maisha yangu,How a joke about my baldness changed my life,0.0,[]
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Marekani yafanya shambulizi Nigeria,  dhidi ya nani na kwa nini?","The United States is attacking Nigeria, against whom and why?",0.0,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Muonekano wa Yesu ulikuwa vipi, Wanahistoria wanasema nini?","What was the appearance of Jesus, what do Historians say?",0.0,"[('Jesus', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Habari 10 zilizosomwa sana BBC mwaka 2025,10 most read BBC news in 2025,0.5,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
