Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Las razones detrás de la nueva ola de protestas en Irán,The reasons behind the new wave of protests in Iran,-0.13181818181818183,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Neorrurales"": los jóvenes españoles que han abandonado las grandes ciudades para asentarse en el campo escapando de los altos precios de la vivienda","""Neorrurals"": young Spaniards who have left big cities to settle in the countryside, escaping high housing prices",0.065,"[('Spaniards', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""El olor a pólvora era fuerte"": testigos hablan de la presunta explosión que destruyó una estructura en la Alta Guajira de Venezuela","""The smell of gunpowder was strong"": witnesses speak of the alleged explosion that destroyed a structure in the Alta Guajira of Venezuela",0.16666666666666663,"[('the Alta Guajira', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué se sabe del incendio en un bar de un centro de esquí en Suiza en el que murieron 40 personas,What is known about the fire in a bar at a ski resort in Switzerland in which 40 people died,0.0,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('40', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Un terremoto de magnitud 6,5 sacude el centro y el sur de México",A 6.5 magnitude earthquake shakes central and southern Mexico,0.0,"[('6.5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अमेरिका के हमले की ख़बर पर वेनेज़ुएला की पहली प्रतिक्रिया","Live, Venezuela's first reaction to the news of US attack",0.19318181818181818,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पाकिस्तान के स्पीकर ने जयशंकर को 'चालाक नेता' कहा, ढाका में हाथ मिलाने का वाक़या बताया","Pakistan speaker calls Jaishankar a 'cunning leader', narrates the incident of handshake in Dhaka",0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Jaishankar', 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सौ साल की डॉ. लक्ष्मीबाई, जिन्होंने घर बेचकर 3.4 करोड़ रुपये एम्स को दे दिए","Hundred year old Dr. Lakshmibai, who sold her house and gave Rs 3.4 crore to AIIMS",0.1,"[('Hundred year old', 'DATE'), ('Lakshmibai', 'PERSON'), ('3.4', 'CARDINAL'), ('AIIMS', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ख़ालिदा ज़िया के भारत के जलपाईगुड़ी में जन्म और उनके पिता इस्कंदर मजूमदार के बारे में जानिए,"Know about Khaleda Zia's birth in Jalpaiguri, India and her father Iskander Majumdar",0.0,"[(""Khaleda Zia's"", 'PERSON'), ('Jalpaiguri', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Iskander Majumdar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश के क्रिकेटर मुस्तफ़िज़ुर रहमान को बीसीसीआई ने केकेआर से हटाने के लिए कहा,BCCI asks to remove Bangladesh cricketer Mustafizur Rahman from KKR,0.0,"[('BCCI', 'ORG'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Mustafizur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('KKR', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,बांग्लादेश और नेपाल में होने वाले चुनाव इन वजहों से भारत के लिए होंगे अहम- द लेंस, अवधि 29,54","Video, Elections to be held in Bangladesh and Nepal will be important for India for these reasons - The Lens, Duration 29,54",0.4,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Nepal', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चीन की बीवाईडी ने एलन मस्क की टेस्ला को पीछे छोड़ा,China's BYD overtakes Elon Musk's Tesla,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('BYD', 'ORG'), (""Elon Musk's"", 'PERSON'), ('Tesla', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,स्विट्ज़रलैंड के बार में आग क्या शैंपेन की बोतलों पर लगाए गए स्पार्कलर से लगी थी?,Was the Swiss bar fire caused by sparklers placed on champagne bottles?,0.0,"[('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ज़ोहरान ममदानी के उमर ख़ालिद को लिखे नोट पर बीजेपी ने कहा, 'भारत के अंदरूनी मामलों में दख़ल बर्दाश्त नहीं'","On Zohran Mamdani's note to Omar Khalid, BJP said, 'Interference in India's internal affairs will not be tolerated'",0.0,"[(""Zohran Mamdani's"", 'PERSON'), ('Omar Khalid', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quais eleições América Latina terá em 2026 (e o quanto Trump pode influir nelas),What elections will Latin America have in 2026 (and how much can Trump influence them),0.2,"[('Latin America', 'LOC'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que estudo citado por 25 anos para defender agrotóxico mais usado no Brasil foi invalidado,Why a study cited for 25 years to defend the most used pesticide in Brazil was invalidated,0.5,"[('25 years', 'DATE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os motivos que levaram Alexandre de Moraes a decretar prisão de Filipe Martins,The reasons that led Alexandre de Moraes to arrest Filipe Martins,-0.05,"[('Alexandre de Moraes', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Disseram que meu pai era um dublê': a mulher que foi induzida pela mãe a acreditar que era perseguida pela máfia,'They said my father was a stuntman': the woman who was induced by her mother to believe she was being chased by the mafia,0.0,"[('mafia', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,'Foguetinho': o gari que faz acrobacias e transformou a coleta de lixo em sucesso nas redes sociais, Duration 2,06","Video, 'Foguetinho': the street sweeper who performs stunts and turned garbage collection into a success on social media, Duration 2.06",0.16666666666666666,"[('2.06', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Velas em garrafas de champanhe são causa provável do incêndio na Suíça, diz procuradora","Candles in champagne bottles are likely cause of fire in Switzerland, says prosecutor",0.0,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Vídeo mostra homem tentando apagar fogo em bar na Suíça; ao menos 40 pessoas morreram, Duration 0,09","Video,Video shows man trying to put out fire in bar in Switzerland; at least 40 people died, Duration 0.09",-0.3,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('at least 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('0.09', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,'Achei que ia sufocar': o relato de um dos sobreviventes de incêndio na Suíça, Duration 0,43","Video,'I thought I was going to suffocate': the account of one of the fire survivors in Switzerland, Duration 0.43",0.0,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('0.43', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Em questão de segundos, todo o teto estava em chamas': os relatos de sobreviventes do incêndio que matou ao menos 40 na Suíça","'In a matter of seconds, the entire ceiling was on fire': reports from survivors of the fire that killed at least 40 in Switzerland",-0.16666666666666666,"[('seconds', 'TIME'), ('at least 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Каракасе слышны взрывы. СМИ пишут, что Трамп отдал приказ нанести удары по военным объектам Венесуэлы",Explosions are heard in Caracas. The media write that Trump gave the order to strike military targets in Venezuela,-0.1,"[('Caracas', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Удар в новогоднюю ночь: что известно об атаке на ресторан в оккупированной Херсонской области?,Strike on New Year's Eve: what is known about the attack on a restaurant in the occupied Kherson region?,0.13636363636363635,"[(""New Year's Eve"", 'EVENT'), ('Kherson', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Конфликт в Йемене: союзники Саудовской Аравии пошли в наступление на союзников Эмиратов,Conflict in Yemen: Saudi Arabia's allies go on the offensive against Emirati allies,0.0,"[('Yemen', 'GPE'), (""Saudi Arabia's"", 'GPE'), ('Emirati', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Харькове уже двое погибших; офис Зеленского возглавит глава разведки Буданов","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: two dead already in Kharkov; Zelensky's office will be headed by intelligence chief Budanov",-0.2,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kharkov', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Budanov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Зеленский назвал нового главу офиса президента: вопреки многим прогнозам им станет глава военной разведки Кирилл Буданов,"Zelensky named the new head of the presidential office: contrary to many forecasts, he will be the head of military intelligence Kirill Budanov",0.1787878787878788,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Kirill Budanov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Я видел, как люди горели». Что рассказывают очевидцы пожара на швейцарском курорте","""I saw people burning."" What eyewitnesses say about the fire at the Swiss resort",0.0,"[('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп: США вмешаются, если Иран будет убивать протестующих",Trump: US will intervene if Iran kills protesters,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В ЦРУ считают, что украинские дроны не целились в дом Путина. К попыткам переубедить США подключился шеф российского ГРУ",The CIA believes that the Ukrainian drones were not aimed at Putin's house. The chief of the Russian GRU joined in attempts to convince the United States,0.0,"[('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Нас просто обманывают». Более 27 млн американцев остались в 2026 году без медицинской страховки,“We are simply being deceived.” More than 27 million Americans will remain without health insurance in 2026,0.25,"[('More than 27 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В пожаре на швейцарском горнолыжном курорте погибли около 40 человек, сообщила полиция","About 40 people have died in a fire at a Swiss ski resort, police said.",0.0,"[('About 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,シャンパンボトルの手持ち花火が原因か、スイスのバー火災で多数死亡,Many killed in Swiss bar fire possibly caused by hand-held fireworks from champagne bottles,0.075,"[('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏が側近人事、大統領府長官に情報機関トップのブダノフ氏　国防相も交代,"Mr. Zelensky reshuffles his close aides, with Mr. Budanov, head of the intelligence agency, appointed as head of the presidential palace; defense minister also replaced.",0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Budanov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イランで物価高騰への抗議が拡大、デモ隊と治安部隊の衝突で死者も,"Protests against rising prices expand in Iran, with deaths resulting from clashes between demonstrators and security forces",0.0,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,メキシコでマグニチュード6.5の地震、少なくとも2人死亡,Magnitude 6.5 earthquake kills at least 2 people in Mexico,-0.3,"[('Magnitude 6.5', 'PERSON'), ('at least 2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,マスク氏のAI「Grok」に服をデジタルで消された……「人間性を奪われた」と被害女性,Victim says her clothes were digitally erased by Musk's AI ``Grok''... ``My humanity was taken away'',-0.037500000000000006,"[('Victim', 'PERSON'), ('Grok', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、医師の推奨量より多くアスピリンを服用と　米紙インタビューで健康を強調,"Trump takes more aspirin than doctor recommended, emphasizes health in US newspaper interview",0.5,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】マムダニ新NY市長が直面する四つの課題,[Commentary] Four challenges facing New York City Mayor Mamdani,0.13636363636363635,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('New York City', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スイスのスキーリゾートのバーで出火、多数死傷,"Fire breaks out at bar at Swiss ski resort, many dead and injured",0.15,"[('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU外交トップ、ウクライナがプーチン氏公邸を攻撃したとするロシアの主張を否定　和平プロセスへの妨害と非難,"EU diplomat denies Russia's claim that Ukraine attacked Putin's residence, accuses it of interfering with peace process",0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Venezuela yashambuliwa huku mvutano na Marekani ukiendelea","Directly, Venezuela is attacked while the tension with the United States continues",0.1,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanasiasa maarufu Tanzania walioaga dunia 2025,Famous Tanzanian politicians who passed away in 2025,0.5,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi Ulaya Jumamosi: Rodrygo atakiwa Arsenal, Morgan, Nwaneri Chelsea","Rumors in Europe Saturday: Rodrygo wants Arsenal, Morgan, Nwaneri Chelsea",0.2,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Rodrygo wants Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Morgan', 'ORG'), ('Nwaneri Chelsea', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,AFCON 2025: Safari ya timu 16 kusaka robo fainali inaanza leo,AFCON 2025: The 16-team journey to the quarter-finals begins today,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kisiwa cha Marekani kisicho na magari, ni baiskeli na farasi tu","An American island with no cars, just bicycles and horses",0.0,"[('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Hiki ndicho kilichovunja ndoa ya Maresca na Chelsea, nani kurithi mikoba yake?","This is what broke the marriage of Maresca and Chelsea, who will inherit his bags?",0.0,"[('Maresca', 'GPE'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, siasa za Kenya 2026 zinaanzaje bila Raila Odinga?",How does the politics of Kenya 2026 begin without Raila Odinga?,0.0,"[('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('Raila Odinga', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marais watano wa Afrika walioondoka madarakani kwa hiari,Five African presidents who left power voluntarily,0.0,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Israel imezishambulia nchi hizi 7?,Why has Israel attacked these 7 countries?,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_03,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Roma inataka kumsajili Mohamed Salah,European Football Rumors Friday: Roma want to sign Mohamed Salah,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Mohamed Salah', 'PERSON')]"
