Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué se sabe del nuevo plan ""secreto"" de Estados Unidos para poner fin a la guerra entre Rusia y Ucrania","What is known about the United States' new ""secret"" plan to end the war between Russia and Ukraine",-0.13181818181818183,"[(""the United States'"", 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""No me silenciarán"": el joven francés que lucha contra el narcotráfico en Marsella y cuyos dos hermanos fueron asesinados","""They will not silence me"": the young Frenchman who fights against drug trafficking in Marseille and whose two brothers were murdered",0.1,"[('Frenchman', 'PERSON'), ('Marseille', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Condenan a 20 años de cárcel en México a una mujer por el asesinato de dos hermanos surfistas australianos y un amigo de estos,A woman is sentenced to 20 years in prison in Mexico for the murder of two Australian surfer brothers and their friend,0.0,"[('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Skhūl I, el niño que vivió hace 140.000 años y que científicos creen que es la mezcla más antigua entre un Homo sapiens y un neandertal","Skhūl I, the boy who lived 140,000 years ago and who scientists believe is the oldest mix between Homo sapiens and a Neanderthal",0.0,"[('140,000 years ago', 'DATE'), ('Homo', 'ORG'), ('Neanderthal', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La impresionante imagen de un hombre en caída libre frente al Sol,The impressive image of a man in free fall in front of the Sun,0.7,"[('Sun', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"फ़ातिमा बॉश बनीं मिस यूनिवर्स, इन्हें लेकर इवेंट में हुआ काफ़ी विवाद","Fatima Bosch became Miss Universe, there was a lot of controversy about her at the event",0.0,"[('Fatima Bosch', 'PERSON'), ('Universe', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,बिहार में उपमुख्यमंत्री पद मांगने के सवाल पर क्या बोले चिराग","Live, what did Chirag say on the question of seeking the post of Deputy Chief Minister in Bihar?",0.13636363636363635,"[('Chirag', 'PERSON'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,धर्मस्थला मामला: एसआईटी ने शिकायतकर्ता के ख़िलाफ़ दाखिल की रिपोर्ट,Dharamsthala case: SIT files report against complainant,0.0,"[('Dharamsthala', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नीतीश कुमार मुश्किलों के बावजूद बिहार में इतने प्रासंगिक क्यों हैं?,Why is Nitish Kumar so relevant in Bihar despite difficulties?,0.4,"[('Nitish', 'NORP'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दीपक प्रकाश: ना एमएलए ना एमएलसी, फिर भी नीतीश सरकार में मंत्री बने उपेंद्र कुशवाहा के बेटे","Deepak Prakash: Neither MLA nor MLC, yet Upendra Kushwaha's son became a minister in Nitish government.",0.0,"[('MLA', 'PERSON'), ('MLC', 'ORG'), (""Upendra Kushwaha's"", 'PERSON'), ('Nitish', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'16 साल की उम्र में मुझ पर सीआईए ने किए थे प्रयोग, अब मैं मुकदमा कर रही हूं'","'At the age of 16, CIA conducted experiments on me, now I am suing'",0.0,"[('the age of 16', 'DATE'), ('CIA', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दिल्ली: साल में इतने दिन लोग ज़हरीली हवा में सांस लेने को हैं मजबूर,Delhi: People are forced to breathe poisonous air for so many days in a year.,0.09999999999999998,"[('so many days in', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"अमेरिकी रिपोर्ट में दावा- 'भारत के साथ सैन्य संघर्ष में पाकिस्तान को मिली बढ़त', कांग्रेस ने किया सरकार से सवाल","US report claims- 'Pakistan has got advantage in military conflict with India', Congress questions the government",-0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नीतीश की नई सरकार में शामिल तीन महिला और एक मुस्लिम मंत्री के बारे में जानें,Know about three women and one Muslim minister included in Nitish's new government,0.13636363636363635,"[('about three', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Nitish', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump suspende tarifas de 40% sobre café, carne, frutas e outros produtos agrícolas do Brasil","Trump suspends 40% tariffs on coffee, meat, fruit and other agricultural products from Brazil",-0.125,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('40%', 'PERCENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Suspensão de tarifaço 'é passo na direção certa', diz Celso Amorim","Suspension of tariffs 'is a step in the right direction', says Celso Amorim",0.2857142857142857,"[('Celso Amorim', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Custo de vida impactou a agenda política de Trump: o que disse a imprensa internacional sobre a suspensão do tarifaço,Cost of living impacted Trump's political agenda: what the international press said about the suspension of tariffs,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Pavilhão da COP30 atingido por incêndio é reaberto, mas reuniões só serão retomadas na sexta","COP30 pavilion hit by fire reopens, but meetings will only resume on Friday",0.0,"[('Friday', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,VÍDEO: O momento em que COP30 é evacuada por causa de incêndio, Duration 1,01","Video,VIDEO: The moment COP30 is evacuated because of fire, Duration 1.01",0.0,"[('1.01', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Fidelidade ao PT e religião: quem é Jorge Messias, indicado de Lula ao STF","Loyalty to the PT and religion: who is Jorge Messias, Lula’s nominee to the STF",0.0,"[('Jorge Messias', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que já escreveu Messias: 'ultraliberalismo' de Bolsonaro, 'autoritarismo' da Corte e 'monopólio' das big techs","What Messias has already written: Bolsonaro's 'ultraliberalism', the Court's 'authoritarianism' and big tech's 'monopoly'",0.0,"[('Messias', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Ser perfeccionista é bom ou ruim?,Is being a perfectionist good or bad?,5.551115123125783e-17,[]
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Tony Tornado, 95 anos: as 1001 vidas do homem que fez o Brasil assumir seu black power","Tony Tornado, 95 years old: the 1001 lives of the man who made Brazil assume its black power",-0.033333333333333326,"[('Tony Tornado', 'PERSON'), ('95 years old', 'DATE'), ('1001', 'DATE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Страна на салфетках. 30-летие Дейтонского соглашения о мире в Боснии и уроки для Дональда Трампа,Country on napkins. 30th anniversary of the Dayton Peace Agreement in Bosnia and lessons for Donald Trump,0.0,"[('30th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Bosnia', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Лукашенко анонсировал новую встречу с «американскими партнерами». Литва открыла свои КПП на границе. Главное в Беларуси за неделю,Lukashenko announced a new meeting with “American partners.” Lithuania has opened its border checkpoints. The main things in Belarus in a week,0.101010101010101,"[('Lukashenko', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Lithuania', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский готов работать над пунктами мирного плана Трампа, при российской атаке на Запорожье погибли пять человек","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky is ready to work on points of Trump’s peace plan, five people were killed in the Russian attack on Zaporozhye",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Делегация военных США обсудила в Киеве план окончания войны в Украине. Трамп его поддерживает, пишут американские СМИ","A US military delegation discussed a plan to end the war in Ukraine in Kyiv. Trump supports him, American media write",-0.05,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,На климатической конференции COP30 в Бразилии вспыхнул пожар. Участников пришлось эвакуировать,A fire broke out at the COP30 climate conference in Brazil. Participants had to be evacuated,0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Вместо детского смеха — плач и слезы». Истории погибших при российском ударе по Тернополю,"""Instead of children's laughter - crying and tears."" Stories of those killed in the Russian attack on Ternopil",-0.13333333333333333,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ternopil', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Бывшую сотрудницу Конгресса США обвинили в инсценировке нападения на саму себя,Former US Congressional staffer accused of faking attack on herself,0.0,"[('US Congressional', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Янтарь» у берегов Британии: насколько серьезен маневр российского разведывательного корабля?,"""Yantar"" off the coast of Britain: how serious is the maneuver of the Russian reconnaissance ship?",-0.16666666666666666,"[('Yantar', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Уже не только риторика. Спор Японии и Китая из-за Тайваня обострился: Пекин ограничил туризм и импорт товаров, Токио не извиняется","It's not just rhetoric anymore. The dispute between Japan and China over Taiwan has escalated: Beijing has limited tourism and imports of goods, Tokyo does not apologize",-0.07142857142857142,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('Beijing', 'GPE'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Первые санкции Трампа против России за войну в Украине вступают в силу. Сработают ли они?,Trump's first sanctions against Russia over the war in Ukraine take effect. Will they work?,0.25,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、民主党議員による米兵への呼びかけを扇動行為と非難　「死刑に値する」,Trump denounces Democratic congressman's call for US troops as sedition; ``Deserves the death penalty.'',0.0,"[('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英のコロナ対策、「不十分で遅すぎた」と独立調査委　政府対応で第1波の死者増えたと,"Britain's coronavirus response was 'insufficient and too slow', independent commission says, with government response leading to more deaths in first wave",0.11249999999999999,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、ウクライナに新たな和平案を提示　ゼレンスキー氏とトランプ氏が協議へ,US presents new peace plan to Ukraine; Zelenskyy and Trump to hold talks,0.13636363636363635,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskyy', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,米主導のガザ停戦監視センター、パレスチナ代表の姿はなく……BBCが取材, 所要時間 1,40","Video, US-led Gaza ceasefire monitoring center, no Palestinian representative in sight...BBC coverage, time required 1,40",-0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('1,40', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 デフリンピック、東京で100周年記念大会　パラとの違いや選手の思い,"[Commentary] Deaflympics, 100th anniversary event held in Tokyo - Differences from Para and athletes' thoughts",0.0,"[('Commentary] Deaflympics', 'ORG'), ('100th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('Para', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米放送規制当局がBBCに書簡、トランプ氏演説の編集めぐり,US broadcast regulator writes letter to BBC over editing of Trump speech,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ホワイトハウスから謝罪受けたと韓国・現代自動車CEO　米ジョージア州での強制捜査めぐり,"South Korea's Hyundai CEO says he received apology from White House over raid in Georgia, US",0.0,"[(""South Korea's"", 'GPE'), ('Hyundai', 'ORG'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、「エプスティーン・ファイル」公開を司法省に命じる法案に署名,Trump signs bill ordering Justice Department to release Epstein file,0.0,"[('Justice Department', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍高官がウクライナ入り、戦争終結に向け協議　米ロが新たな和平案用意と報じられるなか,"High-ranking US military officials enter Ukraine to hold talks towards ending the war, amid reports that the US and Russia are preparing a new peace plan",0.018181818181818174,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Zelensky kuzungumza na Trump baada ya Marekani kupendekeza mpango wa amani kati ya Urusi na Ukraine","Directly, Zelensky spoke with Trump after the United States proposed a peace plan between Russia and Ukraine",0.1,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Rais Samia aitetea Tume ya Oktoba 29, aipa miezi mitatu kujibu hoja 7","President Samia defended the October 29 Commission, giving three months to answer 7 points",0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON'), ('October 29 Commission', 'DATE'), ('three months', 'DATE'), ('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maelfu ya watoto wa Ukraine waliolazimishwa na Urusi kupigana dhidi ya nchi yao wenyewe,Thousands of Ukrainian children forced by Russia to fight against their own country,0.14999999999999997,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maridhiano Tanzania: Jumuiya ya Madola na mustakabali wa ghasia za uchaguzi,Reconciliation Tanzania: The Commonwealth and the future of electoral violence,0.0,"[('Commonwealth', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, uwezo wa kijeshi wa Venezuela ni upi na inawezaje kujibu mashambulizi ya Marekani?",What is Venezuela's military capability and how can it respond to US attacks?,-0.1,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Man Utd, Liverpool na Newcastle zapigana vikumbo kwa Anderson","European Football Rumors Friday: Man Utd, Liverpool and Newcastle battle it out for Anderson",0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Newcastle', 'GPE'), ('Anderson', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Gattuso yuko sahihi kwamba Ulaya haitendewi haki katika kufuzu Kombe la Dunia?",Is Gattuso right that Europe is not being treated fairly in qualifying for the World Cup?,0.4928571428571428,"[('Gattuso', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Tumeliondoa wingu jeusi la nyuklia la Iran kutoka kichwani mwako','We have removed Iran's nuclear black cloud from your head',-0.16666666666666666,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, chama cha Raila Odinga kitamudu hadi uchaguzi ujao?",Will Raila Odinga's party survive until the next election?,0.0,"[(""Will Raila Odinga's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_21,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"CHADEMA, ACT waikataa Tume ya Oktoba 29, CCM yaunga mkono","CHADEMA, ACT reject the October 29 Commission, CCM supports it",0.0,"[('October 29 Commission', 'DATE'), ('CCM', 'ORG')]"
