Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Trump anuncia la muerte del ""Niño Guerrero"", líder del Tren de Aragua, en una operación militar de EE.UU.","Trump announces the death of the ""Warrior Boy"", leader of the Aragua Train, in a US military operation.",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the Aragua Train', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las represalias de China contra Panamá después de que le revocaran las licencias de dos puertos en el canal,China's retaliation against Panama after the licenses of two ports in the canal were revoked,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Panama', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué algunos lugares quieren ser retirados de la Lista del Patrimonio Mundial de la Unesco,Why some places want to be removed from the UNESCO World Heritage List,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quién era Monika Silva Koniuszek, la activista polaca hallada muerta en Ecuador (y por qué la fiscalía pide ayuda internacional para la investigación)","Who was Monika Silva Koniuszek, the Polish activist found dead in Ecuador (and why the prosecution is asking for international help for the investigation)",0.0,neutral,"[('Monika Silva Koniuszek', 'PERSON'), ('Polish', 'NORP'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Por qué en EE.UU. le dicen al fútbol soccer y cuál es el origen de esa palabra (no, no la crearon los estadounidenses)","Why in the US do they call football soccer and what is the origin of that word (no, the Americans did not create it)",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las imágenes satelitales que muestran que más de 50 bases iraníes han sufrido los ataques de EE.UU. e Israel desde el inicio de la guerra,Satellite images showing that more than 50 Iranian bases have suffered attacks from the US and Israel since the start of the war,-0.3333,negative,"[('more than 50', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Sabelotodo, un ego desbordante y un orador tímido"": Elon Musk, el genio excéntrico al que no le bastó con ser el hombre más rico del mundo y el primer billonario de la historia","""Know-it-all, an overflowing ego and a timid speaker"": Elon Musk, the eccentric genius who was not enough to be the richest man in the world and the first billionaire in history",1.0,positive,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quién era la princesa Bajrakitiyabha de Tailandia, que murió tras pasar más de 3 años en coma","Who was Princess Bajrakitiyabha of Thailand, who died after spending more than 3 years in a coma?",0.0,neutral,"[('Bajrakitiyabha', 'GPE'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('more than 3 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Elecciones en Perú: Keiko Fujimori adelanta a Roberto Sánchez con una ventaja de unos 4.000 votos en las disputadas presidenciales,"Elections in Peru: Keiko Fujimori overtakes Roberto Sánchez with an advantage of about 4,000 votes in the presidential dispute",0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('about 4,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué son los precios dinámicos y por qué explican el altísimo costo de las entradas del Mundial,What are dynamic prices and why do they explain the very high cost of World Cup tickets?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,जोरहाट में वायु सेना विमान क्रैश में दो अफ़सरों और दो अग्निवीरवायु समेत पांच जवानों की मौत,Five soldiers including two officers and two Agniveervayu killed in Air Force plane crash in Jorhat,-1.0,negative,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Agniveervayu', 'GPE'), ('Air Force', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वीडियो,भारत में क्या क्षेत्रीय दलों की भूमिका लगातार सीमित होती जा रही है? - द लेंस, अवधि 38,48","Video: Is the role of regional parties increasingly limited in India? - The Lens, Duration 38,48",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,कल्याण बनर्जी बोले, 'बाग़ी सांसद बीजेपी की शरण में रहना चाहते हैं'","Live, Kalyan Banerjee said, 'Rebel MPs want to stay in the shelter of BJP'",0.0,neutral,"[('Kalyan Banerjee', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिकी हमले में तीन भारतीयों के मारे जाने के असर पर विदेशी मीडिया में छिड़ी ऐसी बहस,Such a debate broke out in the foreign media on the impact of the killing of three Indians in the American attack.,-1.0,negative,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,यूएई और क़तर के साथ ईरान के गुप्त समझौतों वाली रिपोर्ट पर दोनों देशों ने क्या कहा?,What did both the countries say on the report of Iran's secret agreements with UAE and Qatar?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारत अमेरिका के लिए क्या अब उस तरह से मायने नहीं रखता है? जयशंकर ट्रंप के दूसरे कार्यकाल पर बोले,Does India no longer matter to America in that way? Jaishankar spoke on Trump's second term,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Jaishankar', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ऐसे स्पर्म डोनर्स जो बच्चे की चाह रखने वाली महिलाओं का कर रहे हैं शोषण,Sperm donors who are exploiting women who want to have a child,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिकी हमलों से ईरान के भीतर कितना नुक़सान हुआ है?,How much damage has the US attacks caused inside Iran?,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"मीनाक्षी नटराजन को सुप्रीम कोर्ट से नहीं मिली राहत, अब क्या रास्ता बचा है?","Meenakshi Natarajan did not get relief from the Supreme Court, what option is left now?",0.0,neutral,"[('Meenakshi Natarajan', 'PERSON'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,कनेक्टेड दुनिया में अकेलेपन की क्या हैं मुश्किलें,What are the difficulties of loneliness in a connected world?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump anuncia morte do líder do grupo venezuelano Tren de Aragua em operação militar dos EUA,Trump announces death of leader of Venezuelan group Tren de Aragua in US military operation,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('Tren de Aragua', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Tren de Aragua: como facção venezuelana na mira de Trump age no Norte do Brasil,Tren de Aragua: how Venezuelan faction in Trump's sights acts in Northern Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Northern Brazil', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como conquistar a Gen Z? As campanhas presidenciais testam suas armas,How to win over Gen Z? Presidential campaigns test their weapons,1.0,positive,"[('Gen Z', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"O que você precisa saber sobre o Marrocos, adversário do Brasil na estreia deste sábado","What you need to know about Morocco, Brazil's opponent in this Saturday's debut",0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,4 a 1: EUA fazem estreia impressionante na Copa e goleiam o Paraguai,4 to 1: USA make impressive debut in the World Cup and thrash Paraguay,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que nos EUA o futebol se chama 'soccer' e qual a origem da palavra (que não foi criada pelos americanos),Why in the USA football is called 'soccer' and what is the origin of the word (which was not created by Americans),0.0,neutral,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Irã diz que acordo para encerrar conflito com os EUA 'nunca esteve tão próximo',Iran says agreement to end conflict with US 'has never been closer',-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Elon Musk se torna o primeiro trilionário do mundo após disparada das ações da SpaceX na estreia na bolsa,Elon Musk becomes the world's first trillionaire after SpaceX shares soar on stock market debut,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('SpaceX', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Com Neymar, álbum da Copa é atualizado: as chances matemáticas de conseguir completá-lo","With Neymar, World Cup album is updated: the mathematical chances of being able to complete it",0.0,neutral,"[('Neymar', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Tecnécio-99: o que é o material radiativo envolvido em incidente na USP e para que é usado,Technetium-99: what is the radioactive material involved in an incident at USP and what is it used for,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Иран заявляет, что соглашение с США приведет к возобновлению работы Ормузского пролива. Что отвечает Вашингтон?",Iran says the agreement with the US will lead to the reopening of the Strait of Hormuz. What is Washington's response?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('Washington', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трамп заявил, что американские военные убили лидера группировки Tren de Aragua",Trump said that the US military killed the leader of the Tren de Aragua group,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the Tren de Aragua', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: российские военные нанесли ночью удары по Донецкой, Днепропетровской и Запорожской областям","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Russian military carried out strikes in the Donetsk, Dnepropetrovsk and Zaporozhye regions at night",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Donetsk', 'GPE'), ('Dnepropetrovsk', 'GPE'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Поджоги, драки и воровство: что происходит, когда виртуальным городом управляют ИИ-агенты?","Arson, fights and theft: what happens when a virtual city is controlled by AI agents?",0.0,neutral,"[('Arson', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Проект бального зала Трампа при Белом доме за год стал вдвое больше и вдвое дороже,The Trump White House ballroom project has become twice as large and twice as expensive in a year.,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump White House', 'PERSON'), ('a year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Илон Маск стал первым в истории триллионером. SpaceX вышла на биржу, ее стоимость превысила два триллиона","Elon Musk became the first trillionaire in history. SpaceX went public, its value exceeded two trillion",0.0,neutral,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('SpaceX', 'PERSON'), ('two trillion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Диверсия в Москве: как убили полковника Давыдова? | Видеоподкаст «Что это было», Продолжительность 18,50","Video, Sabotage in Moscow: how was Colonel Davydov killed? | Video podcast “What was that”, Duration 18.50",-1.0,negative,"[('Video, Sabotage', 'ORG'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Davydov', 'PERSON'), ('18.50', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Канада заработала первое очко за всю историю участия в чемпионатах мира по футболу, сыграв вничью с Боснией. Как прошел матч?",Canada earned its first point in its history at the World Cup with a draw with Bosnia. How was the match?,0.0,neutral,"[('Canada', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Bosnia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Умер британский художник Дэвид Хокни — одна из главных фигур современного искусства,"British artist David Hockney, one of the main figures of modern art, has died",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('David Hockney', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,60 дней на переговоры? Что известно о будущем «меморандуме о взаимопонимании» Ирана и США,60 days for negotiations? What is known about the future “memorandum of understanding” between Iran and the United States,0.0,neutral,"[('60 days', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イラン、戦闘終結で合意ならホルムズ海峡は再開と,Iran will reopen Strait of Hormuz if agreement ends fighting,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,マスク氏が世界初の「トリリオネア」に　スペースXの株式公開で資産1兆ドル超え,"Musk becomes world's first 'trillionaire', with wealth exceeding $1 trillion after SpaceX goes public",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('$1 trillion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英現代画家ホックニー氏が死去、国王も追悼,"British contemporary painter Hockney dies, King pays tribute",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Hockney', 'GPE'), ('King', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,韓国・尹前大統領、さらに懲役30年の判決　北朝鮮にドローン飛ばすよう指示,"Former South Korean President Yoon sentenced to 30 years in prison, ordered to send drones to North Korea",0.0,neutral,"[('South Korean', 'NORP'), ('Yoon', 'PERSON'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本はどんなチームなのか　BBCスポーツ記者が分析,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] What kind of team is Japan? BBC sports reporter analyzes,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英国防相が辞任、防衛費めぐり政府内で対立　スターマー氏の指導力に新たな打撃,UK Defense Minister resigns as government conflict over defense spending deals another blow to Starmer's leadership,-1.0,negative,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Starmer', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 英国防相の辞任、スターマー政権と防衛計画にどんな影響があるのか,[Commentary] What impact does the resignation of the UK Defense Secretary have on the Starmer government and defense plans?,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 メキシコで開幕、いきなり3人退場の波乱　色鮮やかな開会式も,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Opening in Mexico, turbulent with 3 people suddenly sent off, colorful opening ceremony too",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup] Opening', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、戦争終結の合意に近づいていると表明　対イラン攻撃の中止を発表後,"Trump says he is close to a deal to end the war, after announcing a halt to attacks on Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,アメリカとの国境線上にある図書館、カナダ側にも入り口を新設　トランプ政権の規制強化で, 所要時間 2,26","Video, A library on the border with the United States has a new entrance on the Canadian side. Due to the Trump administration's tightened regulations, the time required is 2.26",0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('2.26', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yaishambulia Iran licha ya makubaliano kuwa karibu kuafikiwa","Directly, the United States attacked Iran despite the agreement being reached",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, wanadamu wanaweza kupata watoto katika anga za juu?",Can humans have children in outer space?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini baadhi ya watu wanashauriwa kujiepusha kula maembe,Why are some people advised to refrain from eating mangoes?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Arsenal, Man Utd zamgombania Fernandes","European Football Rumors: Arsenal, Man Utd vying for Fernandes",0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors: Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Fernandes', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwanini Tanzania inaweza kufuzu Kombe la Dunia 2030,Why Tanzania can qualify for the 2030 World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('the 2030 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mkataba wa amani kati ya Marekani na Iran utasainiwa Jumapili huko Geneva,The peace agreement between the US and Iran will be signed on Sunday in Geneva,1.0,positive,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Geneva', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mataifa 10 ya Afrika yaliyo na uwezo mkubwa wa kiviwanda: Morocco yaipiku Afrika Kusini,10 African countries with the greatest industrial potential: Morocco surpasses South Africa,1.0,positive,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Marekani itabadili msimamo na 'kupinga' uhuru wa Taiwan?",Will the United States change its position and 'oppose' Taiwan's independence?,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tanzania inavyoufanya mtihani wa diplomasia ya dunia,Tanzania is doing the test of world diplomacy,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Mexico yaichapa Afrika Kusini, kadi nyekundu tatu zatolewa","World Cup 2026: Mexico beats South Africa, three red cards are issued",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US orders Anthropic to disable AI models for all foreign nationals,US orders Anthropic to disable AI models for all foreign nationals,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Knicks in five? New York head to San Antonio, one win away from NBA title","Knicks in five? New York head to San Antonio, one win away from NBA title",1.0,positive,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('San Antonio', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Right to protest genocide’ denied: Scotland’s Palestine Action supporters,‘Right to protest genocide’ denied: Scotland’s Palestine Action supporters,0.0,neutral,"[('Scotland’s Palestine Action', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 106: US and Iran say deal close but Lebanon fighting continues,Iran war day 106: US and Iran say deal close but Lebanon fighting continues,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('day 106', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Molokhia cigarettes: Gaza’s toxic alternative to tobacco,Molokhia cigarettes: Gaza’s toxic alternative to tobacco,0.0,neutral,"[('Molokhia', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Doctors Without Borders investigation finds exploitation by staff in Chad,Doctors Without Borders investigation finds exploitation by staff in Chad,0.0,neutral,"[('Chad', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup Day 3: Brazil begin campaign as Trump, Partey make headlines","World Cup Day 3: Brazil begin campaign as Trump, Partey make headlines",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day', 'EVENT'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Partey', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Topuria shoves Gaethje by Lincoln Memorial ahead of White House UFC event,Topuria shoves Gaethje by Lincoln Memorial ahead of White House UFC event,0.0,neutral,"[('Topuria', 'ORG'), ('Gaethje', 'PERSON'), ('Lincoln Memorial', 'ORG'), ('White House', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,England training equipment stolen ahead of squad’s arrival in Kansas City,England training equipment stolen ahead of squad’s arrival in Kansas City,0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('Kansas City', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Four killed as Israel hits south Lebanon, issues forced displacement orders","Four killed as Israel hits south Lebanon, issues forced displacement orders",-1.0,negative,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Five IAF personnel killed in AN-32 aircraft crash in Assam's Jorhat,Five IAF personnel killed in AN-32 aircraft crash in Assam's Jorhat,-1.0,negative,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('IAF', 'ORG'), ('AN-32', 'PRODUCT'), ('Assam', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"DRDO demonstrates advanced missile defence, anti-ship strike capabilities in three successful flight tests","DRDO demonstrates advanced missile defence, anti-ship strike capabilities in three successful flight tests",1.0,positive,"[('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Amit Shah directs committee on demographic change to study border districts,Amit Shah directs committee on demographic change to study border districts,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"2020 Delhi riots: Sharjeel Imam, Umar Khalid move fresh bail pleas in ‘larger conspiracy’ case","2020 Delhi riots: Sharjeel Imam, Umar Khalid move fresh bail pleas in ‘larger conspiracy’ case",0.0,neutral,"[('2020', 'DATE'), ('Sharjeel Imam', 'ORG'), ('Umar Khalid', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,AI sovereignty hawks see red as U.S. moves to block Anthropic’s Mythos and Fable models,AI sovereignty hawks see red as U.S. moves to block Anthropic’s Mythos and Fable models,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Anthropic’s Mythos', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Rahul Gandhi’s approach helping BJP, not strengthening INDIA bloc, says Kerala ex-CM Pinarayi Vijayan","Rahul Gandhi’s approach helping BJP, not strengthening INDIA bloc, says Kerala ex-CM Pinarayi Vijayan",0.0,neutral,"[('Rahul Gandhi’s', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Kerala ex-CM Pinarayi', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Bengal police breaks into Abhishek Banerjee’s residence,West Bengal police breaks into Abhishek Banerjee’s residence,0.0,neutral,"[('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('Abhishek Banerjee’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Assam halts Aadhaar issuance to those aged above 18: CM,Assam halts Aadhaar issuance to those aged above 18: CM,0.0,neutral,"[('Aadhaar', 'ORG'), ('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('CM', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia war LIVE: Lebanon reports Israeli strikes in south after evacuation warning,West Asia war LIVE: Lebanon reports Israeli strikes in south after evacuation warning,-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_13,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The human cost of a deadly weed killer: banning of  paraqua in Telangana,The human cost of a deadly weed killer: banning of  paraqua in Telangana,-1.0,negative,"[('Telangana', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Deal to end fighting would lead to Hormuz reopening, Iran says","Deal to end fighting would lead to Hormuz reopening, Iran says",0.0,neutral,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Switzerland to vote on plan to cap population at 10 million,Switzerland to vote on plan to cap population at 10 million,0.0,neutral,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('10 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Married at First Sight Australia stars not told partners had drug and violence convictions,Married at First Sight Australia stars not told partners had drug and violence convictions,0.0,neutral,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('Sight', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Elon Musk becomes world's first trillionaire as SpaceX soars in stock market debut,Elon Musk becomes world's first trillionaire as SpaceX soars in stock market debut,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('SpaceX', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Fans on concourses instead of in seats, claims Fifa","Fans on concourses instead of in seats, claims Fifa",0.0,neutral,"[('Fifa', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US kills leader of Venezuela's Tren de Aragua gang in airstrike, Trump says","US kills leader of Venezuela's Tren de Aragua gang in airstrike, Trump says",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Anthropic suspends new AI tools over US government security concerns,Anthropic suspends new AI tools over US government security concerns,0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Warner Bros $111bn sale to Paramount approved by US justice department,Warner Bros $111bn sale to Paramount approved by US justice department,-1.0,negative,"[('Warner Bros', 'ORG'), ('111bn', 'ORG'), ('Paramount', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,King leads tributes to 'giant of the art world' David Hockney,King leads tributes to 'giant of the art world' David Hockney,0.0,neutral,"[('David Hockney', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_13,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,French town buries murdered child as questions mount over police failings,French town buries murdered child as questions mount over police failings,-1.0,negative,"[('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"With a Deal Seemingly Close, the U.S. Faces an Iran More Willing to Withstand Pressure","With a Deal Seemingly Close, the U.S. Faces an Iran More Willing to Withstand Pressure",0.0,neutral,"[('the U.S. Faces', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Withstand Pressure', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Russia Is Rich in Ballistic Missiles. Ukraine Is Short of Ways to Stop Them.,Russia Is Rich in Ballistic Missiles. Ukraine Is Short of Ways to Stop Them.,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ballistic Missiles', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"At the Canadian Screen Awards, the Industry Steps Outside Hollywood’s Shadow","At the Canadian Screen Awards, the Industry Steps Outside Hollywood’s Shadow",-1.0,negative,"[('the Canadian Screen Awards', 'ORG'), ('the Industry Steps Outside Hollywood’s Shadow', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Family Ravaged by Land Mines in Myanmar,A Family Ravaged by Land Mines in Myanmar,0.0,neutral,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Brazilians Revive a World Cup Ritual to Cheer on Their National Team,Brazilians Revive a World Cup Ritual to Cheer on Their National Team,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilians Revive', 'PERSON'), ('Cheer on Their National Team', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Should Switzerland Cap Its Population at 10 Million? Voters Will Decide.,Should Switzerland Cap Its Population at 10 Million? Voters Will Decide.,0.0,neutral,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('10 Million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,What to Know About the Ebola Outbreak,What to Know About the Ebola Outbreak,0.0,neutral,"[('the Ebola Outbreak', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Cease-Fire Deal Appears Within Reach, Officials Say","Cease-Fire Deal Appears Within Reach, Officials Say",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Plan Is Said to Pull a Third of Fighter Jets It Provides NATO for Europe,U.S. Plan Is Said to Pull a Third of Fighter Jets It Provides NATO for Europe,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_13,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A Dangerous Limbo Leaves Iran, and the World, Between Peace and War","A Dangerous Limbo Leaves Iran, and the World, Between Peace and War",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Between Peace and War', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
