Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El sufrimiento silencioso de los niños en Gaza que han perdido la capacidad de hablar,The silent suffering of children in Gaza who have lost the ability to speak,0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los “mesías” de la machosfera: cómo los influencers de la masculinidad conquistaron internet | Documental BBC,The “messiahs” of the machosphere: how masculinity influencers conquered the internet | BBC Documentary,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC Documentary', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Irán asegura que atacó una base militar de EE.UU. en respuesta a la nueva ofensiva de Washington en el sur de la nación islámica,Iran claims it attacked a US military base in response to Washington's new offensive in the south of the Islamic nation,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Islamic', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué es el cortisol, qué función cumple esta hormona y por qué recomiendan bajar sus niveles","What is cortisol, what function does this hormone play and why do they recommend lowering its levels?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,100 años de Marilyn Monroe: su estrecha relación con México y otros 3 hechos menos conocidos de la vida de la icónica actriz,100 years of Marilyn Monroe: her close relationship with Mexico and 3 other lesser-known facts from the life of the iconic actress,0.0,neutral,"[('100 years', 'DATE'), ('Marilyn Monroe', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""El escenario se mexicanizó"": cómo se transformó la violencia en Colombia y por qué sigue definiendo las elecciones","""The scene became Mexicanized"": how violence was transformed in Colombia and why it continues to define the elections",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexicanized', 'PRODUCT'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Casi 500.000 soldados rusos han muerto en la guerra de Ucrania, según los servicios de inteligencia británicos","Nearly 500,000 Russian soldiers have died in the Ukraine war, according to British intelligence services",-1.0,negative,"[('Nearly 500,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quién es Christopher Olah, el pionero de la IA y cofundador de Anthropic clave en la encíclica de León XIV sobre las amenazas de esa tecnología","Who is Christopher Olah, the AI ​​pioneer and co-founder of Anthropic who is key in Leo XIV's encyclical on the threats of this technology",0.0,neutral,"[('Christopher Olah', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'GPE'), (""Leo XIV's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué a Venezuela le falta energía pese a su riqueza petrolera y cómo eso limita su recuperación económica,Why Venezuela lacks energy despite its oil wealth and how this limits its economic recovery,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El experimento de una reserva holandesa que pasó de ser un santuario de animales a un campo de muerte,The experiment of a Dutch reserve that went from being an animal sanctuary to a death camp,-1.0,negative,"[('Dutch', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'सत्ता छीननी पड़ती है':  'कांग्रेस के संकटमोचक' डीके शिवकुमार कैसे पहुँचे सीएम की कुर्सी तक,'Power has to be snatched': How 'Congress' troubleshooter' DK Shivkumar reached CM's chair,0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('DK Shivkumar', 'PERSON'), ('CM', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,कुवैत ने मिसाइल और ड्रोन हमले रोकने का किया दावा","Live, Kuwait claims to have stopped missile and drone attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Kuwait', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सिद्धारमैया ने छोड़ी कर्नाटक के सीएम की कुर्सी, डीके शिवकुमार होंगे अगले मुख्यमंत्री","Siddaramaiah leaves the chair of Karnataka CM, DK Shivakumar will be the next Chief Minister",0.0,neutral,"[('Siddaramaiah', 'PERSON'), ('Karnataka CM', 'ORG'), ('DK Shivakumar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारत का रुपया गिर रहा है लेकिन दूसरे कई एशियाई देशों की मुद्रा मज़बूत कैसे हो रही है?,India's rupee is falling but how are the currencies of many other Asian countries strengthening?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Asian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारत के सबसे गर्म ज़िलों में शामिल बांदा में क्यों बिगड़ते जा रहे हैं हालात?,"Why is the situation worsening in Banda, one of the hottest districts of India?",0.0,neutral,"[('Banda', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'हेटर्स कहेंगे कि तुम 15 के नहीं हो...', गेल, रसेल से लेकर सचिन तक हुए वैभव के मुरीद, किसने क्या कहा?","'Haters will say that you are not 15...', Vaibhav's admirers from Gayle, Russell to Sachin, who said what?",0.0,neutral,"[('Haters', 'ORG'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('Vaibhav', 'PERSON'), ('Gayle', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इस अमेरिकी सीनेटर की किस बात से ख़फ़ा हैं पाकिस्तान के सोशल मीडिया यूज़र्स,What are Pakistan's social media users angry about about this American senator?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिका ने ईरान के भीतर सैन्य ठिकानों पर नए हमले किए,US launches new attacks on military targets inside Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान से तनाव के बीच ट्रंप ने अपने सहयोगी देश ओमान को उड़ाने की धमकी क्यों दी,Why did Trump threaten to blow up his ally Oman amid tension with Iran?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Oman', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'मैं गेंदबाज़ों के बारे में ज़्यादा नहीं सोचता', वैभव  के करिश्मे से राजस्थान खिताब के क़रीब","'I don't think much about bowlers', Rajasthan close to title due to Vaibhav's charisma",0.0,neutral,"[('Rajasthan', 'PERSON'), ('Vaibhav', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Fim da escala 6x1 é aprovada na Câmara e proposta vai ao Senado: 'Dia histórico',End of the 6x1 scale is approved in the Chamber and proposal goes to the Senate: 'Historic day',0.0,neutral,"[('6x1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chamber', 'ORG'), ('Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o dono da Ford criou a escala de trabalho 5x2 há 100 anos — e como isso impactou o mundo,Why the owner of Ford created the 5x2 work schedule 100 years ago — and how it impacted the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Ford', 'ORG'), ('5x2', 'ORG'), ('100 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A 1ª grande vitória do balconista de farmácia que lançou movimento pelo fim da escala 6x1 com desabafo no TikTok,The first big victory for the pharmacy clerk who launched the movement to end the 6x1 scale with an outburst on TikTok,1.0,positive,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('6x1', 'CARDINAL'), ('TikTok', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Explosões, ordem de evacuação e medo: Israel ataca novamente o sul do Líbano, apesar de cessar-fogo","Explosions, evacuation order and fear: Israel attacks southern Lebanon again, despite ceasefire",-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Copa não é convite para explorar nossos moradores': o que procuradora de NY alega para pedir investigação sobre preço de ingressos da Fifa,'World Cup is not an invitation to exploit our residents': what NY prosecutor claims to request investigation into FIFA ticket prices,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('NY', 'ORG'), ('FIFA', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Funcionário do Google é acusado de usar dados internos e ganhar US$ 1 milhão com apostas,Google employee accused of using internal data and making $1 million from bets,0.0,neutral,"[('Google', 'ORG'), ('$1 million', 'MONEY')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,EUA atacam Irã pela 2ª vez em três dias em meio a frágil cessar-fogo,US attacks Iran for the second time in three days amid fragile ceasefire,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('three days', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Grupo é encontrado com vida após uma semana em caverna inundada no Laos,Group found alive after a week in flooded cave in Laos,0.0,neutral,"[('a week', 'DATE'), ('Laos', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Enquanto Brasil discute fim da escala 6x1, Argentina vai na contramão do mundo com reforma que retira direitos e permite jornada de até 12 horas por dia","While Brazil discusses the end of the 6x1 scale, Argentina goes against the world with a reform that removes rights and allows working hours of up to 12 hours a day",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the end of the', 'DATE'), ('6x1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('working hours', 'TIME'), ('up to 12 hours', 'TIME')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Скачок самолета на тысячу миль: в Европе резко участились случаи GPS-спуфинга,A plane jumps a thousand miles: cases of GPS spoofing have increased sharply in Europe,0.0,neutral,"[('a thousand miles', 'QUANTITY'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зачем Путин угрожает Пашиняну накануне выборов? Объясняет журналист Кирилл Кривошеев,Why is Putin threatening Pashinyan on the eve of the elections? Journalist Kirill Krivosheev explains,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Kirill Krivosheev', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский прибыл в Швецию; Верховная Рада ратифицировала соглашение с ЕС о кредите в 90 млрд евро","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky arrived in Sweden; The Verkhovna Rada ratified an agreement with the EU on a loan of 90 billion euros",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('The Verkhovna Rada', 'ORG'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('90 billion', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Подмосковье запрещают полеты малой авиации. Самолеты легко перепутать с дронами?,Small aircraft flights are prohibited in the Moscow region. Are airplanes easily confused with drones?,0.0,neutral,"[('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Джилл Байден заявила, что во время провальных предвыборных дебатов с Трампом она думала, что у ее мужа случился инсульт",Jill Biden said she thought her husband was having a stroke during his disastrous presidential debate with Trump.,0.0,neutral,"[('Jill Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трампа не устраивают условия сделки с Ираном, и он начал угрожать Оману","Trump is not satisfied with the terms of the deal with Iran, and he began to threaten Oman",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Oman', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Бывшая участница немецкой «Фракции Красной армии» осуждена за вооруженные ограбления. Она скрывалась 30 лет,A former member of the German Red Army Faction has been convicted of armed robbery. She hid for 30 years,0.0,neutral,"[('the German Red Army Faction', 'ORG'), ('30 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Будто из тюрьмы выпустили: иранцы вздохнули с облегчением после окончания блокировки интернета,It’s like being released from prison: Iranians breathed a sigh of relief after the end of the Internet blockade,0.0,neutral,"[('Iranians', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Байден судится с администрацией Трампа из-за собственных мемуаров,Biden is suing the Trump administration over his own memoirs,0.0,neutral,"[('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Дорогие братья и сестры, я вчера вышел из тюрьмы». Митрополит Иларион рассказал о своем аресте в Чехии","“Dear brothers and sisters, I was released from prison yesterday.” Metropolitan Hilarion spoke about his arrest in the Czech Republic",0.0,neutral,"[('yesterday', 'DATE'), ('Metropolitan Hilarion', 'ORG'), ('the Czech Republic', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエル、レバノン南部の広範囲に避難命令,Israel orders evacuation of large area of ​​southern Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、イランと交渉中の合意条件に「満足していない」,Trump 'not satisfied' with terms of deal being negotiated with Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、イランを再び空爆　イスラム革命防衛隊も米基地を攻撃と,US airstrikes Iran again; Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps also attacks US bases,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシア兵約50万人がウクライナでの戦争で死亡と英情報当局,"About 500,000 Russian soldiers killed in war in Ukraine, British intelligence says",-1.0,negative,"[('About 500,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,豪当局、シリアから戻った女性を「イスラム国」参加で起訴　帰国相次ぐなか,"Australian authorities indict a woman who returned from Syria for participating in the Islamic State, as many return home",0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('Islamic', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,中国の反体制活動家、ゴムボートで脱出　韓国で拘束される,"Chinese dissident escapes in rubber boat, detained in South Korea",0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリス、年内にも子どものSNS利用に関する規制を導入へ　首相は行動を約束,"UK to introduce regulations on children's use of social media by the end of the year, Prime Minister promises action",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('the end of the year', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,レストランが客に水道水を出さず、これは「合法」とイタリア最高裁　法律上の義務なし,"Restaurants not serving tap water to customers is ``legal,'' says Italy's Supreme Court; there is no legal obligation.",0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イラン、アメリカの空爆を非難　停戦合意への「重大な違反」と,"Iran condemns US airstrike, calling it 'serious violation' of ceasefire agreement",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリスの5月の最高気温、2日連続で更新　ロンドンで35度を超える,Highest temperature in May in the UK updated for 2nd consecutive day - over 35 degrees in London,0.0,neutral,"[('May', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('2nd consecutive day', 'DATE'), ('35 degrees', 'QUANTITY'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Wanafunzi 16 wafariki katika moto wa bweni la shule ya Utumishi Girls, Kenya","Directly, 16 students died in a fire in the dormitory of Utumi Girls school, Kenya",0.0,neutral,"[('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('Utumi Girls school', 'ORG'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mzozo wa Iran: Kwanini Trump anatishia kuishambulia Oman?,Iran conflict: Why is Trump threatening to attack Oman?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Oman', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini baadhi ya watoto wa Gaza wameacha kuzungumza?,Why have some children in Gaza stopped talking?,0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Siku iliomtoa machozi Pep Guardiola,A day that brought tears to Pep Guardiola,0.0,neutral,"[('A day', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Fahamu mpango wa NASA unaojumuisha hatua tatu katika vituo vya mwezi,Learn about NASA's three-stage lunar station plan,0.0,neutral,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Israel yatangaza kumuua kamanda wa Hamas baada ya shambulizi la anga Gaza,Israel announces the killing of a Hamas commander after an airstrike in Gaza,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mashambulizi ya Israel dhidi ya Lebanon ni mashambulizi makali zaidi tangu usitishaji vita ulipoanza,Israel's attack on Lebanon is the most serious attack since the ceasefire began,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini gari lako huenda linakusanya na kutoa taarifa zako binafsi?,Why might your car collect and release your personal information?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kuoga na maji ya barafu hadi kunywa maziwa ya lozi: Siri ya mafanikio ya Mohamed Salah Liverpool,From taking an ice bath to drinking almond milk: The secret to Mohamed Salah's Liverpool success,1.0,positive,"[(""Mohamed Salah's"", 'PERSON'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Waislamu kote duniani wanaadhimisha sherehe za Eid al-Adha,Muslims around the world are celebrating Eid al-Adha,0.0,neutral,"[('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('Eid al-Adha', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel kills children in strikes on Gaza as fear taints Eid joy,Israel kills children in strikes on Gaza as fear taints Eid joy,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ireland football coach urges players to ‘win this war’ against Israel,Ireland football coach urges players to ‘win this war’ against Israel,0.0,neutral,"[('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Argentina’s ‘El Loco’ faces Uruguay mutiny ahead of World Cup,Argentina’s ‘El Loco’ faces Uruguay mutiny ahead of World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina’s ‘El Loco', 'PERSON'), ('Uruguay', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran says it has a new air defence system. How significant is it?,Iran says it has a new air defence system. How significant is it?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,At least 16 students killed in fire at Kenya girls school dorm,At least 16 students killed in fire at Kenya girls school dorm,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 16', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Germany’s Voeller urges players to avoid political statements at World Cup,Germany’s Voeller urges players to avoid political statements at World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Children with Down syndrome struggle with devastation of war in Gaza,Children with Down syndrome struggle with devastation of war in Gaza,-1.0,negative,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,China’s secret weapon in AI race with US? Lots of cheap energy,China’s secret weapon in AI race with US? Lots of cheap energy,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('AI', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Israeli attack on Gaza City kills at least 10, including four children","Israeli attack on Gaza City kills at least 10, including four children",-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza City', 'GPE'), ('at least 10', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_28,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Two uncapped players named in South Africa’s World Cup squad,Two uncapped players named in South Africa’s World Cup squad,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Africa’s', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Ending days of speculation, Siddaramaiah informed his Cabinet colleagues that he is stepping down, paving way for a new Chief Minister in Karnataka","Ending days of speculation, Siddaramaiah informed his Cabinet colleagues that he is stepping down, paving way for a new Chief Minister in Karnataka",0.0,neutral,"[('Ending days', 'DATE'), ('Siddaramaiah', 'PERSON'), ('Cabinet', 'ORG'), ('Karnataka', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Siddaramaiah, Nitish Kumar and the final bow of their socialist politics","Siddaramaiah, Nitish Kumar and the final bow of their socialist politics",0.0,neutral,"[('Siddaramaiah', 'GPE'), ('Nitish Kumar', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Siddaramaiah: A leader whose politics went beyond dominant castes,Siddaramaiah: A leader whose politics went beyond dominant castes,0.0,neutral,"[('Siddaramaiah', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Tussle for the top spot in Karnataka | Timeline,Tussle for the top spot in Karnataka | Timeline,0.0,neutral,"[('Karnataka', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Iran-Israel war LIVE: U.S. military conducts another strike against Iran after Trump says Iran 'negotiating on fumes',Iran-Israel war LIVE: U.S. military conducts another strike against Iran after Trump says Iran 'negotiating on fumes',-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Resolve water disputes through cooperation, says PM Modi to States","Resolve water disputes through cooperation, says PM Modi to States",0.0,neutral,"[('PM Modi', 'PERSON'), ('States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"India, China hold 'constructive' talks on LAC; agree border peace key to normalising ties","India, China hold 'constructive' talks on LAC; agree border peace key to normalising ties",1.0,positive,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('LAC', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,WFI moves SC against HC order allowing Vinesh Phogat to participate in Asian Games selection trials,WFI moves SC against HC order allowing Vinesh Phogat to participate in Asian Games selection trials,1.0,positive,"[('WFI', 'ORG'), ('SC', 'ORG'), ('HC', 'ORG'), ('Vinesh Phogat', 'ORG'), ('Asian Games', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,BJP bets on Jat Sikh card with Dhillon’s appointment as Punjab chief,BJP bets on Jat Sikh card with Dhillon’s appointment as Punjab chief,0.0,neutral,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Jat Sikh', 'PERSON'), ('Dhillon’s', 'ORG'), ('Punjab', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Samsung workers win, but the pay divide remains","Samsung workers win, but the pay divide remains",1.0,positive,"[('Samsung', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Iran says it targeted American base after fresh US strikes,Iran says it targeted American base after fresh US strikes,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Man arrested after three injured in stabbing at Swiss train station,Man arrested after three injured in stabbing at Swiss train station,0.0,neutral,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US justice department launches criminal investigation into Trump accuser E Jean Carroll, reports say","US justice department launches criminal investigation into Trump accuser E Jean Carroll, reports say",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Jean Carroll', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Sixteen pupils killed in Kenya school fire,Sixteen pupils killed in Kenya school fire,-1.0,negative,"[('Sixteen', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Heavy Israeli strikes hit southern Lebanon after large-scale evacuation orders,Heavy Israeli strikes hit southern Lebanon after large-scale evacuation orders,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Jill Biden says she thought husband was having a stroke during 2024 debate,Jill Biden says she thought husband was having a stroke during 2024 debate,0.0,neutral,"[('Jill Biden', 'PERSON'), ('2024', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Australia charges woman who returned from Syria with joining Islamic State,Australia charges woman who returned from Syria with joining Islamic State,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('Islamic', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Australia sues US giant 3M over 'forever chemicals' in firefighting foam,Australia sues US giant 3M over 'forever chemicals' in firefighting foam,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Google worker charged with using internal data to make $1.2m on bets,Google worker charged with using internal data to make $1.2m on bets,0.0,neutral,"[('1.2', 'MONEY')]"
2026_05_28,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Matthew Perry's assistant jailed for 41 months over actor's ketamine death,Matthew Perry's assistant jailed for 41 months over actor's ketamine death,-1.0,negative,"[(""Matthew Perry's"", 'PERSON'), ('41 months', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iran War Live Updates: U.S. and Iran Trade Strikes, Further Threatening Negotiations","Iran War Live Updates: U.S. and Iran Trade Strikes, Further Threatening Negotiations",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates', 'EVENT'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Mideast Is Baffled by Trump’s Call to Expand Abraham Accords,The Mideast Is Baffled by Trump’s Call to Expand Abraham Accords,0.0,neutral,"[('Mideast', 'LOC'), ('Trump’s Call', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Guatemala Agrees to Joint Strikes With U.S. Against Drug Gangs,Guatemala Agrees to Joint Strikes With U.S. Against Drug Gangs,0.0,neutral,"[('Guatemala Agrees', 'PERSON'), ('Joint Strikes', 'PERSON'), ('U.S. Against Drug Gangs', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Ukraine’s Street Style Is Shaped by the War,How Ukraine’s Street Style Is Shaped by the War,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Argentina, U.S. Tech Billionaire Peter Thiel Finds An Escape","In Argentina, U.S. Tech Billionaire Peter Thiel Finds An Escape",0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Peter Thiel Finds', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Why Pakistan and Afghanistan Are Still Fighting,Why Pakistan and Afghanistan Are Still Fighting,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Cuba Loses Its Chance at Fuel After Russian Tanker Changes Route,Cuba Loses Its Chance at Fuel After Russian Tanker Changes Route,0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba Loses Its Chance at Fuel', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Fire at School Dormitory in Kenya Kills at Least 16,Fire at School Dormitory in Kenya Kills at Least 16,-1.0,negative,"[('Kenya Kills', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Quiet Pacific Village Becomes China’s Security Testing Ground,A Quiet Pacific Village Becomes China’s Security Testing Ground,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_28,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Lebanese Resigned to a Long War, Even if U.S. and Iran Make a Deal","Lebanese Resigned to a Long War, Even if U.S. and Iran Make a Deal",-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanese', 'NORP'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
