Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los gráficos que muestran la magnitud y el impacto de los potentes terremotos en Venezuela,Graphs showing the magnitude and impact of the powerful earthquakes in Venezuela,1.0,positive,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Un ""esfuerzo colectivo masivo"": la ayuda internacional rumbo a Venezuela tras los devastadores terremotos","A ""massive collective effort"": international aid heading to Venezuela after the devastating earthquakes",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué es el ""doblete sísmico"" que sacudió Venezuela y por qué provocó tantos daños","What is the ""seismic double"" that shook Venezuela and why did it cause so much damage?",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Están sacando a la gente con uñas y dientes"": la desesperación por salvar a las personas que se encuentran bajo los escombros en Venezuela","""They are taking people out tooth and nail"": the desperation to save people who are under the rubble in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Mi corazón me dice que está vivo"": la esperanza de una joven que aguarda el rescate de su hermano bajo los escombros de un edificio en Caracas","""My heart tells me that he is alive"": the hope of a young woman who awaits the rescue of her brother under the rubble of a building in Caracas",0.0,neutral,"[('Caracas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué se sabe de los dos fuertes terremotos que causaron graves destrozos y muertes en Caracas y otras zonas de Venezuela,What is known about the two strong earthquakes that caused serious damage and deaths in Caracas and other areas of Venezuela,-1.0,negative,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Caracas', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,EN VIDEO | El momento en el que dos terremotos golpean Venezuela provocando graves daños,ON VIDEO | The moment when two earthquakes hit Venezuela causing serious damage,0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Transmisión especial: doble terremoto en Venezuela,Special broadcast: double earthquake in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Del deslave del 1999 a los terremotos de 2026: La Guaira, uno de los estados de Venezuela más golpeados por desastres naturales","From the 1999 landslide to the 2026 earthquakes: La Guaira, one of the states of Venezuela hardest hit by natural disasters",-1.0,negative,"[('1999', 'DATE'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('La Guaira', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Video,EN VIDEO | Cómo fue el ""doblete sísmico"" que devastó a Venezuela, Duración 6,04","Video, ON VIDEO | How was the ""seismic double"" that devastated Venezuela, Duration 6.04",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('6.04', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,महरंग बलोच कौन हैं जिन्हें पाकिस्तान में एक सैनिक की हत्या के मामले में उम्रक़ैद की सज़ा सुनाई गई,Who is Mehrang Baloch who was sentenced to life imprisonment in the case of murder of a soldier in Pakistan?,0.0,neutral,"[('Mehrang Baloch', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वेनेज़ुएला में भूकंप: तस्वीरों में दिखी भारी तबाही, लापता लोगों की तलाश में जुटे राहतकर्मी","Earthquake in Venezuela: Huge devastation seen in pictures, relief workers busy searching for missing people",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,किस सरकारी कंपनी में हिस्सेदारी बेचने के ख़िलाफ़ तमिलनाडु के सीएम विजय ने पीएम मोदी को लिखी चिट्ठी","Live, Tamil Nadu CM Vijay wrote a letter to PM Modi against selling stake in which government company?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारतीय स्टूडेंट्स के लिए अब क्यों मुश्किल होता जा रहा है विदेशों में पढ़ाई का सपना,Why is the dream of studying abroad becoming difficult for Indian students?,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वैभव सूर्यवंशी को लेकर आयरलैंड के ख़िलाफ़ मैच से पहले ऐसी चर्चा, राहुल द्रविड़ की ये टिप्पणी","Such discussion before the match against Ireland regarding Vaibhav Suryavanshi, this comment of Rahul Dravid",0.0,neutral,"[('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Rahul Dravid', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अयोध्या राम मंदिर के चढ़ावे में चोरी का मामला: ये आठ लोग हिरासत में, जानिए क्या थी इनकी ज़िम्मेदारी","Case of theft in the offerings of Ayodhya Ram temple: These eight people are in custody, know what was their responsibility",0.0,neutral,"[('Ayodhya Ram', 'ORG'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इम्तियाज़ अली: 'मैं वापस आऊंगा' इतिहास की राख में प्रेम की बची हुई चिंगारियां तलाशने वाली फ़िल्म,"Imtiaz Ali: 'I will come back', a film that searches for the remaining sparks of love in the ashes of history",0.0,neutral,"[('Imtiaz Ali', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ताजमहल: प्यार की निशानी में छिपी मुमताज़ महल की दर्दनाक कहानी,Taj Mahal: The painful story of Mumtaz Mahal hidden in the symbol of love,0.0,neutral,"[('Taj Mahal', 'PERSON'), ('Mumtaz Mahal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बांग्लादेश: तारिक़ रहमान ने भारत के पहले मलेशिया और चीन को क्यों चुना?,Bangladesh: Why did Tariq Rahman choose Malaysia and China before India?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tariq Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Malaysia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,महिला टी20 वर्ल्ड कप: बांग्लादेश के ख़िलाफ़ जीत के बावजूद भारत के लिए सेमीफ़ाइनल की राह क्यों नहीं है आसान,Women's T20 World Cup: Why is the path to the semi-finals not easy for India despite the win against Bangladesh?,1.0,positive,"[(""Women's T20 World Cup:"", 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Meu total apoio': pré-candidato do PL ao governo do RJ defende que EUA bombardeiem embarcações do tráfico na costa brasileira,'My full support': PL pre-candidate for the government of RJ defends that the US bombs trafficking vessels on the Brazilian coast,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Vídeo de Michelle é novo revés para a campanha de Flávio, diz jornal britânico","Michelle's video is a new setback for Flávio's campaign, says British newspaper",0.0,neutral,"[('Michelle', 'ORG'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil vai enfrentar o Japão no mata-mata; relembre histórico de confrontos,Brazil will face Japan in the knockout stage; remember the history of clashes,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Dois brasileiros estão entre as 235 vítimas de terremoto; Venezuela busca sobreviventes,Two Brazilians are among the 235 earthquake victims; Venezuela searches for survivors,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazilians', 'NORP'), ('235', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Meu coração diz que está vivo': a esperança da jovem que espera irmão ser resgatado de escombros na Venezuela,'My heart says it's alive': the hope of the young woman who waits for her brother to be rescued from the rubble in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Estão tirando as pessoas com unhas e dentes': o desespero para salvar quem está sob os escombros na Venezuela,'They are taking people out tooth and nail': the desperation to save those under the rubble in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Estamos juntos, Cabo Verde': o país que nasceu de um vulcão e incendeia a Copa do Mundo","'We are together, Cape Verde': the country that was born from a volcano and sets the World Cup on fire",0.0,neutral,"[(""Cape Verde'"", 'PRODUCT'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Organização, velocidade e 'Messi japonês': o que esperar do Japão, próximo adversário do Brasil","Organization, speed and 'Japanese Messi': what to expect from Japan, Brazil's next opponent",0.0,neutral,"[('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem já está no mata-mata da Copa? Veja os classificados e o que falta decidir,Who is already in the knockout stages of the World Cup? See the classifieds and what remains to be decided,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump e eleições no Brasil: Celso Amorim diz que tentativa de intervenção pode ter efeito contrário,Trump and elections in Brazil: Celso Amorim says that attempted intervention could have the opposite effect,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: власти сообщили о крупнейшей с начала года ночной атаке дронов на Россию","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Authorities report the largest nighttime drone attack on Russia since the beginning of the year",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('the beginning of the year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Ученые при помощи ИИ впервые полностью прочли текст с обуглившегося свитка из Геркуланума,Scientists using AI for the first time fully read the text from a charred scroll from Herculaneum,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Herculaneum', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Что известно о потерях России в Украине к концу июня?,What is known about Russia's losses in Ukraine by the end of June?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('the end of June', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Суперджет» могут не успеть сертифицировать в 2026 году,Superjet may not have time to be certified in 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('Superjet', 'ORG'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Король Карл решил не переселяться в Букингемский дворец после ремонта,King Charles decided not to move into Buckingham Palace after renovations,0.0,neutral,"[('King Charles', 'PERSON'), ('Buckingham Palace', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Зеленский заявил, что Беларусь отключила «ретрансляторы» для дронов после ультиматума, Лукашенко рассказал о встрече с представителями Киева. Главное в Беларуси за неделю","Zelensky said that Belarus turned off the “relays” for drones after the ultimatum, Lukashenko spoke about a meeting with representatives of Kyiv. The main things in Belarus in a week",0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Belarus', 'ORG'), ('Lukashenko', 'PERSON'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,ООН приостановила эвакуацию моряков из Ормузского пролива после удара по грузовому судну,UN suspends evacuation of sailors from Strait of Hormuz after cargo ship hit,0.0,neutral,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Волна зноя в Европе сдвигается на восток. К 40-градусной жаре готовятся Германия, Чехия и Австрия","The heat wave in Europe is moving east. Germany, the Czech Republic and Austria are preparing for 40-degree heat",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('the Czech Republic', 'GPE'), ('Austria', 'GPE'), ('40-degree', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«За деньги можно получить практически все». На что тратят миллионы супербогатые болельщики на ЧМ по футболу,“You can get almost anything for money.” What super-rich World Cup fans spend millions on,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Венесуэле — сильнейшее землетрясение за 100 лет: более 200 погибших, тысячи людей пропали без вести","In Venezuela - the strongest earthquake in 100 years: more than 200 dead, thousands of people missing",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('100 years', 'DATE'), ('more than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本、スウェーデンと引き分け決勝T進出　ベスト32戦はブラジルと,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Japan draws with Sweden to advance to the final T, the last 32 match will be against Brazil",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴェネズエラ地震、生存者の捜索続く　死傷者さらに増える恐れも,Search for survivors of Venezuela earthquake continues; casualties feared to rise further,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ヴェネズエラの地震の翌日、がれきの撤去と捜索　広場では物資の寄付, 所要時間 1,04","Video, The day after the earthquake in Venezuela, debris removal and search, donations of supplies in the plaza, time required 1,04",0.0,neutral,"[('The day', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('1,04', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリスで今年最高気温の36.7度に　「赤色」高温警報が続く,'Red' high temperature warning continues as Britain hits this year's highest temperature of 36.7 degrees,-1.0,negative,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('36.7 degrees', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,チャールズ英国王が納税額を公表、君主として初　昨年度は約27億円,"King Charles of England announces tax amount, first for monarch - approximately 2.7 billion yen last year",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('approximately 2.7 billion yen', 'MONEY'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリス国王夫妻、改修後のバッキンガム宮殿に住まないと　一般公開を拡大へ,Britain's King and Queen will have to live in the renovated Buckingham Palace to expand public access,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('King and Queen', 'ORG'), ('Buckingham Palace', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,国連、ホルムズ海峡で足止めの船員退避計画を一時停止　貨物船への攻撃受け,UN suspends evacuation plan for sailors stranded in Strait of Hormuz after attack on cargo ship,-1.0,negative,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Strait of', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米検察、ワインスティーン受刑者に対する強姦罪での起訴を1件取り下げ　他の有罪判決は有効,"US prosecutors drop one rape charge against Weinstein, other convictions stand",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Weinstein', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 なぜ北米では「フットボール」ではなく「サッカー」と呼ぶのか　元はイギリス語との説も,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Why is it called ""soccer"" instead of ""football"" in North America? There is a theory that it is originally a British word.",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 「クールダウン拠点」、映画無料券、窓に「白い粉」……欧州各国の熱波対策,"[Explanation] ""Cool-down bases"", free movie tickets, ""white powder"" on windows... Heat wave measures in European countries",1.0,positive,"[('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetemeko la ardhi Venezuela: Waokoaji mbioni kuwatafuta manusura, idadi ya waliofariki ikifikia 235","Venezuela earthquake: Rescuers on the run to find survivors, death toll reaches 235",-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('235', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,UN yasitisha mpango wa uokoaji wa Mlango wa Bahari wa Hormuz baada ya meli ya mizigo kushambuliwa","Directly, the UN suspends the rescue plan of the Strait of Hormuz after the cargo ship was attacked",-1.0,negative,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Vita vya nani mwenye ushawishi' katika mlango bahari wa Hormuz,'Battle of who has influence' in the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Matetemeko 10 ya ardhi mabaya zaidi kuwahi kutikisa dunia,The 10 worst earthquakes to ever hit the world,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mataifa 10 yenye amani zaidi barani Afrika 2026,10 most peaceful countries in Africa 2026,1.0,positive,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Watu 355 wakamatwa Kenya wakati wa maandamano ya kumbukumbu ya miaka miwili - Waziri,355 people were arrested in Kenya during the two-year anniversary protest - Minister,0.0,neutral,"[('355', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('two-year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nani anayedhibiti Mlango-Bahari wa Hormuz sasa baada ya makubaliano?,Who controls the Strait of Hormuz now after the agreement?,0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Arsenal wamtaka Bruno Guimaraes wa Newcastle,European football rumors Friday: Arsenal want Newcastle's Bruno Guimaraes,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Newcastle', 'GPE'), ('Bruno Guimaraes', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Familia za waathiriwa wa maandamano ya Gen Z waweka mashada ya maua,Families of Gen Z protest victims lay wreaths,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_26,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Manowari mpya ya Hangor ya Pakistan ina nguvu kiasi gani?,How powerful is Pakistan's new Hangor submarine?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Hangor', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Russia reports downing 660 Ukrainian drones, denies seeking Belarus war aid","Russia reports downing 660 Ukrainian drones, denies seeking Belarus war aid",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('660', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Belarus', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup 2026: Day 16 schedule, predictions and Round of 32 race","World Cup 2026: Day 16 schedule, predictions and Round of 32 race",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Day 16', 'DATE'), ('Round', 'PRODUCT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Mother gives birth amid Venezuela earthquake devastation,Mother gives birth amid Venezuela earthquake devastation,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Venezuela earthquakes: Why is Caracas so vulnerable?,Venezuela earthquakes: Why is Caracas so vulnerable?,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Caracas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘London cooking’: Why can’t the UK cope with the heat; when will it adapt?,‘London cooking’: Why can’t the UK cope with the heat; when will it adapt?,0.0,neutral,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,North Korea conducts major weapons tests; South training ‘drone warriors’,North Korea conducts major weapons tests; South training ‘drone warriors’,-1.0,negative,"[('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('South training', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Driver plows through Mexico World Cup crowd,Driver plows through Mexico World Cup crowd,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico World Cup', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World aids rescue effort as Venezuela quake death toll hits 235,World aids rescue effort as Venezuela quake death toll hits 235,-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('235', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 119: Israel hits Lebanon as IAEA says it will return to Iran,Iran war day 119: Israel hits Lebanon as IAEA says it will return to Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('119', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('IAEA', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US ends deportation protections (TPS) for Haitians and Syrians,US ends deportation protections (TPS) for Haitians and Syrians,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('TPS', 'ORG'), ('Haitians', 'NORP'), ('Syrians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"In Telangana, the right to walk derailed by design","In Telangana, the right to walk derailed by design",0.0,neutral,"[('Telangana', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,A 28-year-old’s killing woke up Bihar’s conscience,A 28-year-old’s killing woke up Bihar’s conscience,-1.0,negative,"[('28-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Rise in shrimp feed prices leaves aqua farmers in deep waters in Andhra Pradesh,Rise in shrimp feed prices leaves aqua farmers in deep waters in Andhra Pradesh,0.0,neutral,"[('Andhra', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Where are Kannada cinema’s next stars?,Where are Kannada cinema’s next stars?,0.0,neutral,"[('Kannada', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"As India rapidly ages, more people require medical care at home. What’s missing? Insurance","As India rapidly ages, more people require medical care at home. What’s missing? Insurance",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ram temple donation row: All eight accused named in FIR arrested,Ram temple donation row: All eight accused named in FIR arrested,0.0,neutral,"[('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('FIR', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Nihang-police standoff in Uttarakhand ends after talks, group returns to Himachal","Nihang-police standoff in Uttarakhand ends after talks, group returns to Himachal",0.0,neutral,"[('Uttarakhand', 'GPE'), ('Himachal', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Death toll in Kolkata warehouse collapse rises to 15,Death toll in Kolkata warehouse collapse rises to 15,-1.0,negative,"[('Kolkata', 'GPE'), ('15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Punjab CM Bhagwant Mann’s fake video controversy | Explained,Punjab CM Bhagwant Mann’s fake video controversy | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_26,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Venezuela earthquake LIVE: World sends rescuers, aid as Venezuela reels from quakes","Venezuela earthquake LIVE: World sends rescuers, aid as Venezuela reels from quakes",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Rescuers search rubble for survivors as Venezuela earthquakes kill at least 235,Rescuers search rubble for survivors as Venezuela earthquakes kill at least 235,-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('at least 235', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Earthquake is devastating blow to Venezuela at time of uncertainty,Earthquake is devastating blow to Venezuela at time of uncertainty,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,People flee as building collapses on Caracas outskirts,People flee as building collapses on Caracas outskirts,0.0,neutral,"[('Caracas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,UN pauses Strait of Hormuz evacuation plan after cargo ship attacked,UN pauses Strait of Hormuz evacuation plan after cargo ship attacked,-1.0,negative,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Women alleging rape and sexual assault in France call to abolish statute of limitations,Women alleging rape and sexual assault in France call to abolish statute of limitations,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Supreme Court allows Trump to end protected status for Haitian and Syrian immigrants,Supreme Court allows Trump to end protected status for Haitian and Syrian immigrants,0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Haitian', 'NORP'), ('Syrian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Reflecting Pool liner cut with sharp knife or razor, National Park Service says","Reflecting Pool liner cut with sharp knife or razor, National Park Service says",0.0,neutral,"[('National Park Service', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Asia stock markets slide as tech shares slump,Asia stock markets slide as tech shares slump,0.0,neutral,"[('Asia', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Housing board votes to freeze New York rents in victory for Mamdani,Housing board votes to freeze New York rents in victory for Mamdani,1.0,positive,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Row over alleged theft of donations from India's landmark Ram temple,Row over alleged theft of donations from India's landmark Ram temple,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Venezuela Live Updates: More Rescuers Join Urgent Search for Quake Survivors,Venezuela Live Updates: More Rescuers Join Urgent Search for Quake Survivors,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela Live', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Three Months of War Changed the Gulf Forever,How Three Months of War Changed the Gulf Forever,-1.0,negative,"[('Three Months', 'DATE'), ('the Gulf Forever', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Zelensky Steps Up Threats Against Belarus for Aiding Drone Attacks,Zelensky Steps Up Threats Against Belarus for Aiding Drone Attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Zelensky Steps', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Europe’s Deadly Heat Wave: A Jolt for Climate Action, or Just for A.C.?","Europe’s Deadly Heat Wave: A Jolt for Climate Action, or Just for A.C.?",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe’s Deadly Heat Wave: A Jolt for Climate Action', 'ORG'), ('A.C.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A $2.5 Billion Whodunit: The Hack That Dented the U.K. Economy,A $2.5 Billion Whodunit: The Hack That Dented the U.K. Economy,0.0,neutral,"[('$2.5 Billion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran’s Long World Cup Journey Defined by War and Political Tension,Iran’s Long World Cup Journey Defined by War and Political Tension,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Heat Wave Prompts Paris to Suspend Sports Events and Public Drinking,Heat Wave Prompts Paris to Suspend Sports Events and Public Drinking,0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE'), ('Suspend Sports Events', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,World Cups Fans in Myanmar Boycott Junta-Linked Broadcasts,World Cups Fans in Myanmar Boycott Junta-Linked Broadcasts,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cups Fans', 'ORG'), ('Myanmar', 'GPE'), ('Boycott Junta', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Deadly Heat Wave in Europe Continues to Smash Temperature Records,Deadly Heat Wave in Europe Continues to Smash Temperature Records,0.0,neutral,"[('Deadly Heat Wave', 'PERSON'), ('Europe Continues', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_26,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Can a Youth Boom Survive South Sudan’s Education Crisis?,Can a Youth Boom Survive South Sudan’s Education Crisis?,-1.0,negative,[]
