Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Elecciones en Chile: la comunista Jara y el ultraderechista Kast competirán con modelos opuestos por la presidencia en la segunda vuelta el 14 de diciembre,Elections in Chile: the communist Jara and the far-right Kast will compete with opposing models for the presidency in the second round on December 14,-0.1,"[('Chile', 'GPE'), ('Jara', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('December 14', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Jeannette Jara, la comunista pragmática de origen popular que busca defender el poder de la izquierda en Chile","Jeannette Jara, the pragmatic communist of popular origin who seeks to defend the power of the left in Chile",0.3,"[('Jeannette Jara', 'PERSON'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"José Antonio Kast, el ultraderechista que quiere aglutinar el voto de oposición y ser presidente de Chile al tercer intento","José Antonio Kast, the far-right who wants to unite the opposition vote and be president of Chile on the third try",0.1,"[('José Antonio Kast', 'PERSON'), ('Chile', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Ecuador vota ""no"" a las 4 preguntas del referéndum promovido por el presidente Daniel Noboa","Ecuador votes ""no"" to the 4 questions of the referendum promoted by President Daniel Noboa",0.0,"[('Ecuador', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Daniel Noboa', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo llegó a los bosques de EE.UU. el euskera, la lengua más antigua de Europa","How Basque, the oldest language in Europe, arrived in the US forests",0.0,"[('Basque', 'NORP'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"एसआईआर का दूसरा चरण, ऑनलाइन कैसे भरें फॉर्म, कौन से दस्तावेज हैं ज़रूरी","Second phase of SIR, how to fill the form online, what documents are required",0.0,"[('Second', 'ORDINAL'), ('SIR', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,'ऑपरेशन सिंदूर' पर आर्मी चीफ़ उपेंद्र द्विवेदी बोले- 'मूवी शुरू भी नहीं हुई, सिर्फ़ ट्रेलर दिखाया'","Live, Army Chief Upendra Dwivedi said on 'Operation Sindoor' - 'The movie has not even started, only the trailer was shown'",0.06818181818181818,"[('Army', 'ORG'), ('Upendra Dwivedi', 'PERSON'), (""Operation Sindoor' - 'The"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"फॉरेंसिक साइंस क्या होती है, इसकी पढ़ाई में क्या होता है, नौकरियां कहां लगती हैं?","What is Forensic Science, what is involved in its study, where are the jobs available?",0.4,"[('Forensic Science', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान में 'इस्लाम धर्म अपनाने और निकाह करने वाली' भारतीय महिला की क्यों हो रही है तलाश,Why is the Indian woman who 'converted to Islam and married' being searched in Pakistan?,0.25,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Islam', 'NORP'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार: नीतीश कुमार सीएम बने तो एनडीए सरकार के सामने होंगी ये चुनौतियां,"Bihar: If Nitish Kumar becomes CM, NDA government will face these challenges.",0.0,"[('Nitish', 'NORP'), ('CM', 'ORG'), ('NDA', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'गोल्डन ब्लड' ग्रुप क्या है, जिसे लैब में तैयार करने की कोशिश कर रहे हैं वैज्ञानिक","What is 'Golden Blood' group, which scientists are trying to prepare in the lab?",0.3,"[(""Golden Blood'"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार में चुनाव के दौरान '3 लाख वोटर' बढ़ने पर कांग्रेस ने उठाए ये सवाल,Congress raised these questions on increase of '3 lakh voters' during elections in Bihar,0.0,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), (""'3"", 'DATE'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'पत्नी चली गई, सम्मान चला गया': 100 रुपये की रिश्वत का आरोप, 39 साल बाद बाइज़्ज़त बरी","'Wife is gone, respect is gone': Accused of taking bribe of Rs 100, honorably acquitted after 39 years",0.0,"[('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('39 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लालू परिवार से इतनी नाराज़ क्यों हैं रोहिणी आचार्य, पार्टी में क्या है संजय यादव का रोल?","Why is Rohini Acharya so angry with Lalu family, what is Sanjay Yadav's role in the party?",-0.5,"[('Rohini Acharya', 'PERSON'), ('Lalu', 'PERSON'), (""Sanjay Yadav's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Ex-ministra comunista e 'Bolsonaro chileno' disputarão 2º turno no Chile: o que eles defendem,Former communist minister and 'Chilean Bolsonaro' will compete in the 2nd round in Chile: what they defend,-0.06666666666666667,"[(""Chilean Bolsonaro'"", 'PERSON'), ('2nd', 'ORDINAL'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como segurança virou tema central em eleição no Chile — mesmo com criminalidade considerada baixa,How security became a central theme in elections in Chile — even with crime considered low,0.0,"[('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,EUA dizem que Maduro lidera suposto cartel de drogas que será declarado terrorista,US says Maduro leads alleged drug cartel that will be declared terrorist,-0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Protestos contra governo no México deixam pelo menos 120 feridos; o que se sabe,Anti-government protests in Mexico leave at least 120 injured; what is known,-0.3,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('at least 120', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O protesto de Raoni, maior liderança indígena do Brasil, por não discursar oficialmente na COP30","The protest by Raoni, Brazil's largest indigenous leader, for not speaking officially at COP30",0.0,"[('Raoni', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A proposta ambiciosa que fez o 'pai do Pix' deixar o Banco Central,The ambitious proposal that made the 'father of Pix' leave the Central Bank,0.125,"[('the Central Bank', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,De Martha Washington a Melania Trump: como primeiras-damas dos EUA usaram o poder da moda a seu favor,From Martha Washington to Melania Trump: how US first ladies used the power of fashion to their advantage,0.25,"[('Martha Washington', 'PERSON'), ('Melania Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como China venceu corrida global das baterias para veículos elétricos,How China won the global battery race for electric vehicles,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que EUA ganham ao ajudar Coreia do Sul a construir submarinos nucleares,What does the US gain from helping South Korea build nuclear submarines?,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Авиационный новострой. Какими получаются импортозамещенные российские самолеты?,Aviation new building. How do import-substituted Russian aircraft turn out?,0.06818181818181818,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп рассорился с членом Конгресса Марджори Тейлор Грин из-за Эпштейна. Она известна как противница помощи Украине,Trump feuded with Congresswoman Marjorie Taylor Greene over Epstein. She is known as an opponent of aid to Ukraine,0.0,"[('Marjorie Taylor Greene', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в результате ракетного удара по городу Балаклея погибли три человека, 10 пострадали, среди них трое детей","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: as a result of a missile attack on the city of Balakleya, three people were killed, 10 were injured, including three children",-0.2,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Balakleya', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Украинский хакер Вячеслав «Танк» Пенчуков раскрыл тайны своей кибербанды в интервью Би-би-си из тюрьмы в США,Ukrainian hacker Vyacheslav “Tank” Penchukov revealed the secrets of his cybergang in an interview with the BBC from prison in the United States,0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Vyacheslav “Tank” Penchukov', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Новые правила для просителей убежища в Британии: прибывшим в страну нелегально придется ждать 20 лет, чтобы получить ПМЖ",New rules for asylum seekers in Britain: those arriving in the country illegally will have to wait 20 years to obtain permanent residence,-0.18181818181818182,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('20 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Власти Ирана начали засев облаков, чтобы искусственно вызвать дождь в условиях засухи",Iranian authorities have begun seeding clouds to artificially induce rain in drought conditions,-0.6,"[('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Мексике тысячи людей вышли на акцию протеста. Более 100 человек пострадали, большинство — полицейские","Thousands of people protested in Mexico. More than 100 people were injured, most of them police officers.",0.5,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('More than 100', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Заедаете стресс? Вы не одиноки. Почему мы это делаем и можно ли это контролировать?,Are you eating stress? You are not alone. Why do we do this and can it be controlled?,0.0,[]
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Valve представила новую игровую консоль. Сможет ли она конкурировать с Xbox и PlayStation?,Valve introduced a new gaming console. Can it compete with Xbox and PlayStation?,0.13636363636363635,"[('Xbox', 'ORG'), ('PlayStation', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Действительно ли украинская энергетика оказалась беззащитной перед ударами России и что с ней будет дальше,Is the Ukrainian energy sector really defenseless against Russian attacks and what will happen to it next?,-0.13333333333333333,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告のファイル完全公開、トランプ氏が一転し支持　共和党議員らも要求,Trump backs full release of Epstein's files; Republican lawmakers also demand,0.35,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Republican', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日本の観光・小売株が下落、台湾めぐる中国との対立で,Japan's tourism and retail stocks fall due to conflict with China over Taiwan,-0.125,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,違法移民がイギリスを引き裂いているとマムード英内相、BBC番組で発言　難民政策変更の方針,"Illegal immigration is tearing Britain apart, Home Secretary Mahmoud says on BBC program, plans to change refugee policy",-0.5,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Home', 'ORG'), ('Mahmoud', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,化石燃料による排出が再び増加　一方で再生可能エネルギーも急成長、気候変動対策に希望,"Emissions from fossil fuels are on the rise again, while renewable energy is also growing rapidly, offering hope for climate change countermeasures",0.0,[]
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,メキシコ首都で数千人が政府に抗議、警官隊との衝突で120人負傷,"Thousands protest against government in Mexican capital, 120 injured in clashes with police",0.0,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('120', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インド・デリーの車両爆発で1人逮捕、当局は「テロ事件」として捜査,"One person arrested after car explosion in Delhi, India, authorities investigate as ``terrorist incident''",0.0,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、「相互関税」の対象から数十の食品を除外　コーヒーやトマト、牛肉など,"Trump excludes dozens of foods from 'reciprocal tariffs' including coffee, tomatoes, beef",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、BBCを来週にも提訴すると　演説映像の編集めぐり,Trump plans to sue BBC next week over editing of speech video,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('next week', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアのドローン、キーウの集合住宅に直撃　首都各地で死傷者,"Russian drone hits apartment complex in Kiv, causing casualties across the capital",-0.15,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kiv', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国外務省、日本への渡航自粛を呼びかけ　日本大使呼び出しも,"China's Ministry of Foreign Affairs calls for people to refrain from traveling to Japan, and also summons the Japanese ambassador",-0.0625,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Ministry of Foreign Affairs', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Watu 32 wapoteza maisha baada ya mgodi wa Kobalti kuporomoka DRC","Directly, 32 people lost their lives after a cobalt mine collapsed in the DRC",0.1,"[('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('DRC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Droni za ajabu zinazoonekana usiku katika viwanja vya ndege Ulaya. Je, tunapaswa kuwa na wasiwasi?",Strange drones seen at night in European airports. Should we be worried?,-0.025,"[('night', 'TIME'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kwa nini Papa anataka 'kusahihisha' sifa ya Bikira Maria, mama yake Yesu?","Why does the Pope want to 'correct' the reputation of the Virgin Mary, the mother of Jesus?",0.0,"[('the Virgin Mary', 'GPE'), ('Jesus', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Liverpool inamfukuzia Semenyo Bournemouth,European Football Rumors Monday: Liverpool chase Semenyo Bournemouth,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool', 'ORG'), ('Semenyo Bournemouth', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Fifa yaripoti machapisho 30,000 ya lugha chafu mtandaoni mwaka huu","Fifa reports 30,000 posts of foul language online this year",0.0,"[('Fifa', 'ORG'), ('30,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('this year', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, msongo wa mawazo hukufanya ule kupita kiasi?",Does stress make you overeat?,0.0,[]
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, inawezekana kuhuisha moyo ""uliokufa""?","Is it possible to revive a ""dead"" heart?",-0.1,[]
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Marekani kuisaidia Korea Kusini kujenga manowari za nyuklia za 'mashambulizi', hatua hii ina maana gani?","US to help South Korea build 'attack' nuclear submarines, what does this move mean?",-0.3125,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jeshi la DRC lawashawishi wanamgambo wa FDLR kuweka silaha chini,The DRC army persuaded the FDLR militia to lay down their arms,-0.15555555555555559,"[('FDLR', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Maandamano Tanzania: Wakuu wa vyombo vya ulinzi na usalama wote wawajibike, yasema TEC","Protests in Tanzania: The heads of all security and defense agencies should be held accountable, says TEC",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('TEC', 'ORG')]"
