Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""No tiene el respeto ni el apoyo"": en qué lugar quedan María Corina Machado y la oposición de Venezuela tras la captura de Maduro","""He does not have the respect or the support"": where María Corina Machado and the Venezuelan opposition remain after the capture of Maduro",0.0,"[('María Corina Machado', 'ORG'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Fui secuestrado y sigo siendo el presidente"": Nicolás Maduro se declara no culpable ante el tribunal de Nueva York","""I was kidnapped and I am still the president"": Nicolás Maduro pleads not guilty before the New York court",0.19318181818181818,"[('Nicolás Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Vengo con dolor, pero también con honor"": Delcy Rodríguez juramenta como presidenta encargada de Venezuela tras la captura de Maduro","""I come with pain, but also with honor"": Delcy Rodríguez is sworn in as president in charge of Venezuela after the capture of Maduro",0.0,"[('Delcy Rodríguez', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo la muerte de 32 cubanos en los ataques de EE.UU. en Venezuela confirmó los estrechos vínculos entre los cuerpos de seguridad de ambos países,How the death of 32 Cubans in the US attacks in Venezuela confirmed the close ties between the security forces of both countries,0.4,"[('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cubans', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,5 países a los que Trump ha lanzado advertencias después de la detención de Maduro,5 countries to which Trump has issued warnings after Maduro's arrest,-0.05,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,वेनेज़ुएला में 'तेल के खेल' का क्या भारत को फ़ायदा होगा?,Will India benefit from the 'oil game' in Venezuela?,-0.4,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,मोहम्मद शमी को चुनाव आयोग ने क्यों भेजा नोटिस? जानिए पूरा मामला","Live, why did the Election Commission send notice to Mohammed Shami? Know the whole matter",0.16818181818181818,"[('the Election Commission', 'ORG'), ('Mohammed Shami', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'मुझे किडनैप किया गया और मैं अब भी राष्ट्रपति हूँ', अमेरिकी कोर्ट में और क्या बोले मादुरो","'I was kidnapped and I am still the President', what else Maduro said in the US court",0.0,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"फ़िल्मों में एंग्री मेन की वाहवाही, पर्दे से क्यों लापता लेडीज़","Angry men praised in films, why are ladies missing from the screen?",-0.35,[]
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,कंटेंट क्रिएशन में असली कमाई कौन कर रहा है- पैसा वसूल, अवधि 3,38","Who's Making Real Money in Video Content Creation - Paisa Vasool, Duration 3,38",0.2,[]
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वेनेज़ुएला के पास कितना गोल्ड, कॉपर और तेल है","How much gold, copper and oil does Venezuela have?",0.2,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,इस्लाम क़ुबूल करके निकाह करने वाली भारतीय महिला को पाकिस्तान में 'हिरासत' में लिया गया,Indian woman who converted to Islam and got married was 'detained' in Pakistan,0.25,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Islam', 'ORG'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,मुस्तफ़िज़ुर रहमान विवाद और टी20 वर्ल्ड कप पर बांग्लादेश के पत्रकार और मीडिया क्या कह रहे हैं?,What are Bangladeshi journalists and media saying on Mustafizur Rahman controversy and T20 World Cup?,0.0,"[('Bangladeshi', 'PERSON'), ('Mustafizur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('T20 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,वेनेज़ुएला पर भारत के बयान की विदेश नीति के विश्लेषक क्यों कर रहे हैं आलोचना?,Why are foreign policy analysts criticizing India's statement on Venezuela?,-0.125,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Na crise da Venezuela, Brasil é mais forte frente a Trump do que outros países da região, diz Ian Bremmer","In the Venezuela crisis, Brazil is stronger in the face of Trump than other countries in the region, says Ian Bremmer",-0.125,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Ian Bremmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Filho de Maduro declara 'apoio incondicional' à presidente interina da Venezuela,Maduro's son declares 'unconditional support' for Venezuela's interim president,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Fui sequestrado e sigo presidente': o que Maduro disse sobre acusações de Trump em tribunal de NY,'I was kidnapped and I'm still president': what Maduro said about Trump's accusations in a NY court,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('NY', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Depois de ameaçar Colômbia, Trump volta a falar em anexar a Groenlândia","After threatening Colombia, Trump once again talks about annexing Greenland",0.0,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Greenland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem é Delcy Rodríguez, a poderosa sucessora de Maduro com trânsito nos EUA, na China e entre empresários","Who is Delcy Rodríguez, Maduro's powerful successor with a presence in the USA, China and among businesspeople",0.3,"[('Delcy Rodríguez', 'PERSON'), ('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,EUA ataca Venezuela e captura Maduro: confira a cobertura completa em tempo real da BBC,US attacks Venezuela and captures Maduro: check out BBC's complete real-time coverage,0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A história de Maduro, da escolha por Chávez para dar continuidade a seu legado à captura em operação militar dos EUA","Maduro's story, from Chávez's choice to continue his legacy to his capture in a US military operation",-0.1,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Chávez', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Espiões, drones e maçaricos: como os EUA capturaram Maduro?","Spies, drones and blowtorches: how did the US capture Maduro?",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como é prisão onde Maduro está detido em Nova York: 'Inferno na Terra',What is it like in the prison where Maduro is being held in New York: 'Hell on Earth',0.13636363636363635,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Не просто первая леди, а первый боец. Что известно о Силии Флорес, супруге Николаса Мадуро","Not just the first lady, but the first fighter. What is known about Celia Flores, wife of Nicolas Maduro",0.25,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Celia Flores', 'PERSON'), ('Nicolas Maduro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Я невиновен. Я — порядочный человек». Репортаж Би-би-си из зала суда над Мадуро,"“I'm innocent. I am a decent person."" BBC report from Maduro's courtroom",0.3333333333333333,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Кто такая Делси Родригес, занявшая место Мадуро. Марионетка Трампа или защитница Венесуэлы?","Who is Delcy Rodriguez, who took Maduro's place. Trump puppet or defender of Venezuela?",0.0,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Твери обломок украинского дрона попал в квартиру, погиб человек — власти","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: in Tver, a fragment of a Ukrainian drone hit an apartment, a person died - authorities",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Tver', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Иране вторую неделю продолжаются протесты. СМИ пишут, что у аятоллы Хаменеи есть план бегства в Москву",Protests continue in Iran for the second week. The media write that Ayatollah Khamenei has a plan to escape to Moscow,0.0,"[('Protests', 'NORP'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the second week', 'DATE'), ('Ayatollah Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Мадуро в суде Нью-Йорка заявил, что он «по-прежнему президент», Родригес принесла присягу временного президента Венесуэлы","LIVELive, Maduro in a New York court said that he is “still president”, Rodriguez took the oath of interim president of Venezuela",0.13636363636363635,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"При захвате Мадуро были убиты 32 кубинца, охранявших президента Венесуэлы. Что об этом известно","During the capture of Maduro, 32 Cubans guarding the Venezuelan President were killed. What is known about this",-0.2,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cubans', 'NORP'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Зеленский объявил об отставке главы СБУ Василия Малюка,Zelensky announced the resignation of SBU head Vasily Malyuk,0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('SBU', 'ORG'), ('Vasily Malyuk', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Поджог ЛЭП оставил без света 30 тыс. семей в Берлине, ответственность взяли на себя левые радикалы",The arson of power lines left 30 thousand families in Berlin without electricity; left-wing radicals took responsibility,0.0,"[('30 thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('Berlin', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Во Франции десять человек признаны виновными в травле первой леди Брижит Макрон. Они распространяли фейк, что та родилась мужчиной","In France, ten people have been found guilty of harassing First Lady Brigitte Macron. They spread the fake news that she was born a man",-0.1875,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('ten', 'CARDINAL'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('Lady Brigitte Macron', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヴェネズエラで暫定大統領が宣誓就任、マドゥロ氏は米連邦地裁で無罪主張,"Venezuela's interim president is sworn in, Maduro pleads not guilty in US federal court",0.25,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イラン、ここ数年で最も弱体化　抗議デモと米国の警告が体制揺るがす,Iran is at its weakest point in years as protests and US warnings shake the regime,0.0,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「劇的だった」　マドゥロ夫妻の初出廷、傍聴したBBC記者の報告, 所要時間 0,50","Video, ""It was dramatic"" Maduro and his wife's first court appearance, reported by a BBC reporter who attended, Duration 0,50",-0.09166666666666665,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,マクロン仏大統領夫人に対するネットいじめ、10人に有罪判決　パリ裁判所,Paris court finds 10 people guilty of cyberbullying French President Macron,-0.25,"[('Paris', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Macron', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ジャンクフード広告を禁止する措置、イギリスで施行,Measures to ban junk food advertising come into force in the UK,0.0,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「私は戦争捕虜だ」、マドゥロ氏が米連邦地裁に初出廷　無罪主張,"``I am a prisoner of war,'' Maduro says in his first appearance in US federal court, pleading not guilty",0.25,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,マドゥロ大統領夫妻、手錠かけられ裁判所へ移送, 所要時間 1,08","Video, President Maduro and his wife are handcuffed and taken to court, duration 1,08",0.0,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('1,08', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】トランプ氏はヴェネズエラの石油を欲しがっている　その計画はうまくいくのか,[Commentary] Mr. Trump wants Venezuelan oil. Will the plan work?,0.2,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,デンマーク首相、グリーンランドへの「脅し」やめるようトランプ氏に要求,Denmark's prime minister asks Trump to stop 'threatening' Greenland,0.0,"[('Denmark', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Greenland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Rais wa mpito aapishwa Venezueala, Maduro akikana mashitaka Marekani","Directly, the interim president is sworn in in Venezuela, Maduro denying the charges in the United States",0.1,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Mimi ni mfungwa wa kivita' - Yaliyojiri   Maduro alipofikishwa mahakamani,'I am a prisoner of war' - What happened when Maduro was brought to court,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumanne: Rashford kurejea Man United?,European Football Rumors Tuesday: Rashford to return to Man United?,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Rashford', 'PERSON'), ('Man United', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi majasusi na makomando wa Marekani walivyomnasa Maduro,How American spies and commandos caught Maduro,0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nani anaweza kuwa meneja wa kudumu wa Man Utd?,Who can be the permanent manager of Man Utd?,0.0,[]
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini magonjwa ya wanyama ni rahisi kuenea kwa binadamu na ni hatari zaidi?,Why animal diseases are easy to spread to humans and are more dangerous?,0.11111111111111112,[]
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Trump anataka mafuta ya Venezuela, Je, mpango wake utafanikiwa?","Trump wants Venezuelan oil, will his plan succeed?",0.2,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Cilia Flores ni nani, na sababu za kukamatwa kwake akiwa na Maduro ni zipi?","Who is Cilia Flores, and what are the reasons for her arrest with Maduro?",-0.05,"[('Cilia Flores', 'PERSON'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ni nani anaongoza Venezuela sasa na kipi kitakachofuata?,Who is leading Venezuela now and what will happen next?,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"'Huonekani, hupo' - maisha bila cheti cha kuzaliwa","'You are not seen, you are not there' - life without a birth certificate",0.0,[]
