Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué Venezuela es tan propensa a sufrir terremotos destructivos (y cómo se comparan los de esta semana con los del pasado),Why Venezuela is so prone to destructive earthquakes (and how this week's compares to those in the past),0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('week', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Imágenes satelitales del antes y el después muestran la devastación causada por el doble terremoto en Venezuela,Before and after satellite images show the devastation caused by the double earthquake in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Le contaré cómo la salvaste"": la emotiva despedida a una joven madre que murió protegiendo a su hija en los terremotos de Venezuela","""I'll tell her how you saved her"": the emotional farewell to a young mother who died protecting her daughter in the earthquakes in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Hospitales completamente desbordados"": cómo el terremoto pone más presión al ya deteriorado sistema de salud de Venezuela",'Hospitals completely overwhelmed': How the earthquake puts more pressure on Venezuela's already deteriorating health system,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Así te lo contamos: equipos de rescate internacionales se suman a la búsqueda de sobrevivientes en Venezuela mientras la cifra de muertos aumenta,This is what we tell you: international rescue teams join the search for survivors in Venezuela while the death toll increases,-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Por qué es imposible predecir el momento preciso de un terremoto?,Why is it impossible to predict the precise moment of an earthquake?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Lo que pasó me tiene el corazón chiquito"": la ciudad más venezolana de EE.UU. se moviliza para enviar ayuda a los afectados por los terremotos","""What happened has my heart small"": the most Venezuelan city in the US mobilizes to send aid to those affected by the earthquakes",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los gráficos que muestran la magnitud y el impacto de los potentes terremotos en Venezuela,Graphs showing the magnitude and impact of the powerful earthquakes in Venezuela,1.0,positive,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Mi corazón me dice que está vivo"": la esperanza de una joven que aguarda el rescate de su hermano bajo los escombros de un edificio en Caracas","""My heart tells me that he is alive"": the hope of a young woman who awaits the rescue of her brother under the rubble of a building in Caracas",0.0,neutral,"[('Caracas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Análisis BBC: los terremotos son un golpe devastador para una Venezuela en crisis desde hace años,BBC analysis: the earthquakes are a devastating blow for a Venezuela in crisis for years,-1.0,negative,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"महाराष्ट्र में टीईटी परीक्षा का पेपर लीक, कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी ने क्या कहा","TET exam paper leaked in Maharashtra, what Cockroach Janata Party said",0.0,neutral,"[('TET', 'ORG'), ('Maharashtra', 'NORP'), ('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वीडियो,द लेंस: परीक्षाओं में गड़बड़ी का ज़िम्मेदार कौन?, अवधि 32,41","Video,The Lens: Who is responsible for exam irregularities?, Duration 32,41",0.0,neutral,"[('32,41', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,वैभव सूर्यवंशी की बैटिंग और डेब्यू के बारे में पूर्व कप्तान दिलीप वेंगसरकर ने दिया बयान","Live, former captain Dilip Vengsarkar gave statement about Vaibhav Suryavanshi's batting and debut.",0.0,neutral,"[('Dilip Vengsarkar', 'PERSON'), (""Vaibhav Suryavanshi's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"मुंबई लोकल ट्रेन में हत्या: मृतक की बहन बोलीं, 'इतने लोग थे कोई मेरे भाई को बचाने नहीं आया'","Murder in Mumbai local train: Sister of the deceased said, 'There were so many people, no one came to save my brother'",0.0,neutral,"[('Mumbai', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पीएम मोदी का शिक्षा मंत्री धर्मेंद्र प्रधान को जन्मदिन की बधाई देना क्यों बहस का मुद्दा बन गया?,Why did PM Modi's birthday greeting to Education Minister Dharmendra Pradhan become a matter of debate?,0.0,neutral,"[('Education', 'ORG'), ('Dharmendra Pradhan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"दुबई: इंफ़्लुएंसर पर बॉयफ़्रेंड की हत्या का आरोप, कहा- अपने प्रेमी से था जान का ख़तरा","Dubai: Influencer accused of murdering boyfriend, said- there was a threat to his life from his lover",0.0,neutral,"[('Dubai', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वर्ल्ड कप फ़ुटबॉल 2026: ईरान और मिस्र के बीच मैच ड्रॉ, फ़्रांस की नॉर्वे पर ज़ोरदार जीत","World Cup Football 2026: Match draw between Iran and Egypt, France's strong victory over Norway",1.0,positive,"[('World Cup Football', 'EVENT'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ईरान का दावा, 'क्षेत्र के अमेरिकी ठिकानों को बनाया निशाना', समझौते के 10 दिन बाद ही अमेरिका-ईरान फिर आमने-सामने","Iran claims, 'American targets in the region were targeted', America-Iran face to face again just 10 days after the agreement",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('just 10 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ईरान: अली ख़ामेनेई के अंतिम संस्कार में पीएम मोदी जाएंगे या नहीं, भारत के लिए क्यों है दुविधा?",Iran: Why is there a dilemma for India whether PM Modi will attend the funeral of Ali Khamenei or not?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('PM Modi', 'GPE'), ('Ali Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"फ़ीफ़ा वर्ल्ड कप 2026: आठ हज़ार करोड़ रुपए से भी ज़्यादा की इनामी राशि, विनर को मिलेंगे इतने करोड़","FIFA World Cup 2026: Prize money of more than eight thousand crore rupees, the winner will get so many crores",1.0,positive,"[('FIFA World Cup', 'ORG'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('more than eight thousand', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Terremoto com quase 1.000 mortos na Venezuela é duro golpe em país mergulhado em incerteza e anos de degradação estrutural,"Earthquake with almost 1,000 deaths in Venezuela is a severe blow to a country steeped in uncertainty and years of structural degradation",-1.0,negative,"[('almost 1,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As imagens de antes e depois que mostram a devastação provocada pelos terremotos na Venezuela,Before and after images showing the devastation caused by the earthquakes in Venezuela,1.0,positive,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Sobe para 920 o número de mortos em terremotos da Venezuela enquanto equipes de resgate trabalham contra o relógio,Death toll from Venezuela earthquakes rises to 920 as rescue teams work around the clock,-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('920', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Cabo Verde faz história e se classifica para o mata-mata em sua primeira Copa; veja 6 fatos sobre o país que virou xodó do torneio,Cape Verde makes history and qualifies for the knockout stage in its first World Cup; see 6 facts about the country that became the favorite of the tournament,0.0,neutral,"[('Cape Verde', 'PRODUCT'), ('first World Cup', 'MONEY'), ('6', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O matemático 'guru das Copas' que previu confronto entre Brasil e Japão - e aposta em vitória dos japoneses,The mathematician 'World Cup guru' who predicted a clash between Brazil and Japan - and bets on a Japanese victory,1.0,positive,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem já está no mata-mata da Copa do Mundo? Veja a tabela e o que falta decidir,Who is already in the World Cup knockout stages? See the table and what remains to be decided,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,EUA bombardeiam alvos no Irã após ataque a navio no Estreito de Ormuz,US bombs targets in Iran after attack on ship in Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Big techs exploram e vendem nossas vulnerabilidades emocionais, diz pesquisadora britânica","Big tech exploits and sells our emotional vulnerabilities, says British researcher",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Meu total apoio': pré-candidato do PL ao governo do RJ defende que EUA bombardeiem embarcações do tráfico na costa brasileira,'My full support': PL pre-candidate for the government of RJ defends that the US bombs trafficking vessels on the Brazilian coast,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Vídeo de Michelle é novo revés para a campanha de Flávio, diz jornal britânico","Michelle's video is a new setback for Flávio's campaign, says British newspaper",0.0,neutral,"[('Michelle', 'ORG'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский заявил об ударе ракетами «Фламинго» по оборонному предприятию в Волгограде","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky announced a strike with Flamingo missiles on a defense plant in Volgograd",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Flamingo', 'ORG'), ('Volgograd', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Маленькая Кабо-Верде, дебютант ЧМ, сенсационно вышла в плей-офф. В чем секрет успеха?","Little Cape Verde, a World Cup debutant, sensationally reached the playoffs. What is the secret of success?",1.0,positive,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Украинский боксер Александр Усик отказался от всех своих поясов. Почему он это делает и что дальше?,Ukrainian boxer Alexander Usik renounced all his belts. Why is he doing this and what next?,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Alexander Usik', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Зной в Европе: самый жаркий июньский день в истории в Германии и Британии, отменены концерты, число умерших растет","Heat in Europe: the hottest June day on record in Germany and Britain, concerts canceled, death toll rising",-1.0,negative,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('June day', 'DATE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,60 миллионов звезд в одном снимке — и охота за новыми планетами,60 million stars in one image - and the hunt for new planets,0.0,neutral,"[('60 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Неприятная неожиданность: иностранные болельщики на ЧМ по футболу столкнулись с американской культурой чаевых,Unpleasant surprise: foreign fans at the World Cup encountered American tipping culture,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,США нанесли удары по Ирану в ответ на обстрел грузового судна в Ормузском проливе,The US launched strikes on Iran in response to the shelling of a cargo ship in the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Это сообщение Путину». Почему видео с угрозой военного мятежа от неизвестного блогера собрало миллионы просмотров,"""This is a message to Putin."" Why did a video threatening a military mutiny from an unknown blogger receive millions of views?",0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Умер бывший министр обороны России Сергей Иванов,Former Russian Defense Minister Sergei Ivanov has died,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Sergei Ivanov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Израиль и Ливан подписали рамочное соглашение при посредничестве США. Но «Хезболла» в нем не участвует,Israel and Lebanon signed a framework agreement brokered by the United States. But Hezbollah is not participating in it,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米軍がイランの標的を攻撃、貨物船へのドローン攻撃に対応と,"US military attacks targets in Iran, responds to drone attack on cargo ship",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,南米ヴェネズエラ地震、死者増える　余震200回以上,More than 200 aftershocks as deaths rise in Venezuelan earthquake in South America,-1.0,negative,"[('More than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('South America', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ドイツで史上最高気温、イベントも中止に……欧州で熱波の影響続く,"Record-high temperature in Germany, events canceled...Heat wave continues in Europe",0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ボルトン元米大統領補佐官、機密文書の扱いで有罪認める　政権解任後に批判に転じる,"Former US presidential aide John Bolton pleads guilty for handling classified documents, turns to criticism after being dismissed from administration",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('John Bolton', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,チャールズ英国王が納税額を公表、君主として初　昨年度は約27億円,"King Charles of England announces tax amount, first for monarch - approximately 2.7 billion yen last year",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('approximately 2.7 billion yen', 'MONEY'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリス国王夫妻、改修後のバッキンガム宮殿に住まないと　一般公開を拡大へ,Britain's King and Queen will have to live in the renovated Buckingham Palace to expand public access,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('King and Queen', 'ORG'), ('Buckingham Palace', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本、スウェーデンと引き分け決勝T進出　ベスト32戦はブラジルと,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Japan draws with Sweden to advance to the final T, the last 32 match will be against Brazil",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Sweden', 'GPE'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,国連、ホルムズ海峡で足止めの船員退避計画を一時停止　貨物船への攻撃受け,UN suspends evacuation plan for sailors stranded in Strait of Hormuz after attack on cargo ship,-1.0,negative,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Strait of', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米検察、ワインスティーン受刑者に対する強姦罪での起訴を1件取り下げ　他の有罪判決は有効,"US prosecutors drop one rape charge against Weinstein, other convictions stand",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Weinstein', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴェネズエラ地震、生存者の捜索続く　死傷者さらに増える恐れも,Search for survivors of Venezuela earthquake continues; casualties feared to rise further,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Zuio la mikutano ya kisiasa Tanzania ni mtihani kwa taasisi za dola au vyama vya siasa?,Is the ban on political meetings in Tanzania a test for government institutions or political parties?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yaishambulia Iran baada ya vikosi vyake kushambulia meli ya mizigo","Directly, the United States attacked Iran after its forces attacked a cargo ship",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,DR Congo yaishtaki Rwanda katika Mahakama ya Kimataifa ya Haki,DR Congo sues Rwanda in the International Court of Justice,0.0,neutral,"[('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE'), ('Rwanda', 'GPE'), ('the International Court of Justice', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vipi ni vipaumbele vya uchumi wa Iran iwapo mali zinazozuiliwa zitaachiliwa?,What are the priorities of Iran's economy if the blocked assets are released?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Serikali yapiga marufuku tena mikutano ya kisiasa Tanzania,The government has again banned political meetings in Tanzania,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mambo 5 yanayosababisha wenza kutoelewana,5 things that cause partners to disagree,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Marupurupu na matatizo ya chakula: nini kinaendelea ndani ya timu ya Senegal?,Benefits and food problems: what is going on inside the Senegalese team?,0.0,neutral,"[('Senegalese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Vita vya nani mwenye ushawishi' katika mlango bahari wa Hormuz,'Battle of who has influence' in the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Matetemeko 10 ya ardhi mabaya zaidi kuwahi kutikisa dunia,The 10 worst earthquakes to ever hit the world,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mataifa 10 yenye amani zaidi barani Afrika 2026,10 most peaceful countries in Africa 2026,1.0,positive,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Venezuelans dig for earthquake survivors as 72-hour rescue window nears end,Venezuelans dig for earthquake survivors as 72-hour rescue window nears end,1.0,positive,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP'), ('72-hour', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Thai police arrest Australian over killing of teenager found in suitcase,Thai police arrest Australian over killing of teenager found in suitcase,-1.0,negative,"[('Thai', 'NORP'), ('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Germany braces for record-breaking temperatures as heatwave moves east,Germany braces for record-breaking temperatures as heatwave moves east,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Somali intelligence helps US arrest alleged leader of Minnesota fraud,Somali intelligence helps US arrest alleged leader of Minnesota fraud,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Minnesota', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran war day 120: Tehran condemns US strikes, says it violates MoU","Iran war day 120: Tehran condemns US strikes, says it violates MoU",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('120', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('MoU', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Who profits from Africa’s gold?,Who profits from Africa’s gold?,0.0,neutral,"[('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Trossard brace guides Belgium to World Cup knockouts as New Zealand exit,Trossard brace guides Belgium to World Cup knockouts as New Zealand exit,0.0,neutral,"[('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran and US trade blame for attacks, threatening fragile ceasefire","Iran and US trade blame for attacks, threatening fragile ceasefire",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup knockouts: Who has made it to the round of 32 stage?,World Cup knockouts: Who has made it to the round of 32 stage?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Which teams are in the World Cup round of 32, and what’s the schedule?","Which teams are in the World Cup round of 32, and what’s the schedule?",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,K. Bhagyaraj: Tamil cinema’s master of screenplay and storytelling,K. Bhagyaraj: Tamil cinema’s master of screenplay and storytelling,0.0,neutral,"[('K. Bhagyaraj', 'PERSON'), ('Tamil', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Politics: where the versatile Bhagyaraj could not make a dent,Politics: where the versatile Bhagyaraj could not make a dent,0.0,neutral,"[('Bhagyaraj', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,5 must-watch films of the master writer-director,5 must-watch films of the master writer-director,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"In pictures: K Bhagyaraj, the master storyteller","In pictures: K Bhagyaraj, the master storyteller",0.0,neutral,"[('K Bhagyaraj', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Maharashtra Teacher Eligibility Test postponed day before exam after suspicion of paper leak,Maharashtra Teacher Eligibility Test postponed day before exam after suspicion of paper leak,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,What is the Ram Temple embezzlement case | Explainer,What is the Ram Temple embezzlement case | Explainer,0.0,neutral,"[('Explainer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Kerala KEAM results: Roshan Raju tops engineering, Vinayak Narayan bags first rank in pharmacy","Kerala KEAM results: Roshan Raju tops engineering, Vinayak Narayan bags first rank in pharmacy",0.0,neutral,"[('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('Roshan Raju', 'ORG'), ('Vinayak', 'GPE'), ('Narayan', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"K. Bhagyaraj, prominent actor and director, passes away","K. Bhagyaraj, prominent actor and director, passes away",0.0,neutral,"[('K. Bhagyaraj', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia war LIVE: Explosive drone targets Iranian Kurdish opposition camp north of Iraq's Erbil, sources say","West Asia war LIVE: Explosive drone targets Iranian Kurdish opposition camp north of Iraq's Erbil, sources say",-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Kurdish', 'NORP'), ('Iraq', 'GPE'), ('Erbil', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Explained | China, Bangladesh in talks over Teesta project","Explained | China, Bangladesh in talks over Teesta project",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Teesta', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US strikes Iran after attack on cargo ship,US strikes Iran after attack on cargo ship,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Venezuela earthquakes kill 920 people as international rescue teams arrive,Venezuela earthquakes kill 920 people as international rescue teams arrive,-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('920', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Mother dies saving daughter in Venezuela earthquakes,Mother dies saving daughter in Venezuela earthquakes,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Meloni and Trump: A very public fall-out that is proving very hard to fix,Meloni and Trump: A very public fall-out that is proving very hard to fix,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Europe's deadly heatwave breaks German record and halts public events,Europe's deadly heatwave breaks German record and halts public events,0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('German', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Religion row as Texas makes Bible stories required reading in schools,Religion row as Texas makes Bible stories required reading in schools,0.0,neutral,"[('Texas', 'GPE'), ('Bible', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,DR Congo takes Rwanda to international court over decades of conflict,DR Congo takes Rwanda to international court over decades of conflict,-1.0,negative,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG'), ('Rwanda', 'GPE'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Israel and Lebanon sign framework agreement after US-brokered talks,Israel and Lebanon sign framework agreement after US-brokered talks,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ex-Trump adviser John Bolton pleads guilty to mishandling classified documents,Ex-Trump adviser John Bolton pleads guilty to mishandling classified documents,0.0,neutral,"[('John Bolton', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Christmas market attacker jailed for life for murdering six in Germany,Christmas market attacker jailed for life for murdering six in Germany,-1.0,negative,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Volunteers Are Risking Their Lives to Stop Ebola. They Aren’t Always Welcome.,Volunteers Are Risking Their Lives to Stop Ebola. They Aren’t Always Welcome.,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mexican Officials Have Become Informants for the Trump Administration,Mexican Officials Have Become Informants for the Trump Administration,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexican', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Venezuela’s Economy Was On the Rise. Then the Earthquakes Struck.,Venezuela’s Economy Was On the Rise. Then the Earthquakes Struck.,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela’s Economy Was On', 'PERSON'), ('Earthquakes Struck', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"After New York Elections, Israelis Fear Further Rupture in U.S.-Israeli Relationship","After New York Elections, Israelis Fear Further Rupture in U.S.-Israeli Relationship",0.0,neutral,"[('New York Elections', 'ORG'), ('Israelis', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Exiled Chefs From Myanmar Give Burmese Food Chance to Shine on International Stage,Exiled Chefs From Myanmar Give Burmese Food Chance to Shine on International Stage,0.0,neutral,"[('Exiled Chefs', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Sculptor Rushes to Finish a Lionel Messi Statue During the World Cup,A Sculptor Rushes to Finish a Lionel Messi Statue During the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi Statue', 'PERSON'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Trump’s Vow to ‘Run’ Venezuela Is Tested After Quakes,Trump’s Vow to ‘Run’ Venezuela Is Tested After Quakes,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump’s Vow', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Strikes Iran in Retaliation for Attack on Vessel in Strait of Hormuz,U.S. Strikes Iran in Retaliation for Attack on Vessel in Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Retaliation', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Europe Sweats, Some Politicians Talk of Air-Conditioning, Not Climate Action","As Europe Sweats, Some Politicians Talk of Air-Conditioning, Not Climate Action",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Zelensky Steps Up Threats Against Belarus for Aiding Drone Attacks,Zelensky Steps Up Threats Against Belarus for Aiding Drone Attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Zelensky Steps', 'PERSON')]"
