Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Los minicerebros humanos desarrollados por científicos para ""alimentar"" computadoras","Human Minicerebros developed by scientists to ""feed"" computers",0.05,[]
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सुप्रीम कोर्ट में चीफ़ जस्टिस पर हमले की कोशिश, कोर्ट के अंदर क्या हुआ था","Attempted attack on Chief Justice in Supreme Court, what happened inside the court",0.0,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,UPSC इंटरव्यू में फ़ेल होने के बावजूद ऐसे मिल सकती है सरकारी नौकरी,"Despite failing in UPSC interview, such a government job can be found",0.0,"[('UPSC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार चुनाव से पहले नीतीश कुमार ने कितनी 'फ़्री' घोषणाएं की ,विपक्ष ने पूछा- पैसा कहां से आएगा?","Before the Bihar elections, how much 'free' announcements Nitish Kumar made, the opposition asked- where will the money come from?",0.4,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('Nitish Kumar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"जगह बदली, इवेंट बदला... लेकिन भारत-पाकिस्तान क्रिकेट में नहीं बदली विवाद की तस्वीर","Place changed, event changed ... but not changed in India-Pakistan cricket, picture of controversy",0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"भूमि पेडनेकर जूझ रही हैं स्किन की इस बीमारी से, जानिए क्या है इसका इलाज","Bhumi Pednekar is struggling with this skin disease, know what is its treatment",0.0,"[('Bhumi Pednekar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,José Dirceu: 'Bolsonaro não tem condições de ir para a prisão comum',José Dirceu: 'Bolsonaro is unable to go to the common prison',-0.4,"[('José Dirceu', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A corrida contra o tempo para resgatar mais de 200 pessoas presas no Monte Everest,The race against time to rescue more than 200 people arrested on Mount Everest,0.5,"[('more than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mount Everest', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que novo premiê francês renunciou após menos de um mês no cargo,Why New French Premier resigned after less than a month in office,-0.010101010101010102,"[('New French', 'NORP'), ('less than a month', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Após reportagem da BBC, AGU manda Facebook tirar do ar venda de material usado para falsificar bebidas","After BBC report, AGU has Facebook gets out of sale of material used to falsify drinks",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('AGU', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"TikTok recomenda conteúdo sexual e pornografia para crianças, denuncia relatório","Tiktok recommends sexual content and pornography for children, reports report",0.5,[]
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vistos de meio milhão, regras mais duras: a ofensiva de Trump para reduzir também imigração legal","Half Million Visas, Hardris Rules: Trump's offensive to reduce legal immigration as well",0.016666666666666677,"[('Half Million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os argumentos de Trump para enviar tropas federais para Chicago - e o que diz a oposição,Trump's arguments to send federal troops to Chicago - and what the opposition says,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Chicago', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Tenho seus nudes e tudo para arruinar você': BBC rastreia golpista que visa meninos adolescentes,'I have your nudes and all to ruin you': BBC Scammer Scrap that aims to teen boys,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como casos de HIV aumentaram mais de 1.000% em um pequeno país do Pacífico,"Such as HIV cases increased more than 1,000% in a small Pacific country",0.08333333333333333,"[('more than 1,000%', 'PERCENT'), ('Pacific', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в России: в Сумах беспилотник попал в крышу роддома, в Белгороде при ракетном ударе погиб мужчина","Livelive, War in Russia: in Sumy, the drone hit the roof of the maternity hospital, in Belgorod, a man died on a missile strike",0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Sumy', 'PERSON'), ('Belgorod', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нобелевскую премию по медицине и физиологии присудили за открытия в области иммунитета,The Nobel Prize for Medicine and Physiology was awarded for discoveries in the field of immunity,0.0,"[('The Nobel Prize for Medicine and Physiology', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Премьер-министр Франции  Лекорню подал в отставку. Во главе кабинета он пробыл меньше месяца,The Prime Minister of France Locorn resigned. He stayed at the head of the office for less than a month,-0.16666666666666666,"[('France Locorn', 'ORG'), ('less than a month', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что изменилось во Франции спустя год после процесса по делу Жизель Пелико,What changed in France a year after the process in the case of Giselle Pelico,0.0,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Giselle Pelico', 'FAC')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Израиль и ХАМАС обсудят в Египте возвращение заложников. Трамп призвал все стороны «действовать быстро»,"Israel and Hamas will discuss the return of hostages in Egypt. Trump called on all aspects ""act quickly""",0.3333333333333333,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нобель для президента. Как воинственный американский лидер уговорил Россию подписать договор и получил премию мира,Nobel is for the president. How a warlike American leader persuaded Russia to sign an agreement and received a world award,0.0,"[('Nobel', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Расизм, любовь к насилию и женоненавистничество. Что выявила скрытая съемка в полицейском участке Лондона","Racism, love of violence and femininity. What was revealed hidden shooting in the police station London",0.16666666666666669,"[('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Дроны, язык жестов и попытки «выглядеть как американец»: как иммигранты в США пытаются перехитрить агентов ICE","Drones, gestures and attempts to “look like an American”: how immigrants in the United States are trying to outwit ICE agents",0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Массированный удар по Украине: Россия выпустила более 50 ракет и около 500 дронов,Massive blow to Ukraine: Russia produced more than 50 missiles and about 500 drones,0.25,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('more than 50', 'CARDINAL'), ('about 500', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Пропалестинские акции в Европе: в Риме четверть миллиона человек прошли маршем мимо Колизея, в Лондоне почти 500 арестованных","Rosmostinsky actions in Europe: in Rome, a quarter of a million people passed a march past the Coliseum, in London almost 500 arrested",-0.25,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Rome', 'GPE'), ('a quarter', 'CARDINAL'), ('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Coliseum', 'LOC'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('almost 500', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、オレゴン州にカリフォルニア州兵を派遣　連邦地裁が差し止め命令,Trump sends California National Guard to Oregon; federal district court orders to stop him,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('California National Guard', 'ORG'), ('Oregon', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日経平均が過去最高値を更新、終値でも　ビジネス重視の高市氏の自民総裁就任後初取引,"Nikkei average hits record highs, and even at closing prices, Takaichi, who is a business-focused member of the LDP, will make his first transaction since becoming president of the LDP",0.18333333333333335,"[('Takaichi', 'ORG'), ('LDP', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('LDP', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ガザ交渉の仲介役に「迅速な行動」を要求　間接交渉の前日,"Trump demands ""quick action"" from intermediary in Gaza negotiations; the day before indirect negotiations",0.21666666666666667,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('the day', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,オーストラリアとパプアニューギニアが新たな防衛条約を締結、太平洋地域の安全保障見据え,Australia and Papua New Guinea sign new defense treaties to protect the Pacific region,0.13636363636363635,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Papua New Guinea', 'GPE'), ('Pacific', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エヴェレストのキャンプサイト、数百人が大雪で動けず　救助活動進む,"Hundreds of people are unable to move due to heavy snow, rescue operations are underway at campsite in Everest",-0.27499999999999997,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシア、ウクライナ各地をミサイルとドローンで攻撃　5人死亡とゼレンスキー氏,Five people killed in Russia and Ukraine attacks with missiles and drones,-0.2,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,チェコ下院選、バビシュ前首相率いるポピュリスト政党が第1党に,Populist party led by former Prime Minister Babis becomes the first party in Czech House election,0.125,"[('Babis', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Czech', 'NORP'), ('House', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ハマスのイスラエル襲撃から2年、ロンドンなどで集会　マンチェスターではシナゴーグ襲撃事件の追悼も,"Two years after the Hamas attack on Israel, rally in London and other places; Manchester also commemorates the synagogue attack",-0.125,"[('Two years', 'DATE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Manchester', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,犬や猫、カメも祝福……キリスト教「動物の守護聖人」の祝日に, 所要時間 1,20","Video, Dogs, Cats, and Turtles are also blessed... On the holiday of Christian ""Patron Saints of Animals"", duration 1,20",0.0,"[('Turtles', 'PRODUCT'), ('Christian', 'NORP'), ('Patron Saints of Animals', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Humphrey Polepole: Familia yathibitisha 'katekwa na wasiojulikana',Humphrey Slowly: Family Confirms 'captured by anonymous',-0.30000000000000004,"[(""Humphrey Slowly: Family Confirms '"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Watu 21 wauawa Gaza katika kipindi cha saa 24 zilizopita","Directly, 21 people killed in Gaza in the past 24 hours",-0.11666666666666665,"[('21', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('the past 24 hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Nitaenda kusherehekea na Ferguson na Wenger' - Guardiola,'I'm going to celebrate with Ferguson and Wenger' - Guardiola,0.0,"[('Ferguson', 'PERSON'), ('Wenger', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Samia ameshindwa kukamilisha mageuzi kwa namna na kiwango alichoahidi?,Why has Samia failed to complete the reform in the form and level he promised?,-0.2,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Polisi Tanzania yaonya usambazaji maudhui ya 'uhalifu na uchochezi',Police in Tanzania warn the 'crime and inflammatory content' content,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi VVU vilivyoongezeka kwa zaidi ya 1000% katika taifa hili dogo la  pasifiki,How HIV has increased by more than 1000% in this small Pacific nation,0.125,"[('more than 1000%', 'PERCENT'), ('Pacific', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Chelsea sasa yamtaka mshambuliaji wa Bournemouth Antoine Semenyo,European football rumors Monday: Chelsea now wants Bournemouth striker Antoine Semenyo,0.1,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Chelsea', 'PERSON'), ('Bournemouth', 'ORG'), ('Antoine Semenyo', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi ya kulinda magoti yako kadiri unavyozeeka,How to protect your knees as you get older,0.16666666666666666,[]
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Netanyahu asema anatarajia kutangaza kuachiliwa kwa mateka katika 'siku zijazo',Netanyahu says he hopes to announce the release of the captives in the 'future',0.0,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini mlo wenye chumvi kidogo una athari sawa na wenye chumvi nyingi?,Why does a low salt diet have the same effect as high salt?,0.05333333333333334,[]
