Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Devadasis, las jóvenes entregadas a los dioses que quedan atrapadas en una vida de explotación sexual","Devadasis, the young women dedicated to the gods who become trapped in a life of sexual exploitation",0.13333333333333333,[]
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué Trinidad y Tobago defiende el despliegue militar de Trump en el Caribe (y cómo eso tensa sus relaciones con la vecina Venezuela),Why Trinidad and Tobago defends Trump's military deployment in the Caribbean (and how it strains its relations with neighboring Venezuela),-0.1,"[('Trinidad', 'GPE'), ('Tobago', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Detienen a Yifat Tomer-Yerushalmi, la exabogada principal del ejército de Israel que filtró un video que muestra los abusos de soldados a un preso palestino","Yifat Tomer-Yerushalmi, the former top lawyer for the Israeli army who leaked a video showing soldiers abusing a Palestinian prisoner, is arrested",0.25,"[('Yifat Tomer-Yerushalmi', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Cualquier contacto puede exterminarlos"": la lucha por proteger a los mashco piro, una de las últimas tribus aisladas del mundo","""Any contact can exterminate them"": the fight to protect the Mashco Piro, one of the last isolated tribes in the world",0.0,"[('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Soy el hombre más afortunado del mundo, pero cada día es un sufrimiento"": el único sobreviviente del accidente de Air India en el que murieron 241 personas","""I am the luckiest man in the world, but every day is suffering"": the only survivor of the Air India crash in which 241 people died",0.0,"[('every day', 'DATE'), ('Air India', 'ORG'), ('241', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ट्रंप की धमकी के बाद ज़ोहरान ममदानी बोले- डर गए हैं अमेरिकी राष्ट्रपति,"After Trump's threat, Zohran Mamdani said - American President is scared",0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ईरान के सर्वोच्च नेता ख़ामेनेई ने अमेरिका के साथ सहयोग के लिए रखीं ये तीन शर्तें,Iran's Supreme Leader Khamenei put forward these three conditions for cooperation with America,0.0,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Supreme', 'ORG'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,स्टारबक्स का चीन में अपने कारोबार को लेकर बड़ा फ़ैसला, किस पर कितना असर","Live, Starbucks' big decision regarding its business in China, how much impact will it have on whom?",0.11212121212121212,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'मैं अब भी गहरी तकलीफ़ में हूं', एयर इंडिया विमान हादसे में अकेले ज़िंदा बचे शख़्स की आपबीती","'I am still in deep pain', the story of the sole survivor of the Air India plane crash",0.0,"[('Air India', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव: लेफ्ट पार्टियों के लिए 2020 के प्रदर्शन को दोहरा पाना कितनी बड़ी चुनौती?,Bihar Elections: How big a challenge is it for the Left parties to repeat the performance of 2020?,0.0,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON'), ('Left', 'PERSON'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार चुनावः लालू यादव के रोड शो पर चिराग के सवाल, पीएम मोदी के बयान पर तेजस्वी की आपत्ति","Bihar Elections: Chirag's questions on Lalu Yadav's road show, Tejashwi's objection to PM Modi's statement",0.0,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON'), ('Chirag', 'PERSON'), (""Lalu Yadav's"", 'PERSON'), ('Tejashwi', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'उस टाइम मुझे मम्मी ने अपने गहने बेचकर मैच खेलने भेजा था', वर्ल्ड चैंपियन क्रांति गौड़ के संघर्ष की कहानी","'At that time my mother sold her jewelery and sent me to play the match', the story of the struggle of world champion Kranti Gaur",0.0,"[('Kranti Gaur', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप का रूस, चीन और पाकिस्तान समेत कई देशों पर परमाणु परीक्षण का आरोप: 'वे अंडरग्राउंड टेस्ट करते हैं, लेकिन बताते नहीं'","Trump accuses many countries including Russia, China and Pakistan of nuclear testing: 'They test underground, but don't tell'",0.5,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बदायूं: दलित परिवार की बारात के दौरान हिंसा के मामले में जांच शुरू, अब तक क्या पता है?","Badaun: Investigation started in the case of violence during the marriage procession of a Dalit family, what is known so far?",0.1,"[('Dalit', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Narcoterrorismo': como governos usam o termo em discurso de guerra a facções criminosas como o Comando Vermelho,'Narcoterrorism': how governments use the term in war discourse against criminal factions such as the Red Command,-0.13333333333333333,"[('the Red Command', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os agentes ambientais que botam fogo na natureza,Environmental agents that set nature on fire,0.0,[]
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A pedido de Helder Barbalho, Lula decreta GLO em Belém durante a COP","At the request of Helder Barbalho, Lula decrees GLO in Belém during the COP",0.0,"[('Helder Barbalho', 'ORG'), ('COP', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Bateram nela, puxaram o cabelo dela. E não tinha ninguém lá dentro': a faxineira presa por fazer live da polícia em sua casa durante operação no Rio","'They beat her, pulled her hair. And there was no one inside': the cleaning lady arrested for live streaming the police in her home during an operation in Rio",0.13636363636363635,"[('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem são 115 de 117 suspeitos mortos em megaoperação no Rio, segundo a polícia","Who are 115 of 117 suspects killed in mega operation in Rio, according to police",-0.2,"[('115', 'CARDINAL'), ('117', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Sou o homem mais sortudo do mundo, mas também estou sofrendo, diz único sobrevivente do acidente da Air India","I'm the luckiest man in the world, but I'm also suffering, says sole survivor of Air India crash",0.0,"[('Air India', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Suprema Corte dos EUA pode barrar tarifas de Trump?,Can the US Supreme Court block Trump's tariffs?,0.0,"[('the US Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Sem cadeira erótica e espelho no teto: como motéis se adaptaram para a COP30 em Belém,Without erotic chair and mirror on the ceiling: how motels adapted for COP30 in Belém,0.7,[]
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump diz que dias de Maduro como presidente da Venezuela estão contados,Trump says Maduro's days as president of Venezuela are numbered,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('days', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Выборы мэра Нью-Йорка: удастся ли «демократическому социалисту» Мамдани стать новым главой города?,New York mayoral election: will the “democratic socialist” Mamdani succeed in becoming the new head of the city?,0.24090909090909093,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Приходится писать смски».  Помогают ли «белые списки» при отключениях интернета в России?,“We have to text.”  Do “white lists” help during Internet outages in Russia?,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: взрыв на нефтехимическом заводе в Башкирии после атаки дронов","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: explosion at a petrochemical plant in Bashkiria after a drone attack",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Bashkiria', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Из-под завалов обрушившейся в Риме средневековой башни извлекли рабочего,A worker was pulled out from under the rubble of a medieval tower that collapsed in Rome.,0.0,"[('Rome', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Ким Кардашьян заявила, что американцы не высаживались на Луну. НАСА пригласило ее на запуск «Артемиды»",Kim Kardashian said that Americans did not land on the moon. NASA invited her to the Artemis launch,0.0,"[('Kim Kardashian', 'PERSON'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('NASA', 'ORG'), ('Artemis', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Мальдивы запрещают курение родившимся после 2007 года. Туристов это тоже коснется,The Maldives bans smoking for those born after 2007. This will also affect tourists,0.0,"[('Maldives', 'ORG'), ('2007', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Нападение с ножом в поезде в Англии: нападавший предстал перед судом, его проверяют на причастность к другим преступлениям",Knife attack on a train in England: the attacker appeared in court and is being investigated for involvement in other crimes,-0.125,"[('England', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Лидер Валенсии ушел в отставку на фоне резкой критики его действий во время наводнения, унесшего жизни 229 человек",Valencia's leader resigns amid harsh criticism of his handling of floods that killed 229 people,-0.2,"[('Valencia', 'PERSON'), ('229', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Израиль подтвердил личности еще трех заложников, тела которых вернул ХАМАС",Israel has confirmed the identities of three more hostages whose bodies were returned to Hamas,0.45,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Афганистане произошло мощное  землетрясение. По меньшей мере 20 человек погибли, сотни пострадали",A powerful earthquake occurred in Afghanistan. At least 20 people were killed and hundreds injured,-0.06666666666666667,"[('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('At least 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英列車内での刺傷事件、32歳男性を殺人未遂などで起訴　直前の別件でも起訴,32-year-old man charged with attempted murder in stabbing incident on British train; also charged in separate case,-0.3,"[('32-year-old', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル軍の元法務トップ逮捕、パレスチナ人拘束者への「虐待映像」流出めぐり,Former Israeli military legal chief arrested over leaked footage of abuse of Palestinian detainees,0.03333333333333333,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米NY市長選、トランプ氏がクオモ氏支持を表明　民主党候補が勝てば補助金削減と脅す,"Trump announces support for Cuomo in NY mayoral election, threatens to cut subsidies if Democratic candidate wins",0.3,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Cuomo', 'PERSON'), ('NY', 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アフガニスタン北部でM6.3の地震、少なくとも20人死亡と当局　「多数の死傷者」が出るおそれ,"M6.3 earthquake in northern Afghanistan kills at least 20 people, authorities fear ``many casualties''",0.1,"[('M6.3', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('at least 20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,モルディヴ、2007年以降生まれのたばこ使用・購入・販売を禁止　観光客も,"Maldives bans people born after 2007 from using, purchasing and selling tobacco, including tourists",0.0,"[('Maldives', 'ORG'), ('2007', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英王室のアンドリュー氏、元妻と約2.8億円で契約の企業に宮殿ツアー手配　BBCの取材で判明,"British royal family member Andrew arranged a palace tour with a company he contracted with his ex-wife for approximately 280 million yen, revealed in an interview with the BBC",-0.2,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('approximately 280 million yen', 'MONEY'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、恩赦与えた暗号資産取引バイナンス元CEOを「知らない」と発言,"Trump says he ""doesn't know"" the former CEO of cryptocurrency exchange Binance, whom he pardoned",0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Binance', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「助けも食料も水もない」　ハリケーンに襲われ救援待つジャマイカの町,"``No help, no food, no water'' - Jamaican town awaiting relief after being hit by hurricane",0.0,"[('Jamaican', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,仏ルーヴル美術館の宝飾品盗難、犯罪組織の犯行ではないと検察,Prosecutors say the theft of jewelry from France's Louvre Museum was not the work of a criminal organization,-0.4,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Louvre Museum', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Wakili wa zamani wa jeshi la Israel akamatwa kwa kuvujisha video ya wafungwa wa Kipalestina wakinyanyaswa","Live, Former Israeli army lawyer arrested for leaking video of Palestinian prisoners being tortured",0.06818181818181818,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,SADC yasema Uchaguzi wa Tanzania uligubikwa na dosari,SADC says Tanzania's election was marred by flaws,0.0,"[('SADC', 'PERSON'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Samia atoa onyo dhidi ya waliochochea vurugu,President Samia warns against those who incite violence,0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumanne: Mainoo anakaribia kuondoka Man Utd,European Football Rumors Tuesday: Mainoo is set to leave Man Utd,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Mainoo', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Sijamuona mwanangu tangu Jumatano',Protests in Tanzania: 'I haven't seen my son since Wednesday',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mtandao warejea Tanzania,Internet returning to Tanzania,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi kuzimwa kwa mtandao Tanzania kunavyosababisha habari potofu,How the internet blackout in Tanzania is causing misinformation,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Marekani ina haki ya kuingia Nigeria kupambana na ugaidi?",Does the United States have the right to enter Nigeria to fight terrorism?,0.2857142857142857,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Nigeria', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Samia Suluhu Hassan aliyeshinda uchaguzi Tanzania kwa zaidi ya asilimia 97 ni nani?,Who is Samia Suluhu Hassan who won the election in Tanzania by more than 97 percent?,0.5,"[('Hassan', 'PERSON'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('more than 97 percent', 'PERCENT')]"
2025_11_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maporomoko mengine ya ardhi yakumba Kenya na Uganda,Other landslides hit Kenya and Uganda,-0.125,"[('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('Uganda', 'GPE')]"
