Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué las ideas de un gran estratega de las Guerras Napoleónicas siguen vigentes para entender el actual conflicto en Irán,Why the ideas of a great strategist from the Napoleonic Wars are still valid to understand the current conflict in Iran,-0.3333,negative,"[('the Napoleonic Wars', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo la familia Andic construyó el imperio de la moda Mango y qué poder tiene Jonathan, el heredero acusado de la muerte de su padre","How the Andic family built the Mango fashion empire and what power Jonathan, the heir accused of his father's death, has",-1.0,negative,"[('Andic', 'PERSON'), ('Mango', 'LOC'), ('Jonathan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Vendí a mi hija de 5 años para que recibiera tratamiento médico"": las familias que se enfrentan a decisiones imposibles en Afganistán",'I sold my 5-year-old daughter for medical treatment': Families facing impossible decisions in Afghanistan,0.0,neutral,"[('5-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Las imágenes del ejercicio militar de EE.UU. en Caracas autorizado por el gobierno de Venezuela,Images of the US military exercise in Caracas authorized by the government of Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Caracas', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo es Bután, el remoto reino del Himalaya que ahora se abre al mundo","What Bhutan is like, the remote Himalayan kingdom that is now opening up to the world",0.0,neutral,"[('Bhutan', 'GPE'), ('Himalayan', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo es el Jardín de los Venenos, que alberga más de 100 plantas tóxicas (incluida la más venenosa del mundo)","What is the Garden of Poisons like, which houses more than 100 toxic plants (including the most poisonous in the world)",0.0,neutral,"[('the Garden of Poisons', 'FAC'), ('more than 100', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Agentes del Servicio Secreto abaten a un sospecho de un tiroteo afuera de la Casa Blanca,Secret Service agents kill suspect in shooting outside White House,-1.0,negative,"[('White House', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Trump anuncia que tiene un acuerdo ""prácticamente negociado"" con Irán que incluiría la apertura del estrecho de Ormuz","Trump announces that he has a ""practically negotiated"" agreement with Iran that would include the opening of the Strait of Hormuz",1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Nervios de acero"": Tammie Jo Shults, la piloto de combate que salvó la vida de 148 pasajeros","""Nerves of steel"": Tammie Jo Shults, the fighter pilot who saved the lives of 148 passengers",0.0,neutral,"[('Tammie Jo Shults', 'PERSON'), ('148', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El director ejecutivo de un banco pide disculpas tras describir a sus trabajadores como ""capital humano de menor valor""","Bank CEO apologizes after describing his workers as ""lower value human capital""",0.0,neutral,"[('Bank', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दिल्ली जिमखाना को खाली कराने का पूरा मामला क्या है, जानिए 113 साल पुराने क्लब का इतिहास","What is the whole matter of vacating Delhi Gymkhana, know the history of 113 year old club",0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi Gymkhana', 'PERSON'), ('113 year old', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अभिनेता राम चरण ने गेंदबाज़ बुमराह से इस बात के लिए मांगी माफ़ी","Live, actor Ram Charan apologized to bowler Bumrah for this",0.0,neutral,"[('Ram Charan', 'PERSON'), ('Bumrah', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"गुरिंदरवीर सिंह कौन हैं, जो बन गए हैं भारत के सबसे तेज़ धावक","Who is Gurinderveer Singh, who has become India's fastest runner?",0.0,neutral,"[('Gurinderveer Singh', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप ने ईरान के साथ समझौते को लेकर किया अहम दावा, होर्मुज़ स्ट्रेट को खोलने पर ये कहा","Trump made an important claim regarding the agreement with Iran, said this on opening the Strait of Hormuz",1.0,positive,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,प्रेस फ्रीडम पर सवाल उठाकर यूरोप ने क्या भारत पर अपना रुख़ बदला है?,Has Europe changed its stance on India by raising questions on press freedom?,0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दुनिया के 'सबसे प्रदूषित' कहे गए मेघालय के इस इलाके में अब कैसे हैं हालात?,"How is the situation now in this area of ​​Meghalaya, which has been called the 'most polluted' in the world?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्राउडफ़ंडिंग के 34 करोड़ रुपये से केरल के एक व्यक्ति की सऊदी अरब में मौत की सज़ा कैसे माफ़ हुई,How a Kerala man's death sentence was commuted in Saudi Arabia with Rs 34 crore of crowdfunding,-1.0,negative,"[('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('34', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अमेरिका के इस फ़ैसले का भारतीय युवाओं पर क्या होगा असर,What will be the impact of this decision of America on Indian youth?,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बेल मिलते ही जेल के बाहर रेप अभियुक्त के स्वागत पर एफ़आईआर दर्ज, क्या है पूरा मामला","FIR registered on welcoming rape accused outside the jail as soon as he got bail, what is the whole matter",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,खाड़ी के देशों में काम करने गईं कुछ भारतीय महिलाओं की आपबीती,The ordeal of some Indian women who went to work in Gulf countries,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Captura, mudança de poder e colapso: o que pode acontecer em Cuba após governo Trump indiciar Raúl Castro?","Capture, change of power and collapse: what could happen in Cuba after the Trump government indicts Raúl Castro?",-1.0,negative,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Vendi minha filha de 5 anos para pagar tratamento médico': os relatos de pais afegãos diante da pobreza extrema,'I sold my 5-year-old daughter to pay for medical treatment': reports from Afghan parents faced with extreme poverty,0.0,neutral,"[('5-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Afghan', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Suspeito é morto após abrir fogo contra agentes do Serviço Secreto da Casa Branca, nos Estados Unidos",Suspect is killed after opening fire on White House Secret Service agents in the United States,-1.0,negative,"[('White House Secret Service', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump diz que acordo com Irã foi 'amplamente negociado', incluindo a reabertura do Estreito de Ormuz","Trump says Iran deal was 'largely negotiated', including reopening of Strait of Hormuz",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait of', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como um império bilionário da moda virou palco de uma disputa familiar e de uma acusação de homicídio,How a billion-dollar fashion empire became the scene of a family dispute and a murder accusation,0.0,neutral,"[('billion-dollar', 'MONEY')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Em busca do soldado Tom: a solução do mistério do prisioneiro de guerra soviético da 2ª Guerra Mundial,In Search of Private Tom: Solving the WWII Soviet Prisoner of War Mystery,-1.0,negative,"[('the WWII Soviet Prisoner of War Mystery', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que as séries de TV não mostram de quem vive de OnlyFans,What TV series don't show about those who live on OnlyFans,0.0,neutral,"[('OnlyFans', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O 'último cidadão soviético': o cosmonauta 'abandonado' no espaço há 35 anos durante o colapso da União Soviética,The 'last Soviet citizen': the cosmonaut 'abandoned' in space 35 years ago during the collapse of the Soviet Union,-1.0,negative,"[('Soviet', 'NORP'), ('35 years ago', 'DATE'), ('the Soviet Union', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Flávio Bolsonaro vai aos EUA em busca de Trump e agenda positiva em meio a crise e sob olhar atento do governo Lula,Flávio Bolsonaro goes to the USA in search of Trump and a positive agenda amid the crisis and under the watchful eye of the Lula government,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Óculos inteligentes são invasão de privacidade?,Are smart glasses an invasion of privacy?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Разрушения по всему Киеву и в Черкассах, погибшие и много раненых: последствия ночного удара России","Destruction throughout Kyiv and Cherkassy, ​​dead and many wounded: the consequences of Russia's night strike",0.0,neutral,"[('Cherkassy', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Россия ударила по Украине ракетами «Орешник», «Кинжал» и «Циркон», в Киеве масштабные разрушения, двое погибших и десятки раненых","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Russia hit Ukraine with Oreshnik, Kinzhal and Zircon missiles, large-scale destruction in Kyiv, two dead and dozens wounded",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Oreshnik', 'GPE'), ('Kinzhal', 'ORG'), ('Zircon', 'ORG'), ('Kyiv', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Секретная служба США застрелила человека, открывшего стрельбу у Белого Дома — всего через месяц после перестрелки на ужине корреспондентов","The US Secret Service shot and killed a man who opened fire outside the White House, just a month after the Correspondents' Dinner shooting.",-1.0,negative,"[('The US Secret Service', 'ORG'), ('the White House', 'FAC'), ('just a month', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Александр Усик победил «короля кикбоксинга» Рико Верховена,Alexander Usyk defeated the “king of kickboxing” Rico Verhoeven,0.0,neutral,"[('Alexander Usyk', 'PERSON'), ('Rico Verhoeven', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,От Мьянмы до Венесуэлы: как люди сопротивляются интернет-блокировкам,From Myanmar to Venezuela: how people resist internet blocking,0.0,neutral,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Господин президент РФ, закончите эту бойню», — Андрей Звягинцев получил Гран-при Каннского кинофестиваля","“Mr. President of the Russian Federation, end this massacre,” Andrei Zvyagintsev received the Grand Prix at the Cannes Film Festival",0.0,neutral,"[('the Russian Federation', 'GPE'), ('Andrei Zvyagintsev', 'PERSON'), ('the Grand Prix', 'FAC'), ('the Cannes Film Festival', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп заявил, что соглашение с Ираном почти достигнуто и включает открытие Ормузского пролива",Trump said an agreement with Iran was almost reached and included the opening of the Strait of Hormuz.,1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Голод или жадность: сколько еды класть себе в тарелку?,Hunger or greed: how much food should you put on your plate?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Участницы британского реалити-шоу «Женаты с первого взгляда»  заявили, что их насиловали экранные мужья",Participants in the British reality show Married at First Sight said they were raped by their on-screen husbands,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Около 90 рабочих погибли при взрыве на угольной шахте в Китае,About 90 workers died in a coal mine explosion in China,0.0,neutral,"[('About 90', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ポーランドに米兵追加配備すると発表　NATO会合の最中に,Trump announces deployment of additional US troops to Poland during NATO meeting,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エボラ出血熱のリスク、WHOが「非常に高い」に引き上げ　コンゴ民主共和国について,WHO raises Ebola risk to 'very high' for Democratic Republic of Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('Democratic Republic of Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン氏、ウクライナが学生寮を攻撃と非難　報復誓う,"Putin accuses Ukraine of attacking student dormitory, vows retaliation",-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ギャバード米国家情報長官、6月末に辞任へ　夫のがんが判明と,US Director of National Intelligence Gabbard to resign at the end of June after her husband was diagnosed with cancer,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('National Intelligence Gabbard', 'ORG'), ('the end of June', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米深夜番組「ザ・レイト・ショー」が終了　最後のゲストはマッカートニー氏,"US late-night show ""The Late Show"" ends with McCartney as the final guest",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('late-night', 'TIME'), ('The Late Show', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('McCartney', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 アメリカのカストロ元議長起訴、キューバで何が起こり得るのか,[Commentary] What could happen in Cuba after the indictment of former US President Castro?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアと中国、キューバ元指導者を起訴した米国を非難　米長官はキューバは「安全保障上の脅威」,"Russia, China criticize US for indicting former Cuban leader; US Secretary of State calls Cuba a 'security threat'",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuban', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、台湾への武器売却を一時停止　イランとの戦争が理由と,US suspends arms sales to Taiwan due to war with Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トイレ・更衣室は生物学的性別に基づく利用を、ジェンダー中立空間の必要性も明記　英平等委が新指針,"British Equality Commission's new guidelines specify that toilets and changing rooms should be used based on biological sex, and that gender-neutral spaces are required.",0.0,neutral,"[(""British Equality Commission's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「ノーの意味はノー」　グリーンランド住民、新しい米領事館前でトランプ氏に抗議,'No means no': Greenlanders protest against Trump in front of new US consulate,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Makubaliano ya kumaliza vita vya Iran 'yamejadiliwa kwa kiasi kikubwa' - Trump","Directly, The agreement to end the war with Iran has been 'substantially negotiated' - Trump",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"'Nilinusurika mashambulizi ya makombora Hormuz, lakini rafiki yangu hajapatikana'","'I survived the missile attacks in Hormuz, but my friend has not been found'",-1.0,negative,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, kutakuwa na uvamizi wa Marekani?: Hatima ya Cuba ni nini baada ya mashtaka dhidi ya Raúl Castro",Will there be a US invasion?: What is the fate of Cuba after the impeachment against Raúl Castro?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ebola: Uganda yathibitisha maambukizi mapya 3,Ebola: Uganda confirms 3 new infections,0.0,neutral,"[('Uganda', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Video za mitandao ya kijamii kuhusu usalama wa chakula India zilivyoibua hofu,Social media videos about food safety in India have sparked panic,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nadharia tatu kuhusu uwezekano wa kutokea mwisho wa dunia,Three theories about the possibility of the end of the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hadithi ya msichana aliyebakwa na sheikh aliyekuwa 'akimtibu',The story of a girl who was raped by a sheikh who was 'treating' her,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marekani yamuwekea vikwazo Mafwele kwa madai ya 'kuwatesa' wanaharakati wa haki za binadamu,The United States has imposed sanctions on Mafele for allegedly 'torturing' human rights activists,0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Mafele', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Masuala yanayokwaza mazungumzo kati ya Marekani na Iran,Issues hindering negotiations between the United States and Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Marekani imepata hasara kiasi gani katika vita vya Iran, kuanzia ndege za kivita hadi droni?","How much has the US lost in the Iran war, from warplanes to drones?",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('the Iran war', 'EVENT')]"
