Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El partido de Javier Milei obtiene un fuerte respaldo en las elecciones de medio término: ""Hoy comienza la construcción de la Argentina grande""","Javier Milei's party obtains strong support in the mid-term elections: ""Today the construction of the great Argentina begins""",0.6166666666666667,"[(""Javier Milei's"", 'ORG'), ('Today', 'DATE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Arrestan a dos sospechosos de cometer el robo de joyas del Louvre,Two suspects arrested for committing Louvre jewelry robbery,0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Los ""héroes de Járkov"" que rescataron a 48 niños de un jardín de infantes que fue atacado por drones rusos en Ucrania","The ""heroes of Kharkiv"" who rescued 48 children from a kindergarten that was attacked by Russian drones in Ukraine",0.0,"[('48', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Mi testimonio falso condenó a 3 adolescentes a cadena perpetua y la culpa me ha perseguido desde entonces""","""My false testimony sentenced 3 teenagers to life in prison and the guilt has followed me ever since""",-0.4000000000000001,"[('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Sammi y Safi, la historia de amor entre un musulmán y una judía que se gestó mientras rescataban personas de las manos del Talibán","Sammi and Safi, the love story between a Muslim and a Jewish woman that developed while they were rescuing people from the hands of the Taliban",0.19999999999999998,"[('Sammi', 'ORG'), ('Safi', 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"कैलाश विजयवर्गीय के महिलाओं पर 'बिगड़े बोल', बीजेपी मंत्री के वो 5 बयान जिन पर मचा हंगामा","Kailash Vijayvargiya's 'bad words' on women, those 5 statements of BJP minister which created uproar",-0.6999999999999998,"[(""Kailash Vijayvargiya's"", 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,दिल्ली दंगा मामला: सुप्रीम कोर्ट ने उमर ख़ालिद और शरजील इमाम की ज़मानत याचिकाओं पर क्या कहा?","Live, Delhi riots case: What did the Supreme Court say on the bail pleas of Umar Khalid and Sharjeel Imam?",0.13636363636363635,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Umar Khalid', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ट्रंप और जिनपिंग की मुलाक़ात: ट्रेड वॉर लड़ रहे दोनों नेताओं में पहले कौन झुकेगा,Meeting of Trump and Jinping: Who will bow down first between the two leaders fighting trade war?,0.04722222222222221,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,एमएस स्वामीनाथन: वह वैज्ञानिक जिन्होंने भारत को भूख से बचाया,MS Swaminathan: The scientist who saved India from hunger,0.0,"[('MS Swaminathan', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्या ट्रंप दोहरा सकते हैं सोवियत दौर की 'सस्ते तेल की साज़िश',Can Trump repeat the Soviet-era 'cheap oil conspiracy'?,0.4,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Soviet', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,यूजीसी-नेट क्लियर करने पर सिर्फ़ एकेडमिक्स में ही नौकरी... अगर आप भी ऐसा सोचते हैं तो जानिए और कहां-कहां हैं मौक़े,"After clearing UGC-NET, you can get job only in academics... If you also think like this then know where else the opportunities are.",0.0,"[('UGC-NET', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ग़ज़ा में युद्ध ने कैसे बदला मध्य पूर्व और दुनिया का शक्ति संतुलन,How the war in Gaza changed the balance of power in the Middle East and the world,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"यूपी में बीते कुछ दिनों में दलित उत्पीड़न के तीन मामले आए सामने, जानकार क्या कहते हैं?","In the last few days, three cases of Dalit oppression have come to light in UP, what do experts say?",0.06666666666666667,"[('the last few days', 'DATE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dalit', 'PERSON'), ('UP', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जब औरंगज़ेब ने की मुग़ल साम्राज्य के पतन की भविष्यवाणी - विवेचना,When Aurangzeb predicted the decline of the Mughal Empire - Discussion,0.0,"[('Aurangzeb', 'PERSON'), ('the Mughal Empire - Discussion', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Lula sobre tarifaço: 'Trump me garantiu que fará acordo, e vai ser mais rápido do que muita gente pensa'","Lula on tariffs: 'Trump assured me that he will make an agreement, and it will be faster than many people think'",0.5,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Milei conquista vitória 'surpreendente' em eleições legislativas na Argentina,Milei wins 'surprising' victory in legislative elections in Argentina,0.5,"[('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Reunião com Trump foi 'tremenda vitória' de Lula, mas não garante fim do tarifaço, diz cientista político","Meeting with Trump was a 'tremendous victory' for Lula, but does not guarantee an end to tariffs, says political scientist",0.16666666666666666,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula diz que reunião com Trump foi 'ótima' e abriu negociação 'imediata' de tarifaço e sanções,Lula says meeting with Trump was 'great' and opened 'immediate' negotiations on tariffs and sanctions,0.8,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Trump disse admirar trajetória política de Lula, relata ministro, Duration 0,47","Video, Trump said he admires Lula's political trajectory, reports minister, Duration 0.47",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('0.47', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump não mencionou Bolsonaro em reunião com Lula, diz governo brasileiro","Trump did not mention Bolsonaro in meeting with Lula, says Brazilian government",0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'A força de vontade não existe' e outras lições de irmãos médicos para uma vida com menos culpa,'Willpower does not exist' and other lessons from medical brothers for a life with less guilt,-0.09722222222222221,[]
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O brasileiro que flagra ladrões de celulares em Londres: 'Mais eficaz que a polícia',The Brazilian who catches cell phone thieves in London: 'More effective than the police',0.55,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Suspeitos por roubo de joias no Museu do Louvre são presos em Paris,Suspects in jewelry theft from Louvre Museum arrested in Paris,0.0,"[('Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Партия президента Аргентины Хавьера Милея добилась важной победы на промежуточных выборах,Argentine President Javier Miley's party scores important victory in midterm elections,0.4,"[('Argentine', 'NORP'), (""Javier Miley's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Минобороны России заявило об отражении атаки 34 беспилотников, летевших на Москву","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: The Russian Ministry of Defense announced that it had repelled an attack by 34 drones flying towards Moscow",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('The Russian Ministry of Defense', 'ORG'), ('34', 'CARDINAL'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Я поседела в 14 лет». Почему волосы теряют цвет, и всегда ли этот процесс необратим?","“I turned gray at 14.” Why does hair lose color, and is this process always irreversible?",0.0,"[('14', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Китай и США договорились о «рамках» торговой сделки в преддверии встречи Си и Трампа,China and US agree on trade deal 'framework' ahead of Xi-Trump meeting,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Xi-Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Глава Генштаба России сообщил об испытаниях «Буревестника». Утверждается, что ракета пролетела 14 тысяч километров",The head of the Russian General Staff reported on the tests of the Burevestnik. It is alleged that the rocket flew 14 thousand kilometers,-0.016666666666666663,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('General Staff', 'ORG'), ('14 thousand kilometers', 'QUANTITY')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Во Франции задержали подозреваемых в ограблении Лувра. Один из них пытался покинуть страну,"In France, suspects in the robbery of the Louvre were detained. One of them tried to leave the country",0.0,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON'), ('One', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Ученые разработали имплант, с помощью которого ослепшие пациенты снова могут читать",Scientists have developed an implant that can help blind patients read again,-0.2,[]
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп начал турне по Азии с подписания «договора о мире» между Таиландом и Камбоджей. Сами они его так не называют,Trump began his tour of Asia with the signing of a “peace treaty” between Thailand and Cambodia. They don't call it that themselves,0.0,"[('Asia', 'LOC'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Герои Харькова. Как удалось спасти 48 детей из детсада, по которому ударил российский дрон",Heroes of Kharkov. How 48 children were saved from a kindergarten hit by a Russian drone,0.0,"[('Kharkov', 'GPE'), ('48', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Видео: жители Киева рассказали о ночной атаке дронами, Продолжительность 1,03","Video,Video: Kyiv residents spoke about a night drone attack, Duration 1.03",0.0,"[('about a night', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、エジプトと赤十字のガザ入り認める　人質の遺体捜索に参加,"Israel allows Egypt and the Red Cross to enter Gaza, joins search for hostage bodies",0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('the Red Cross', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米中閣僚協議、貿易「枠組み」で合意　首脳会談に道筋,"US-China ministerial talks agree on trade framework, paving the way for summit",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,国外退去のはずが誤って釈放、移民の受刑者を2日後に再逮捕　イギリス,Immigrant prisoner who was supposed to be deported but mistakenly released was rearrested two days later in the UK,0.0,"[('two days later', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,仏ルーヴル美術館の宝石盗難事件、2人を逮捕,Two people arrested in connection with jewelry theft from France's Louvre Museum,0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Louvre Museum', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,タイとカンボジアが国境紛争めぐる共同声明に署名、トランプ氏は「和平協定」だと自画自賛, 所要時間 1,10","Video, Thailand and Cambodia sign joint statement on border dispute, Trump self-praises it as a ""peace deal"", Duration 1,10",0.0,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ホワイトハウスの東棟、完全に解体　人工衛星画像から, 所要時間 1,07","Video, East Wing of the White House completely demolished from satellite images, Required time 1,07",0.05,"[('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシア産石油・ガス、世界市場から排除すると　ウクライナ支援の「有志連合」が表明,"Russian oil and gas will be excluded from the world market, says coalition supporting Ukraine",0.125,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカは「戦争をねつ造している」、ヴェネズエラ大統領が非難　近海への軍艦派遣めぐり,"Venezuelan president criticizes US for ""fabricating war"" over sending warships to nearby waters",0.0,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,上司に「できません」と言いにくい時、どう言えばいい,"What to say when it's difficult to say ""I can't"" to your boss",-0.5,[]
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mstari mwembamba kati ya dini na siasa unavyotikisa uchaguzi Tanzania,The thin line between religion and politics is shaking the elections in Tanzania,-0.4,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,'Trump anataka kuipindua serikali’ – Afisa wa Venezuela","Directly, 'Trump wants to overthrow the government' - Venezuelan official",0.15000000000000002,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"""Atakayevunja sheria Oktoba 29 asilaumu"" – Polisi Tanzania","""Whoever breaks the law on October 29 should not be blamed"" - Tanzania Police",0.0,"[('October 29', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Tottenham inataka kumuuza Solanke,European football rumors Monday: Tottenham want to sell Solanke,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Tottenham', 'GPE'), ('Solanke', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tukio la Manchester lililoleta mapinduzi makubwa Afrika,The Manchester incident that brought about a great revolution in Africa,0.8,"[('Manchester', 'PERSON'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Hamas inaweza kujiimarisha upya baada ya masaibu ya Israel?",Can Hamas re-establish itself after Israel's debacle?,0.0,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tanzania yasikitishwa na madai ya Amnesty kuhusu ukandamizaji wa haki za binadamu,Tanzania is saddened by Amnesty's claims about the suppression of human rights,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Amnesty', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"""Alisalia na saa nne kabla ya kunyongwa"": Alitumikia miaka 40 gerezani kabla ya kubainika kuwa hana hatia","""He was four hours away from being hanged"": He served 40 years in prison before being found not guilty",0.25,"[('four hours', 'TIME'), ('40 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"'Baada ya kushambuliwa, sasa napata hofu nyakati za uchaguzi Tanzania'","'After being attacked, now I get scared during elections in Tanzania'",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Heche anashikiliwa mahabusu ya Polisi Dodoma, anyimwa dhamana-CHADEMA","Heche is being held in Dodoma Police custody, he is denied bail-CHADEMA",0.0,"[('Heche', 'ORG'), ('Dodoma', 'GPE')]"
