Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo los cerdos y los insectos están ayudando a encontrar a los desaparecidos en México,How pigs and insects are helping to find the missing in Mexico,-0.2,"[('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,शटडाउन के बाद अमेरिका में क्या हो रहा है?,What is happening in America after shutdown?,0.0,"[('America', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अमेरिकी शांति प्रस्ताव के बीच ग़ज़ा में इसराइल के हमले जारी","Israel's attacks continue in Gaza amid live, US peace proposal",0.13636363636363635,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क़तर से माफ़ी मांगने के लिए नेतन्याहू की इसराइल में तीखी आलोचना,Netanyahu's sharp criticism in Israel for apologizing to Qatar,-0.125,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सिलेंडर के दाम से लेकर बैंक लोन तक, जानिए एक अक्तूबर से कौन-कौन से नियम बदल गए?","From the price of the cylinder to the bank loan, know which rules have changed from October 1?",0.0,"[('October 1', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पोटैशियम की कमी से हो सकती है ये गंभीर बीमारी, खाने में इन चीज़ों को करें शामिल","Lack of potassium can cause this serious disease, involve these things in food",-0.3333333333333333,[]
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'आसिम मुनीर मुझसे बोले आपने बचाई लाखों ज़िंदगियां'- भारत पाकिस्तान संघर्ष पर ट्रंप ने और क्या कहा?,"'Asim Munir said to me, you saved millions of lives'- what else did Trump say on India Pakistan struggle?",0.0,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नेतन्याहू ने क़तर से मांगी माफ़ी, क्यों बदले उनके तेवर?","Netanyahu apologizes to Qatar, why change his attitude?",0.0,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os conselhos de especialista para salvar intoxicados por metanol: 'É um assassino silencioso',The expert advice to save methanol intoxicated: 'It is a silent killer',0.0,"[('methanol', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como o metanol aparece na bebida alcóolica — e por que isso gera lucro para alguns,How methanol appears in alcohol - and why it generates profit for some,0.0,[]
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por dentro de grupos de WhatsApp de  brasileiros que usam até drones contra blitzes de Trump: 'Pegaram uma mulher e uma menina',Inside Brazil's WhatsApp groups who use Drones against Trump's blitzes: 'They took a woman and a girl',0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('WhatsApp', 'ORG'), ('Drones', 'FAC'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Câmara vota isenção de Imposto de Renda até R$ 5 mil; entenda o que está em jogo,"House votes for income tax exemption up to R $ 5,000; Understand what is at stake",0.0,"[('House', 'ORG'), ('5,000', 'MONEY'), ('Understand', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como se saber se bebida está adulterada  — e outras dúvidas sobre intoxicação por metanol,How to know if drink is tampered with - and other doubts about methanol poisoning,-0.125,[]
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump cita 'inimigo interno' e diz que cidades americanas serão 'campo de treinamento' para militares,Trump cites 'internal enemy' and says that American cities will be 'training camp' for military personnel,-0.03333333333333333,"[('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Plano de paz de Trump para Gaza ignora os interesses dos palestinos', diz membro do Hamas à BBC","'Trump's Peace Plan for Gaza ignores the interests of the Palestinians,' says Hamas member to the BBC",0.0,"[(""Trump's Peace Plan"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que o governo dos EUA foi paralisado e quem serão os mais afetados,Why the US government has been paralyzed and who will be the most affected,0.5,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A briga na Justiça entre Ibama e influenciadora pela guarda da jaguatirica Pituca na Amazônia,The fight in justice between Ibama and influencer for the guard of Jaguatirica Pituca in the Amazon,0.0,"[('Ibama', 'GPE'), ('Jaguatirica Pituca', 'PERSON'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Дело об изнасиловании и убийстве школьницы всколыхнуло Кыргызстан. Президент страны предложил ввести за это смертную казнь,The case of rape and murder of a schoolgirl stirred Kyrgyzstan. The president of the country proposed to introduce the death penalty for this,0.0,"[('Kyrgyzstan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в ЕС нет единства по поводу «репарационного займа» Киеву из замороженных российских активов","Livelive, War in Ukraine: In the EU there is no unity about the “reparation loan” to Kyiv from frozen Russian assets",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Стена против дронов». Лидеры ЕС обсуждают на саммите в Дании, как защититься от России","""Wall against drones."" EU leaders are discussing at a summit in Denmark how to protect themselves from Russia",0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Denmark', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Пока мир ждет ответа ХАМАС на новый план Трампа по Газе, ЦАХАЛ почти окружил столицу сектора","While the world awaits Hamas’s answer to the new plan of Trump on Gaza, the IFAL almost surrounded the capital of the sector",0.13636363636363635,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Правительство США частично прекращает работу. Это четвертый шатдаун при Дональде Трампе,The US government partially stops working. This is the fourth Shatdown under Donald Trump,-0.05,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL'), ('Shatdown', 'GPE'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Ученые впервые создали эмбрион, использовав ДНК из клеток кожи человека",Scientists first created an embryo using DNA from human skin cells,0.125,[]
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Саудовская Аравия и зять Трампа купили гиганта игровой индустрии Electronic Arts за $55 млрд. Зачем Эр-Рияд захватывает рынок игр?,Saudi Arabia and Trump's son-in-law bought a giant of the Electronic Arts gaming industry for $ 55 billion. Why is Er-Riyad capturing the game market?,-0.2,"[('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the Electronic Arts', 'ORG'), ('$ 55 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Компьютерный ужас Голливуда. Американских кинозвезд напугала Тилли Норвуд — актриса, созданная искусственным интеллектом","Hollywood computer horror. Tilly Norwood, an actress created by artificial intelligence, scared American movie stars",-0.3,"[('Hollywood', 'GPE'), ('Tilly Norwood', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Мощное землетрясение на Филиппинах: погибли по меньшей мере 69 человек, спасатели разбирают завалы","A powerful earthquake in the Philippines: at least 69 people died, rescuers disassemble the rubble",0.0,"[('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('at least 69', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«У меня не было миллионов в 14 лет». Джоан Роулинг не приняла оливковую ветвь от Эммы Уотсон, протянутую после ссоры вокруг трансфобии","""I did not have millions at 14 years old."" Joan Rowling did not accept the olive branch from Emma Watson stretched after a quarrel around Transfobia",0.025,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('14 years old', 'DATE'), ('Joan Rowling', 'PERSON'), ('Emma Watson', 'PERSON'), ('Transfobia', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏のガザ和平案は「パレスチナ人の利益を無視」　ハマス幹部、BBCに語る,"Trump's Gaza peace plan ""ignors Palestinian interests"" Hamas executive tells BBC",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ政府が閉鎖、7年ぶり　連邦議会で予算案可決されず,"US government shuts down for the first time in 7 years, budget proposal not passed by Congress",0.04722222222222222,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('7 years', 'DATE'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,フィリピン中部セブ島沖でM6.9の地震、少なくとも69人死亡,"At least 69 people die in M6.9 earthquake off Cebu, central Philippines",-0.15,"[('At least 69', 'CARDINAL'), ('M6.9', 'DATE'), ('Cebu', 'GPE'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,トランプ氏の和平計画、ガザ住民とイスラエル人の反応は, 所要時間 1,21","Video, Trump's peace plan, reactions between Gaza and Israelis, duration 1,21",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israelis', 'NORP'), ('1,21', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,暗号資産「世界最大」の押収、中国籍の女性が資金洗浄などで有罪　イギリス,"Chinese woman convicted of money laundering and other crypto assets, UK",-0.0625,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、アメリカの都市を「軍の訓練場」にすべきと　将官らに演説,"Trump gives generals the idea that American cities should be turned into ""military training grounds""",-0.05,"[('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 トランプ氏のガザ和平案、「勢い」が強みだが「細部の欠如」が弱み　国際編集長,"[Explanation] Trump's Gaza peace proposal is his strength, but his weakness is his lack of detail; International Editor-in-Chief",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('International', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノルド・ストリーム爆破、ウクライナ人ダイバーを関与の疑いで拘束　ポーランド警察,Nord Stream Blasts Detains Ukrainian Diver on suspicion of involvement Polish police,0.0,"[('Nord Stream Blasts Detains Ukrainian Diver', 'ORG'), ('Polish', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,コンゴ民主共和国の前大統領、欠席裁判で死刑判決　戦争犯罪など,Former president of the Democratic Republic of Congo sentences death penalty in absent trial; war crimes etc.,0.0,"[('the Democratic Republic of Congo', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Serikali ya Marekani yafunga shughuli zake rasmi","Directly, the US government closes its official activities",0.1,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Zaidi ya wapiganaji 7,000 wameajiriwa na M23- Umoja wa Mataifa","More than 7,000 fighters employed by M23- UN",0.5,"[('More than 7,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, kufungwa kwa serikali ya Marekani kutakuwa na athari gani?",What effect will the closure of the US government have?,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu mpango wa amani wa Trump  Gaza wenye vipengele 20 kwa kina,Be aware of Trump Gaza Peace Plan with 20 components in depth,0.25,"[('Trump Gaza Peace Plan', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais wa zamani wa Congo ahukumiwa kifo kwa uhalifu wa kivita,Former Congo president is sentenced to death for war crimes,0.0,"[('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Mtandao ndio ulikuwa tegemeo, jinsi wanawake wa Afghanistan walivyopoteza 'tumaini lao pekee'","The Internet was the most dependent, how Afghan women lost their 'hope only'",0.25,"[('Afghan', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mbinu mpya inayowezesha utengenezaji wa viinitete kutokana na ngozi ya binadamu,A new technique that enables the manufacture of vintage from human skin,0.06818181818181818,[]
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Zijue pandashuka za ushirikiano wa Trump na Netanyahu,Know the Trump and Netanyahu Partnerships.,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Netanyahu Partnerships', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumatano: Tottenham Hotspur sasa yamtaka beki wa Crystal Palace Marc Guehi,European football rumors on Wednesday: Tottenham Hotspur now wants Crystal Palace defender Marc Guehi,0.1,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Tottenham Hotspur', 'PERSON'), ('Crystal Palace', 'LOC'), ('Marc Guehi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mshukiwa wa ugaidi aliyekwepa mitego ya FBI kwa miaka 21 alivyokamatwa,A terrorist suspect who has avoided FBI traps for 21 years arrested,0.0,"[('FBI', 'ORG'), ('21 years', 'DATE')]"
