Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué se sabe de los dos fuertes terremotos que sacudieron la costa central de Venezuela causando muertes y daños en Caracas y sus alrededores,What is known about the two strong earthquakes that shook the central coast of Venezuela causing deaths and damage in Caracas and its surroundings,-1.0,negative,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Caracas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Pidan ayuda. Estamos aquí"": los primeros testimonios tras el terremoto de magnitud 7,2 y su potente réplica en Venezuela","""Ask for help. We are here"": the first testimonies after the 7.2 magnitude earthquake and its powerful aftershock in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('7.2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las imágenes de los graves daños causados en Caracas por los potentes terremotos que han golpeado Venezuela,The images of the serious damage caused in Caracas by the powerful earthquakes that have hit Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Caracas', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,EN VIDEO | El momento en el que dos terremotos golpean Venezuela provocando graves daños,ON VIDEO | The moment when two earthquakes hit Venezuela causing serious damage,0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Hermana, pensé que íbamos a morir"": las horas de caos y angustia que viví hasta localizar a mi familia tras los terremotos en Venezuela","""Sister, I thought we were going to die"": the hours of chaos and anguish that I experienced until I located my family after the earthquakes in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('the hours', 'TIME'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Iván Cepeda reconoce la derrota en las elecciones de Colombia y De la Espriella será el nuevo presidente,Iván Cepeda recognizes defeat in the Colombian elections and De la Espriella will be the new president,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('De la Espriella', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"5 claves que explican el ""boom"" económico de Paraguay (pese a que no toda la población percibe los beneficios)","5 keys that explain Paraguay's economic ""boom"" (despite the fact that not the entire population perceives the benefits)",0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Francia sufre cortes de luz en el día más caluroso desde que existen registros,France suffers power outages on the hottest day since records exist,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('the hottest day', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué un hincha de la República Democrática del Congo se para como una estatua viviente en todos los partidos de su selección,Why a fan from the Democratic Republic of the Congo stands like a living statue at all his team's matches,0.0,neutral,"[('the Democratic Republic of the Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Ranking BBC: los mejores partidos, momentos, goles y jugadores del Mundial 2026 hasta ahora","BBC Ranking: the best games, moments, goals and players of the 2026 World Cup so far",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC Ranking', 'ORG'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वेनेज़ुएला में एक के बाद एक आए भीषण भूकंप से 32 लोगों की मौत, 700 घायल","32 people died, 700 injured due to massive earthquakes one after the other in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('700', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,राहुल गांधी ने शिवराज सिंह चौहान के बेटे से जुड़े मानहानि मामले में जताया खेद","Live, Rahul Gandhi expressed regret in the defamation case related to Shivraj Singh Chouhan's son.",0.0,neutral,"[('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON'), (""Shivraj Singh Chouhan's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"तेज प्रताप ने भंग की पार्टी की संगठन इकाई, पीए ग़ायब, पत्नी ने जताई ये आशंका","Tej Pratap dissolved party's organization unit, PA missing, wife expressed this fear",0.0,neutral,"[('Tej Pratap', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,दिल्ली और दूसरे भारतीय शहरों पर भूकंप का कितना ख़तरा,What is the danger of earthquake on Delhi and other Indian cities?,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लंबे समय तक बैठे रहते हैं तो हो जाएं सावधान, इतने मिनट का वॉक ब्रेक लेना ज़रूरी","Be careful if you sit for a long time, it is important to take a walk break of so many minutes",0.0,neutral,"[('so many minutes', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारत का पासपोर्ट अगर नागरिकता का प्रमाण नहीं है तो फिर कौन सा दस्तावेज़ काम आएगा?,If Indian passport is not proof of citizenship then which document will be useful?,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"मोदी सरकार लोकसभा और राज्यसभा में इस तरह पहुँचने जा रही है दो तिहाई समर्थन के क़रीब, जानिए क्या होगा असर","This is how Modi government is going to reach close to two-thirds support in Lok Sabha and Rajya Sabha, know what will be the effect.",0.0,neutral,"[('two-thirds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lok Sabha', 'PERSON'), ('Rajya Sabha', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वैभव सूर्यवंशी सिर्फ क्रिकेट नहीं बल्कि बिहार को एक नई पहचान कैसे दे रहे हैं,How Vaibhav Suryavanshi is giving not just cricket but a new identity to Bihar,0.0,neutral,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सरियों से पिटाई, चोकर की रोटी और पिटबुल का पहरा: 12 बंधुआ मज़दूरों की आपबीती","Beating with rods, bran bread and guarding by pit bulls: stories of 12 bonded laborers",0.0,neutral,"[('12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लखनऊ आग हादसा: 'पापा, आग लग गई है, मुझे बचा लो'","Lucknow fire accident: 'Papa, there is a fire, save me'",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Terremotos consecutivos na Venezuela provocam mais de 30 mortes, 700 feridos e são sentidos no Brasil; o que se sabe","Consecutive earthquakes in Venezuela cause more than 30 deaths, 700 injuries and are felt in Brazil; what is known",-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('more than 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('700', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"As horas de angústia vividas por jornalista da BBC até achar a família após terremotos na Venezuela: 'Irmã, pensei que fôssemos morrer'","The hours of anguish experienced by a BBC journalist until he found his family after earthquakes in Venezuela: 'Sister, I thought we were going to die'",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O pedido de desculpas de Flávio Bolsonaro após vídeo de Michelle,Flávio Bolsonaro's apology after Michelle's video,0.0,neutral,"[(""Flávio Bolsonaro's"", 'PERSON'), ('Michelle', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Tumor com menos de 1 centímetro fez adolescente ganhar 40 quilos em 6 meses,Tumor measuring less than 1 centimeter caused teenager to gain 40 kilos in 6 months,0.0,neutral,"[('less than 1 centimeter', 'QUANTITY'), ('40 kilos', 'QUANTITY'), ('6 months', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Brasil 3 x 0 Escócia: com gols de Vini Jr e Matheus Cunha, seleção se classifica em primeiro lugar do grupo","Brazil 3 x 0 Scotland: with goals from Vini Jr and Matheus Cunha, the team ranks first in the group",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('0', 'CARDINAL'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Vini Jr', 'PERSON'), ('Matheus Cunha', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Michelle abre guerra nas redes contra Flávio Bolsonaro e tenta influenciar decisão do PL no Ceará: 'Me tratam como idiota',Michelle opens a war online against Flávio Bolsonaro and tries to influence the PL decision in Ceará: 'They treat me like an idiot',-1.0,negative,"[('Michelle', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('PL', 'ORG'), ('Ceará', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem eram os vikings e por que a Noruega celebra a 'remada viking' na Copa do Mundo,Who were the Vikings and why Norway celebrates the 'Viking row' at the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Vikings', 'ORG'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), (""the 'Viking row'"", 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Mãe denuncia ameaça a filho de 3 anos em escola militar no RS: 'Chora com vontade, senão vou te dar um tiro'","Mother reports threat to 3-year-old son at military school in RS: 'Cry hard, otherwise I'll shoot you'",0.0,neutral,"[('3-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que tantas pessoas estão morrendo afogadas em onda de calor na Europa?,Why are so many people drowning in Europe's heat wave?,0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quando é o próximo jogo do Brasil na Copa e quem será o adversário? Os cenários de cada resultado,When is Brazil's next World Cup game and who will be the opponent? The scenarios for each outcome,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Венесуэле произошло сильное землетрясение, в Каракасе разрушены дома","A strong earthquake occurred in Venezuela, houses were destroyed in Caracas",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Caracas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Трамп заявил, что Зеленский «держится» и дела у него идут «довольно хорошо»","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Trump says Zelensky is 'holding together' and doing 'pretty well'",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,От цен на газ до борьбы со «схемами» и коррупцией. Что обещает Украина в обмен на кредиты ЕС и МВФ?,From gas prices to the fight against “schemes” and corruption. What does Ukraine promise in exchange for loans from the EU and IMF?,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('IMF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Запрет на несогласие». Зампреда «Яблока» Максима Круглова приговорили к семи годам за два поста,"""Ban on dissent."" Deputy Chairman of Yabloko Maxim Kruglov was sentenced to seven years for two posts",0.0,neutral,"[('Yabloko Maxim Kruglov', 'ORG'), ('seven years', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Европа в красной зоне температурной угрозы: закрываются школы, сокращено движение транспорта, десятки жертв","Europe is in the red zone of temperature threat: schools are closed, traffic is reduced, dozens of victims",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Как-то так вышло, что штурмовики нужнее». Как российские студенты идут в беспилотные войска и погибают",“Somehow it turned out that stormtroopers were more needed.” How Russian students join unmanned troops and die,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Прогресса нет». Лавров усомнился в позиции Трампа по Украине и раскритиковал состояние отношений России с США,"""There is no progress."" Lavrov doubted Trump’s position on Ukraine and criticized the state of Russia’s relations with the United States",1.0,positive,"[('Lavrov', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Заклятые соседи, или Как разобраться в украинской дипломатии. Рассылка «Контекст»","Sworn neighbors, or How to understand Ukrainian diplomacy. Newsletter ""Context""",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,ВСУ ударили по энергетике Крыма: Севастополь и другие города остались без света. Что известно,The Ukrainian Armed Forces hit the Crimean energy sector: Sevastopol and other cities were left without electricity. What is known,0.0,neutral,"[('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Crimean', 'NORP'), ('Sevastopol', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Хотите почувствовать себя лучше на работе? Поможет пятиминутная прогулка каждый час (и это не шутка),Want to feel better at work? A five-minute walk every hour will help (and this is not a joke),0.0,neutral,"[('five-minute', 'TIME'), ('every hour', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヨーロッパ西部で熱波　フランス、イギリス、スペインで記録的高温,"Heatwave hits western Europe; record high temperatures in France, UK and Spain",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴェネズエラでM7超の大規模地震、建物倒壊し救助活動　被害甚大との見方も,Large-scale earthquake exceeding M7 in Venezuela causes buildings to collapse and rescue operations to be carried out; damage expected to be severe,0.0,neutral,"[('M7', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 「クールダウン拠点」、映画無料券、窓に「白い粉」……欧州各国の熱波対策,"[Explanation] ""Cool-down bases"", free movie tickets, ""white powder"" on windows... Heat wave measures in European countries",1.0,positive,"[('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,南米ヴェネズエラで強い地震が2度発生　マグニチュード7超, 所要時間 1,04","Video, Two strong earthquakes occur in Venezuela, South America, magnitude over 7, time required 1,04",0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('South America', 'LOC'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('1,04', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 なぜ北米では「フットボール」ではなく「サッカー」と呼ぶのか　元はイギリス語との説も,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Why is it called ""soccer"" instead of ""football"" in North America? There is a theory that it is originally a British word.",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシア占領下のクリミア最大都市で停電、ウクライナのドローン攻撃後,Power outage in Russian-occupied Crimea's largest city after Ukrainian drone attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Crimea', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,IAEA、イラン核施設を査察すると　合意に基づき実施予定と事務局長,"IAEA plans to inspect Iranian nuclear facilities based on agreement, director general says",0.0,neutral,"[('IAEA', 'ORG'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ政権、約14兆円の追加予算を議会に要請　大半は対イラン戦争関連費,"Trump administration requests Congress for approximately 14 trillion yen in additional budget, mostly for war-related costs against Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('approximately 14 trillion yen', 'MONEY'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,マスク氏が「トリリオネア」でなくなる　ハイテク株急落でスペースXに打撃,"Musk ceases to be a ""trillionaire"" as tech stocks plummet, hitting SpaceX",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_25,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 ロナウド、6大会連続ゴールの新記録　批判はね返す,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Ronaldo sets new record for goals in 6 consecutive tournaments, bounces back from criticism",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('6', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Polisi wafunga barabara kuu jijini Nairobi huku Kenya ikijiandaa na maandamano ya Gen Z","Directly, the Police closed the highway in Nairobi as Kenya prepared for the Gen Z protest",0.0,neutral,"[('Nairobi', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetemeko la ardhi ya Venezuela: Watu 32 wafariki dunia, mamia wajeruhiwa","Venezuela earthquake: 32 people died, hundreds were injured",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Kwa nini kuna wachezaji wengi wanaochezea mataifa ambayo hawakuzaliwa?,World Cup 2026: Why are there so many players playing for nations they weren't born in?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Al-Aqsa: Waislamu wahofia mipango ya Waisrael juu ya eneo lao takatifu zaidi huko Jerusalem,Al-Aqsa: Muslims fear Israeli plans for their holiest site in Jerusalem,0.0,neutral,"[('Al-Aqsa', 'ORG'), ('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Alhamisi:  Man United yamwania Malo Gusto wa Chelsea,European soccer rumors Thursday: Man United are in the running for Chelsea's Malo Gusto,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Man United', 'PERSON'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Malo Gusto', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Iran haiko tayari kuiacha Hezbollah nje ya makubaliano yake na Marekani, Kwa nini?","Iran is not ready to leave Hezbollah out of its agreement with the United States, Why?",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'NORP'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, ndege ya Trump ya hali ya juu ina uwezo gani?",What is Trump's super jet capable of?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Maoni: Je, Muungano wa Zanzibar na Tanganyika una matatizo?",Opinion: Does the Union of Zanzibar and Tanganyika have problems?,0.0,neutral,"[('the Union of Zanzibar', 'ORG'), ('Tanganyika', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Waridi wa BBC: Niliacha shule kidato cha pili, niwe mfanyabiashara mkubwa","BBC Rose: I left school in second form, to become a big businessman",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Nimerudi' - Ronaldo awajibu wakosoaji baada ya kuvunja rekodi,'I'm back' - Ronaldo responds to critics after breaking records,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Oil prices back to pre-war levels on rising Middle East supply,Oil prices back to pre-war levels on rising Middle East supply,-1.0,negative,"[('Middle East', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,In pictures: Aftermath of twin earthquakes in Venezuela,In pictures: Aftermath of twin earthquakes in Venezuela,1.0,positive,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World reacts as devastating Venezuela earthquakes kill at least 32,World reacts as devastating Venezuela earthquakes kill at least 32,-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('at least 32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup knockouts: Who has made it to the round of 32 stage?,World Cup knockouts: Who has made it to the round of 32 stage?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran warns against Hormuz crossings without authorisation,Iran warns against Hormuz crossings without authorisation,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Magnitude 6.9 earthquake strikes northern Japan,Magnitude 6.9 earthquake strikes northern Japan,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Mexico fans celebrate three World Cup group-stage wins in a row,Mexico fans celebrate three World Cup group-stage wins in a row,1.0,positive,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 118: IRGC rejects new Hormuz route; Rubio to meet GCC leaders,Iran war day 118: IRGC rejects new Hormuz route; Rubio to meet GCC leaders,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('118', 'CARDINAL'), ('IRGC', 'ORG'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('GCC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Incredibly proud moment’: South Africa fans hail historic World Cup run,‘Incredibly proud moment’: South Africa fans hail historic World Cup run,0.0,neutral,"[('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_25,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"ICC judges sue Trump over sanctions, call measures unlawful","ICC judges sue Trump over sanctions, call measures unlawful",0.0,neutral,"[('ICC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"If a passport is not proof of citizenship, then what is? | Explained","If a passport is not proof of citizenship, then what is? | Explained",0.0,neutral,"[('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,UDF government’s stance on PM SHRI unconstitutional,UDF government’s stance on PM SHRI unconstitutional,0.0,neutral,"[('UDF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"New gates of Tungabhadra dam inaugurated, three States vow to protect interests of farmers","New gates of Tungabhadra dam inaugurated, three States vow to protect interests of farmers",0.0,neutral,"[('Tungabhadra dam', 'LOC'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why has India-U.S. trade deal been delayed?,Why has India-U.S. trade deal been delayed?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Former IAS officer Sujata Rout Karthikeyan joins Biju Janata Dal,Former IAS officer Sujata Rout Karthikeyan joins Biju Janata Dal,0.0,neutral,"[('IAS', 'ORG'), ('Sujata Rout Karthikeyan', 'ORG'), ('Biju Janata Dal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Rubio says Hormuz tolls would 'spread like contagion' to other waterways | LIVE,Rubio says Hormuz tolls would 'spread like contagion' to other waterways | LIVE,0.0,neutral,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,NCERT introduces section on Emergency in Class IX textbook for first time,NCERT introduces section on Emergency in Class IX textbook for first time,0.0,neutral,"[('NCERT', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Chennai’s Dr. Priya Selvaraj on surviving a crevasse fall and summiting Mount Everest,Chennai’s Dr. Priya Selvaraj on surviving a crevasse fall and summiting Mount Everest,0.0,neutral,"[('Chennai', 'ORG'), ('Priya Selvaraj', 'PERSON'), ('Mount Everest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Viksit and Surakshit: On the Lucknow fire,Viksit and Surakshit: On the Lucknow fire,0.0,neutral,"[('Surakshit', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Razor’s edge: On the progress of the southwest monsoon,Razor’s edge: On the progress of the southwest monsoon,1.0,positive,"[('Razor', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'I thought I was going to die' - Venezuelans describe earthquake panic,'I thought I was going to die' - Venezuelans describe earthquake panic,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"France, UK and Spain see record temperatures as heatwave grips western Europe","France, UK and Spain see record temperatures as heatwave grips western Europe",0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Trump asks Congress for billions for Iran war, after tension with Republicans","Trump asks Congress for billions for Iran war, after tension with Republicans",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('billions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Republicans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Oil price falls back to pre-Iran war levels,Oil price falls back to pre-Iran war levels,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Philippines bans video game played by alleged high school shooter,Philippines bans video game played by alleged high school shooter,0.0,neutral,"[('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Police seal off key roads in Nairobi as Kenya braces for Gen Z protests,Police seal off key roads in Nairobi as Kenya braces for Gen Z protests,0.0,neutral,"[('Nairobi', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Anthropic accuses Chinese rival Alibaba of illicitly extracting AI capabilities,Anthropic accuses Chinese rival Alibaba of illicitly extracting AI capabilities,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Independent MPs launch new Australian centrist party,Independent MPs launch new Australian centrist party,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Clean sweep for Mamdani-backed candidates in New York's Democratic primary,Clean sweep for Mamdani-backed candidates in New York's Democratic primary,0.0,neutral,"[('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), (""New York's"", 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_25,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Air conditioning creates political divide after France records hottest day,Air conditioning creates political divide after France records hottest day,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('hottest day', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Venezuela Live Updates: Rescuers Mount Frantic Search for Survivors of Twin Earthquakes,Venezuela Live Updates: Rescuers Mount Frantic Search for Survivors of Twin Earthquakes,1.0,positive,"[('Venezuela Live', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Live Updates: Spain Warns of High Death Toll in Heat Wave,Live Updates: Spain Warns of High Death Toll in Heat Wave,-1.0,negative,"[('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"To Escape the Heat, Parisians Jump into an Old Industrial Canal","To Escape the Heat, Parisians Jump into an Old Industrial Canal",0.0,neutral,"[('Parisians Jump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A Puppy-Abuse Case in China, Caught on Video, Prompts Rare Public Protest","A Puppy-Abuse Case in China, Caught on Video, Prompts Rare Public Protest",0.0,neutral,"[('Puppy-Abuse Case', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Caught on Video', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"North Korea Deploys Its First Destroyer, Vowing to Project Nuclear Power by Sea","North Korea Deploys Its First Destroyer, Vowing to Project Nuclear Power by Sea",1.0,positive,"[('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Vowing', 'ORG'), ('Project Nuclear Power', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iran’s Loyalists Promote a Wider Nationalism, Unveiled Women Included","Iran’s Loyalists Promote a Wider Nationalism, Unveiled Women Included",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Myanmar’s Civil War Has Become an Apocalypse,Myanmar’s Civil War Has Become an Apocalypse,-1.0,negative,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,See Record-Breaking Extreme Heat Wave Across Europe in Photos,See Record-Breaking Extreme Heat Wave Across Europe in Photos,0.0,neutral,"[('Photos', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Rubio Seeks to Reassure Gulf Arab Partners on Iran Deal,Rubio Seeks to Reassure Gulf Arab Partners on Iran Deal,0.0,neutral,"[('Rubio Seeks', 'PERSON'), ('Reassure Gulf Arab Partners', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_25,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,France Identifies Its First Case of Ebola,France Identifies Its First Case of Ebola,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
