Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Palaos, el pequeño país cercano a Taiwán que sufre las consecuencias del enfrentamiento diplomático entre China y Estados Unidos","Palau, the small country near Taiwan that suffers the consequences of the diplomatic confrontation between China and the United States",-0.25,"[('Palau', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Hay cosas que no son ni de derecha ni de izquierda, entre esas, compartir la cama"": escucha ""Improbable"", el nuevo podcast de BBC Mundo sobre un amor que triunfó contra todo pronóstico","""There are things that are neither right nor left, among them, sharing a bed"": listen to ""Improbable"", the new BBC Mundo podcast about a love that triumphed against all odds",0.2305194805194805,"[('BBC Mundo', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El caso de la doctora condenada en Venezuela a 30 años de cárcel por criticar a Maduro en un audio de WhatsApp,The case of the doctor sentenced in Venezuela to 30 years in prison for criticizing Maduro in a WhatsApp audio,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('WhatsApp', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué fue tan devastador y otras 5 preguntas sobre  el incendio en las torres de viviendas de Hong Kong que dejó al menos 128 muertos,Why it was so devastating and 5 other questions about the fire in the Hong Kong tower blocks that left at least 128 dead,-0.325,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('at least 128', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Una agente de la Guardia Nacional muere tras un tiroteo cerca de la Casa Blanca en Washington D.C.,A National Guard officer dies after a shooting near the White House in Washington D.C.,0.05,"[('National Guard', 'ORG'), ('the White House', 'FAC'), ('Washington D.C.', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"चीन और जापान के बीच बढ़ा तनाव, प्रधानमंत्री से टिप्पणी वापस लेने की मांग पर अड़ा चीन","Tension increases between China and Japan, China adamant on demanding withdrawal of remarks from Prime Minister",0.1,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,रूस के राष्ट्रपति पुतिन के भारत दौरे की तारीख़ की घोषणा हुई","Live, date of Russian President Putin's visit to India announced",0.06818181818181818,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"उपेंद्र कुशवाहा की पार्टी में इस्तीफ़ों की झड़ी, बेटे को मंत्री बनाने से बढ़ा असंतोष","A wave of resignations in Upendra Kushwaha's party, dissatisfaction increased over making his son a minister.",0.0,"[(""Upendra Kushwaha's"", 'ORG')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान: बारिश में आइसक्रीम की तलाश में निकली बच्ची 17 साल बाद यूं लौटी घर,Pakistan: The girl who went in search of ice cream in the rain returned home like this after 17 years,0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('17 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,इमरान ख़ान के बेटे कासिम ख़ान ने कई तरह की अफ़वाहों के बीच अपने पिता को लेकर क्या कहा,What did Imran Khan's son Qasim Khan say about his father amid various rumors?,0.0,"[(""Imran Khan's"", 'PERSON'), ('Qasim Khan', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"कर्नाटक में सिद्धारमैया और शिवकुमार के बीच शब्दों में वार पलटवार, गहराया संकट","In Karnataka, there was a war of words between Siddaramaiah and Shivakumar, the crisis deepened.",0.0,"[('Karnataka', 'GPE'), ('Siddaramaiah', 'PERSON'), ('Shivakumar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पोप ने अपनी पहली विदेश यात्रा के लिए तुर्की के इस छोटे से शहर को क्यों चुना?,Why did the Pope choose this small town in Türkiye for his first trip abroad?,0.0,"[('Türkiye', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,धर्मेंद्र की पाकिस्तान में रहने वाली फ़ैन, जो कहती हैं कि वो उन्हें बेटी की तरह प्यार देते थे, अवधि 7,32","Video, Dharmendra's fan living in Pakistan, who says he loved her like a daughter, duration 7,32",0.7,"[('Dharmendra', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"रेयर अर्थ मैग्नेट होते क्या हैं, जिनके लिए मोदी सरकार ने 7 हज़ार करोड़ का प्लान बनाया","What are rare earth magnets, for which Modi government made a plan of Rs 7 thousand crores",0.3,"[('7 thousand', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Rita Lobo: 'Se pensar só em proteína e carboidrato, o pão vira inimigo'","Rita Lobo: 'If you only think about protein and carbohydrates, bread becomes the enemy'",0.0,[]
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Congresso impõe derrota a Lula e 'ressuscita' pontos polêmicos da lei do licenciamento ambiental dias após COP,Congress defeats Lula and 'resurrects' controversial points in the environmental licensing law days after COP,0.55,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('COP', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Fraudes, sonegação e dívida de R$ 26 bi: entenda o caso da Refit em 3 pontos","Fraud, tax evasion and debt of R$26 billion: understand the case of Refit in 3 points",0.0,"[('R$26 billion', 'MONEY'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Tarcísio não representa o bolsonarismo, mas sistema quer candidato como ele, diz influenciador da direita Paulo Figueiredo","Tarcísio does not represent Bolsonarism, but the system wants a candidate like him, says right-wing influencer Paulo Figueiredo",0.2,"[('Tarcísio', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonarism', 'PERSON'), ('Paulo Figueiredo', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Para o engenheiro de IA que tem o inglês em dia, dá para ganhar em dólar remotamente no Brasil, e em ótimas empresas'","'For the AI ​​engineer who has up-to-date English, you can earn dollars remotely in Brazil, and in great companies'",0.23333333333333336,"[('English', 'LANGUAGE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A brasileira parente de porta-voz da Casa Branca presa pelo serviço de imigração de Trump,Brazilian relative of White House spokesperson arrested by Trump's immigration service,0.0,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Icônicos andaimes de bambu podem ter ajudado a espalhar fogo em incêndio devastador em Hong Kong,Iconic bamboo scaffolding may have helped spread fire in devastating Hong Kong fire,-0.25,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A tragédia do incêndio em Hong Kong que deixou pelo menos 94 mortos: 'Dava para ver as chamas por dentro',The tragedy of the fire in Hong Kong that left at least 94 people dead: 'You could see the flames inside',-0.16666666666666666,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('at least 94', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como aprender qualquer coisa do zero,How to learn anything from scratch,0.0,[]
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,У главы офиса Зеленского проходит обыск,The head of Zelensky's office is being searched,0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: обыск у Ермака и визит Орбана к Путину","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: search of Ermak and Orban’s visit to Putin",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Ermak', 'GPE'), ('Orban', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Косплей, карты таро, «Страдающее средневековье». Где российская полиция находит сатанизм?","Cosplay, tarot cards, “The Suffering Middle Ages.” Where do Russian police find Satanism?",0.0,"[('The Suffering Middle Ages', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Скончалась военнослужащая Национальной гвардии США, пострадавшая при стрельбе в Вашингтоне",US National Guard soldier injured in Washington DC shooting dies,0.0,"[('US National Guard', 'ORG'), ('Washington DC', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Администрация Трампа проверит грин-карты выходцев из 19 стран, в том числе из Афганистана","The Trump administration will review the green cards of people from 19 countries, including Afghanistan",-0.2,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Весь иконостас путинских наград». Российский суд объявил ФБК террористами — что это значит?,“The entire iconostasis of Putin’s awards.” A Russian court declared FBK terrorists - what does this mean?,-0.10416666666666667,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('FBK', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Не проект договора, а «набор вопросов» для обсуждения. Что Путин сказал о плане США по окончанию войны в Украине","Not a draft treaty, but a “set of issues” for discussion. What Putin said about the US plan to end the war in Ukraine",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Число жертв пожара в жилом комплексе в Гонконге продолжает расти. По делу о пожаре задержаны три человека,The number of victims of a fire in a residential complex in Hong Kong continues to rise. Three people were detained in connection with the fire,-0.3,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Военные, захватившие власть в Гвинее-Бисау, назначили временного президента страны",The military that seized power in Guinea-Bissau appointed an interim president of the country,-0.1,"[('Guinea', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Восьмерых обвиняемых по делу о взрыве на Крымском мосту приговорили к пожизненному сроку,Eight defendants in the Crimean Bridge bombing case were sentenced to life imprisonment,0.0,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Crimean Bridge', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン氏、ウクライナの領土を改めて要求　米との協議を前に,Putin renews demands for Ukrainian territory ahead of talks with US,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港の高層住宅群火災、住民から「防げたはずだ」と怒りの声　死者少なくとも94人に,"At least 94 people killed in Hong Kong high-rise residential fire, residents say it could have been prevented",-0.25,"[('At least 94', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,行方不明者の家族ら、苦しみのなか待ち続ける　香港高層住宅群火災,Families of missing people continue to wait in agony as fire breaks out in Hong Kong high-rise housing complex,-0.25,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米首都銃撃で負傷した州兵1人が死亡、容疑者は過去にアフガニスタンで米CIAと協力,One National Guard soldier injured in US capital shooting dies; suspect previously worked with US CIA in Afghanistan,-0.16666666666666666,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('National Guard', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ルーヴル美術館、欧州圏以外からの来場者の入場料を45％値上げへ　改修資金に,Louvre Museum to raise admission fee by 45% for visitors from outside Europe to fund renovations,0.0,"[('Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('45%', 'PERCENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,フランスが限定的な兵役を再導入へ、徴兵制廃止から25年,"France to reintroduce limited military service, 25 years after abolishing conscription",-0.08571428571428572,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('25 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,香港火災で火が広がる様子の映像　出火場所と一致, 所要時間 0,45","Video, footage of the fire spreading in Hong Kong, matches the location of the fire, time required 0,45",0.0,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ギニアビサウでクーデターか、将軍が暫定大統領に就任　拘束された大統領の自作との見方も,A coup d'état or a general becomes interim president in Guinea-Bissau; some say it was the detainee's own work,0.325,"[('Guinea', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イタリア議会、全会一致で「フェミサイド」を独立した犯罪に　自動的に終身刑,"Italian parliament unanimously declares 'femicide' an independent crime, automatically punishable by life imprisonment",0.0,"[('Italian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hatua ya bunge la Ulaya dhidi ya Tanzania ina maana gani?,What does the action of the European Parliament against Tanzania mean?,-0.07083333333333333,"[('the European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Putin azidisha matakwa yake kabla ya mazungumzo ya Ukraine na Marekani","Directly, Putin increases his demands before the talks between Ukraine and the United States",0.1,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Afrika na zimwi la mapinduzi yasiyoisha,Africa and the monster of endless revolution,-0.125,"[('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Kagame aonyesha matumaini juu ya mazungumzo yaliyopangwa na Rais wa Congo,President Kagame expresses hope about the talks organized by the President of the Congo,0.0,"[('Kagame', 'PERSON'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais aliyeondolewa madarakani wa Guinea-Bissau awasili Senegal,The deposed president of Guinea-Bissau arrives in Senegal,0.0,"[('Guinea-Bissau', 'ORG'), ('Senegal', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Bunge la Ulaya lapitisha azimio la kuitaka kamisheni kusitisha ufadhili kwa Tanzania,The European Parliament passes a resolution calling on the commission to stop funding for Tanzania,0.0,"[('The European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Man Utd, City macho kwa Vinicius Jr","Football rumors in Europe: Man Utd, City watch for Vinicius Jr",0.0,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Vinicius Jr', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Ligi ya Mabingwa: Jedwali, matokeo na timu zipi ziko mbioni kufuzu kwa awamu ya mtoano","Champions League: Table, results and which teams are in the running to qualify for the knockout phase",0.0,"[('Champions League: Table', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Unajua wewe ni kizazi gani? Millennials, Baby Boomers au Gen Z?","Do you know what generation you are? Millennials, Baby Boomers or Gen Z?",0.0,[]
2025_11_28,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Fahamu jinsi Mahakama ya ICC inavyofanya kazi,Protests in Tanzania: Know how the ICC Court works,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('the ICC Court', 'ORG')]"
