Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué China quiere que sus jóvenes gasten más dinero pero ellos se resisten,Why China wants its young people to spend more money but they resist,0.26666666666666666,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Crie a 3 hijos que son marines de EE.UU. y ahora temo que me deporten a México""","""I raised 3 sons who are US Marines and now I fear they will deport me to Mexico""",0.0,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('US Marines', 'NORP'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cuál es la capacidad militar de Venezuela y cómo puede responder a un eventual ataque de EE.UU.,What is Venezuela's military capacity and how can it respond to a possible US attack?,-0.05,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Sufrirán una derrota aplastante"": la respuesta de China a los comentarios de la primera ministra de Japón que desataron la ira del gobierno de Pekín","""They will suffer a crushing defeat"": China's response to comments by Japan's prime minister that sparked the anger of the Beijing government",-0.14999999999999997,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Roya Karimi, la mujer que escapó de un matrimonio infantil en Afganistán para convertirse en campeona de fisicoculturismo","Roya Karimi, the woman who escaped a child marriage in Afghanistan to become a bodybuilding champion",0.0,"[('Roya Karimi', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"जम्मू-कश्मीर: नौगाम पुलिस थाने में रखे विस्फ़ोटक से सैंपल लेते समय बड़ा धमाका, नौ लोगों की मौत","Jammu and Kashmir: Big blast while taking samples from explosive kept in Naugam police station, nine people died",0.0,"[('Jammu', 'GPE'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC'), ('Naugam', 'GPE'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव: जिन मुस्लिम उम्मीदवारों को जीत मिली,Bihar elections: Muslim candidates who won,0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,प्रशांत किशोर के राजनीति छोड़ने के सवाल पर जन सुराज ने दिया यह जवाब","Live, Jan Suraj gave this answer to the question of Prashant Kishore leaving politics",0.13636363636363635,"[('Prashant Kishore', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"तेज प्रताप यादव महुआ में तीसरे नंबर पर क्यों रहे, जानिए अहम कारण","Why Tej Pratap Yadav stood third in Mahua, know the important reason",0.2,"[('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Mahua', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नीतीश कुमार: सेहत और लोकप्रियता पर उठते सवालों के बावजूद बिहार के लोगों ने भरोसा क्यों किया,"Nitish Kumar: Despite questions being raised on health and popularity, why did the people of Bihar trust him?",0.0,"[('Nitish', 'ORG'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"तेजस्वी यादव कहाँ चूक गए, अब आरजेडी की राह क्या होगी?","Where did Tejashwi Yadav go wrong, what will be the path for RJD now?",-0.5,"[('Tejashwi Yadav', 'PERSON'), ('RJD', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सिर्फ़ 27 वोटों से जीते राधा चरण साह, और कौन-सी सीटों पर हुआ नज़दीकी मुक़ाबला?","Radha Charan Shah won by only 27 votes, on which other seats was there a close contest?",-0.0625,"[('Radha Charan Shah', 'PERSON'), ('only 27', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump suspende 'tarifaço' sobre café, carne, banana, açaí e outros produtos agrícolas","Trump suspends 'tariff' on coffee, meat, bananas, açaí and other agricultural products",-0.125,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,STF forma maioria para tornar Eduardo Bolsonaro réu por coação; o que pode acontecer em caso inédito na Justiça brasileira?,STF forms majority to make Eduardo Bolsonaro a defendant for coercion; What could happen in an unprecedented case in Brazilian Justice?,0.6,"[('STF', 'ORG'), ('Eduardo Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Justiça inglesa condena mineradora BHP em ação de vítimas de Mariana; indenizações podem chegar a R$ 250 bi,English court condemns mining company BHP in lawsuit involving victims of Mariana; compensation can reach R$250 billion,0.0,"[('English', 'NORP'), ('BHP', 'ORG'), ('Mariana', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Qual é a capacidade militar da Venezuela e como ela pode responder a um possível ataque dos EUA?,What is Venezuela's military capacity and how can it respond to a possible US attack?,-0.05,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As 10 principais apostas para ganhar o Oscar 2026 até agora — e quem deixou de ser favorito ao prêmio,The 10 main bets to win the 2026 Oscar so far — and who is no longer favorite for the award,0.39166666666666666,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('Oscar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A missão oculta de Rosalía em 'Lux', sua jogada mais audaciosa","Rosalía's hidden mission in 'Lux', her most audacious move",0.16666666666666669,"[('Rosalía', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que diabetes tipo 1 é mais grave em crianças pequenas,Why type 1 diabetes is more serious in young children,0.0888888888888889,"[('1', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Reencontrei minha irmã 30 anos após vulcão enterrar minha cidade e separar minha família,I met my sister again 30 years after the volcano buried my city and separated my family,0.0,"[('30 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Não me entrego para essa história de idade': as lições de Dona Onete, 86, rainha do carimbó","'I don't give in to this old story': the lessons of Dona Onete, 86, queen of carimbó",0.1,"[('Dona Onete', 'ORG'), ('86', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Конец нефтегазовой эры откладывается. Запад пересмотрел прогнозы на радость Трампу, России и ОПЕК","The end of the oil and gas era is being delayed. The West revised its forecasts to the delight of Trump, Russia and OPEC",0.0,"[('West', 'LOC'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('OPEC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В мире становится холоднее? И человек здесь вообще ни при чем? Проверяем мифы о климате,Is the world getting colder? And the person has nothing to do with it at all? Checking climate myths,0.0,[]
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: США отложили санкции против «Лукойла» в Болгарии; ночной налет дронов на Днепр и Одесскую область","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: US postpones sanctions against Lukoil in Bulgaria; night drone raid on the Dnieper and Odessa region",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Lukoil', 'ORG'), ('Bulgaria', 'GPE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Dnieper', 'PERSON'), ('Odessa', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«От одного до пяти миллиардов». Трамп пообещал подать в суд на Би-би-си из-за монтажа его речи,"""One to five billion."" Trump vowed to sue the BBC over editing of his speech",0.0,"[('One to five billion', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Волки, которые долго жили с людьми». Породы собак начали развиваться еще в Каменном веке","""Wolves who lived with people for a long time."" Dog breeds began to develop back in the Stone Age",-0.025,[]
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп приказал расследовать возможные связи Эпштейна с Клинтоном и банкирами. Минюст США подчинился,Trump ordered an investigation into Epstein's possible ties to Clinton and the bankers. The US Department of Justice complied,0.0,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('The US Department of Justice', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Власти ЮАР расследуют «загадку» прибытия самолета, полного  палестинцев",South African authorities are investigating the “mystery” of the arrival of a plane full of Palestinians,0.175,"[('South African', 'NORP'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Никто не говорит, что с ними». Истории пострадавших от российского удара по Киеву","""Nobody says what's wrong with them."" Stories of victims of the Russian strike on Kyiv",-0.25,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Стокгольме автобус врезался в остановку. Три человека погибли,"In Stockholm, a bus crashed into a bus stop. Three people died",0.0,"[('Stockholm', 'GPE'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Китай поругался с Японией из-за Тайваня. Что происходит?,China had a fight with Japan over Taiwan. What's happening?,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、BBCを来週にも提訴すると　演説映像の編集めぐり,Trump plans to sue BBC next week over editing of speech footage,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('next week', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、「相互関税」の対象から数十の食品を除外　コーヒーやトマト、牛肉など,"Trump excludes dozens of foods from 'reciprocal tariffs' including coffee, tomatoes, beef",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアのドローン、キーウの集合住宅に直撃　首都各地で死傷者,"Russian drone hits apartment complex in Kiv, causing casualties across the capital",-0.15,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kiv', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国外務省、日本への渡航自粛を呼びかけ　日本大使呼び出しも,"China's Ministry of Foreign Affairs calls for people to refrain from traveling to Japan, and also summons the Japanese ambassador",-0.0625,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Ministry of Foreign Affairs', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 パリ連続襲撃事件から10年、いまだ消えない脅威,"[Commentary] 10 years after the Paris attacks, the threat still persists",0.0,"[('10 years', 'DATE'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,BBC、トランプ氏に謝罪も賠償は拒否　新たな「誤解編集映像」を英紙が指摘,BBC apologizes to Trump but refuses compensation; British newspaper points out new 'misunderstood edited footage',0.06818181818181818,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,独連立政権、新たな兵役制度導入でまとまる　兵力増強へ,German coalition government to strengthen military force by introducing new military service system,-0.015909090909090914,"[('German', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英王室アンドリュー氏は「ジュフリー氏と写真撮った」、エプスティーン元被告のメールに記述,"British royal Andrew ``took a photo with Giuffre,'' says Epstein in email",0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Andrew ``', 'PERSON'), ('Giuffre', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ボスニアへの「民間人狙撃ツアー」に多数参加と告発　イタリア当局が捜査着手,"Italian authorities launch investigation after accusations of multiple participation in ""civilian sniper tour"" to Bosnia",0.0,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Bosnia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mambo 5 kutoka hotuba ya Rais Samia iliyowalenga Gen Z wa Tanzania,5 things from President Samia's speech aimed at Gen Z in Tanzania,0.0,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Samia', 'PERSON'), ('Gen Z', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump athibitisha rasmi kuishtaki BBC","Directly, Trump officially confirms to sue the BBC",0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Olise kumrithi Mo Salah Liverpool,European football rumours: Olise to succeed Mo Salah Liverpool,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Mo Salah Liverpool', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Samia atangaza 'msamaha' kwa vijana waliokamatwa kwenye maandamano,President Samia announces 'amnesty' for the youth arrested in the protest,0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mwigulu Nchemba: Kutoka kuchunga ng'ombe hadi Uwaziri Mkuu wa Tanzania,Mwigulu Nchemba: From herding cattle to the Prime Ministership of Tanzania,0.0,[]
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"AFCON 2025: Je, unayajua majina ya timu zitakazoshiriki Kombe la Mataifa ya Afrika?",AFCON 2025: Do you know the names of the teams that will participate in the Africa Cup of Nations?,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('the Africa Cup of', 'EVENT')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Sukari iliyofichika: Unakula kiasi gani kwa kweli?,Hidden Sugar: How Much Are You Really Eating?,0.07777777777777779,"[('Hidden Sugar: How Much Are You Really Eating', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,BBC yamwomba Trump msamaha lakini yakataa kulipa fidia,The BBC apologized to Trump but refused to pay compensation,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tunachojua kuhusu barua pepe mpya za Epstein zinazomtaja Trump,What we know about Epstein's new emails that mention Trump,0.13636363636363635,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_15,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Zaidi ya Wakenya 200 wamesajiliwa katika jeshi la Urusi - waziri,More than 200 Kenyans are registered in the Russian army - minister,0.25,"[('More than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenyans', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
