Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Víctimas de engaños, secuestros y violencia sexual: investigación de la BBC revela abusos en escuelas para ""adolescentes rebeldes"" en China","Victims of deception, kidnapping and sexual violence: BBC investigation reveals abuse in schools for ""rebellious teenagers"" in China",0.5,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo el bloqueo petrolero ""total y completo"" de Trump puede impactar la economía de Venezuela (y jugar en contra de EE.UU.)","How Trump's ""total and complete"" oil blockade can impact Venezuela's economy (and work against the US)",0.05,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Doctrina Donroe"": cómo Trump ve América Latina, según su estrategia de seguridad nacional","""Donroe Doctrine"": how Trump sees Latin America, according to his national security strategy",0.0,"[('Donroe Doctrine', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Una horrible y devastadora pérdida"": los hijos de Rob Reiner rompen su silencio tras el asesinato del director de cine y su esposa","'A horrible, devastating loss': Rob Reiner's children break their silence after the murder of the film director and his wife",-1.0,"[(""Rob Reiner's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Mi padre abusó de 130 niños y descubrir la verdad fue horrible""","""My father abused 130 children and discovering the truth was horrible""",-1.0,"[('130', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सऊदी अरब के इस परिवार की दौलत एक साल में ही इतनी ज़्यादा कैसे बढ़ी? सबसे अमीर परिवारों की लिस्ट में कहां है अंबानी फ़ैमिली,How did the wealth of this Saudi Arabian family increase so much in just one year? Where is Ambani family in the list of richest families?,0.2,"[('Saudi Arabian', 'NORP'), ('just one year', 'DATE'), ('Ambani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"भारत-दक्षिण अफ़्रीका के बीच मैच रद्द होने पर क्रिकेट फ़ैंस का फूटा ग़ुस्सा, जानकारों ने कहा अंतरराष्ट्रीय स्तर पर हुई 'बेइज़्ज़ती'","Cricket fans got angry over the cancellation of the match between India and South Africa, experts said it was an 'insult' at the international level.",-0.25,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अभिनेत्री निधि अग्रवाल से धक्का-मुक्की, भीड़ के बर्ताव पर सोशल मीडिया में भड़के लोग","Live, scuffle with actress Nidhi Agarwal, people angry on social media over the behavior of the crowd",-0.1101010101010101,"[('Nidhi Agarwal', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अरविंद केजरीवाल दिल्ली से क्यों हैं ग़ायब?,Why is Arvind Kejriwal missing from Delhi?,-0.2,"[('Arvind Kejriwal', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दिल्ली: साल में कितने दिन लोग ज़हरीली हवा में सांस लेने को हैं मजबूर?,Delhi: How many days in a year are people forced to breathe poisonous air?,0.09999999999999998,[]
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,राहुल गांधी और सोनिया गांधी को क्या वाकई नेशनल हेराल्ड मामले में अदालत से राहत मिली है?,Have Rahul Gandhi and Sonia Gandhi really got relief from the court in the National Herald case?,0.2,"[('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('Sonia Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('National Herald', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बोंडी बीच हमला: ऑस्ट्रेलिया के मीडिया में भारतीय नागरिक साजिद अकरम और उनके बेटे नवीद के बारे में क्या कहा जा रहा है?,Bondi Beach attack: What is being said in Australian media about Indian citizen Sajid Akram and his son Navid?,0.0,"[('Bondi Beach', 'GPE'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Sajid Akram', 'PERSON'), ('Navid', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बोंडी बीच अटैक: हमलावर साजिद का भारत से नाता, क्या कह रहा है पाकिस्तानी मीडिया","Bondi Beach Attack: Attacker Sajid has links with India, what Pakistani media is saying",0.0,"[('Bondi Beach', 'PERSON'), ('Attacker Sajid', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,कमज़ोर होते भारतीय रुपये के कारण नेपाल को क्यों हो रहा है भारी नुक़सान,Why is Nepal facing huge losses due to weakening Indian rupee?,0.13750000000000004,"[('Nepal', 'PERSON'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Senado aprova redução de penas que beneficia Bolsonaro, e Lula vai decidir se sanciona ou veta","Senate approves sentence reduction that benefits Bolsonaro, and Lula will decide whether to sanction or veto",0.0,"[('Senate', 'ORG'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Crise na fronteira e caos pós-Maduro: os cenários avaliados pelo governo Lula em caso de ataque dos EUA à Venezuela,Border crisis and post-Maduro chaos: the scenarios evaluated by the Lula government in the event of a US attack on Venezuela,0.0,"[('post-Maduro', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump ordena bloqueio 'total' de todos os petroleiros sancionados que entrem e saiam da Venezuela,Trump orders 'total' blockade of all sanctioned oil tankers entering and leaving Venezuela,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que mudança radical de Trump na política externa dos EUA preocupa Europa,Why Trump's radical change in US foreign policy worries Europe,-0.125,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Enel em SP: 'reforço externo' durante crise de energia elevou equipes em menos de 5%,Enel in SP: 'external reinforcement' during the energy crisis increased teams by less than 5%,-0.08333333333333333,"[('less than 5%', 'PERCENT')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os conselhos da Nobel de literatura para novos escritores,Nobel literature's advice for new writers,0.13636363636363635,"[('Nobel', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A dominatrix que criou empresa para combater pornô de vingança após ter imagens vazadas por clientes,The dominatrix who created a company to combat revenge porn after having images leaked by clients,0.0,[]
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Padre Júlio Lancellotti proibido de fazer lives: quando e como a Igreja censura seus religiosos,Father Júlio Lancellotti banned from doing lives: when and how the Church censors its religious,0.0,"[('Júlio Lancellotti', 'PERSON'), ('Church', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Gripe K é identificada no Brasil: como é a variante do influenza A que gerou alerta da OMS para 2026,Flu K is identified in Brazil: what is the variant of influenza A that generated a WHO alert for 2026?,0.0,"[('Flu K', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Туда и обратно: как украинский подросток сбежал из Финляндии в Россию,There and back: how a Ukrainian teenager ran away from Finland to Russia,0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Finland', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в результате удара по порту в Ростове загорелся танкер, есть жертвы","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: a tanker caught fire as a result of an attack on the port in Rostov, there are casualties",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Rostov', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Политзаключенные в обмен на санкции. Какую выгоду дипломатия приносит Трампу и Лукашенко?,Political prisoners in exchange for sanctions. How does diplomacy benefit Trump and Lukashenko?,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Lukashenko', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Год назад наша страна была мертва». Трамп обратился к народу, чтобы объявить о своих успехах в экономике","""A year ago our country was dead."" Trump addresses the nation to announce his economic success",0.09999999999999999,"[('A year ago', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сыну режиссера Роба Райнера предъявили обвинение в убийстве родителей. На первом заседании суда он сказал всего три слова,Director Rob Reiner's son has been charged with the murder of his parents. At the first court hearing he said only three words,0.125,"[(""Rob Reiner's"", 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('only three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Полный шатдаун: в Петербурге уже неделю почти не работает мобильный интернет,Complete shutdown: mobile Internet has hardly been working in St. Petersburg for a week now,-0.09583333333333334,"[('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Стармер грозит Абрамовичу судом, если тот не направит деньги от продажи «Челси» на помощь Украине",Starmer threatens Abramovich with court if he does not use money from the sale of Chelsea to help Ukraine,0.0,"[('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В ожидании экстремальной жары в Испании оборудуют сеть климатических убежищ,"In anticipation of extreme heat, a network of climate shelters will be installed in Spain",-0.125,"[('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Северск на грани падения: почему это угроза для Славянска и Краматорска,Seversk is on the verge of falling: why is it a threat to Slavyansk and Kramatorsk,0.0,"[('Seversk', 'GPE'), ('Slavyansk', 'GPE'), ('Kramatorsk', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Британии будут арестовывать за лозунг «Глобализировать интифаду»,People will be arrested in Britain for the slogan “Globalize the intifada”,0.0,"[('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ガザで豪雨、避難民の生活環境がさらに悪化　低体温症のリスクを国連が警告,Heavy rains in Gaza worsen living conditions for displaced people; UN warns of risk of hypothermia,-0.2,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシア富豪アブラモヴィッチ氏に英首相が警告、チェルシー売却益を「今すぐ拠出せよ」　法的措置も示唆,"British Prime Minister warns Russian billionaire Abramovich to ""donate the proceeds from sale of Chelsea immediately"", suggesting legal action",0.07500000000000001,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ウクライナで拡大する兵器製造、秘密のミサイル工場を取材, 所要時間 3,05","Video, Expanding weapons manufacturing and secret missile factories in Ukraine, Duration 3,05",-0.4,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,NASA長官にアイザックマン氏、米上院が承認　マスク氏と近い資産家,"US Senate approves Isaacman as NASA administrator, wealthy man close to Musk",0.5,"[('US Senate', 'ORG'), ('Isaacman', 'PERSON'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,NATOの防衛費拡大合意は「トランプ氏最大の外交成果」　ルッテ事務総長がBBCに語る,"NATO's defense spending expansion agreement is ""Trump's biggest diplomatic achievement,"" Secretary-General Rutte tells the BBC",0.0,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Rutte', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 約9300円の「手頃な」チケット販売へ　出場チームのサポーター向け,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] ""Affordable"" tickets will be sold for approximately 9,300 yen for supporters of participating teams",-0.4,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('approximately 9,300 yen', 'MONEY')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告の共犯者、刑の取り消しを申し立て　裁判が公正でなかったと,"Epstein's co-defendant petitions for sentence to be vacated, saying trial was not fair",-0.35,[]
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ミス・フィンランドの「つり目」写真、東アジア各国で人種差別と激しい批判,Miss Finland's ``slanted eyes'' photo sparks intense criticism of racism in East Asian countries,0.1,"[('Finland', 'GPE'), ('East Asian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヴェネズエラ出入港の制裁対象タンカーを「全面封鎖」、トランプ氏が命じる,Trump orders 'total blockade' of sanctioned tankers entering and exiting Venezuelan ports,0.0,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Putin awaita viongozi wa Ulaya “nguruwe”","Directly, Putin calls European leaders ""pigs""",0.05,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hiki ndicho kiwanda cha siri cha makombora mapya ya 'kumtetemesha' Putin,This is the secret factory of new missiles to 'shake' Putin,-0.13181818181818183,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Zifahamu familia 5 tajiri zaidi duniani,Get to know the 5 richest families in the world,0.0,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Zirkzee njia panda Roma,European Football Rumors: Zirkzee cross paths with Roma,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Roma', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marekani yaweka vikwazo vipya kwa wasafiri kutoka Tanzania,The United States imposes new restrictions on travelers from Tanzania,0.13636363636363635,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwenda haja kubwa mara tu baada ya kula kunaashiria  ugonjwa?,Going to defecate immediately after eating indicates a disease?,0.0,[]
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,BBC itapinga kesi ya kashfa ya Donald Trump: Tutegemee nini?,The BBC will challenge Donald Trump's defamation case: What should we expect?,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), (""Donald Trump's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini Marekani inahusisha vita dhidi ya madawa ya kulevya na ugaidi?,Why does the United States associate the war on drugs with terrorism?,0.0,"[('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wakenya 18 waliohadaiwa kujiunga na kikosi cha Urusi warejea nyumbani,18 Kenyans who were threatened to join the Russian army have returned home,0.0,"[('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenyans', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanamgambo wa RSF wanaficha mauaji ya halaiki huko el-Fasher-Watafiti,RSF militants cover up genocide in el-Fasher-Watafiti,0.0,"[('el-Fasher-Watafiti', 'ORG')]"
