Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué se sabe del buque petrolero incautado por EE.UU. cerca de las costas de Venezuela,What is known about the oil tanker seized by the US near the coast of Venezuela,0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Fuerzas de EE.UU. interceptan y confiscan un buque petrolero sancionado frente a las costas de Venezuela,US forces intercept and confiscate a sanctioned oil tanker off the coast of Venezuela,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El gobierno de Venezuela califica de ""robo descarado y acto de piratería"" la incautación de un buque petrolero frente a sus costas por parte de EE.UU.","The government of Venezuela describes the seizure of an oil tanker off its coast by the United States as ""brazen theft and an act of piracy.""",0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La opositora venezolana María Corina Machado realiza su primera aparición pública en Oslo tras pasar más de un año en la clandestinidad,Venezuelan opposition activist María Corina Machado makes her first public appearance in Oslo after spending more than a year in hiding,0.25,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('María Corina Machado', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Oslo', 'GPE'), ('more than a year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es Ana Corina Sosa, la hija de María Corina Machado que recogió el Premio Nobel de la Paz en nombre de su madre","Who is Ana Corina Sosa, the daughter of María Corina Machado who received the Nobel Peace Prize on behalf of her mother",0.0,"[('Ana Corina Sosa', 'PERSON'), ('María Corina Machado', 'ORG'), ('the Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बारात में नोट उठाने पर सीआईएसएफ़ जवान ने बच्चे पर चलाई गोली, क्या कह रहा है मृतक का परिवार?","CISF jawan opened fire on a child for picking up currency notes in a marriage procession, what is the family of the deceased saying?",0.0,"[('CISF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,पेट्रोल में एथेनॉल मिलाए जाने पर नितिन गडकरी ने संसद को क्या बताया","Live, what did Nitin Gadkari tell the Parliament on mixing of ethanol in petrol?",0.13636363636363635,"[('Nitin Gadkari', 'PERSON'), ('Parliament', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप ने 'ईगो' की वजह से भारत पर लगाया टैरिफ़, रघुराम राजन के इस बयान पर क्या कह रहे विश्लेषक","Trump imposed tariff on India because of 'ego', what are analysts saying on this statement of Raghuram Rajan",0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Raghuram Rajan', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,गोवा नाइट क्लब हादसा: अभियुक्त लूथरा ब्रदर्स को थाईलैंड में हिरासत में लिया गया,Goa nightclub incident: Accused Luthra brothers detained in Thailand,0.0,"[('Accused Luthra', 'PERSON'), ('Thailand', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ज़िंदगी में सबसे ज़्यादा प्यार किससे है? स्मृति मंधाना ने बताया,Whom do you love most in life? Smriti Mandhana told,0.5,"[('Smriti Mandhana', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'सिर्फ़ भारत को ही मौक़ा क्यों मिले', इंडोनेशिया के राष्ट्रपति ने पुतिन से ये क्यों कहा","'Why should only India get a chance', why did the President of Indonesia say this to Putin",0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अक्षय खन्ना लाइमलाइट से दूर रहने के बाद फिर 'धुरंधर' कैसे बन जाते हैं?,How does Akshaye Khanna become 'Dhurandhar' after staying away from limelight?,0.0,"[('Akshaye Khanna', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,राजकोट में सात वर्षीय बच्ची के साथ रेप और हिंसा का मामला,Case of rape and violence with seven year old girl in Rajkot,0.1,"[('seven year old', 'DATE'), ('Rajkot', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चुनाव सुधार पर बहस: अमित शाह और राहुल गांधी के आमने-सामने आने से लेकर विपक्ष के वॉकआउट तक,Debate on electoral reforms: From Amit Shah and Rahul Gandhi coming face to face to the opposition's walkout,0.0,"[('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como escola pública de Cubatão deixou rotina de drogas e violência e se tornou uma das 'melhores do mundo',How a public school in Cubatão left a routine of drugs and violence and became one of the 'best in the world',0.3333333333333333,"[('Cubatão', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Câmara rejeita cassação de Carla Zambelli apesar de condenação no STF,Chamber rejects impeachment of Carla Zambelli despite conviction in the STF,0.0,"[('Carla Zambelli', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Câmara aprova suspensão do deputado Glauber Braga, que escapa da perda de mandato","Chamber approves suspension of deputy Glauber Braga, who escapes loss of mandate",0.0,"[('Chamber', 'ORG'), ('Glauber Braga', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Gilmar Mendes recua e permite que qualquer cidadão proponha impeachment de ministros do STF,Gilmar Mendes backs down and allows any citizen to propose impeachment of STF ministers,-0.15555555555555559,"[('Gilmar Mendes', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As imagens de satélite que mostram ciclone com ventos de até 120 km/h no Brasil visto do espaço,Satellite images that show a cyclone with winds of up to 120 km/h in Brazil seen from space,0.0,"[('up to 120 km/h', 'QUANTITY'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Venezuela acusa EUA de 'pirataria' após captura de petroleiro; governo Trump fala de violação a sanções,Venezuela accuses US of 'piracy' after oil tanker captured; Trump administration talks about violation of sanctions,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,EUA podem exigir que turistas apresentem histórico de redes sociais dos últimos 5 anos para entrar no país,US may require tourists to present social media history from the last 5 years to enter the country,0.011111111111111112,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('the last 5 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Pai de Madeleine McCann fala à BBC em rara entrevista sobre desaparecimento da filha,Madeleine McCann's father speaks to the BBC in a rare interview about his daughter's disappearance,0.3,"[(""Madeleine McCann's"", 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Governo Lula está 'de mãos amarradas' com PL da dosimetria, diz analista político","Lula government's 'hands are tied' with dosimetry PL, says political analyst",0.0,"[('PL', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Невозможно стало жить». Куда уезжают из России трудовые мигранты?,“It has become impossible to live.” Where do labor migrants leave Russia?,-0.26515151515151514,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,США захватили нефтяной танкер у берегов Венесуэлы,US seizes oil tanker off Venezuela,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Стала ли Украина ближе к выборам? Как понимать заявления Зеленского о готовности к кампании,Has Ukraine become closer to elections? How to understand Zelensky’s statements about readiness for the campaign,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: почти 300 дронов сбили над регионами России; Киев передал США ответ на «мирный план» Трампа","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: almost 300 drones shot down over Russian regions; Kyiv conveyed to the United States its response to Trump’s “peace plan”",-0.07777777777777779,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('almost 300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,США собираются проверять соцсети у туристов из стран-союзниц. Как это будет работать — непонятно,The United States is going to check the social networks of tourists from allied countries. How this will work is unclear,0.03333333333333333,"[('The United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Трамп требует выборов в Украине? | Подкаст «Что это было?», Продолжительность 40,19","Video, Trump demands elections in Ukraine? | Podcast “What was that?”, Duration 40.19",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Podcast', 'PERSON'), ('40.19', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Сперма донора с мутировавшим геном, вызывающим рак, была использована для зачатия почти 200 детей по всей Европе",Sperm from a donor with a mutated cancer-causing gene has been used to conceive nearly 200 children across Europe,0.1,"[('nearly 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп о судьбе Европы, мигранты и президентские выборы во Франции.  Лидер французских ультраправых дал интервью Би-би-си","Trump on the fate of Europe, migrants and the presidential elections in France.  The leader of the French far right gave an interview to the BBC",0.12857142857142856,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Марокко рухнули два жилых дома, погибли как минимум 22 человека","Two residential buildings collapsed in Morocco, killing at least 22 people",-0.3,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('at least 22', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Преднамеренный акт запугивания». Россия и Китай провели воздушные учения у границ Японии и Южной Кореи, Токио и Сеул протестуют","""A deliberate act of intimidation."" Russia and China held air exercises near the borders of Japan and South Korea, Tokyo and Seoul protest",0.1,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('Seoul', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノーベル平和賞授賞式、マチャド氏の娘が代理出席　演説を代読,Machado's daughter attended the Nobel Peace Prize ceremony on his behalf and read the speech on his behalf,0.0,"[('Machado', 'ORG'), ('the Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英米仏独の首脳、ウクライナめぐり「集中作業」続くと　ゼレンスキー氏は「選挙の準備できている」,"Leaders of Britain, the United States, France and Germany continue ``intensive work'' on Ukraine, Zelenskiy says ``we are ready for elections''",0.2,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskiy', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,韓国、中ロの軍用機が防空識別圏に進入と抗議,South Korea protests that Chinese and Russian military aircraft enter air defense identification zone,-0.03333333333333333,"[('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イタリア料理がユネスコ無形文化遺産に　「家族やコミュニティーとつながる手段」,"Italian cuisine designated as a UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage, ``a means of connecting with family and community''",0.05,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,16歳未満のSNS禁止法、オーストラリアで施行　世界初,Law banning social media for people under 16 comes into force in Australia - world's first,0.14166666666666666,"[('under 16', 'DATE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、欧州諸国は「衰退している」と　欧州首脳は「弱い」とも批判,"Trump says European countries are ""in decline"" and criticizes European leaders as ""weak""",-0.125,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「祖国英雄の日」にロシアの人たちは……「必ず勝利する」, 所要時間 2,38","Video, Russian people on ""Heroes of the Fatherland Day""... ""We will definitely win"", Duration 2,38",0.4,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Heroes of the Fatherland Day', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイとカンボジアの衝突続く　アメリカは戦闘停止を要求,Clashes between Thailand and Cambodia continue; US calls for cessation of fighting,0.0,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナでイギリス軍の一員が事故死,British military member dies in accident in Ukraine,-0.05,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,‘Droni’ zaua 100, maelfu wakikimbia makazi yao Mashariki mwa DRC","Directly, 'Drones' kill 100, thousands flee their homes in Eastern DRC",0.1,"[('Drones', 'PERSON'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Eastern DRC', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini mapinduzi ya Benin yalifeli wakati mengine yalifanikiwa Afrika Magharibi?,Why did the Benin revolution fail when others succeeded in West Africa?,-0.5,"[('Benin', 'PERSON'), ('West Africa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kwanini ndege ya kijeshi ya Nigeria iliivamia Burkina Faso, Traore kujibu mapigo?","Why did the Nigerian military plane attack Burkina Faso, Traore in response to the blows?",-0.1,"[('Nigerian', 'NORP'), ('Burkina Faso', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Man united inamtaka 'mzee' Sergio Ramos,European football rumours: Man United want the 'old' Sergio Ramos,0.05,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Sergio Ramos', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Kwanini Disemba 9 yameshindikana?,Protests in Tanzania: Why did December 9 fail?,-0.5,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('December 9', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uingereza inaweza kupigana kwa muda gani ikiwa vita vitazuka?,How long can Britain fight if war breaks out?,-0.05,"[('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kwa nini China na Urusi zinaonekana kumtenga Maduro, wakati huu akivutana na Marekani?","Why do China and Russia seem to isolate Maduro, this time he is fighting with the United States?",0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Salah kutimkia Saudi Arabia Januari,European football rumours: Salah to go to Saudi Arabia in January,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Salah', 'NORP'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('January', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hali ya usalama wa nchi ni shwari - Polisi Tanzania,The country's security situation is stable - Tanzania Police,0.0,[]
2025_12_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mataifa gani yanapigiwa chapuo kubeba kombe la dunia 2026?,Which countries are being beaten to carry the 2026 world cup?,0.0,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
