Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार चुनाव: नीतीश, तेजस्वी या पीके किसके पक्ष में जा रहा है एमवाई समीकरण?","Bihar Elections: Nitish, Tejashwi or PK, in whose favor is the MY equation going?",0.0,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON'), ('Nitish', 'NORP'), ('Tejashwi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula e Papa Leão 14: os temas que devem surgir em reunião no Vaticano,Lula and Pope Leo 14: the themes that should arise in a meeting at the Vatican,0.0,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Vatican', 'FAC')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula em Roma: Brasil tem desafios para reduzir desperdício de alimentos enquanto celebra saída do Mapa da Fome,Lula in Rome: Brazil faces challenges in reducing food waste while celebrating exit from the Hunger Map,-0.2,"[('Rome', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Após ameaça de Trump, China diz que não tem medo de guerra tarifária","After Trump threat, China says it is not afraid of tariff war",0.3,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Atrasos, desconfiança e preços dinâmicos: até que ponto a Copa do Mundo será 'receptiva'?","Delays, mistrust and dynamic pricing: how 'responsive' will the World Cup be?",0.0,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,María Corina Machado à BBC: 'A invasão à Venezuela já existe; o que precisamos é de uma libertação',María Corina Machado to the BBC: 'The invasion of Venezuela already exists; What we need is a release',0.0,"[('María Corina Machado', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Nobel da Paz a María Corina 'fortalece ala disposta a tudo para tirar Maduro',Nobel Peace Prize winner María Corina 'strengthens wing willing to do anything to remove Maduro',0.25,"[('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Corina', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A guerra em Gaza em mapas: como 2 anos de combates devastaram o território palestino,The war in Gaza on maps: how 2 years of fighting devastated the Palestinian territory,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('2 years', 'DATE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A herdeira raptada que se aliou a seus sequestradores para 'lutar por povos oprimidos',The kidnapped heiress who allied with her kidnappers to 'fight for oppressed people',0.0,[]
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Жиросжигатели с сибутрамином: как сотни россиян получили уголовные сроки за таблетки для похудения,Fat burners with sibutramine: how hundreds of Russians received criminal sentences for diet pills,-0.4,"[('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russians', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Спасибо, Трамп, спасибо, Уиткофф». Трамп обещал скорое освобождение заложников, в Тель-Авиве прошел многотысячный митинг","“Thank you Trump, thank you Witkoff.” Trump promised the imminent release of the hostages; a rally of thousands was held in Tel Aviv",0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Witkoff', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tel Aviv', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Президент Мадагаскара заявил о попытке захвата власти военными,The President of Madagascar announced an attempt to seize power by the military,-0.1,"[('Madagascar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Кажется, техномиллиардеры готовятся к концу света. Стоит ли нам всем беспокоиться?",It seems tech billionaires are preparing for the end of the world. Should we all be worried?,0.0,[]
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп поручил Пентагону выплатить зарплату военным, несмотря на шатдаун",Trump instructed the Pentagon to pay military salaries despite the shutdown,-0.1,"[('Pentagon', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Малоизвестная Тэтчер: 8 неожиданных фактов биографии «железной леди»,Little-known Thatcher: 8 unexpected facts from the biography of the “Iron Lady”,0.1,"[('Thatcher', 'PERSON'), ('8', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Афганистан заявил об ударах по войскам Пакистана в приграничных районах,Afghanistan announces strikes against Pakistani troops in border areas,0.0,"[('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Умерла Дайан Китон, обладательница «Оскара» за фильмы «Энни Холл» и «Крестный отец»","Diane Keaton, Oscar winner for Annie Hall and The Godfather, has died",0.0,"[('Diane Keaton', 'PERSON'), ('Oscar', 'PERSON'), ('Annie Hall', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: США с лета помогают Украине наносить удары по российским НПЗ, выяснила Financial Times","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: The US has been helping Ukraine strike Russian oil refineries since the summer, the Financial Times has found out",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the summer', 'DATE'), ('the Financial Times', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Украина показывает, что в эту игру могут играть двое». Топливный кризис затронул уже больше половины регионов России",“Ukraine shows that two can play this game.” The fuel crisis has already affected more than half of Russia's regions,-0.022222222222222227,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Israel inatarajia mateka kuachiliwa Jumatatu asubuhi;Trump akijiandaa kwa ziara ya Mashariki ya Kati","Directly, Israel expects the captives to be released on Monday morning; Trump preparing for a visit to the Middle East",0.05,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Monday morning', 'TIME'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ofisi ya rais wa Madagascar inasema jaribio la kunyakua mamlaka linaendelea,Madagascar's presidential office says an attempt to grab authority is underway,0.0,"[('Madagascar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Israel iko tayari kupokea mateka mapema Jumatatu asubuhi, serikali inasema","Israel is ready to receive captives early Monday morning, the government says",0.15000000000000002,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('early Monday morning', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, ni nani atanyakuwa nafasi zilizosalia kufuzu Kombe la Dunia 2026?",Who will be the remaining positions to qualify for the 2026 World Cup?,0.0,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, chapati, mkate na wali vinahatarisha vipi afya yako?","How do chapati, bread and rice risk your health?",0.0,[]
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Methanoli au uchovu? Jinsi ya kujua ikiwa kinywaji chako kina sumu ya methanoli,Methanoli or fatigue? How to find out if your drink is toxic to Methanoli,0.0,"[('Methanoli', 'GPE'), ('Methanoli', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Man Utd wanavutiwa na Wharton wa Palace - Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumapili,Man Utd are interested in Palace Wharton - European football rumors on Sunday,0.125,"[('Palace Wharton - European', 'ORG'), ('Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Mshindi wa Tuzo ya Amani ya Nobel 2025, Maria Corina Machado ni nani?","Who is the winner of the Nobel Peace Prize 2025, who is Maria Corina Machado?",0.0,"[('the Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('Maria Corina Machado', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, rais mkongwe zaidi duniani atatetea kiti chake na kushawishi wapiga kura vijana?",Will the world's oldest president defend his seat and persuade young voters?,0.1,[]
2025_10_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Dozi ya kifo: Jinsi uraibu wa dawa za kikohozi zinavyowaangamiza watoto,Death dose: How the addiction of cough drugs destroys children,0.0,[]
