Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Vi cuerpos sin cabeza, cuerpos completamente desfigurados"": el fotógrafo que siguió durante 24 horas el operativo policial que dejó más de 120 muertos en Río de Janeiro","""I saw headless bodies, completely disfigured bodies"": the photographer who followed for 24 hours the police operation that left more than 120 dead in Rio de Janeiro",0.09999999999999999,"[('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('more than 120', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué es Comando Vermelho y cuánto poder tiene la banda criminal contra la que la policía en Brasil lanzó un operativo que dejó más de 120 muertos,What is Comando Vermelho and how much power does the criminal gang have against which the police in Brazil launched an operation that left more than 120 dead?,0.019999999999999997,"[('Comando Vermelho', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('more than 120', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Las impactantes imágenes de las favelas de Río tras el megaoperativo policial contra Comando Vermelho que dejó más de 100 muertos,The shocking images of the favelas of Rio after the mega police operation against Comando Vermelho that left more than 100 dead,-0.175,"[('Rio', 'ORG'), ('Comando Vermelho', 'ORG'), ('more than 100', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Es una traición"": la furia de los ganaderos en EE.UU. porque el gobierno de Trump quiere importar más carne argentina","""It's a betrayal"": the fury of ranchers in the US because the Trump government wants to import more Argentine meat",0.35,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Argentine', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Por qué no deberías obsesionarte con dormir 8 horas y otros 3 consejos de salud de Chris y Xand van Tulleken, los médicos gemelos de la BBC","Why you shouldn't be obsessed with sleeping 8 hours and 3 other health tips from Chris and Xand van Tulleken, the BBC's twin doctors",-0.3125,"[('8 hours', 'TIME'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chris', 'PERSON'), ('Xand van Tulleken', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'भगवान ने मुझे कुछ ना कुछ अच्छा करने के लिए यहां भेजा है': शेफ़ाली वर्मा,'God has sent me here to do something good': Shefali Verma,0.7,"[('Shefali Verma', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ऑस्ट्रेलिया में फ़िलिप ह्यूज जैसा एक और हादसा, प्रैक्टिस के दौरान कैसे हुई 17 साल के क्रिकेटर की मौत","Another accident like Phillip Hughes in Australia, how a 17 year old cricketer died during practice",0.1,"[('Phillip Hughes', 'PERSON'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('17 year old', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,'आमार शोनार बांग्ला' गीत विवाद पर महुआ मोइत्रा ने बीजेपी पर साधा निशाना, जानिए क्या कहा","Live, Mahua Moitra targets BJP on 'Amar Shonar Bangla' song controversy, know what she said",0.13636363636363635,"[('Mahua Moitra', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), (""Amar Shonar Bangla'"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप ने कहा, 'हम जल्द करेंगे परमाणु परीक्षण', किस देश के पास हैं सबसे ज़्यादा परमाणु हथियार","Trump said, 'We will do nuclear tests soon', which country has the most nuclear weapons?",0.5,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप ने चीन पर 'फ़ेंटानिल टैरिफ़' कम किया, रेयर अर्थ का मामला भी सुलझाने का दावा","Trump reduces 'fentanyl tariff' on China, claims to solve rare earth issue too",0.3,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,प्रशांत किशोर के गाँव में उनके पिता की पहचान पड़ती है भारी- ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट,Prashant Kishore's father's identity weighs heavy in his village - ground report,-0.2,"[('Kishore', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दिल्ली में 'क्लाउड सीडिंग' से बारिश कराने का प्लान क्यों हुआ फ्लॉप?,Why did the plan to make rain in Delhi through 'cloud seeding' flop?,0.0,"[('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार चुनाव के प्रचार में राहुल गांधी की एंट्री और पीएम मोदी पर टिप्पणी, अमित शाह क्या बोले","Rahul Gandhi's entry in Bihar election campaign and comment on PM Modi, what did Amit Shah say?",0.0,"[(""Rahul Gandhi's"", 'PERSON'), ('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('Amit Shah', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ग़ज़ा में 104 फ़लस्तीनियों की मौत, इसराइल ने हमास पर लगाया सैनिक को मारने का आरोप","104 Palestinians killed in Gaza, Israel accuses Hamas of killing soldier",-0.2,"[('104', 'CARDINAL'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Vi corpo sem cabeça, corpos totalmente desfigurados': o fotógrafo que acompanhou por 24 horas a operação policial que deixou 121 mortos no Rio","'I saw a headless body, totally disfigured bodies': the photographer who followed the police operation for 24 hours that left 121 people dead in Rio",-0.06666666666666667,"[('24 hours', 'TIME'), ('121', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Operação contra o CV: moradores recolhem mais de 50 corpos,Operation against CV: residents collect more than 50 bodies,0.5,"[('more than 50', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,MPF pede dados da perícia dos corpos de vítimas de megaoperação no RJ e STF também cobra explicações do governo estadual,MPF requests forensic data on bodies of victims of mega-operation in RJ and STF also demands explanations from the state government,0.0,"[('MPF', 'ORG'), ('RJ', 'GPE'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como fuzis importados chegam às mãos do crime organizado no Brasil,How imported rifles reach the hands of organized crime in Brazil,0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O aumento do consumo de cocaína no mundo que está dando mais poder a facções brasileiras,The increase in cocaine consumption in the world is giving more power to Brazilian factions,0.5,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como Comando Vermelho surgiu e se espalhou pelo Brasil,How Comando Vermelho emerged and spread throughout Brazil,0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Mulher morre após ter sido 'esquecida' por navio de cruzeiro em ilha da Austrália,Woman dies after being 'forgotten' by cruise ship on Australian island,0.0,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A mulher que vivia com suas 3 filhas em abrigo para moradores de rua e se tornou cientista renomada,The woman who lived with her 3 daughters in a homeless shelter and became a renowned scientist,0.0,"[('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Kim Kataguiri: Bolsonaro deve cumprir pena na cadeia e ir ao hospital quando necessário,Kim Kataguiri: Bolsonaro should serve time in jail and go to the hospital when necessary,-0.05,"[('Kim Kataguiri', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Покровск и Мирноград на грани падения: насколько ситуация там критична для Украины?,Pokrovsk and Mirnograd are on the verge of falling: how critical is the situation there for Ukraine?,0.0,"[('Pokrovsk', 'GPE'), ('Mirnograd', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп после встречи с лидером Китая: оценка «12 из 10», тарифы снизят, по войне в Украине будут «работать вместе»","Trump after a meeting with the leader of China: rating “12 out of 10”, tariffs will be reduced, they will “work together” on the war in Ukraine",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: новая массированная атака ракетами и дронами, в большинстве регионов аварийные отключения электричества","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: new massive attack by missiles and drones, power outages in most regions",0.21212121212121213,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Посейдон» после «Буревестника»: почему Путин заявляет об испытаниях необычных ядерных вооружений?,“Poseidon” after “Burevestnik”: why does Putin announce tests of unusual nuclear weapons?,0.2,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Британия депортировала нелегального иммигранта из Эфиопии, которого до этого по ошибке выпустили из тюрьмы",Britain has deported an illegal immigrant from Ethiopia who had previously been mistakenly released from prison.,-0.3333333333333333,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Ethiopia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Ураган «Мелисса»: пять погибших на Ямайке, 20 — на Гаити, разрушения по всему Карибскому региону","Hurricane Melissa: Five dead in Jamaica, 20 in Haiti, destruction across the Caribbean",-0.2,"[('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jamaica', 'GPE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В крупнейшей полицейской операции против преступной группировки в Рио-де-Жанейро погибли по меньшей мере 132 человека,At least 132 people are killed in the biggest police operation against a criminal gang in Rio de Janeiro.,-0.3,"[('At least 132', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Певицу Наоко в Петербурге второй раз подряд отправили под административный арест на 13 суток,Singer Naoko in St. Petersburg was sent under administrative arrest for 13 days for the second time in a row,-0.025,"[('Naoko', 'PERSON'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('13 days', 'DATE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Во Франции судят болгар, осквернивших еврейский мемориал. Французские власти считают, что они действовали по заказу России",Bulgarians are being tried in France for desecrating a Jewish memorial. French authorities believe they acted on orders from Russia,0.0,"[('Bulgarians', 'NORP'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Арбузный шербет. Основатель Ben & Jerry's поругался с владельцами бренда из-за мороженого в поддержку палестинцев,Watermelon sorbet. Ben & Jerry's founder argued with brand owners over ice cream in support of Palestinians,0.0,"[(""Ben & Jerry's"", 'ORG'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、核兵器の試験再開を指示　過去30年ほど行われず,"Trump orders resumption of nuclear weapons testing, something that hasn't happened in the past 30 years",-0.25,"[('the past 30 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカと韓国が首脳会談、「包括的な貿易合意」に達したと　トランプ氏は習氏との会談見据える,"US and South Korea hold summit and reach ``comprehensive trade agreement,'' Trump says, looking ahead to meeting with Xi",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Xi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ブラジル・リオデジャネイロで警察がギャング掃討作戦、少なくとも132人死亡と当局,"At least 132 people killed in police operation to wipe out gangs in Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, authorities say",-0.25,"[('At least 132', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 トランプ氏の一連のレアアース合意、中国による世界的支配を変えられるのか,[Commentary] Will Trump's series of rare earth agreements change China's global dominance?,0.15,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スーダンの準軍事組織、病院で民間人460人を殺害か　WHOトップが懸念表明,WHO chief expresses concern over Sudanese paramilitary group killing 460 civilians at hospital,0.0,"[('Sudanese', 'NORP'), ('460', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,誤って釈放した移民の性犯罪者を強制送還、500ポンド渡したうえで　英野党は批判,British opposition party criticizes deportation of mistakenly released immigrant sex offender after giving him 500 pounds,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('500 pounds', 'QUANTITY')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ハリケーン「メリッサ」、ジャマイカで死者5人　被害が甚大な南西部の状況は, 所要時間 1,18","Video, 5 dead in Jamaica due to Hurricane Melissa, situation in the southwestern part of the country, where damage is severe. Required time 1,18",-0.1625,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jamaica', 'GPE'), ('Hurricane Melissa', 'EVENT'), ('1,18', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエルがガザを空爆、死者100人以上　停戦合意にハマスが違反したと非難,"Israel bombs Gaza, kills over 100 people, accuses Hamas of violating ceasefire agreement",0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('over 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 レアアース、ノーベル賞推薦、賛辞……トランプ氏が訪日終える,"[Commentary] Rare earths, Nobel Prize nomination, compliments... Trump ends his visit to Japan",0.3,"[('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Uchaguzi mkuu wa Tanzania 2025: Serikali yawaagiza wafanyakazi wa umma kufanyia kazi nyumbani","Live, Tanzania's general election 2025: The government orders public employees to work from home",0.062121212121212126,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Tutatangaza matokeo ya uchaguzi Zanzibar ndani ya saa 24' - ZEC,'We will announce the election results in Zanzibar within 24 hours' - ZEC,0.0,"[('Zanzibar', 'NORP'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump aiomba Idara ya Ulinzi Marekani kuanza tena majaribio ya silaha za nyuklia","Directly, Trump asked the US Department of Defense to resume nuclear weapons testing",0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the US Department of Defense', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Matokeo ya uchaguzi mkuu wa Tanzania 2025,The results of the general election of Tanzania 2025,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Polisi warusha mabomu ya machozi baada ya maandamano kuzuka Tanzania,Police throw tear gas after protests erupted in Tanzania,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Mkuu Tanzania 2025: Kura au maandamano? mizani ya haki za kikatiba inavyopimwa,Tanzania General Election 2025: Vote or protest? the balance of constitutional rights is measured,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzania General', 'ORG'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"VPN ni nini, na unahitaji kuitumia katika mazingira gani?","What is a VPN, and in what environment do you need to use it?",0.0,[]
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Waridi wa BBC: Mwanamke aliyelazimishwa kunywa maji ya maiti,BBC Rose: Woman forced to drink corpse water,0.14999999999999997,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Silaha za kijeshi za Uingereza zilifikaje kwa vikosi vya Rapid Support Forces?  - The Guardian,How did British military equipment get to the Rapid Support Forces?  - The Guardian,-0.05,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('the Rapid Support Forces', 'ORG'), ('Guardian', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"China inadhibiti madini adimu ambayo ulimwengu hununua..je, mikataba mipya ya Trump inaweza kubadilisha hilo?",China controls the rare metals the world buys..can Trump's new deals change that?,0.21818181818181817,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
