Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los temas clave que quedan sin resolver en el acuerdo entre EE.UU. e Irán (y una incógnita de US$300.000 millones),The key issues left unresolved in the US-Iran deal (and a $300 billion unknown),0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('$300 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué ventajas y riesgos tiene la polémica propuesta de Kast de reducir el impuesto a las empresas en Chile (y por qué la comparación internacional puede ser engañosa),What advantages and risks does Kast's controversial proposal to reduce the corporate tax in Chile have (and why the international comparison can be misleading),0.0,neutral,"[('Kast', 'ORG'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Me convertí en una prisionera dentro de mi propia casa"": las bandas narco en Reino Unido que ocupan cientos de casas con sus habitantes adentro","""I became a prisoner in my own house"": the drug gangs in the United Kingdom that occupy hundreds of houses with their inhabitants inside",0.0,neutral,"[('the United Kingdom', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere a los 35 años Daveigh Chase, actriz de ""The Ring"" y una de las voces de ""Lilo & Stitch""","Daveigh Chase, actress of ""The Ring"" and one of the voices of ""Lilo & Stitch,"" dies at 35",0.0,neutral,"[('Daveigh Chase', 'PERSON'), ('The Ring', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lilo & Stitch', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('35', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los gráficos que muestran cómo el cuerpo de los futbolistas ha cambiado en los últimos 50 años,Graphs showing how footballers' bodies have changed over the last 50 years,1.0,positive,"[('the last 50 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¡El show de Luis Díaz! Colombia se impone 3-1 a Uzbekistán en su debut del Mundial 2026,The Luis Díaz show! Colombia beats Uzbekistan 3-1 in its debut of the 2026 World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('The Luis Díaz', 'PERSON'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Toma lo que quieras mientras puedas: la feroz disputa por la soberanía en el mar de China Meridional,Take what you want while you can: the fierce dispute over sovereignty in the South China Sea,0.0,neutral,"[('the South China Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Llévenselo de aquí"": condenan a cadena perpetua al asesino en serie que mató a 8 mujeres y atemorizó Nueva York","""Take him away from here"": the serial killer who killed 8 women and terrorized New York is sentenced to life in prison",-1.0,negative,"[('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cuáles son los puntos clave del acuerdo firmado por EE.UU. e Irán para poner fin a la guerra y reabrir el estrecho de Ormuz,What are the key points of the agreement signed by the US and Iran to end the war and reopen the Strait of Hormuz?,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los récords que Leo Messi logró en su debut en el Mundial 2026 (y otros con los que ha dejado su huella en la historia de la Copa del Mundo),The records that Leo Messi achieved in his debut at the 2026 World Cup (and others with which he has left his mark on the history of the World Cup),0.0,neutral,"[('Leo Messi', 'PERSON'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इन तीन वजहों से पटरी से उतर सकता है अमेरिका-ईरान समझौता,America-Iran agreement may derail due to these three reasons,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,जंग शुरू होने के बाद यूक्रेन का मॉस्को पर सबसे ज़ोरदार हमला, ज़ेंलेस्की ने क्या कहा?","Live, Ukraine's most powerful attack on Moscow since the war started, what did Zelensky say?",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सिर पर तलवार के वार से मारी गई थीं रानी लक्ष्मीबाई,Rani Laxmibai was killed by a sword blow on the head,-1.0,negative,"[('Rani Laxmibai', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान अमेरिका के साथ हुए समझौते को अपनी जीत क्यों मान रहा है?,Why is Iran considering the agreement with America as its victory?,1.0,positive,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"राहुल गांधी के कोटा कार्यक्रम को बीजेपी ने बताया नौटंकी, कांग्रेस ने दिया ये जवाब","BJP called Rahul Gandhi's quota program a gimmick, Congress gave this answer",0.0,neutral,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), (""Rahul Gandhi's"", 'PERSON'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"शिवसेना (यूबीटी) की बैठक में 9 में से सिर्फ़ 3 सांसद पहुंचे, संजय राउत बोले- 'शिंदे को बेईमानी महंगी पड़ेगी'","Only 3 out of 9 MPs attended the Shiv Sena (UBT) meeting, Sanjay Raut said - 'Dishonesty will be costly for Shinde'",0.0,neutral,"[('Only 3', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Shiv Sena', 'FAC'), ('UBT', 'ORG'), ('Sanjay Raut', 'PERSON'), ('Shinde', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,क्या अमेरिका ईरान को समझौते के बदले में 300 अरब डॉलर देगा?,Will America give Iran $300 billion in exchange for the agreement?,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('$300 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बढ़ती उम्र में भी फ़िट बने रहने के लिए करें ये एक्सरसाइज़,Do these exercises to remain fit even as you age.,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,जी-7 में मोदी-ट्रंप की मुलाक़ात: क्या हुआ और इसे कैसे देखा जा रहा है?,Modi-Trump meeting in G-7: What happened and how is it being viewed?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_18,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका-ईरान एग्रीमेंट पर लगी मुहर, जानिए समझौते में क्या-क्या है?","America-Iran agreement sealed, know what is there in the agreement?",0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Líder do governo Lula no Senado é alvo de nova fase de operação contra Banco Master: o que se sabe,Leader of the Lula government in the Senate is the target of a new phase of operation against Banco Master: what is known,0.0,neutral,"[('Senate', 'ORG'), ('Banco Master', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Ex-escritor de discursos demitido, lobista e linha dura: quem são os aliados de Flávio Bolsonaro no governo Trump","Fired former speechwriter, lobbyist and hardliner: who are Flávio Bolsonaro's allies in the Trump administration",0.0,neutral,"[(""Flávio Bolsonaro's"", 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que você precisa saber sobre o acordo de 14 pontos entre EUA e Irã para tentar acabar com a guerra,What you need to know about the 14-point agreement between the US and Iran to try to end the war,-1.0,negative,"[('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Acordo EUA e Irã: o que pode dar errado e as perguntas ainda em aberto, segundo especialistas","US and Iran agreement: what could go wrong and the questions still open, according to experts",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Entre farpas e diplomacia: o saldo de Lula no G7 com Trump, UE e Ucrânia","Between barbs and diplomacy: Lula's balance in the G7 with Trump, EU and Ukraine",0.0,neutral,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Não se meta nas eleições do Brasil', diz Lula após fala de Trump citando Bolsonaros","'Don't interfere in Brazil's elections', says Lula after Trump's speech quoting Bolsonaros",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump diz que Brasil é 'politicamente perigoso' e que 'querem prender Bolsonaro Jr.',Trump says that Brazil is 'politically dangerous' and that 'they want to arrest Bolsonaro Jr.',0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), (""Bolsonaro Jr.'"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Ganhei viagem com tudo pago para a Copa do Mundo e tive o visto negado','I won an all-expenses-paid trip to the World Cup and was denied a visa',0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Quem era Daveigh Chase, voz de 'Lilo & Stitch' e atriz de 'O Chamado' morta aos 35 anos","Who was Daveigh Chase, voice of 'Lilo & Stitch' and actress of 'The Ring' dead at 35",0.0,neutral,"[('Daveigh Chase', 'PERSON'), (""Lilo & Stitch'"", 'ORG'), (""'The Ring'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('35', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O país vizinho do Brasil onde empregados passaram a trabalhar menos e a ganhar mais (com desemprego na mínima histórica),The country neighboring Brazil where employees started to work less and earn more (with unemployment at a historic low),0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Москва подверглась одной из крупнейших за последнее время атак дронов. Что известно,Moscow has suffered one of the largest drone attacks in recent memory. What is known,-1.0,negative,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский назвал массированную атаку на Москву ответом на удар по Киево-Печерской лавре","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky called a massive attack on Moscow a response to the attack on the Kiev Pechersk Lavra",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Соглашение между США и Ираном не решает главные вопросы, в том числе о $300 млрд на восстановление Ирана","The agreement between the United States and Iran does not resolve key issues, including the $300 billion for the reconstruction of Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('$300 billion', 'MONEY'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,США и Иран подписали предварительное соглашение о мире. Что сказано в 14 пунктах документа,The US and Iran have signed a preliminary peace agreement. What is said in the 14 points of the document,1.0,positive,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Убийцу c Гилго-бич» суд в штате Нью-Йорк приговорил к пожизненному сроку за убийство семи женщин,The Gilgo Beach Killer was sentenced to life in prison in New York State for the murder of seven women.,-1.0,negative,"[('The Gilgo Beach Killer', 'ORG'), ('New York State', 'GPE'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Петербурге по делу об убийстве задержан бизнесмен Трабер. Он знаком с Путиным с 90-х,"In St. Petersburg, businessman Traber was detained in connection with the murder. He has known Putin since the 90s",0.0,neutral,"[('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('Traber', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('90s', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Давал столько поводов, за которые сейчас убивают людей». Чем известен художник Скрепецкий, застреленный в Польше","“He gave so many reasons for which people are being killed now.” What is the artist Skrepetsky, who was shot dead in Poland, famous for?",-1.0,negative,"[('Skrepetsky', 'PERSON'), ('Poland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Три причины, по которым суда пока не идут через Ормузский пролив",Three reasons why ships are not yet sailing through the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Принц Гарри и Меган привезут детей в Британию впервые за четыре года,Prince Harry and Meghan will bring their children to Britain for the first time in four years,0.0,neutral,"[('Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Meghan', 'PERSON'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('four years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Тегеран называет соглашение с США своей победой. Все ли иранцы считают так же?,Tehran calls the agreement with the US a victory. Do all Iranians feel the same way?,1.0,positive,"[('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカとイラン、14項目の合意文書に署名　何が書かれているのか,America and Iran sign 14-point agreement; what's in it?,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 米・イランの合意、重要な争点は未解決のまま……復興資金など難題も,"[Commentary] U.S.-Iran agreement, important issues remain unresolved... Reconstruction funding and other difficult issues remain",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエル、レバノンをまた空爆　トランプ氏が批判するなか,Israel launches another airstrike on Lebanon amid Trump criticism,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,子宮頸がんの死亡数、HPVワクチン接種した若い女性でゼロに　英研究,Cervical cancer deaths cut to zero for young women vaccinated with HPV vaccine: British study,-1.0,negative,"[('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('HPV', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,小泉防衛相、防衛力強化は戦争の抑止に「極めて重要」　BBC単独インタビュー,"Defense Minister Koizumi says strengthening defense capabilities is ""extremely important"" to deter war - BBC exclusive interview",-1.0,negative,"[('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Koizumi', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,小泉防衛相のBBC単独インタビュー、安全保障政策や憲法9条改正について語る, 所要時間 1,14","Video, Defense Minister Koizumi's exclusive interview with BBC, talks about security policy and amendment to Article 9 of the Constitution, Duration 1,14",0.0,neutral,"[('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Koizumi', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Article 9 of the Constitution, Duration', 'LAW')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,トランプ氏、仏ヴェルサイユ宮殿で米・イラン合意に署名, 所要時間 0,33","Video, Trump signs US-Iran deal at Versailles, France, duration 0,33",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Versailles', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,BBCが550人を削減へ、5億ポンドの経費節減計画の第1段階,BBC to cut 550 jobs in first phase of £500m cost-cutting plan,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('550', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('500', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【検証】 スターマー英首相を標的にした放火、背後にロシア　BBC取材で判明,"[Verification] Russia is behind the arson that targeted British Prime Minister Starmer, revealed by BBC coverage",0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ハンガリー国会、憲法改正でオルバン氏の首相復帰を阻止　在任期間を8年に制限,"Hungarian parliament prevents Orbán from returning as prime minister by amending the constitution, limiting his term in office to eight years",0.0,neutral,"[('Hungarian', 'NORP'), ('Orbán', 'NORP'), ('eight years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Milio ya risasi yasikika katika uwanja wa ndege wa mji mkuu wa Niger","Directly, shots are heard in the airport of the capital of Niger",0.0,neutral,"[('Niger', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Enzi ya mizinga inafikia mwisho, Ukraine inataka kuirudisha vipi kwenye uwanja wa vita?","The era of tanks is coming to an end, how does Ukraine want to bring it back to the battlefield?",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mambo muhimu 14 waliyokubaliana Iran na Marekani,14 important things agreed between Iran and the United States,0.0,neutral,"[('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Tunahofia maisha yetu': Muda wa mwisho kwa wahamiaji kuondoka Afrika Kusini wakaribia,'We fear for our lives': Deadline for migrants to leave South Africa looms,0.0,neutral,"[('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: DRC chupuchupu wamchezeshe Ronaldo ndombolo ya solo, Ureno 1vs DRC 1","World Cup 2026: DRC almost played Ronaldo in a solo match, Portugal 1 vs DRC 1",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('Portugal 1', 'ORG'), ('1', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ratiba, msimamo na matokeo","World Cup 2026: Schedule, standings and results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za usajili: Man Utd na Spurs 'zatoana roho' kwa Summerville,Transfer rumours: Man Utd and Spurs 'will join forces' for Summerville,0.0,neutral,"[('Spurs', 'PERSON'), ('Summerville', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Sababu tatu zinazozuia meli kupita Hormuz licha ya makubaliano ya Marekani na Iran,Three reasons preventing ships from passing through Hormuz despite the agreement between the United States and Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini viongozi wa dini ya Kiislamu wanakamatwa Urusi?,Why are Islamic religious leaders arrested in Russia?,0.0,neutral,"[('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Utata wa $300 bilioni za Iran unavyoibua vita mpya Marekani,The $300 billion Iran dispute is sparking a new war in the US,-1.0,negative,"[('$300 billion', 'MONEY'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Hegseth slams NATO allies during roundtable meeting,Hegseth slams NATO allies during roundtable meeting,0.0,neutral,"[('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Taiwan hopes US arms sale package can be approved soon, president says","Taiwan hopes US arms sale package can be approved soon, president says",0.0,neutral,"[('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Top five ‘must-watch’ World Cup matches of the second group phase,Top five ‘must-watch’ World Cup matches of the second group phase,0.0,neutral,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Why do AI models struggle with online hate speech detection?,Why do AI models struggle with online hate speech detection?,0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ukraine hits Moscow refinery as Zelenskyy seeks Trump support to end war,Ukraine hits Moscow refinery as Zelenskyy seeks Trump support to end war,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskyy', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup Day 8: Mexico face South Korea as Golden Boot race heats up,World Cup Day 8: Mexico face South Korea as Golden Boot race heats up,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day', 'EVENT'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Golden Boot', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 111: Tehran warns US as 14-point plan takes effect,Iran war day 111: Tehran warns US as 14-point plan takes effect,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('111', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,From a meatball lunch to a hug: The normalisation of Sweden’s far right,From a meatball lunch to a hug: The normalisation of Sweden’s far right,0.0,neutral,"[('Sweden', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup: Diaz dazzles as Colombia beat newcomers Uzbekistan 3-1,World Cup: Diaz dazzles as Colombia beat newcomers Uzbekistan 3-1,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Trump’s MoU with Iran draws backlash from some Republicans,Trump’s MoU with Iran draws backlash from some Republicans,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump’s MoU', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Republicans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Delhi HC reserves judgment on Telegram’s plea challenging temporary ban ahead of NEET retest,Delhi HC reserves judgment on Telegram’s plea challenging temporary ban ahead of NEET retest,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi HC', 'PERSON'), ('Telegram', 'ORG'), ('NEET', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Governor’s address passes off smoothly as first session of 17th T.N. Assembly begins,Governor’s address passes off smoothly as first session of 17th T.N. Assembly begins,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('17th', 'ORDINAL'), ('T.N. Assembly', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Education Minister Dharmendra Pradhan holds  review meeting for NEET re-examination preparations,Education Minister Dharmendra Pradhan holds  review meeting for NEET re-examination preparations,0.0,neutral,"[('Education', 'ORG'), ('Dharmendra Pradhan', 'PERSON'), ('NEET', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,ED arrests former AP Minister’s son in liquor transport scam probe,ED arrests former AP Minister’s son in liquor transport scam probe,0.0,neutral,"[('ED', 'ORG'), ('AP', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Banning Telegram will not stop paper leaks: Kejriwal,Banning Telegram will not stop paper leaks: Kejriwal,0.0,neutral,"[('Telegram', 'ORG'), ('Kejriwal', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Govt. ratifies 8.25% EPF interest rate for FY'26, to be credited this month","Govt. ratifies 8.25% EPF interest rate for FY'26, to be credited this month",0.0,neutral,"[('8.25%', 'PERCENT'), (""FY'26"", 'GPE'), ('this month', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Explained | The ‘kafir screenshot’ case in Kerala,Explained | The ‘kafir screenshot’ case in Kerala,0.0,neutral,"[('Kerala', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia LIVE: Iran says missile programme not part of talks with U.S.,West Asia LIVE: Iran says missile programme not part of talks with U.S.,0.0,neutral,"[('West Asia LIVE', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Bengal moves Supreme Court against early release of 1993 Bowbazar blast convict,West Bengal moves Supreme Court against early release of 1993 Bowbazar blast convict,0.0,neutral,"[('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('1993', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_18,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,How the world came to have its first trillionnaire in Elon Musk,How the world came to have its first trillionnaire in Elon Musk,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,What's in the US-Iran agreement?,What's in the US-Iran agreement?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Moscow hit by largest Ukrainian attack since start of Russia's full-scale war,Moscow hit by largest Ukrainian attack since start of Russia's full-scale war,-1.0,negative,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Suspected gang leader shot dead in flower bouquet ambush at airport,Suspected gang leader shot dead in flower bouquet ambush at airport,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Gunfire and explosions heard at Niger capital's airport,Gunfire and explosions heard at Niger capital's airport,0.0,neutral,"[(""Niger capital's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Japan ramping up defence is 'critical' to prevent war, Defence Minister Koizumi tells BBC","Japan ramping up defence is 'critical' to prevent war, Defence Minister Koizumi tells BBC",-1.0,negative,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Defence', 'ORG'), ('Koizumi', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Lawyer in high-profile Ugandan treason case charged with related offence,Lawyer in high-profile Ugandan treason case charged with related offence,0.0,neutral,"[('Ugandan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,First Russian shadow fleet vessel enters Channel since Smyrtos boarding,First Russian shadow fleet vessel enters Channel since Smyrtos boarding,0.0,neutral,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Channel', 'ORG'), ('Smyrtos', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Search for six-year-old Ebola patient after armed men storm DR Congo hospital,Search for six-year-old Ebola patient after armed men storm DR Congo hospital,0.0,neutral,"[('six-year-old', 'DATE'), ('DR Congo', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Serial killer who murdered eight women in Long Island town imprisoned for life,Serial killer who murdered eight women in Long Island town imprisoned for life,-1.0,negative,"[('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Long Island', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran Gets Major Economic Lifeline for Minimal Concessions in Initial Deal,Iran Gets Major Economic Lifeline for Minimal Concessions in Initial Deal,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Russian Film Director Who Chooses Moments to Challenge Putin,The Russian Film Director Who Chooses Moments to Challenge Putin,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Challenge Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine Strikes Moscow Refinery in Large-Scale Drone Attack,Ukraine Strikes Moscow Refinery in Large-Scale Drone Attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Large-Scale Drone Attack', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Taiwan’s President Says He Trusts Trump to Approve Arms Sales,Taiwan’s President Says He Trusts Trump to Approve Arms Sales,0.0,neutral,"[('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Are Your Ancestors Canadian? Here’s What to Know About Becoming a Citizen.,Are Your Ancestors Canadian? Here’s What to Know About Becoming a Citizen.,0.0,neutral,"[('Canadian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Why the By-Election in Makerfield Will Have Giant Consequences for the UK,Why the By-Election in Makerfield Will Have Giant Consequences for the UK,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Southeast Asia, Switching to Solar Offers Relief from Energy Crisis Caused by Iran War","In Southeast Asia, Switching to Solar Offers Relief from Energy Crisis Caused by Iran War",-1.0,negative,"[('Southeast Asia', 'LOC'), ('Solar Offers Relief', 'ORG'), ('Iran War', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Team Medic Recounts Iran’s ‘Stressful’ World Cup Debut in L.A.,Team Medic Recounts Iran’s ‘Stressful’ World Cup Debut in L.A.,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Debut', 'EVENT'), ('L.A.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Bahrain Revoked Their Citizenship, and Then Tried to Expel Them to Iran","Bahrain Revoked Their Citizenship, and Then Tried to Expel Them to Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('Expel Them', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_18,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Trump Angrily Defends Iran Deal and Reveals, Again, His Obsession With Obama","Trump Angrily Defends Iran Deal and Reveals, Again, His Obsession With Obama",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump Angrily Defends Iran', 'ORG')]"
