Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo el cambio radical de Trump en la política exterior de EE.UU. preocupa a Europa (y qué dice de sus intenciones en América Latina),How Trump's radical change in US foreign policy worries Europe (and what it says about his intentions in Latin America),-0.125,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Trump demanda a la BBC por US$5.000 millones por un reportaje en el que se editaron sus palabras,Trump sues BBC for $5 billion over report in which his words were edited,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('$5 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,4 claves que explican el contundente triunfo de Kast en Chile (y qué dicen de los desafíos que enfrenta),4 keys that explain Kast's resounding triumph in Chile (and what they say about the challenges it faces),0.0,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kast', 'ORG'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Quiénes eran los atacantes y otras 3 preguntas sobre el tiroteo que dejó 15 muertos en la playa Bondi Beach de Australia,Who were the attackers and 3 other questions about the shooting that left 15 dead on Bondi Beach in Australia,-0.10833333333333334,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bondi Beach', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Un héroe de la vida real"": quién es Ahmed al Ahmed, el hombre que frenó a uno de los atacantes en el tiroteo de Bondi Beach en Australia","""A real-life hero"": who is Ahmed al Ahmed, the man who stopped one of the attackers in the Bondi Beach shooting in Australia",0.0,"[('Ahmed al Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bondi Beach', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बांग्लादेश: हसनत अब्दुल्लाह ने पूर्वोत्तर राज्यों को लेकर दी चेतावनी, निशाने पर क्यों हैं सेवन सिस्टर्स","Bangladesh: Hasnat Abdullah warns about North-Eastern states, why are Seven Sisters on target?",0.0,"[('Hasnat Abdullah', 'PERSON'), ('North-Eastern', 'LOC'), ('Seven', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बोंडी बीच अटैक: 'साजिद अकरम भारतीय पासपोर्ट पर गए थे मनीला', फिलीपींस के अधिकारियों का दावा","Bondi Beach Attack: 'Sajid Akram had gone to Manila on Indian passport', claim Philippines officials",0.0,"[('Bondi Beach', 'PERSON'), ('Sajid Akram', 'PERSON'), ('Manila', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,गोवा नाइट क्लब हादसा: अभियुक्त लूथरा ब्रदर्स को भारत लाया गया","Live, Goa Night Club Incident: Accused Luthra Brothers brought to India",0.13636363636363635,"[('Luthra Brothers', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नीतीश कुमार का एक आयुष डॉक्टर का हिजाब खींचते हुए वीडियो वायरल,  जानिए पूरा मामला","Video of Nitish Kumar pulling the hijab of an AYUSH doctor goes viral, know the whole matter",0.2,"[('Nitish', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,सेविंग्स अकाउंट खाली कर लोग क्यों करा रहे हैं फ़िक्स्ड डिपॉज़िट?, अवधि 2,56","Video, Why are people opening fixed deposits by emptying their savings accounts?, Duration 2,56",0.1,[]
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"खाना खाने के फौरन बाद क्या आपको शौच जाना पड़ता है, कहीं यह बीमारी का संकेत तो नहीं?","Do you have to go to the toilet immediately after eating, is this a sign of illness?",-0.03333333333333333,[]
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पीएम नरेंद्र मोदी का जॉर्डन दौरा क्यों अहम है?,Why is PM Narendra Modi's visit to Jordan important?,0.4,"[(""Narendra Modi's"", 'PERSON'), ('Jordan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बहनों की शादी के लिए दो दोस्तों ने खोदा हीरा, सिर्फ़ 20 दिनों में किस्मत चमकने की कहानी","Two friends dug a diamond for their sisters' wedding, the story of their luck shining in just 20 days",0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('just 20 days', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,साजिद और नवीद अकरम: ऑस्ट्रेलिया के बोंडी बीच पर हमला करने वाले पिता-पुत्र के बारे में क्या पता है?,Sajid and Navid Akram: What is known about the father-son duo who attacked Australia's Bondi Beach?,0.0,"[('Navid Akram', 'PERSON'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Bondi Beach', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,4 fatores-chave que explicam a retumbante vitória de Kast no Chile,4 key factors that explain Kast's resounding victory in Chile,0.0,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kast', 'LOC'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Presidente eleito do Chile, Kast já chamou Lula de corrupto e elogiou Bolsonaro","President-elect of Chile, Kast has already called Lula corrupt and praised Bolsonaro",-0.5,"[('Chile', 'GPE'), ('Lula', 'PRODUCT'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump processa BBC por acusação de difamação em documentário,Trump sues BBC for defamation in documentary,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Menina de 10 anos, 2 rabinos, sobrevivente do Holocausto: quem eram as vítimas de atirador na Austrália","10-year-old girl, 2 rabbis, Holocaust survivor: who were the shooting victims in Australia",0.0,"[('10-year-old', 'DATE'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que Putin quer para acabar com a guerra na Ucrânia,What Putin wants to end the war in Ukraine,0.2,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Só bolsonarismo entendeu importância das eleições para o Congresso', diz cientista política","'Only Bolsonarism understood the importance of elections for Congress', says political scientist",0.0,"[('Bolsonarism', 'PERSON'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A nova gripe que gerou alerta da OMS para 2026,The new flu that generated a WHO warning for 2026,0.13636363636363635,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Maduro diz que Trump quer petróleo da Venezuela: isso é verdade?,Maduro says Trump wants oil from Venezuela: is that true?,0.275,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem é Ahmed al Ahmed, o 'herói' que tomou arma de atirador na Austrália","Who is Ahmed al Ahmed, the 'hero' who took a sniper's gun in Australia",0.0,"[('Ahmed al Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Переговоры о мире в Украине: главные вопросы, на которые нет ответа",Peace negotiations in Ukraine: the main unanswered questions,0.033333333333333326,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Пока у нас разные позиции». Уиткофф и Кушнер обсудили с Зеленским гарантии безопасности, но вопрос территорий не решен","“We have different positions for now.” Witkoff and Kushner discussed security guarantees with Zelensky, but the issue of territories has not been resolved",0.0,"[('Witkoff', 'PERSON'), ('Kushner', 'ORG'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: США, Киев и Европа на переговорах в Берлине разработали гарантии безопасности по примеру 5-й статьи устава НАТО","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: The USA, Kyiv and Europe at negotiations in Berlin developed security guarantees following the example of Article 5 of the NATO Charter",0.05,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Berlin', 'GPE'), ('Article 5 of the NATO Charter', 'LAW')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп подал иск к Би-би-си на пять миллиардов долларов,Trump sues BBC for $5 billion,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('$5 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Стрельба на пляже в Сиднее во время празднования Хануки: власти говорят о связях стрелявших с ИГИЛ,Shooting on a beach in Sydney during Hanukkah celebrations: authorities say the shooters have links to ISIS,0.0,"[('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('Hanukkah', 'ORG'), ('ISIS', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Украина заявила о поражении подлодки «Варшавянка» подводными дронами. Россия признала факт атаки, но заявила, что ущерба не было",Ukraine announced the defeat of the Varshavyanka submarine by underwater drones. Russia acknowledged the attack but said there was no damage,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Varshavyanka', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Десятилетняя девочка и два раввина: что известно об убитых на пляже в Сиднее во время Хануки,A ten-year-old girl and two rabbis: what is known about those killed on the beach in Sydney during Hanukkah,-0.2,"[('ten-year-old', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('Hanukkah', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Смерть режиссера Роба Райнера и его жены: по подозрению в убийстве арестован их сын Ник,Death of director Rob Reiner and his wife: their son Nick was arrested on suspicion of murder,0.0,"[('Rob Reiner', 'PERSON'), ('Nick', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Разлив мазута в Черном море: как произошла крупнейшая российская экологическая катастрофа XXI века,Fuel oil spill in the Black Sea: how the largest Russian environmental disaster of the 21st century happened,-0.05555555555555555,"[('the Black Sea', 'LOC'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the 21st century', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Редкое выступление главы британской разведки MI6: Россия экспортирует хаос и будет продолжать, пока Путина не остановят",Rare speech by the head of British intelligence MI6: Russia is exporting chaos and will continue until Putin is stopped,0.15,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、ウクライナに「強力な」安全の保証を提供する意向示す　領土問題は解決せず,"US indicates intention to provide 'strong' security guarantees to Ukraine, territorial issue remains unresolved",0.4333333333333333,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ米大統領、BBCを提訴　番組での演説編集めぐり,US President Trump sues BBC over editing of speech on TV show,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「我々は平和と戦争のはざまにいる」　英MI6新長官が初の公開演説, 所要時間 0,51","Video, ``We are between peace and war'', the new British MI6 chief gives his first public speech, duration 0,51",0.09659090909090909,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロブ・ライナー監督夫妻死亡、殺害容疑で息子が逮捕される,"Director Rob Reiner and his wife die, son arrested on suspicion of murder",0.0,"[('Rob Reiner', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,2023年ノーベル平和賞の人権活動家モハンマディ氏、「暴力的な拘束」で病院に搬送　家族が公表,"Mohammadi, the human rights activist who won the 2023 Nobel Peace Prize, was taken to hospital after being ""violently restrained,"" his family says",-0.4,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英MI6新長官がロシアの脅威に言及、初の公開演説で技術導入に意欲,"Britain's new MI6 chief mentions Russian threat, expresses desire to introduce technology in first public speech",0.09659090909090909,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イギリスと韓国、自由貿易協定を更新,UK and South Korea renew free trade agreement,0.4,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,豪ビーチの銃撃犯から銃を奪った「英雄」、果物店主のアフメド・アル・アフメド氏と判明　自分も腕と手を撃たれ,"The 'hero' who stole the gun from the Australian beach gunman has been identified as fruit shop owner Ahmed Al Ahmed, who was also shot in the arm and hand.",0.0,"[('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Ahmed Al Ahmed', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港メディアの大物に有罪判決、国安法違反で「外国勢力と結託」と,Hong Kong media mogul found guilty of ``colluding with foreign forces'' in violation of national security law,-0.3125,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mzozo wa DRC: M23 wadai kujiondoa Uvira baada ya kuudhibiti wiki jana,DRC conflict: M23 demands to withdraw from Uvira after controlling it last week,0.0,"[('M23', 'GPE'), ('Uvira', 'GPE'), ('last week', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump aishitaki BBC kwa kuhariri hotuba yake katika makala ya  Panorama","Directly, Trump sued the BBC for editing his speech in the Panorama article",0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Panorama', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mzozo wa DRC: M23 yasema mamia ya wanajeshi wa Burundi wamekamatwa katika shambulio DRC,DRC conflict: M23 says hundreds of Burundian soldiers have been arrested in an attack in DRC,0.0,"[('M23', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Burundian', 'NORP'), ('DRC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Mimi ni Muislamu lakini ninaadhimisha Shabbat','I am Muslim but I observe Shabbat',0.0,"[('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Shabbat', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi mkakati mpya wa usalama wa Trump unavyobadili sera ya kigeni ya Marekani,How Trump's new security strategy is changing US foreign policy,0.005681818181818177,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kutekwa kwa Uvira na mustakabali wa utawala wa Évariste Ndayishimiye Burundi - Uchambuzi,The capture of Uvira and the future of the administration of Évariste Ndayishimiye Burundi - Analysis,0.0,"[('Uvira', 'GPE'), ('Évariste Ndayishimiye Burundi - Analysis', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"'Shujaa' aliyepigana na mshambuliaji ufukwe wa Bondi amefahamika kwa jina, Ahmed al Ahmed",The 'hero' who fought the Bondi beach bomber has been identified as Ahmed al Ahmed,0.0,"[('Bondi', 'GPE'), ('Ahmed al Ahmed', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumanne: Man City itafanikiwa kumsajili Guehi msimu ujao?,European Football Rumors Tuesday: Will Man City manage to sign Guehi next season?,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Will Man City', 'PERSON'), ('next season', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kipi kitamzuia Putin asiendelee na vita Ukraine?,What will stop Putin from continuing the war in Ukraine?,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_16,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Walikaribia kuwa Wamarekani - ila Trump akafuta sherehe zao za uraia,They almost became Americans - but Trump canceled their citizenship ceremony,0.0,"[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
