Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El inicio de una nueva era en Gibraltar con la eliminación de los controles fronterizos entre España y Reino Unido,The beginning of a new era in Gibraltar with the elimination of border controls between Spain and the United Kingdom,0.0,neutral,"[('Gibraltar', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Eran de cartón"": el colapso de más de 100 viviendas sociales turcas en el terremoto de Venezuela que pone bajo escrutinio el programa estrella de Chávez","""They were made of cardboard"": the collapse of more than 100 Turkish social housing in the Venezuela earthquake that puts Chávez's star program under scrutiny",0.0,neutral,"[('more than 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Turkish', 'NORP'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Chávez', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Matan a tiros a ciudadano colombiano durante una operación de ICE en Maine,Colombian citizen shot dead during ICE operation in Maine,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('Maine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Por qué la infertilidad masculina sigue sin recibir la atención necesaria: ""Se presupone que el problema es de la mujer""","Why male infertility continues to receive the necessary attention: ""It is assumed that the problem belongs to the woman""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Trump restablece el bloqueo a los puertos iraníes e impone un recargo del 20% a la carga que transita por el estrecho de Ormuz,Trump reestablishes the blockade of Iranian ports and imposes a 20% surcharge on cargo transiting the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('20%', 'PERCENT'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere por eutanasia Catalina Giraldo, la mujer de 30 años que emprendió una  batalla legal en Colombia para acceder al suicidio médicamente asistido","Catalina Giraldo, the 30-year-old woman who launched a legal battle in Colombia to access medically assisted suicide, dies from euthanasia",0.0,neutral,"[('Catalina Giraldo', 'PERSON'), ('30-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Los comentarios del expresidente español Mariano Rajoy sobre la selección francesa que provocaron críticas por ""racismo"" antes de las semifinales del Mundial","Former Spanish president Mariano Rajoy's comments about the French team that sparked criticism for ""racism"" before the World Cup semifinals",0.0,neutral,"[('Spanish', 'NORP'), (""Mariano Rajoy's"", 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las personas que se mudan de Occidente a Rusia en busca de valores tradicionales (y la realidad que encuentran),People who move from the West to Russia in search of traditional values ​​(and the reality they find),0.0,neutral,"[('West', 'LOC'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Cumplieron su sueño adoptando a un bebé, pero luego les dijeron que este podía ser víctima de trata de personas","They fulfilled their dream by adopting a baby, but then they were told that he could be a victim of human trafficking",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El auge de la femosfera: las mujeres que renuncian al romance y buscan hombres de ""alto valor""",The Rise of the Phemosphere: Women Giving Up Romance and Seeking 'High Value' Men,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ट्रंप ने कहा- मोजतबा ख़ामेनेई 90 फ़ीसदी ख़त्म हो चुके हैं, ईरान के नए सर्वोच्च नेता को लेकर अटकलें तेज़","Trump said - Mojtaba Khamenei is 90 percent dead, speculations intensify about the new supreme leader of Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Mojtaba Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('90 percent', 'PERCENT'), ('supreme', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,असम सरकार ने बीते दो सालों में कितने लोगों को बांग्लादेश वापस भेजा","Live, how many people did the Assam government send back to Bangladesh in the last two years?",0.0,neutral,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('the last two years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,गौतम गंभीर से क्यों हैं पूर्व क्रिकेटर और एक्सपर्ट ख़फ़ा?,Why are former cricketers and experts angry with Gautam Gambhir?,0.0,neutral,"[('Gautam Gambhir', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सोनम वांगचुक का वज़न 8.5 किलो घटा, कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी अब क्या करने जा रही है?","Sonam Wangchuk lost 8.5 kg weight, what is the cockroach Janata Party going to do now?",0.0,neutral,"[('Sonam Wangchuk', 'ORG'), ('8.5 kg', 'QUANTITY'), ('Janata Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,राम मंदिर के बाद अब बद्रीनाथ धाम में चढ़ावा चोरी का मामला,"After Ram temple, now case of theft of offerings in Badrinath Dham",0.0,neutral,"[('Badrinath Dham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"होर्मुज़ से गुज़रने वाले जहाज़ों पर क्या टोल लगा सकते हैं डोनाल्ड ट्रंप, क्या कहता है क़ानून?","What toll can Donald Trump impose on ships passing through Hormuz, what does the law say?",0.0,neutral,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'दुख दर्द की कहानी सुनाने बैठो तो कहते हैं पंजाब बदनाम हो रहा'- ब्लॉग,"'If you sit to narrate the story of pain and sorrow, they say that Punjab is getting infamous'- Blog",0.0,neutral,"[('Punjab', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,संतोष दुबे से अयोध्या राम मंदिर चढ़ावा चोरी मामले में एसआईटी ने क्या की पूछताछ,What did SIT interrogate Santosh Dubey in the Ayodhya Ram temple offering theft case?,0.0,neutral,"[('SIT', 'ORG'), ('Santosh Dubey', 'PERSON'), ('Ayodhya Ram', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,142 साल में पहली बार हुआ ऐसा और भारतीय टीम ने रच डाला इतिहास,This happened for the first time in 142 years and the Indian team created history.,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('142 years', 'DATE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वैभव सूर्यवंशी ने बताया विंबलडन फ़ाइनल देखने के लिए किसने उन्हें कपड़े दिलाए?,Vaibhav Suryavanshi told who gave him clothes to watch Wimbledon final?,0.0,neutral,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Wimbledon', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A medida de Trump que pode facilitar acesso do CV e do PCC a fuzis americanos,Trump's measure that could facilitate CV and PCC access to American rifles,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON'), ('PCC', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Morre por eutanásia Catalina Giraldo, de 30 anos, que travou batalha judicial na Colômbia para ter acesso ao suicídio assistido por médicos","Catalina Giraldo, 30, who fought a legal battle in Colombia to have access to doctor-assisted suicide, dies by euthanasia",0.0,neutral,"[('Catalina Giraldo', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'DATE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Café: da bebida 'do diabo' aos best-sellers de autoajuda cristã,Coffee: from 'the devil's' drink to Christian self-help bestsellers,0.0,neutral,"[('Christian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Irã quer transformar conflito militar com EUA em guerra econômica, diz especialista","Iran wants to turn military conflict with US into economic war, says expert",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump diz que EUA vão controlar o Estreito de Ormuz e cobrar 20% sobre carga de navios; Lula compara medida com 'pirataria',Trump says the US will control the Strait of Hormuz and charge 20% on ship cargo; Lula compares measure with 'piracy',0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('20%', 'PERCENT')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Os argumentos de Alexandre de Moraes para suspender visitas de Flávio a Bolsonaro por 90 dias,Alexandre de Moraes' arguments to suspend Flávio's visits to Bolsonaro for 90 days,0.0,neutral,"[(""Alexandre de Moraes'"", 'PERSON'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('90 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O chinês formado em universidade de elite que é acusado de ser o 'rei do fentanil' do México,The Chinese graduate from an elite university who is accused of being Mexico's 'fentanyl king',0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Você consegue identificar um rosto feito com inteligência artificial? Faça o teste e descubra,Can you identify a face made with artificial intelligence? Take the test and find out,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A ascensão da 'femosfera': as mulheres que renunciam ao romance e buscam homens de 'alto valor',The rise of the 'femosphere': women who forgo romance and seek 'high-value' men,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A explosão de processos de brasileiros contra bets para receber prêmio: 'dinheiro não sai',The explosion of lawsuits by Brazilians against bets to receive a prize: 'money doesn't come out',0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"США и Иран третий день обмениваются ударами, Вашингтон возобновляет морскую блокаду","The US and Iran exchange blows for the third day, Washington resumes naval blockade",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the third day', 'DATE'), ('Washington', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: беспилотники ВСУ атаковали два НПЗ и танкеры в Азовском море, российские ракеты ударили по Киеву","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Ukrainian Armed Forces drones attacked two oil refineries and tankers in the Sea of ​​Azov, Russian missiles hit Kyiv",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Sea of ​​Azov', 'LOC'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Пытаются расправиться со мной внутри России»: что сказала Собчак о публикации якобы ее переписки,“They are trying to deal with me inside Russia”: what Sobchak said about the publication of her alleged correspondence,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Sobchak', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Британии за связь с добровольческим корпусом ГРУ будут грозить длительные тюремные сроки,"In Britain, links with the GRU volunteer corps will result in long prison sentences.",0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('GRU', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трамп заявил, что возобновляет морскую блокаду Ирана и будет взимать 20% от стоимости грузов в Ормузском проливе",Trump said he was renewing the naval blockade of Iran and would charge 20% of the value of cargo in the Strait of Hormuz.,1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('20%', 'PERCENT'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,У Энди Бернема не будет конкурентов за пост лидера лейбористов. Он станет премьером Британии через неделю,Andy Burnham will have no competition for the post of Labor leader. He will become Prime Minister of Britain in a week,0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('Labor', 'ORG'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Круговорот министров»? Зачем Зеленский меняет премьера и кто может возглавить кабмин. Текстовая версия подкаста «Что это было?»,"""Circle of ministers""? Why is Zelensky changing the prime minister and who can head the cabinet. Text version of the podcast “What was that?”",0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Топ-звезды, заклятые соперники. Чего ждать от полуфиналов чемпионата мира по футболу?","Top stars, sworn rivals. What to expect from the World Cup semi-finals?",0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Делом об убийстве Энн Уидеком после появления новых улик занялась контртеррористическая полиция,Counter-terrorism police take over Ann Widecombe's murder case after new evidence emerges,-1.0,negative,"[(""Ann Widecombe's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Бориса Надеждина обвинили в демонстрации «экстремистской символики» — фото Навального. Это еще один повод не допустить его до выборов в Госдуму,Boris Nadezhdin was accused of demonstrating “extremist symbols” - photo of Navalny. This is another reason to prevent him from participating in the State Duma elections.,0.0,neutral,"[('Boris Nadezhdin', 'PERSON'), ('Navalny', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、対イラン海上封鎖再開と海峡通る貨物の対価20％徴収を表明　攻撃の応酬続く,Trump announces resumption of naval blockade against Iran and levy of 20% remuneration for cargo passing through the Strait; exchange of attacks continues,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('20%', 'PERCENT'), ('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米移民当局、北東部メイン州で男性を射殺　取締作戦中と説明,"US immigration authorities shoot dead man in northeastern Maine, saying it was part of an enforcement operation",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Maine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏とIRSの和解、無効と米地裁　2800億円超の基金設立や税務調査免除の付帯条項に影響か,The settlement between Trump and the IRS is invalidated and the U.S. district court decides whether it will affect the establishment of a fund of over 280 billion yen and the attached clauses for exemption from tax audits,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('IRS', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('over 280 billion yen', 'MONEY')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,「逃げ場がなかった」　タイ首都のバー火災、目撃者が惨状語る,``There was no escape'' Witness describes the tragedy of bar fire in Thailand's capital,0.0,neutral,"[('Thailand', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,俳優サム・ニールさん死去、「ジュラシック・パーク」「ピアノ・レッスン」など出演,"Actor Sam Neill, who appeared in ``Jurassic Park'' and ``The Piano Lesson,'' has passed away.",0.0,neutral,"[('Sam Neill', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 決定力、創造性、空中戦で優れているのは　ベスト4をデータ比較,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Data comparison of the best four who are superior in decisiveness, creativity, and aerial combat",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,パリ近郊の森で火事、空からも消火　馬は避難, 所要時間 0,39","Video, Fire in a forest near Paris, extinguished from the air, horses evacuated, Duration 0,39",0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,パリ郊外の森で山火事、放火の可能性もあると内相,"Forest fire in a forest on the outskirts of Paris, interior minister says there is a possibility of arson",0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,バングラデシュで豪雨と鉄砲水、51人死亡,Heavy rains and flash floods kill 51 people in Bangladesh,-1.0,negative,"[('51', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,タイ首都のバーで火災、少なくとも30人死亡　重体24人含む70人超負傷,"Fire at bar in Thailand's capital kills at least 30 people and injures over 70, including 24 in critical condition",-1.0,negative,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('at least 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('70', 'DATE'), ('24', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Iran yashambulia meli mbili za UAE huku Marekani ikiendeleza mashambulizi","Immediately, Iran attacks two UAE ships while the United States continues its attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('UAE', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Urusi inawaajiri watu wenye ushawishi kutoka nchi za Magharibi ili kuitangaza?",Is Russia hiring Western influencers to promote it?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi ugumba wa wanaume unavyopuuzwa,How male infertility is overlooked,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumanne: Villa waingia kwenye mbio za kumwania Pervis Estupiñán,European football rumors Tuesday: Villa enter the race for Pervis Estupiñán,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Villa', 'ORG'), ('Pervis Estupiñán', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kiongozi Mkuu wa Iran Mojtaba Khamenei yuko wapi?,Where is Iran's Supreme Leader Mojtaba Khamenei?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Supreme', 'ORG'), ('Mojtaba Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Sina ujasiri alio nao Lissu': Mke wa Lissu aelezea gharama ya mapambano ya kisiasa ya Tanzania kwa familia,'I don't have the courage that Lissu has': Lissu's wife explains the cost of Tanzania's political struggle to the family,0.0,neutral,"[('Lissu', 'PERSON'), ('Lissu', 'PERSON'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tutadhibiti Mlango bahari wa Hormuz-Trump,We will control the Strait of Hormuz-Trump,0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz-Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Rais Samia: Hakuna mtu aliye juu ya sheria,President Samia: No one is above the law,0.0,neutral,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Waziri wa zamani nchini Tanzania ashauri Lissu aachiwe huru,A former minister in Tanzania advises Lissu to be released,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Lissu', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wanaume wanaotumia majina ya ukoo wa mama zao nchini Kenya wanavyokabiliana na kejeli,Men who use their mothers' surnames in Kenya face ridicule,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"US bombs Iran again, Tehran strikes Gulf, tankers: What’s the latest?","US bombs Iran again, Tehran strikes Gulf, tankers: What’s the latest?",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Photos: Wildfires ravage historic forest near Paris,Photos: Wildfires ravage historic forest near Paris,0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"‘Country grows, we grow too’: 1 million migrants seek legal status in Spain","‘Country grows, we grow too’: 1 million migrants seek legal status in Spain",0.0,neutral,"[('1 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Who will win the 2026 FIFA World Cup? Here’s what AI predicts,Who will win the 2026 FIFA World Cup? Here’s what AI predicts,1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Bangkok bar fire death toll rises to 30 as police probe possible negligence,Bangkok bar fire death toll rises to 30 as police probe possible negligence,-1.0,negative,"[('Bangkok', 'GPE'), ('30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"With US-Iran trust broken again, can Pakistan bring them back to talks?","With US-Iran trust broken again, can Pakistan bring them back to talks?",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Why is India blocking film on a man who counted Punjab insurgency killings?,Why is India blocking film on a man who counted Punjab insurgency killings?,-1.0,negative,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Punjab', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Mexico’s Sheinbaum announces criminal charges request in US over ICE deaths,Mexico’s Sheinbaum announces criminal charges request in US over ICE deaths,-1.0,negative,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Sheinbaum', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Brazil court bars Bolsonaro’s son from visiting ex-president for 90 days,Brazil court bars Bolsonaro’s son from visiting ex-president for 90 days,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('90 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Oil prices hit 1-month high as US-Iran attacks dim Strait of Hormuz outlook,Oil prices hit 1-month high as US-Iran attacks dim Strait of Hormuz outlook,-1.0,negative,"[('1-month', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,What is the government’s defence on E20 fuel? | Explained,What is the government’s defence on E20 fuel? | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"India’s imports from China soar to $80 billion in first half of 2026, exports up 37%","India’s imports from China soar to $80 billion in first half of 2026, exports up 37%",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('$80 billion', 'MONEY'), ('first half of 2026', 'DATE'), ('37%', 'PERCENT')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,CJP protest Day 25:Wanghcuk’s health worsens; fast enters 17th day,CJP protest Day 25:Wanghcuk’s health worsens; fast enters 17th day,0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Day 25', 'DATE'), ('17th day', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,No more Chemburs: How can Indian cities ensure their trees do not ‘turn against’ their people,No more Chemburs: How can Indian cities ensure their trees do not ‘turn against’ their people,0.0,neutral,"[('Chemburs', 'NORP'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"CBSE sees ‘practical’ way out of three-language resource crunch through retirees, ‘suitable’ PGs","CBSE sees ‘practical’ way out of three-language resource crunch through retirees, ‘suitable’ PGs",0.0,neutral,"[('CBSE', 'ORG'), ('three-language', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia war LIVE: Lebanon and Israel hold talks in Rome amid renewed West Asia fighting,West Asia war LIVE: Lebanon and Israel hold talks in Rome amid renewed West Asia fighting,-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Rome', 'GPE'), ('West Asia', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Migrant worker from Bihar dies in furnace explosion at TN copper recycling unit,Migrant worker from Bihar dies in furnace explosion at TN copper recycling unit,0.0,neutral,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('TN', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Big Tech’s AI race comes at a steep environmental cost | Explained,Big Tech’s AI race comes at a steep environmental cost | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Big Tech’s', 'ORG'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The big blot on the beautiful game | On racism in football,The big blot on the beautiful game | On racism in football,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Unsafe practices: On the Vietnam boat accident,Unsafe practices: On the Vietnam boat accident,0.0,neutral,"[('Vietnam', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Bangkok fire investigation finds locked doors and flammable decor as deaths climb to 30,Bangkok fire investigation finds locked doors and flammable decor as deaths climb to 30,-1.0,negative,"[('Bangkok', 'GPE'), ('30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Australian police reveal unseen photos 25 years after British backpacker murder,Australian police reveal unseen photos 25 years after British backpacker murder,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP'), ('25 years', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Hungary parliament votes to remove president from office,Hungary parliament votes to remove president from office,0.0,neutral,"[('Hungary', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US judge voids Donald Trump's $1.8bn settlement with IRS that gave him immunity from tax audits,US judge voids Donald Trump's $1.8bn settlement with IRS that gave him immunity from tax audits,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), (""Donald Trump's"", 'PERSON'), ('1.8bn', 'MONEY'), ('IRS', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Colombian national killed by ICE agent during operation in Maine,Colombian national killed by ICE agent during operation in Maine,-1.0,negative,"[('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('Maine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Identity of Sydney daycare worker facing 329 child abuse offences revealed,Identity of Sydney daycare worker facing 329 child abuse offences revealed,0.0,neutral,"[('329', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Bison rams grandfather in Yellowstone Park, knocking him metres into the air","Bison rams grandfather in Yellowstone Park, knocking him metres into the air",0.0,neutral,"[('Bison', 'PERSON'), ('Yellowstone Park', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Health fears as frail Indian activist on hunger strike loses 8.2kg,Health fears as frail Indian activist on hunger strike loses 8.2kg,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('8.2kg', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US burrito giant Chipotle opening first outlet in Mexico,US burrito giant Chipotle opening first outlet in Mexico,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Chipotle', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Briton tells of surviving Spain wildfire in car as wife and friends died trying to run to safety,Briton tells of surviving Spain wildfire in car as wife and friends died trying to run to safety,0.0,neutral,"[('Briton', 'PERSON'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Lebanese Hold Fast to Their Land Despite Threat of Long Israeli Occupation,Lebanese Hold Fast to Their Land Despite Threat of Long Israeli Occupation,0.0,neutral,"[('Lebanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"U.S. Strikes Iran for 3rd Night, in Return to Open Conflict","U.S. Strikes Iran for 3rd Night, in Return to Open Conflict",-1.0,negative,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('3rd Night', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.K. to Change Law to Allow Deportation of ‘Grooming Gang’ Leader,U.K. to Change Law to Allow Deportation of ‘Grooming Gang’ Leader,0.0,neutral,"[('U.K.', 'GPE'), ('Change Law', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Japan Builds Intelligence Agency It Hasn’t Had Since World War II,Japan Builds Intelligence Agency It Hasn’t Had Since World War II,-1.0,negative,"[('Japan Builds Intelligence Agency', 'ORG'), ('World War II', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Next Phase in Ukraine’s War With Russia: The Battle for Minds,The Next Phase in Ukraine’s War With Russia: The Battle for Minds,-1.0,negative,"[('The Next Phase', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('The Battle for Minds', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Robot Army Remakes Ground Warfare in Ukraine,A Robot Army Remakes Ground Warfare in Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Ground Warfare', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Residents of Spanish Towns Caught in Fierce Blazes Recount Harrowing Escapes,Residents of Spanish Towns Caught in Fierce Blazes Recount Harrowing Escapes,1.0,positive,"[('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Netherlands Pushes to Make Manure a Hotter Product,The Netherlands Pushes to Make Manure a Hotter Product,0.0,neutral,"[('The Netherlands Pushes to Make Manure a Hotter Product', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Hard-Liners in Iran Want to Keep Fighting America,Hard-Liners in Iran Want to Keep Fighting America,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Keep Fighting America', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Trump Failed to Secure the Strait of Hormuz in His Iran Deal,How Trump Failed to Secure the Strait of Hormuz in His Iran Deal,-1.0,negative,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
