Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,De Cuba a Vietnam: los miles de extranjeros que han muerto combatiendo para Rusia en la guerra con Ucrania,From Cuba to Vietnam: the thousands of foreigners who have died fighting for Russia in the war with Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La FIFA abre una investigación contra Argentina por los incidentes tras la derrota en la final del Mundial 2026,FIFA opens an investigation against Argentina for the incidents after the defeat in the 2026 World Cup final,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,16 títulos en 5 años: por qué España es una fuerza tan dominante en el fútbol masculino y femenino,16 titles in 5 years: why Spain is such a dominant force in men's and women's football,0.0,neutral,"[('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('5 years', 'DATE'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Cadena perpetua para ""El Mayo"" Zambada: por qué esta condena cierra todo un capítulo en la historia del narco en México","Life sentence for ""El Mayo"" Zambada: why this sentence closes an entire chapter in the history of drug trafficking in Mexico",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cambié de trabajo 10 veces en 10 años para conseguir la carrera laboral que quería,I changed jobs 10 times in 10 years to get the career I wanted,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('10 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Condenan a cadena perpetua a ""El Mayo"" Zambada, exlíder del cartel de Sinaloa","""El Mayo"" Zambada, former leader of the Sinaloa cartel, is sentenced to life in prison",0.0,neutral,"[('El Mayo', 'ORG'), ('Sinaloa', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las imágenes de los multitudinarios festejos de los jugadores de España tras proclamarse campeones del Mundial 2026,The images of the massive celebrations of the Spanish players after becoming champions of the 2026 World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La historia de migración y éxito de las familias de Lamine Yamal y Nico Williams, dos de las jóvenes estrellas de la España campeona del mundo","The story of migration and success of the families of Lamine Yamal and Nico Williams, two of the young stars of world champion Spain",1.0,positive,"[('Lamine Yamal', 'PERSON'), ('Nico Williams', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El extraordinario nacimiento en Australia de cuatrillizas idénticas concebidas de forma natural,The extraordinary birth in Australia of identical quadruplets conceived naturally,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Análisis de la BBC: por qué el triunfo de España frente a Argentina fue una victoria para el fútbol,BBC analysis: why Spain's victory against Argentina was a victory for football,1.0,positive,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"राहुल गांधी समेत कांग्रेस सांसदों का प्रधानमंत्री आवास के बाहर धरना, पीएम मोदी ने नीट पर क्या कहा?","Congress MPs including Rahul Gandhi protest outside the Prime Minister's residence, what did PM Modi say on NEET?",0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('PM Modi', 'ORG'), ('NEET', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,असदुद्दीन ओवैसी ने स्टूडेंट्स के प्रदर्शन पर कार्रवाई की तुलना इन आंदोलनों से की","Live, Asaduddin Owaisi compared the action on students' protest with these movements",0.0,neutral,"[('Asaduddin Owaisi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अभिजीत दीपके ने सीजेपी समर्थकों से मांगी माफ़ी, बॉलीवुड से भी उठीं कई आवाज़ें","Abhijeet Deepke apologized to CJP supporters, many voices were raised from Bollywood too",0.0,neutral,"[('Abhijeet Deepke', 'PERSON'), ('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Bollywood', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सीजेपी और सरकार की ये चार बातें जो पैदा करती हैं कई कन्फ्यूजन,These four things about CJP and government which create a lot of confusion,0.0,neutral,"[('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,विदेशी मीडिया सीजेपी के संसद मार्च में जुटी भारी भीड़ को किस संकेत के रूप में देख रहा है?,What signal is the foreign media seeing in the huge crowd gathered in CJP's Parliament march?,0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Parliament', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सौर मंडल के बाहर पृथ्वी जैसे ग्रह पर पहली बार वायुमंडल मिलने के सबूत,Evidence of atmosphere found for the first time on an Earth-like planet outside the solar system,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सीजेपी के संसद मार्च में मीडिया के ख़िलाफ़ नाराज़गी को लेकर आपस में भिड़े पत्रकार,Journalists clash with each other during CJP's Parliament march over anger against media,0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Parliament', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,दिल्ली की सड़कों पर उतरे हज़ारों युवाओं ने कैसे बढ़ाई मोदी सरकार की मुश्किलें,How thousands of youth took to the streets of Delhi increased the problems of Modi government,0.0,neutral,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Modi', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,क्या डॉक्टरों की लापरवाही के कारण 10 साल के लड़के का लिंग आंशिक रूप से हटाना पड़ा?,Did a 10-year-old boy's penis have to be partially removed due to doctors' negligence?,0.0,neutral,"[('10-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"103 साल की महिला, जिसने ज़मीन के लिए लड़ी 32 साल की क़ानूनी लड़ाई","103 year old woman, who fought a legal battle for 32 years for the land",0.0,neutral,"[('103 year old', 'DATE'), ('32 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A epidemia de violência contra professores no Brasil: 'Fui ameaçada de morte pelo pai de um aluno de 6 anos',The epidemic of violence against teachers in Brazil: 'I was threatened with death by the father of a 6-year-old student',-1.0,negative,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('6-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Não haverá mais eleições aqui': o discurso de Daniel Ortega que fecha caminho para oposição na Nicarágua,'There will be no more elections here': Daniel Ortega's speech that closes the way for opposition in Nicaragua,0.0,neutral,"[(""Daniel Ortega's"", 'PERSON'), ('Nicaragua', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Os casos de racismo que mancharam a Copa: 'ele nunca desapareceu',The cases of racism that stained the World Cup: 'it never disappeared',0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump impõe tarifa de 50% sobre produtos do Canadá às vésperas de taxas entrarem em vigor contra o Brasil,Trump imposes 50% tariff on Canadian products on the eve of tariffs coming into force against Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('50%', 'PERCENT'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Tarifas de Trump não vão funcionar e fortalecerão Lula, diz Nobel de Economia","Trump's tariffs will not work and will strengthen Lula, says Nobel Prize in Economics",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como falar sobre pobreza e desigualdade com as crianças,How to talk about poverty and inequality with children,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Nico Williams: a trajetória do campeão mundial cujos pais cruzaram o Saara a pé atrás de um futuro melhor,Nico Williams: the trajectory of the world champion whose parents crossed the Sahara on foot in search of a better future,0.0,neutral,"[('Nico Williams', 'PERSON'), ('Sahara', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Houthis do Iêmen anunciam 'embargo marítimo' à Arábia Saudita em rota crucial do petróleo: 'Olho por olho',Yemen's Houthis announce 'sea embargo' on Saudi Arabia on crucial oil route: 'Tit for tat',0.0,neutral,"[('Yemen', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('Tit', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Análise: Por que triunfo da Espanha sobre a Argentina foi uma vitória para o futebol,Analysis: Why Spain's triumph over Argentina was a victory for football,1.0,positive,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como Kim Jong-un fez uma 'transformação milagrosa' da economia da Coreia do Norte e se fortaleceu: 'O regime está mais rico do que nunca',How Kim Jong-un made a 'miraculous transformation' of North Korea's economy and grew stronger: 'The regime is richer than ever',0.0,neutral,"[('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON'), (""North Korea's"", 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Иран и США десятую ночь подряд обмениваются ударами, Axios пишет о возможном возвращении к переговорам","Iran and the US exchange blows for the tenth night in a row, Axios writes about a possible return to negotiations",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the tenth night', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Россия ударила авиабомбами по жилому кварталу Запорожья, во Владимире дрон ВСУ попал в дом","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Russia hit a residential area of ​​Zaporozhye with air bombs; in Vladimir, a Ukrainian Armed Forces drone hit a house",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Vladimir', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Российский корабль «Неустрашимый» провел учения со стрельбой у берегов Великобритании,The Russian ship Neustrashimy conducted live-fire exercises off the coast of Great Britain,1.0,positive,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Neustrashimy', 'PERSON'), ('Great Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп ввел 50-процентную пошлину на ряд товаров из Канады,Trump imposed a 50% tariff on a number of goods from Canada,1.0,positive,"[('50%', 'PERCENT'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Премьер Венгрии предложил пост президента страны шахматистке Юдит Полгар. Она отказалась,The Prime Minister of Hungary offered the post of President of the country to chess player Judit Polgar. She refused,0.0,neutral,"[('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('Judit Polgar', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Хуситы объявили морскую блокаду Саудовской Аравии и угрожают закрыть Баб-эль-Мандебский пролив,The Houthis have declared a naval blockade of Saudi Arabia and are threatening to close the Bab al-Mandeb Strait,0.0,neutral,"[('Houthis', 'PERSON'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('the Bab al-Mandeb Strait', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Новый премьер-министр Великобритании Энди Бернем сформировал правительство. МИД возглавил Эд Милибэнд,The new British Prime Minister Andy Burnham has formed a government. Ed Miliband heads the Foreign Office,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('Ed Miliband', 'PERSON'), ('the Foreign Office', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Перспективы работы очень туманные». Могут ли продавцы Wildberries добиться компенсаций потерь из-за украинских ударов?,“The job prospects are very dim.” Can Wildberries sellers obtain compensation for losses due to Ukrainian strikes?,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Зачем Украина бьет по Wildberries? |  Видеоподкаст «Что это было?», Продолжительность 27,06","Video, Why is Ukraine hitting Wildberries? |  Video podcast “What was that?”, Duration 27.06",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('27.06', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Обвинение в убийстве политика Энн Уидеком предъявлено 28-летнему британцу,A 28-year-old British man has been charged with the murder of politician Anne Widecombe.,0.0,neutral,"[('28-year-old', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Anne Widecombe', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、10夜連続でイラン空爆　トランプ氏は米兵殺害への報復を警告,"US airstrikes Iran for 10 consecutive nights, Trump warns of retaliation for killing US soldiers",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('10 consecutive nights', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,バーナム新英首相が組閣、財務相にヒーリー前国務相　外相はミリバンド氏,"New British Prime Minister Burnham forms a cabinet, with former Secretary of State Healey as finance minister and Miliband as foreign minister",0.0,neutral,"[('New British', 'NORP'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('State Healey', 'ORG'), ('Miliband', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ米大統領、カナダに50％の追加関税,US President Trump imposes 50% tariff on Canada,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('50%', 'PERCENT'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イエメンのフーシ派、紅海でサウジアラビアに対する「海上封鎖」を発表,Yemen's Houthis announce 'maritime blockade' against Saudi Arabia in Red Sea,0.0,neutral,"[('Yemen', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('Red Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 優勝のスペイン代表、ファン200万人と王室が熱烈に歓迎, 所要時間 1,21","Video, [2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Champion Spain national team warmly welcomed by 2 million fans and the royal family, Duration 1,21",-1.0,negative,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), (""Men's Soccer World Cup]"", 'ORG'), ('Champion Spain', 'ORG'), ('2 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,なぜウクライナの徴兵担当者は自国で暴力に直面しているのか, 所要時間 1,05","Video, Why Ukrainian conscripts are facing violence in their country, Duration 1,05",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アフガニスタン東部で洪水、少なくとも20人死亡　100人以上が行方不明,Floods in eastern Afghanistan kill at least 20 people and leave over 100 missing,-1.0,negative,"[('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('at least 20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,NY中心部の米連邦庁舎前で放火、当局は「移民当局に反対」の陸軍退役軍人を拘束,Arson in front of US federal building in central New York; authorities arrest Army veteran for ``opposing immigration authorities'',0.0,neutral,"[('Arson', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Army', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,スターマー氏が辞任、バーナム氏が就任　約100秒で振り返るイギリスの首相交代, 所要時間 1,38","Video, Mr. Starmer resigns, Mr. Burnham takes office - A look back at the change of British prime minister in about 100 seconds, Duration 1,38",0.0,neutral,"[('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('about 100 seconds', 'TIME'), ('1,38', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナで徴兵担当者への暴力事件が増加　兵員不足と徴兵忌避の溝,Incidents of violence against military recruiters are on the rise in Ukraine; the gap between military shortage and draft evasion,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yafanya mashambulizi mapya dhidi ya Iran, Trump aonya kuhusu kulipiza kisasi kufuatia vifo vya wanajeshi","Live, the United States launches new attacks against Iran, Trump warns of retaliation following the deaths of soldiers",-0.5,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kambi ambayo wanajeshi wa Marekani wameuawa na mashambulizi ya Iran,The camp where American soldiers have been killed by Iranian attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mzozo wa Iran: Tunachojua kuhusu shambulio la Marekani dhidi ya Bandar Abbas,The Iran crisis: What we know about the US attack on Bandar Abbas,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Bandar Abbas', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tofauti ya viti vya ndege za kivita za Marekani na Urusi,The difference between the seats of American and Russian fighter jets,0.0,neutral,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Iran yakubali pendekezo la usitishaji mapigano la siku 10,Iran accepts a 10-day ceasefire proposal,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('10-day', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za soka Jumanne: Man Utd, Arsenal zamuwania Kone","Football rumors Tuesday: Man Utd, Arsenal in the race for Kone",0.0,neutral,"[('Tuesday', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Mshindi na timu zingine zinapata kiasi gani?,World Cup 2026: How much do the winner and other teams get?,1.0,positive,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Israel iko karibu kuanzisha kambi ya kijeshi huko Somaliland?",Is Israel about to establish a military base in Somaliland?,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Somaliland', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Urusi ina wasiwasi kuhusu jitihada za Uturuki za kudhibiti Bahari Nyeusi?",Is Russia concerned about Turkey's efforts to control the Black Sea?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('the Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_21,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Andy Burnham ateuliwa rasmi kuwa Waziri Mkuu wa Uingereza,Andy Burnham has been officially appointed as the Prime Minister of the United Kingdom,0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Philippine Foreign Secretary says ASEAN must work together,Philippine Foreign Secretary says ASEAN must work together,0.0,neutral,"[('Philippine', 'NORP'), ('ASEAN', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Philippine Foreign Secretary says ASEAN must work together,Philippine Foreign Secretary says ASEAN must work together,0.0,neutral,"[('Philippine', 'NORP'), ('ASEAN', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Hormuz tankers on fire, as US, Iran continue attacks: What’s the latest?","Hormuz tankers on fire, as US, Iran continue attacks: What’s the latest?",-1.0,negative,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Farage, Reform in ‘trouble’, as UK braces for crypto influence in politics","Farage, Reform in ‘trouble’, as UK braces for crypto influence in politics",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Australia trio return from injury for Bangladesh Tests,Australia trio return from injury for Bangladesh Tests,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Moment terrifying floodwaters sweep through Afghan village,Moment terrifying floodwaters sweep through Afghan village,0.0,neutral,"[('Afghan', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Lionel Messi thanks Argentina fans: ‘Wound will take time to heal’,Lionel Messi thanks Argentina fans: ‘Wound will take time to heal’,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Active in BDS’: Document reveals how Israel scrutinised global NGOs,‘Active in BDS’: Document reveals how Israel scrutinised global NGOs,0.0,neutral,"[('BDS', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘We just want to live’: Palestinians in Gaza react to Hamas election,‘We just want to live’: Palestinians in Gaza react to Hamas election,0.0,neutral,"[('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘We just want to live’: Palestinians in Gaza react to Hamas election,‘We just want to live’: Palestinians in Gaza react to Hamas election,0.0,neutral,"[('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,No decision to increase ethanol blending with petrol beyond 20%: Petroleum MoS,No decision to increase ethanol blending with petrol beyond 20%: Petroleum MoS,0.0,neutral,"[('20%', 'PERCENT'), ('Petroleum MoS', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Government took ‘strict action’ against NEET paper leakers: PM Modi,Government took ‘strict action’ against NEET paper leakers: PM Modi,0.0,neutral,"[('NEET', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"PM Modi must apologise, resign along with Shah: Rahul on police crackdown on CJP protest","PM Modi must apologise, resign along with Shah: Rahul on police crackdown on CJP protest",0.0,neutral,"[('Shah', 'PERSON'), ('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Supreme Court frees Kerala Waqf Board from State official ‘supervision’,Supreme Court frees Kerala Waqf Board from State official ‘supervision’,0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Kerala Waqf Board', 'ORG'), ('State', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,QDENGA: India’s first approved dengue vaccine,QDENGA: India’s first approved dengue vaccine,0.0,neutral,"[('QDENGA', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,TVK government’s first Budget to be presented on August 5 in Tamil Nadu,TVK government’s first Budget to be presented on August 5 in Tamil Nadu,0.0,neutral,"[('TVK', 'ORG'), ('Budget', 'ORG'), ('August 5', 'DATE'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Adult unmarried daughter can claim financial support for education from father under DV Act: Karnataka High Court,Adult unmarried daughter can claim financial support for education from father under DV Act: Karnataka High Court,0.0,neutral,"[('Karnataka High Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,How Spain smothered Argentina to conquer the World Cup,How Spain smothered Argentina to conquer the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Accommodating dissent: On the TVK government’s actions,Accommodating dissent: On the TVK government’s actions,0.0,neutral,"[('TVK', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Press and play: On the FIFA World Cup 2026,Press and play: On the FIFA World Cup 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump slaps 50% tariffs on Canada and Carney vows to 'intensify' trade talks,Trump slaps 50% tariffs on Canada and Carney vows to 'intensify' trade talks,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('50%', 'PERCENT'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Carney', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US launches fresh strikes on Iran, as Trump warns of retaliation for deaths of soldiers","US launches fresh strikes on Iran, as Trump warns of retaliation for deaths of soldiers",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Yemen's Houthis announce 'maritime embargo' on Saudi Arabia,Yemen's Houthis announce 'maritime embargo' on Saudi Arabia,0.0,neutral,"[('Yemen', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Tate brothers appear in US court for extradition proceedings,Tate brothers appear in US court for extradition proceedings,0.0,neutral,"[('Tate', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"'Anti-ICE' army veteran started fire outside Manhattan federal building, say officials","'Anti-ICE' army veteran started fire outside Manhattan federal building, say officials",0.0,neutral,"[('Manhattan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,At least 27 dead and 83 missing after passenger ferry capsizes off Guyana,At least 27 dead and 83 missing after passenger ferry capsizes off Guyana,0.0,neutral,"[('At least 27', 'CARDINAL'), ('83', 'CARDINAL'), ('Guyana', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Rare identical quadruplets born in Australia,Rare identical quadruplets born in Australia,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Notorious drug cartel leader Ismael Zambada sentenced to life in US prison,Notorious drug cartel leader Ismael Zambada sentenced to life in US prison,0.0,neutral,"[('Ismael Zambada', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ten killed as Russian attacks on merchant ships in Black Sea intensify,Ten killed as Russian attacks on merchant ships in Black Sea intensify,-1.0,negative,"[('Ten', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_21,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Boy, 13, dies during World Cup celebrations in Spain","Boy, 13, dies during World Cup celebrations in Spain",0.0,neutral,"[('13', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Houthis in Yemen Edge Closer to Entering U.S.-Iran War,Houthis in Yemen Edge Closer to Entering U.S.-Iran War,-1.0,negative,"[('Yemen', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Two Young Brothers and Their Search for Venezuela’s Dead,Two Young Brothers and Their Search for Venezuela’s Dead,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Young Brothers', 'ORG'), ('Their Search for Venezuela’s Dead', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"When Protesters Speak, Zelensky Listens, in the Ukrainian Tradition","When Protesters Speak, Zelensky Listens, in the Ukrainian Tradition",0.0,neutral,"[('Protesters Speak', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky Listens', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,New UK Prime Minister Burnham Promises Hope and Change. The Hurdles Are High.,New UK Prime Minister Burnham Promises Hope and Change. The Hurdles Are High.,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,UK’s New Prime Minister Burnham Orders Cut in Taxes on Electricity,UK’s New Prime Minister Burnham Orders Cut in Taxes on Electricity,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Burnham Orders Cut', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Flash Floods Kill at Least 23 in Afghanistan,Flash Floods Kill at Least 23 in Afghanistan,-1.0,negative,"[('Flash Floods Kill', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Australian Woman Gives Birth to ‘Miracle’ Identical Quadruplets,Australian Woman Gives Birth to ‘Miracle’ Identical Quadruplets,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Inside the Deadly U.S. Airstrike on a Shadow Fleet Tanker,Inside the Deadly U.S. Airstrike on a Shadow Fleet Tanker,0.0,neutral,"[('the Deadly U.S. Airstrike', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Inside Andy Burnham’s 1st Day as U.K. Prime Minister,Inside Andy Burnham’s 1st Day as U.K. Prime Minister,0.0,neutral,"[('Inside Andy Burnham’s', 'PERSON'), ('1st Day', 'DATE'), ('U.K.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_21,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Venezuela’s Rubble, a Search for the Family Pets","In Venezuela’s Rubble, a Search for the Family Pets",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
