Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Los padres se saltan comidas para que los niños tengan alimentos"": cómo la pobreza afecta a millones de personas en Reino Unido",'Parents skip meals so children have food': how poverty affects millions of people in the UK,0.0,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Dinamita dorada"": así fue la operación secreta para sacar de Venezuela a María Corina Machado, según el exmilitar que la dirigió","""Golden dynamite"": this was the secret operation to remove María Corina Machado from Venezuela, according to the former military man who directed it",-0.05000000000000001,"[('María Corina Machado', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,¿Quiere realmente EE.UU. apoderarse del petróleo de Venezuela como denuncia el gobierno de Maduro?,Does the US really want to seize Venezuela's oil as the Maduro government denounces?,0.2,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El gobierno de EE.UU. pone fin a programas de reunificación familiar para los ciudadanos de Colombia, Cuba, Ecuador, El Salvador, Guatemala, Haití y Honduras","The US government ends family reunification programs for citizens of Colombia, Cuba, Ecuador, El Salvador, Guatemala, Haiti and Honduras",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE'), ('El Salvador', 'GPE'), ('Guatemala', 'GPE'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('Honduras', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Difunden nuevas fotos de Epstein que muestran a Trump, Clinton y el expríncipe Andrés","New photos of Epstein released showing Trump, Clinton and former Prince Andrew",0.06818181818181818,"[('Epstein', 'PRODUCT'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Clinton', 'PERSON'), ('Prince Andrew', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"गर्मजोशी, हाथ मिलाना और लंबा इंतज़ार: शहबाज़ शरीफ़ और पुतिन के बीच बैठक में क्या हुआ?","Warmth, handshakes and long waits: What happened in the meeting between Shehbaz Sharif and Putin?",-0.05,"[('Shehbaz Sharif', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,मेसी को देखने पहुंचे फैंस ने कोलकाता के स्टेडियम में की तोड़फोड़, लगाए ये आरोप","Fans who came to watch Messi live, vandalized the stadium in Kolkata, made these allegations",0.13636363636363635,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मेसी के कोलकाता कार्यक्रम में बवाल, ममता बनर्जी ने क्या कहा","Chaos in Messi's Kolkata event, what did Mamata Banerjee say?",0.0,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वेनेज़ुएला को निशाना बना रहे ट्रंप, पर ख़ामोश क्यों हैं रूस और चीन","Trump is targeting Venezuela, but why are Russia and China silent?",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"कुछ लोगों को ज़्यादा ठंड लगती है कुछ को कम, ऐसा क्यों होता है","Some people feel more cold and some less, why does this happen?",-0.08888888888888886,[]
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ये 'भारतीय चप्पल' मिलेगी 85000 रुपये की, इटली की कंपनी ने किया लॉन्च","These 'Indian slippers' will be available for Rs 85000, launched by an Italian company",0.2,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('85000', 'DATE'), ('Italian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'हमारे चौधरी असलम तुम्हारे संजय दत्त से ज़्यादा हैंडसम थे', धुरंधर पर पाकिस्तान से ब्लॉग","'Our Chaudhary Aslam was more handsome than your Sanjay Dutt', blog from Pakistan on Dhurandhar",0.5,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Dhurandhar', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,केरल में अभिनेत्री के अपहरण और गैंगरेप मामले में छह लोगों को 20 साल की सज़ा,Six people sentenced to 20 years in the kidnapping and gangrape case of actress in Kerala,0.0,"[('Six', 'CARDINAL'), ('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Kerala', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"शिवराज पाटिल से जब कहा गया, 'पार्टी को बचाने के लिए आपको जाना होगा, कोई दूसरा रास्ता नहीं है'","When Shivraj Patil was told, 'To save the party you will have to go, there is no other way'",0.0625,"[('Shivraj Patil', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Governo Trump retira sanções contra Alexandre de Moraes e esposa pela Lei Magnitsky,Trump administration lifts sanctions against Alexandre de Moraes and his wife under the Magnitsky Act,0.0,"[('Alexandre de Moraes', 'PERSON'), ('the Magnitsky Act', 'LAW')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A reação de Eduardo Bolsonaro à retirada de sanções contra Moraes e esposa pela Lei Magnitsky,Eduardo Bolsonaro's reaction to the removal of sanctions against Moraes and his wife under the Magnitsky Law,0.0,"[(""Eduardo Bolsonaro's"", 'PERSON'), ('Moraes', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaristas falam de 'traição' e 'decepção' com Trump após retirada de Moraes das sanções da Lei Magnitsky,Bolsonarists speak of 'betrayal' and 'disappointment' with Trump after Moraes' withdrawal from Magnitsky Act sanctions,-0.6,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Moraes', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Pedido direto de Lula a Trump levou ao fim da Magnitsky contra Moraes na visão do Planalto,Lula's direct request to Trump led to the end of Magnitsky against Moraes in Planalto's view,0.1,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Magnitsky', 'PERSON'), ('Moraes', 'GPE'), ('Planalto', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Governo Trump chama PL da dosimetria de 'anistia' ao comentar retirada de sanções contra Moraes,Trump government calls dosimetry PL 'amnesty' when commenting on lifting sanctions against Moraes,0.0,"[(""PL '"", 'ORG'), ('Moraes', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A linha do tempo da crise envolvendo Alexandre de Moraes e o governo Trump,The timeline of the crisis involving Alexandre de Moraes and the Trump administration,0.0,"[('Alexandre de Moraes', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Moraes fora da Magnitsky: como ministro do STF se tornou tão poderoso,Moraes outside Magnitsky: how STF minister became so powerful,0.15,"[('Magnitsky', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como imprensa internacional noticiou retirada de sanções contra Moraes pela Lei Magnistky,As international press reported the removal of sanctions against Moraes under the Magnistky Law,0.0,"[('Moraes', 'GPE'), ('the Magnistky Law', 'LAW')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que é a Lei Global Magnitsky, que EUA usaram contra Alexandre de Moraes","What is the Global Magnitsky Act, which the US used against Alexandre de Moraes",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Alexandre de Moraes', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Европа прикрывает границы. Борьба с мигрантами набирает обороты перед решающим 2026 годом,Europe is closing its borders. The fight against migrants is gaining momentum ahead of the decisive year 2026,0.0,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the decisive year 2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский и Уиткофф в выходные обсудят в Берлине план окончания войны в Украине","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky and Witkoff will discuss a plan to end the war in Ukraine this weekend in Berlin",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Witkoff', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('this weekend', 'DATE'), ('Berlin', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Как заключенные выживают в самых жестоких тюрьмах Беларуси | Интервью Би-би-си, Продолжительность 21,10","Video, How prisoners survive in the most brutal prisons in Belarus | BBC Interview, Duration 21.10",-0.1875,"[('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('BBC Interview', 'ORG'), ('21.10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Демократы опубликовали еще несколько фото из архива Эпштейна. На них есть Трамп и другие знаменитости,Democrats published several more photos from Epstein's archive. They have Trump and other celebrities on them.,0.125,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Король Карл III рассказал об успехах своего лечения от рака. В будущем году интенсивность терапии снизится,King Charles III spoke about the success of his cancer treatment. Next year the intensity of therapy will decrease,0.15,"[('Charles III', 'PERSON'), ('Next year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Британии создали единую службу военной разведки. Это объясняется растущей угрозой со стороны России,A unified military intelligence service has been created in Britain. This is due to the growing threat from Russia,-0.1125,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Германия обвинила Россию в кибератаке и попытке вмешательства в выборы,Germany accused Russia of cyberattack and attempt to interfere in elections,0.0,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Герои войны и (не)захваченный Купянск. Рассылка «Контекст»,"War heroes and (not) captured Kupyansk. Newsletter ""Context""",0.0,"[('Kupyansk', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Зеленский приехал в Купянск, о взятии которого недавно доложили Путину. Киев говорит, что там окружены российские войска","Zelensky arrived in Kupyansk, the capture of which was recently reported to Putin. Kyiv says Russian troops are surrounded there",0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Kupyansk', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Венесуэла утверждает, что Трамп хочет завладеть ее нефтью. Так ли это на самом деле?",Venezuela claims Trump wants its oil. Is this really true?,0.275,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU、ロシア資産の無期限凍結で合意　対ウクライナ融資計画への活用を念頭,"EU agrees to indefinitely freeze Russian assets, with consideration for use in loan plans for Ukraine",0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,2023年ノーベル平和賞の人権活動家モハンマディ氏、イランで拘束　支持者が発表,"2023 Nobel Peace Prize winner human rights activist Mohammadi detained in Iran, supporters announce",0.0,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Mohammadi', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイとカンボジアが戦闘停止に合意とトランプ米大統領,"Thailand and Cambodia agree to cease fighting, US President Trump says",0.0,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米移民当局が再拘束のアブレゴ＝ガルシア氏、連邦地裁が釈放を命じ新たな拘束を禁止　政府は反発,"Abrego-Garcia, who was re-detained by US immigration authorities, is released by a federal judge and prohibited from being detained again; the government protests",0.0,"[('Abrego-Garcia', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告めぐる新写真を米民主党議員が公開　トランプ氏などさまざまな著名人の姿,"US Democratic Party member releases new photos of former defendant Epstein, featuring various celebrities including Trump",0.04545454545454545,"[('US Democratic Party', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,チャールズ英国王、がん治療順調と　新年から治療を軽減へ,King Charles' cancer treatment is going well; treatment will be reduced in the new year,0.13636363636363635,"[('the new year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インドネシアを襲ったサイクロンと洪水、オランウータンにも大きな被害か,"Cyclones and floods hit Indonesia, causing great damage to orangutans",0.8,"[('Cyclones', 'GPE'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,韓国大学入試の英語、異常なほど難しいと批判噴出　責任者が辞任,"The person in charge of the Korean university entrance exam, which is criticized for being unusually difficult in English, resigns.",-0.25,"[('Korean', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「自分が最も役立つ場所に身を置く」とノーベル平和賞のマチャド氏　BBC単独インタビュー, 所要時間 8,51","Video, ""Place yourself in the place where you can be most useful,"" says Nobel Peace Prize winner Machado in exclusive BBC interview, duration 8,51",0.4,"[('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Machado', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,EU yaunga mkono kuzuia fedha za Urusi bila kikomo kabla ya mpango wa mkopo kwa Ukraine","Directly, the EU supports the blocking of Russian funds without limit before the loan program for Ukraine",0.05,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumamosi:Palace wamtaka Johnson kutoka Spurs,Football rumors Saturday: Palace want Johnson from Spurs,0.0,"[('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Johnson', 'PERSON'), ('Spurs', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kombe la Mataifa ya Afrika 2025: Ratiba na nyakati za mechi 52 za ​​AFCON nchini Morocco,Africa Cup of Nations 2025: Schedule and times for the 52 AFCON matches in Morocco,0.0,"[('Africa Cup', 'EVENT'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('52', 'CARDINAL'), ('AFCON', 'ORG'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi Venezuela inavyotumia 'meli za mapepo' kukwepa vikwazo vya mafuta,How Venezuela uses 'ghost ships' to evade oil embargoes,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Wahamiaji wote wanapaswa kumlipa msafirishaji haramu... lakini wanawake wanalazimika kutoa huduma za ngono','All migrants have to pay the trafficker... but women are forced to provide sex services',-0.30000000000000004,[]
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi 10 zenye madeni makubwa zaidi Afrika,10 countries with the biggest debts in Africa,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wimbi la vifo vya wapinzani linavyoongezeka duniani,The wave of death of opponents is increasing in the world,0.0,[]
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mahakama ya Kenya imesitisha mpango wa msaada wa afya wa Marekani kutokana na masuala ya faragha,A Kenyan court has suspended the US health aid program due to privacy concerns,-0.125,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Bayern kutupa ndoano kwa Guehi Januari,European football rumours: Bayern to throw the hook for Guehi in January,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Guehi', 'PERSON'), ('January', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_13,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Waandishi bila mipaka: Israel bado inaongoza kusababisha vifo vya waandishi wa habari,Reporters Without Borders: Israel still leads in killing of journalists,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE')]"
