Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Las autoridades en Dinamarca nos quitaron a nuestros bebés tras una prueba de aptitud parental y ahora luchamos para recuperarlos""","""The authorities in Denmark took our babies from us after a parenting suitability test and now we are fighting to get them back""",0.0,"[('Denmark', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Varias aerolíneas internacionales cancelan sus vuelos a Venezuela tras alerta de la FAA sobre ""incremento de la actividad militar"" en ese país","Several international airlines cancel their flights to Venezuela after the FAA alert about ""increased military activity"" in that country",-0.03333333333333333,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('FAA', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Tatiana Schlossberg, nieta de John F. Kennedy, anuncia a los 35 años que tiene cáncer terminal","Tatiana Schlossberg, granddaughter of John F. Kennedy, announces at 35 that she has terminal cancer",0.0,"[('Tatiana Schlossberg', 'PERSON'), ('John F. Kennedy', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Australia: en qué consiste la prohibición del acceso a las redes sociales a los menores de 16 años y cómo la van a implementar,Australia: what is the prohibition of access to social networks for those under 16 years of age and how will they implement it?,0.03333333333333333,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('under 16 years of age', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La fascinante historia del pequeño pueblo europeo que creó el primer dólar y fue clave en el inicio de la era nuclear,The fascinating story of the small European town that created the first dollar and was key in the beginning of the nuclear age,0.13999999999999999,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"उत्तराखंड का वो गाँव, जहाँ इससे ज़्यादा सोने के गहने पहनने पर है पाबंदी","That village in Uttarakhand, where there is a ban on wearing gold jewelery more than this",0.5,"[('Uttarakhand', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,कैट क्या है और इसे देने वालों को कौन सी ग़लतियों से बचना ज़रूरी है,What is CAT and what mistakes should those giving it avoid?,0.0,"[('CAT', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,वीमेंस टी20 वर्ल्ड कप क्रिकेट फ़ॉर ब्लाइंड 2025 का ख़िताब जीतने पर भारतीय टीम को पीएम मोदी ने दी बधाई","Live, PM Modi congratulated the Indian team on winning the title of Women's T20 World Cup Cricket for Blind 2025.",0.04545454545454545,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), (""Women's T20 World Cup Cricket"", 'ORG'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सर्दियों में एड़ियां इतनी क्यों फटती हैं और इन्हें कैसे ठीक रखा जाए,Why do heels crack so much in winter and how to keep them healthy?,0.35,"[('winter', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जस्टिस सूर्यकान्त: भारत के नए चीफ़ जस्टिस के अहम फ़ैसले और विवाद,Justice Surya Kant: Important decisions and controversies of the new Chief Justice of India,0.2681818181818182,"[('Surya Kant', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दिल्ली में इंडिया गेट पर वायु प्रदूषण के ख़िलाफ़ प्रदर्शन को लेकर क्यों हो गया विवाद,Why was there controversy over the protest against air pollution at India Gate in Delhi?,0.0,"[('India Gate', 'FAC'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चंडीगढ़: नेहरू के सपनों के शहर का इतिहास क्या है,Chandigarh: What is the history of Nehru's dream city,0.0,"[('Nehru', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"विपक्ष ईवीएम में धांधली की बात कहता है, फिर चुनाव भी लड़ता है - प्रशांत किशोर","Opposition talks about rigging in EVMs, then also contests elections - Prashant Kishore",0.0,[]
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तेजस प्लेन क्रैश में मारे गए विंग कमांडर नमांश स्याल को पत्नी ने सलामी देकर दी अंतिम विदाई,"Wife salutes Wing Commander Namansh Syal, who died in Tejas plane crash, bids last farewell",0.0,"[('Namansh Syal', 'PERSON'), ('Tejas', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro diz que violou tornozeleira por 'paranoia' e 'alucinação' causadas por remédios e nega que quisesse fugir,Bolsonaro says he broke an ankle bracelet out of 'paranoia' and 'hallucinations' caused by medication and denies he wanted to escape,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro aguarda últimos recursos em semana decisiva para sua condenação,Bolsonaro awaits final appeals in decisive week for his conviction,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('decisive week', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Decisão de Moraes foi 'prudente', e Bolsonaro fica mais perto de cumprir pena na cadeia, analisam especialistas","Moraes' decision was 'prudent', and Bolsonaro is closer to serving time in jail, experts analyze",-0.1,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Vice da diplomacia dos EUA ataca Moraes e critica prisão de Bolsonaro: 'Provocativa e desnecessária',Deputy of US diplomacy attacks Moraes and criticizes Bolsonaro's arrest: 'Provocative and unnecessary',-0.225,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Moraes', 'GPE'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,COP30: os quatro pontos que definiram a conferência do clima em Belém,COP30: the four points that defined the climate conference in Belém,0.0,"[('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Belém', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como uso do celular pode arruinar seu relacionamento,How cell phone use can ruin your relationship,0.0,[]
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Nasci de um erro da clínica de fertilização e hoje tenho mais de 15 irmãos','I was born as a result of a mistake at the fertility clinic and today I have more than 15 siblings',0.5,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('more than 15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A fascinante história do alho (e quais são suas propriedades medicinais),The fascinating history of garlic (and what its medicinal properties are),0.7,[]
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O egípcio que espionou Israel por 17 anos,The Egyptian who spied on Israel for 17 years,0.0,"[('Egyptian', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('17 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Рубио покинул Женеву, заявив о значительном прогрессе в переговорах с Украиной. Главное",Rubio left Geneva announcing significant progress in negotiations with Ukraine. Main,0.18055555555555555,"[('Geneva', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Рубио заявил о «значительном прогрессе» на переговорах в Женеве; четверо погибших при атаке на Харьков","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: Rubio claims 'significant progress' at Geneva talks; four killed in the attack on Kharkov",0.0875,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Geneva', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kharkov', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Взлет «Грипена». Вслед за Украиной шведские боевые самолеты купила Колумбия и захотела Канада,"Takeoff of the Gripen. Following Ukraine, Colombia bought Swedish combat aircraft and Canada wanted them",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Swedish', 'NORP'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Начальник штаба «Хезболлы» убит в результате израильского удара по Бейруту,Hezbollah chief of staff killed in Israeli strike on Beirut,-0.2,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Beirut', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Из приюта для бездомных — к мировому признанию. Как профессор Иджеома Учегбу стала известной ученой,From a homeless shelter to global recognition. How Professor Ijeoma Uchegbu Became a Famous Scientist,0.25,"[('Ijeoma Uchegbu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Женеве обсуждают мирный план США по Украине. Что известно,The US peace plan for Ukraine is being discussed in Geneva. What is known,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Geneva', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В результате наводнений во Вьетнаме погибли по меньшей мере 90 человек,Floods in Vietnam kill at least 90 people,-0.3,"[('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('at least 90', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,COP30 в тупике: на саммите ООН по климату не удалось договориться об отказе от ископаемого топлива,COP30 deadlock: UN climate summit fails to agree on fossil fuel divestment,-0.5,"[('UN', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Англию хотят вернуть диких кошек. Но некоторые боятся, что они будут спариваться с домашними",They want to return wild cats to England. But some are afraid that they will mate with domestic ones,-0.16666666666666666,"[('England', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как украинских подростков вербуют через Telegram для диверсий против своей страны,How Ukrainian teenagers are recruited via Telegram for sabotage against their country,0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Telegram', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナ和平交渉で「和平の枠組み更新」と米・ウが共同声明,U.S. and U.S. jointly announce ``renewal of peace framework'' during Ukraine peace negotiations,0.0,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,COP30、化石燃料削減について新合意を確保できず,COP30 fails to secure new agreement on fossil fuel reduction,0.012121212121212125,[]
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヴェトナムの洪水による死者、少なくとも90人に　12人が行方不明,"At least 90 people killed in Vietnam floods, 12 missing",-0.2333333333333333,"[('At least 90', 'CARDINAL'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、レバノン首都ベイルートを攻撃　ヒズボラ軍事部門トップを殺害と発表,"Israel attacks Lebanese capital Beirut, kills Hezbollah military chief",-0.1,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanese', 'NORP'), ('Beirut', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナ出身力士の安青錦が初優勝、来日から3年,"Ukrainian sumo wrestler Yasuonishiki wins his first championship, three years after coming to Japan.",0.275,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Yasuonishiki', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('three years', 'DATE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ナイジェリアのキリスト教系学校で生徒・教師300人以上誘拐　生徒50人が脱出,Over 300 students and teachers kidnapped at Christian school in Nigeria; 50 students escape,0.0,"[('Over 300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Christian', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('50', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ブラジルのボルソナロ前大統領、自宅軟禁中に足首の監視装置壊し身柄拘束　「薬の影響」と主張,"Former Brazilian President Bolsonaro broke ankle monitoring device while under house arrest and was detained, claiming it was 'effects of drugs'",-0.025,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ウクライナ和平案は「最終提案」ではないと発言,Trump says Ukraine peace plan is not 'final proposal',0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、アメリカの支援失う危険あるとウクライナ国民に演説　ホワイトハウスの和平案めぐり,Zelenskiy speaks to Ukrainians about risk of losing US support over White House peace plan,0.0,"[('Ukrainians', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Kwanini vuguvugu la Gen Z si la Tanzania peke yake?,Protests in Tanzania: Why is the Gen Z movement not unique to Tanzania?,-0.1875,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,'Heko kwa 'hatua kubwa' iliyopigwa katika mazungumzo ya amani ya Ukraine' - Marekani","Live,'Heko for 'big step' taken in Ukraine peace talks' - USA",0.06818181818181818,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Choo hiki sawa na bodaboda 10,000 au nyumba 300 za kisasa","This toilet is equivalent to 10,000 bodabodas or 300 modern houses",0.08333333333333334,"[('10,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('300', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Mabosi' wa BBC kuhojiwa bungeni,BBC 'bosses' to be questioned in parliament,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nani wa kuizuia Arsenal msimu huu?,Who will stop Arsenal this season?,0.0,"[('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('this season', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watoto 50 waliotekwa nyara Nigeria wafanikiwa kutoroka watekaji,50 kidnapped children in Nigeria manage to escape their captors,0.0,"[('50', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Arsenal, Chelsea zamgombania Murillo","European football rumours: Arsenal, Chelsea fight for Murillo",0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('Murillo', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Serikali ya Tanzania yavikosoa vyombo vya habari vya kimataifa,The Tanzanian government criticizes the international media,0.0,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Ingekuwa bora kama wangeniua','It would be better if they killed me',0.15,[]
2025_11_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Sababu za 'bingwa kibonde' Liverpool kuchapwa kila siku,The reasons for the 'basket champion' Liverpool to be beaten every day,0.0,"[('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('every day', 'DATE')]"
