Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Al Aqsa: el temor de los musulmanes ante los planes de los nacionalistas israelíes para uno de los lugares más sagrados del Islam en Jerusalén,Al Aqsa: Muslims' fear of Israeli nationalists' plans for one of Islam's holiest sites in Jerusalem,0.0,neutral,"[('Al Aqsa', 'PERSON'), ('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Islam', 'ORG'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,40 muertos por ahogamiento en Francia: qué es el domo de calor que está causando temperaturas extremas en Europa,40 dead from drowning in France: what is the heat dome that is causing extreme temperatures in Europe,0.0,neutral,"[('40', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las 4 demandas judiciales en EE.UU. que pueden cambiar cómo operan las redes sociales,The 4 lawsuits in the US that can change how social networks operate,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Cristiano Ronaldo, Messi, Modric... Qué dice la ciencia de las estrellas del Mundial que desafían los límites de la longevidad","Cristiano Ronaldo, Messi, Modric... What science says about World Cup stars who challenge the limits of longevity",0.0,neutral,"[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Modric', 'ORG'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La espectacular imagen captada por un telescopio que muestra 60 millones de estrellas a la vez en la Vía Láctea,The spectacular image captured by a telescope that shows 60 million stars at the same time in the Milky Way,0.0,neutral,"[('60 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Milky Way', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué cambia para Colombia con la cercanía que Trump mantiene con De la Espriella tras las tensiones con Petro,What changes for Colombia with the closeness that Trump maintains with De la Espriella after the tensions with Petro,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('De la Espriella', 'ORG'), ('Petro', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Hermanas de esperma"": descubrimos que teníamos el mismo padre donante después de haber cumplido 20 años","""Sperm sisters"": we discovered we had the same donor father after we turned 20",0.0,neutral,"[('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El gigante tecnológico Oracle despide a 21.000 empleados en su apuesta por la IA,"Tech giant Oracle lays off 21,000 employees in its commitment to AI",0.0,neutral,"[('Oracle', 'PERSON'), ('21,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Una comisión de investigación de la ONU dice que Israel está cometiendo genocidio en Gaza al atacar deliberadamente a niños,UN commission of inquiry says Israel is committing genocide in Gaza by deliberately targeting children,0.0,neutral,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La historia de Alejandro Ojeda Carbajal, el fotógrafo mexicano que inmortalizó la ""mano de Dios"" de Maradona hace 40 años","The story of Alejandro Ojeda Carbajal, the Mexican photographer who immortalized Maradona's ""hand of God"" 40 years ago",0.0,neutral,"[('Alejandro Ojeda Carbajal', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Maradona', 'PERSON'), ('40 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,उषा वेंस ने पति जेडी वेंस के सामने ख़ुद के हिन्दू होने पर क्या कहा जिस पर छिड़ी बहस,"What did Usha Vance say to her husband JD Vance about being a Hindu, which sparked a debate",0.0,neutral,"[('Usha Vance', 'PERSON'), ('JD Vance', 'PERSON'), ('Hindu', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,कोलकाता के तारातला में निर्माणाधीन गोदाम ढहा, कई लोगों के फंसे होने की आशंका","Live, warehouse under construction collapsed in Taratala, Kolkata, many people feared trapped",-1.0,negative,"[('Taratala', 'GPE'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भगवंत मान का कथित वीडियो मामला: फ़र्ज़ी फॉरेंसिक रिपोर्ट तैयार करने के आरोप में दो लोग हिरासत में, जानें पूरा मामला","Bhagwant Mann's alleged video case: Two people detained for preparing fake forensic report, know the whole matter",0.0,neutral,"[('Mann', 'PERSON'), ('Two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पुणे की युवती पर मंगेतर की हत्या करने का आरोप, साथी भी गिरफ़्तार, पुलिस ने क्या बताया","Pune girl accused of killing her fiance, partner also arrested, what did the police tell",-1.0,negative,"[('Pune', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बिहार में भरत तिवारी का 'एनकाउंटर', गाँव वालों का आक्रोश और सवालों के घेरे में पुलिस","Bharat Tiwari's 'encounter' in Bihar, villagers angry and police under scanner",-1.0,negative,"[('Bharat', 'NORP'), ('Tiwari', 'PERSON'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,टीएमसी में टूट के बीच महुआ मोइत्रा ने क्यों की शुभेंदु अधिकारी की तारीफ़- ख़ास इंटरव्यू,Why did Mahua Moitra praise Shubhendu Adhikari amid the split in TMC - Special Interview,0.0,neutral,"[('Mahua Moitra', 'PERSON'), ('Shubhendu Adhikari', 'PERSON'), ('TMC - Special Interview', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,कुणाल शाह: बिना मैनेजमेंट और इंजीनियरिंग की डिग्री के कैसे बने व्हाट्सऐप के ग्लोबल हेड,Kunal Shah: How to become global head of WhatsApp without management and engineering degree,0.0,neutral,"[('WhatsApp', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"फ़ीफ़ा वर्ल्ड कप: 'मैं वापस आ गया हूं', दो गोल करने के बाद रोनाल्डो का करारा जवाब","FIFA World Cup: 'I am back', Ronaldo's befitting reply after scoring two goals",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,महिला टी-20 वर्ल्ड कप: भारत ऐसे पहुँच सकता है सेमीफ़ाइनल में,Women's T20 World Cup: This is how India can reach the semi-finals,0.0,neutral,"[(""Women's T20 World Cup"", 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,होर्मुज़ स्ट्रेट को अब कौन कंट्रोल कर रहा है?,Who controls the Strait of Hormuz now?,0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Mãe denuncia ameaça a filho de 3 anos em escola militar no RS: 'Chora com vontade, senão vou te dar um tiro'","Mother reports threat to 3-year-old son at military school in RS: 'Cry hard, otherwise I'll shoot you'",0.0,neutral,"[('3-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como é a bola mais antiga do mundo —  que viajou até Miami para Brasil x Escócia,What the oldest ball in the world looks like — it traveled to Miami for Brazil x Scotland,0.0,neutral,"[('Miami', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Festa Junina: a origem da celebração pagã que virou religiosa e 'caipira' no Brasil,Festa Junina: the origin of the pagan celebration that became religious and 'hillbilly' in Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('Festa Junina', 'PERSON'), ('pagan', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Charles Miller: quem foi o 'pai do futebol brasileiro' com sangue escocês,Charles Miller: who was the 'father of Brazilian football' with Scottish blood,0.0,neutral,"[('Charles Miller', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Scottish', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Resolução inédita aprovada pelo Congresso dos EUA aumenta pressão sobre Trump no conflito com Irã; o que acontece agora,Unprecedented resolution approved by the US Congress increases pressure on Trump in the conflict with Iran; what happens now,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,40 mortos por afogamento na França: o que é o 'domo de calor' que está causando temperaturas extremas na Europa,40 dead from drowning in France: what is the 'heat dome' that is causing extreme temperatures in Europe,0.0,neutral,"[('40', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Quem foi São João, o profeta que teria batizado Jesus","Who was Saint John, the prophet who baptized Jesus",0.0,neutral,"[('Saint John', 'PERSON'), ('Jesus', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil ou Escócia? O guia brasileiro que comanda a torcida em Glasgow com coração dividido e coxinha de haggis,Brazil or Scotland? The Brazilian guide who commands the crowd in Glasgow with a divided heart and haggis drumstick,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Glasgow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem o Brasil pode enfrentar no mata-mata da Copa do Mundo? Os cenários de cada resultado,Who can Brazil face in the World Cup knockout stages? The scenarios for each outcome,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O movimento católico ultraconservador que desafia o papa e cresce no Brasil com missa em latim e padre de costas,The ultraconservative Catholic movement that defies the pope and grows in Brazil with Mass in Latin and a priest with his back,0.0,neutral,"[('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Latin', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Как-то так вышло, что штурмовики нужнее». Как российские студенты идут в беспилотные войска и погибают",“Somehow it turned out that stormtroopers were more needed.” How Russian students join unmanned troops and die,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: еще три региона России ввели ограничения на продажу бензина; Севастополь после атаки дронов остался без света","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: three more regions of Russia have introduced restrictions on the sale of gasoline; Sevastopol was left without electricity after a drone attack",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Sevastopol', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,ВСУ ударили по энергетике Крыма: Севастополь и другие города остались без света. Что известно,The Ukrainian Armed Forces hit the Crimean energy sector: Sevastopol and other cities were left without electricity. What is known,0.0,neutral,"[('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Crimean', 'NORP'), ('Sevastopol', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Зеленский требует убрать из Беларуси «ретрансляторы» для дронов, Москва заявляет об «агрессивных» угрозах. О какой технике идет речь?","Zelensky demands the removal of “relay stations” for drones from Belarus, Moscow declares “aggressive” threats. What technology are we talking about?",0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Суд в Техасе приговорил восемь активистов «Антифа» к крупным срокам за нападение на иммиграционный центр. Лидер группы получил 100 лет тюрьмы,A Texas court has sentenced eight Antifa activists to large prison sentences for attacking an immigration center. The leader of the group received 100 years in prison,-1.0,negative,"[('Texas', 'GPE'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Antifa', 'ORG'), ('100 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,После скандала с «Белым орлом» Зеленский не поедет в Польшу на конференцию по восстановлению Украины,"After the White Eagle scandal, Zelensky will not go to Poland for a conference on the restoration of Ukraine",0.0,neutral,"[('the White Eagle', 'ORG'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Как 100 румынских больниц перешли на ручки и бумагу, чтобы противостоять кибератаке национального масштаба",How 100 Romanian hospitals switched to pens and paper to combat a national cyberattack,-1.0,negative,"[('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Romanian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Прогноз — выше 40°C. Во многих странах Европы объявлен красный уровень опасности из-за жары,The forecast is above 40°C. Many European countries have declared a red alert due to the heat.,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Гонка за «Золотой бутсой»: кто победит в исторической битве бомбардиров на ЧМ-2026?,Race for the Golden Boot: who will win the historic battle of goalscorers at the 2026 World Cup?,1.0,positive,"[('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Три года мятежа Пригожина. Что стало с его империей? | Видеоподкаст «Что это было?», Продолжительность 28,09","Video, Three years of Prigozhin's rebellion. What happened to his empire? | Video podcast “What was that?”, Duration 28.09",0.0,neutral,"[('Three years', 'DATE'), ('Prigozhin', 'ORG'), ('28.09', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエル、レバノン南部で2人殺害　停戦後で初の死者,"Israel kills two people in southern Lebanon, first death since ceasefire",-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,国連、ホルムズ海峡で足止めの船員を退避させると　米国務長官は通行料設定に対し警告,"UN to evacuate sailors stranded in the Strait of Hormuz, US Secretary of State warns against setting tolls",-1.0,negative,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('the Strait of', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,スターマー英首相、バーナム氏と会談　「秩序のとれた」権力移行を模索するなか,"British Prime Minister Starmer meets with Burnham as they seek an ""orderly"" transition of power",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,国連調査委、イスラエルがパレスチナの子どもを意図的に標的にしたと報告　新たにジェノサイドなど認定,UN Commission of Inquiry reports that Israel intentionally targeted Palestinian children; newly recognized as genocide,0.0,neutral,"[('UN Commission of Inquiry', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イラン、試合2日前からの米入国が認められる　第2戦後には平和願う手書きメモ残す,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Iran will be allowed to enter the US two days before the match, leaving a handwritten note wishing for peace after the second match",1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('two days', 'DATE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米上院、対イラン戦争停止の決議案を初可決　両院そろってトランプ政権を批判,U.S. Senate passes resolution to end war against Iran for the first time; both chambers criticize Trump administration,-1.0,negative,"[('U.S. Senate', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,青い塗装がはがれ、水は緑色に……米リンカーン記念堂の反射池の改修でトラブル, 所要時間 1,46","Video, Blue paint peels off, water turns green... Troubles occur during renovation of reflection pond at the Lincoln Memorial, Duration: 1,46",0.0,neutral,"[('the Lincoln Memorial', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 バーナム氏、数週間後にも次期英首相になる可能性が濃厚　スターマー氏辞任で,[Commentary] There is a strong possibility that Mr. Burnham will become the next British Prime Minister in a few weeks due to Mr. Starmer's resignation.,0.0,neutral,"[('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('a few weeks', 'DATE'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ミャンマー軍、6カ月間で民間人700人超を殺害　国連報告,"Myanmar military kills over 700 civilians in 6 months, UN report",-1.0,negative,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE'), ('700', 'CARDINAL'), ('6 months', 'DATE'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、対イラン石油制裁を一時停止　核査察受け入れに同意したと主張するもイランは否定,"US suspends oil sanctions against Iran, claims it has agreed to nuclear inspections, but Iran denies",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Trump alikosoa Bunge la Marekani kwa kusitisha hatua za kijeshi dhidi ya Iran","Directly, Trump criticized the US Congress for suspending military actions against Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Maoni: Je, Muungano wa Zanzibar na Tanganyika una matatizo?",Opinion: Does the Union of Zanzibar and Tanganyika have problems?,0.0,neutral,"[('the Union of Zanzibar', 'ORG'), ('Tanganyika', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Waridi wa BBC: Niliacha shule kidato cha pili, niwe mfanyabiashara mkubwa","BBC Rose: I left school in second form, to become a big businessman",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Nimerudi' - Ronaldo awajibu wakosoaji baada ya kuvunja rekodi,'I'm back' - Ronaldo responds to critics after breaking records,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Serikali ya Tanzania kutaka kukopa BoT kumeibua mjadala?,Why does the Tanzanian government want to borrow BoT raised a debate?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('BoT', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Bayern Munich kumzuia Olise kupitia donge nono,Football rumors in Europe: Bayern Munich to stop Olise through a fat bump,0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mapumziko ya kunywa maji Kombe la Dunia: Nani wanaonufaika na nani wanaopoteza?,World Cup water breaks: Who benefits and who loses?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Israeli iliokolewa na silaha za Marekani','Israel was saved by American weapons',0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Mbio za taji la mfungaji bora duniani - nani ataibuka kidedea?,World Cup 2026: The race for the world's top goalscorer title - who will come out on top?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_24,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wanawake wanaonufaika na utalii kupitia urithi wa utamaduni wao Zanzibar,Women who benefit from tourism through their cultural heritage in Zanzibar,0.0,neutral,"[('Zanzibar', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Four Gaza aid flotilla activists released from Libya detention,Four Gaza aid flotilla activists released from Libya detention,0.0,neutral,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Libya', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israeli soldiers ‘celebrate’ inside displaced Lebanese family’s home,Israeli soldiers ‘celebrate’ inside displaced Lebanese family’s home,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup: Top 10 takeaways from the second round of the group stage,World Cup: Top 10 takeaways from the second round of the group stage,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,North Korea commissions largest-ever warship,North Korea commissions largest-ever warship,-1.0,negative,"[('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ukraine’s recovery to be deliberated in Poland amid Kyiv-Warsaw spat,Ukraine’s recovery to be deliberated in Poland amid Kyiv-Warsaw spat,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv-Warsaw', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Mamdani-backed candidates sweep New York City Democratic primaries,Mamdani-backed candidates sweep New York City Democratic primaries,0.0,neutral,"[('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York City Democratic', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Power outage in France as Europe bakes in record heat,Power outage in France as Europe bakes in record heat,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 117: Nuclear inspections dispute as US Senate curbs war powers,Iran war day 117: Nuclear inspections dispute as US Senate curbs war powers,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('117', 'CARDINAL'), ('US Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Living between fears’: Diabetes and survival in besieged Gaza,‘Living between fears’: Diabetes and survival in besieged Gaza,0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 117: Nuclear inspections dispute as US Senate curbs war powers,Iran war day 117: Nuclear inspections dispute as US Senate curbs war powers,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('117', 'CARDINAL'), ('US Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Maharashtra RTI rules amendments trigger criticism,Maharashtra RTI rules amendments trigger criticism,0.0,neutral,"[('Maharashtra RTI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Pune trekker murder: CCTV clue, a hoodie in 33°C lead police to killers","Pune trekker murder: CCTV clue, a hoodie in 33°C lead police to killers",-1.0,negative,"[('Pune', 'PRODUCT'), ('CCTV', 'ORG'), ('33', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,BJP wants two-thirds majority in Lok Sabha as its 'real target' is to end reservation: Congress,BJP wants two-thirds majority in Lok Sabha as its 'real target' is to end reservation: Congress,0.0,neutral,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), ('two-thirds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lok Sabha', 'PERSON'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Several trapped after warehouse shed collapses at Taratala in Kolkata,Several trapped after warehouse shed collapses at Taratala in Kolkata,-1.0,negative,"[('Taratala', 'GPE'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Explained: Why did Delhi High Court quash charges against NewsClick?,Explained: Why did Delhi High Court quash charges against NewsClick?,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi High Court', 'PERSON'), ('NewsClick', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Iran says deal to end West Asia war 'declaration of U.S. defeat' | LIVE,Iran says deal to end West Asia war 'declaration of U.S. defeat' | LIVE,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Calcutta High Court refuses urgent hearing in cases relating to Trinamool leader Abhishek Banerjee,Calcutta High Court refuses urgent hearing in cases relating to Trinamool leader Abhishek Banerjee,0.0,neutral,"[('Calcutta High Court', 'ORG'), ('Trinamool', 'ORG'), ('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,BJP in tricky spot in Thiruvananthapuram Corporation as 20 councillors asked to retake oath,BJP in tricky spot in Thiruvananthapuram Corporation as 20 councillors asked to retake oath,0.0,neutral,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Thiruvananthapuram Corporation', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The strange link between AI hallucination and creativity,The strange link between AI hallucination and creativity,0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Evident distress: On a war, Index of Eight Core Industries data, indicators","Evident distress: On a war, Index of Eight Core Industries data, indicators",-1.0,negative,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Core Industries', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,France braces for another day of sweltering heat as Europe heatwave spreads,France braces for another day of sweltering heat as Europe heatwave spreads,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('another day', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Congress passes war powers measure for first time, breaking with Trump over Iran","Congress passes war powers measure for first time, breaking with Trump over Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"UN says it will evacuate sailors stranded in Strait of Hormuz, as Rubio warns against tolls","UN says it will evacuate sailors stranded in Strait of Hormuz, as Rubio warns against tolls",-1.0,negative,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Strait of', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('Rubio', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Clean sweep for Mamdani-backed candidates in New York's Democratic primary,Clean sweep for Mamdani-backed candidates in New York's Democratic primary,0.0,neutral,"[('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), (""New York's"", 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ukraine strikes knock out power in key city in Russian-occupied Crimea,Ukraine strikes knock out power in key city in Russian-occupied Crimea,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Crimea', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,France confirms first Ebola case,France confirms first Ebola case,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,French woman allegedly held captive by husband for 12 years rescued in Pakistan,French woman allegedly held captive by husband for 12 years rescued in Pakistan,0.0,neutral,"[('French', 'NORP'), ('12 years', 'DATE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Sydney woman wakes from induced coma more than a week after shark attack,Sydney woman wakes from induced coma more than a week after shark attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Sydney', 'GPE'), ('more than a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Eight sentenced to 450 years in prison over anti-ICE riot where officer was shot,Eight sentenced to 450 years in prison over anti-ICE riot where officer was shot,0.0,neutral,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('450 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_24,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Bondi Beach shooting hero pleads not guilty to alleged assault on his father,Bondi Beach shooting hero pleads not guilty to alleged assault on his father,0.0,neutral,"[('Bondi Beach', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. and Iran Offer Conflicting Accounts of Nuclear Discussions,U.S. and Iran Offer Conflicting Accounts of Nuclear Discussions,-1.0,negative,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘A Terrible Inheritance’: Could Andy Burnham Succeed Where Starmer Failed?,‘A Terrible Inheritance’: Could Andy Burnham Succeed Where Starmer Failed?,-1.0,negative,"[('Andy Burnham Succeed', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Mark Rutte of NATO Manages an Unpredictable Trump,How Mark Rutte of NATO Manages an Unpredictable Trump,0.0,neutral,"[('Mark Rutte', 'PERSON'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran Makes Moves to Assert Control Over the Strait of Hormuz,Iran Makes Moves to Assert Control Over the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Delcy Rodríguez, Venezuela’s President, Struggles to Uphold Trump’s Narrative of Success","Delcy Rodríguez, Venezuela’s President, Struggles to Uphold Trump’s Narrative of Success",1.0,positive,"[('Delcy Rodríguez', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Uphold Trump’s Narrative of Success', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Britain Is Still Deep in the Shadow of Brexit,Britain Is Still Deep in the Shadow of Brexit,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"After Wars and False Starts, Cautious Optimism for U.S.-Iran Talks","After Wars and False Starts, Cautious Optimism for U.S.-Iran Talks",-1.0,negative,"[('False Starts', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Those British Strawberries Are Being Picked by Central Asian Workers,Those British Strawberries Are Being Picked by Central Asian Workers,0.0,neutral,"[('Those British Strawberries Are Being Picked', 'ORG'), ('Central Asian Workers', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"U.S. Warns of ‘Imminent’ Atrocities in El Obeid, Sudan","U.S. Warns of ‘Imminent’ Atrocities in El Obeid, Sudan",-1.0,negative,"[('U.S. Warns of ‘Imminent’ Atrocities', 'ORG'), ('El Obeid', 'GPE'), ('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_24,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Soldier, Scholar and Symbol: Marc Bloch Is Elevated to France’s Panthéon","Soldier, Scholar and Symbol: Marc Bloch Is Elevated to France’s Panthéon",0.0,neutral,"[('Scholar', 'ORG'), ('Marc Bloch', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
