Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Melissa llega a Cuba como huracán de categoría 3 tras dejar una estela de devastación en Jamaica,Melissa arrives in Cuba as a category 3 hurricane after leaving a trail of devastation in Jamaica,0.0,"[('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jamaica', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los mapas que muestran por dónde viaja la droga desde América Latina hasta EE.UU. (y cuánta llega por el Caribe),The maps that show where drugs travel from Latin America to the US (and how much arrives through the Caribbean),0.2,"[('Latin America', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Un megaoperativo contra el grupo criminal Comando Vermelho en Río de Janeiro deja al menos 64 muertos y 81 detenidos,A mega-operation against the Comando Vermelho criminal group in Rio de Janeiro leaves at least 64 dead and 81 detained,-0.3,"[('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE'), ('at least 64', 'CARDINAL'), ('81', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,EE.UU. mata a otras 14 personas que viajaban en 4 supuestas narcolanchas en el Pacífico,The US kills another 14 people traveling on 4 alleged drug boats in the Pacific,-0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Pacific', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La hija de Brigitte Macron asegura que la salud de su madre ""se deterioró"" por las afirmaciones de que es una mujer transgénero","Brigitte Macron's daughter says her mother's health ""deteriorated"" due to claims that she is a transgender woman",-0.125,"[(""Brigitte Macron's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,रतन टाटा के निधन के बाद से टाटा ग्रुप में छिड़ी अंदरूनी लड़ाई की वजह क्या है?,What is the reason for the internal fight that broke out in Tata Group after the death of Ratan Tata?,0.0,"[('Tata Group', 'ORG'), ('Ratan Tata', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"शहाबुद्दीन के बेटे ओसामा चुनावी मैदान में, क्या थमेगा परिवार की हार का सिलसिला?","Shahabuddin's son Osama in the election field, will the series of defeats of the family stop?",0.0,"[('Shahabuddin', 'PERSON'), ('Osama', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,भारत-ऑस्ट्रेलिया टी-20 सिरीज़: ऑस्ट्रेलिया ने टॉस जीता, पहले फ़ील्डिंग करेगा","Live, India-Australia T-20 series: Australia wins the toss, will field first",0.22878787878787876,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('T-20', 'PRODUCT'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दिल्ली की हवा सालभर में करीबन 200 दिन ख़राब, लाहौर और बीजिंग का क्या हाल?","Delhi's air is bad for about 200 days in a year, what is the condition of Lahore and Beijing?",-0.6999999999999998,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('about 200 days', 'DATE'), ('Lahore', 'GPE'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,जन सुराज के टिकट पर लड़ रहीं ट्रांसजेंडर प्रीति किन्नर ने बताया चुनावी एजेंडा, अवधि 4,08","Video, Transgender Preeti Kinnar, contesting on Jan Suraj's ticket, told the election agenda, duration 4,08",0.0,"[('Transgender Preeti Kinnar', 'ORG'), ('4,08', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ग़ज़ा: इसराइली हवाई हमलों में महिलाओं और बच्चों समेत 33 की मौत, अमेरिका क्या बोला","Gaza: 33 including women and children killed in Israeli air strikes, what did America say?",-0.2,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('33', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चीन क्या ट्रेड वॉर में अमेरिका से जीत रहा है?,Is China winning the trade war with America?,0.5,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दुनिया से पूरी तरह अलग-थलग, अब भी तन्हा कैसे रह रहे हैं ये लोग","Completely isolated from the world, how are these people still living alone?",0.1,[]
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'पता नहीं ठीक होगा या नहीं': एमपी में कार्बाइड गन से कैसे हुआ आँखों की रोशनी को ख़तरा,'Don't know whether it will be cured or not': How carbide gun threatened eyesight in MP,0.0,[]
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Megaoperação contra Comando Vermelho no Rio tem 64 mortos e 81 presos: o que se sabe até agora,Megaoperation against Comando Vermelho in Rio leaves 64 dead and 81 arrested: what is known so far,-0.05,"[('Comando Vermelho', 'ORG'), ('Rio', 'GPE'), ('64', 'CARDINAL'), ('81', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Mortes em operação são mais do que o dobro do recorde anterior de letalidade,Deaths in operation are more than double the previous lethality record,0.11111111111111112,[]
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Kim Kataguiri: Bolsonaro deve cumprir pena na cadeia e ir ao hospital quando necessário,Kim Kataguiri: Bolsonaro should serve time in jail and go to the hospital when necessary,-0.05,"[('Kim Kataguiri', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que furacão Melissa é uma tempestade com poder tão grande de destruição?,Why is Hurricane Melissa such a destructive storm?,-0.3,"[('Melissa', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,É sempre necessário tratar a febre? O sintoma que intrigou os médicos durante milênios,Is it always necessary to treat fever? The symptom that has puzzled doctors for millennia,0.0,[]
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Trump não tem intenção de invadir; é tudo uma operação psicológica', diz Elliott Abrams, ex-enviado dos EUA para a Venezuela","'Trump has no intention of invading; It's all a psychological operation', says Elliott Abrams, former US envoy to Venezuela",0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Elliott Abrams', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O chef que se negou a cozinhar menu sem peixes da Amazônia para evento do príncipe William,The chef who refused to cook a menu without Amazonian fish for Prince William's event,0.0,"[('Amazonian', 'NORP'), ('William', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como Milei conseguiu vitória nas eleições legislativas da Argentina apesar de crises e escândalos,How Milei achieved victory in Argentina's legislative elections despite crises and scandals,0.0,"[('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Irmãos na floresta': a luta para proteger aldeia isolada da Amazônia,'Brothers in the forest': the fight to protect isolated village in the Amazon,0.0,"[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Конец щедрости: как регионы России снижают выплаты за подписание военного контракта,The end of generosity: how Russian regions are reducing payments for signing a military contract,-0.05,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: дроны сбивали под Москвой и еще в более 10 регионах России","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: drones were shot down near Moscow and in more than 10 regions of Russia",0.14814814814814814,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('more than 10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В крупнейшей полицейской операции против преступной группировки в Рио-де-Жанейро погибли 64 человека,64 people killed in biggest police operation against gang in Rio de Janeiro,-0.2,"[('64', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Выборы в Нидерландах: как правоцентристы потеряли влияние и при чем тут Марк Рютте,Elections in the Netherlands: how the center-right lost influence and what does Mark Rutte have to do with it,0.0,"[('Netherlands', 'GPE'), ('Mark Rutte', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Ураган «Мелисса» прошелся по Ямайке и ударил по Кубе. Он может стать самым мощным штормом 2025 года,Hurricane Melissa swept through Jamaica and hit Cuba. It could become the most powerful storm of 2025,0.4,"[('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('Jamaica', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Певицу Наоко оштрафовали и продолжают держать в полиции, ей грозят новые обвинения","Singer Naoko was fined and continues to be held in police custody, she faces new charges",0.13636363636363635,"[('Naoko', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Израиль нанес удары по Газе. Трамп говорит, что это не конец перемирия",Israel launched strikes on Gaza. Trump says this is not the end of the truce,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ВСУ разрушили плотину Белгородского водохранилища. Как это повлияет на фронт?,The Ukrainian Armed Forces destroyed the dam of the Belgorod reservoir. How will this affect the front?,0.0,"[('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Belgorod', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Илон Маск создал альтернативу Википедии — Грокипедию,Elon Musk created an alternative to Wikipedia - Grokipedia,0.0,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Wikipedia - Grokipedia', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Черногория приостановила безвизовый въезд граждан Турции. Причиной стали межэтнические столкновения из-за нападения с ножом,Montenegro has suspended visa-free entry for Turkish citizens. The cause was interethnic clashes due to a knife attack,-0.125,"[('Montenegro', 'GPE'), ('Turkish', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、ガザを空爆　停戦合意にハマスが違反したと非難,Israel bombs Gaza; accuses Hamas of violating ceasefire agreement,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 レアアース、ノーベル賞推薦、賛辞……トランプ氏が訪日終える,"[Commentary] Rare earths, Nobel Prize nomination, compliments... Trump ends his visit to Japan",0.3,"[('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,戦争は「しない方がいい」が……防衛から日米関係まで、トランプ氏が米海軍横須賀基地で演説, 所要時間 1,46","Video, War is ""better not""...From defense to Japan-US relations, Trump gives speech at US Navy Yokosuka Base, Duration 1,46",-0.15000000000000002,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US Navy', 'ORG'), ('Yokosuka Base', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍、東太平洋で「麻薬船」4隻を攻撃　14人殺害,"US military attacks 4 drug ships in the Eastern Pacific, killing 14 people",-0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Eastern Pacific', 'LOC'), ('14', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,マクロン仏大統領夫人の生活、ネットのいじめで「悪化した」　娘が裁判で証言,"French President Macron's life has 'deteriorated' due to online bullying, daughter testifies in court",-0.0625,"[('French', 'NORP'), ('Macron', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、有罪評決めぐり控訴　元不倫相手への「口止め料」虚偽記載事件,Trump appeals guilty verdict in case of false statement of ``hush money'' to former affair partner,-0.30000000000000004,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日本の人口危機　ロボットで解決できるのか,Can robots solve Japan's population crisis?,0.0,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏と高市氏が会談　日米「黄金時代」に関する合意文書に署名,Mr. Trump and Mr. Takaichi meet and sign agreement regarding the Japan-U.S. “Golden Era”,0.3,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Takaichi', 'PERSON'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Golden Era', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,オープンAI、躁状態や自殺願望示したチャットGPTユーザー数のデータを公表,Open AI releases data on number of chat GPT users who exhibit manic or suicidal thoughts,0.0,"[('GPT', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Polisi wakabiliana na 'waandamanaji' jijini Dar es Salaam","Directly, the police are facing the 'protesters' in the city of Dar es Salaam",0.1,"[('Dar es Salaam', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Mkuu Tanzania 2025: Kura au maandamano? mizani ya haki za kikatiba inavyopimwa,Tanzania General Election 2025: Vote or protest? the balance of constitutional rights is measured,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzania General', 'ORG'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Israel yaishambulia Gaza baada ya kuishutumu Hamas kukiuka usitishaji mapigano","Directly, Israel attacked Gaza after accusing Hamas of violating the ceasefire",0.1,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Waridi wa BBC: Mwanamke aliyelazimishwa kunywa maji ya maiti,BBC Rose: Woman forced to drink corpse water,0.14999999999999997,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Mkuu Tanzania 2025: Upigaji kura wa mapema wafanyika Zanzibar,Tanzania General Election 2025: Early voting will be held in Zanzibar,0.07500000000000001,"[('Tanzania General', 'ORG'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE'), ('Zanzibar', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"China inadhibiti madini adimu ambayo ulimwengu hununua..je, mikataba mipya ya Trump inaweza kubadilisha hilo?",China controls the rare metals the world buys..can Trump's new deals change that?,0.21818181818181817,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumatano: Tottenham wavutiwa na Scott McTominay,European football rumors Wednesday: Tottenham are interested in Scott McTominay,0.125,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Tottenham', 'GPE'), ('Scott McTominay', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Israel itajibu baada ya Hamas kutoa mabaki ya miili ya mateka yasio sahihi - Netanyahu,Israel will respond after Hamas releases remains of hostages wrong - Netanyahu,-0.5,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mapenzi ya mahabusu: 'Nilizaa na mwanaume aliyekuwa jela na mwanangu',Love of prisoners: 'I gave birth to a man who was in prison and my son',0.5,[]
2025_10_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Mkuu Tanzania 2025: Unajua safari ya kura yako na unavyoipiga?,Tanzania General Election 2025: Do you know the journey of your vote and how you cast it?,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzania General', 'ORG'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE')]"
