Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""¿Cuál fue su crimen?"": la BBC visita la escuela iraní en la que murieron 120 niños en un ataque atribuido a EE.UU.","""What was their crime?"": BBC visits Iranian school where 120 children died in attack blamed on US",-1.0,negative,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('120', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Nicaragua se ha convertido en la Corea del Norte de América Latina"": la oposición condena la intención de Ortega de cancelar las elecciones","""Nicaragua has become the North Korea of ​​Latin America"": the opposition condemns Ortega's intention to cancel the elections",0.0,neutral,"[('Nicaragua', 'GPE'), ('the North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Ortega', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Hallan los restos del avión de Pan Am cuyo accidente hace más de 70 años marcó un antes y un después en la seguridad aérea,They find the remains of the Pan Am plane whose accident more than 70 years ago marked a before and after in air safety,0.0,neutral,"[('Pan Am', 'ORG'), ('more than 70 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"OpenAI dice que su inteligencia artificial se rebeló y lanzó un ciberataque ""sin precedentes""","OpenAI says its artificial intelligence rebelled and launched an ""unprecedented"" cyberattack",-1.0,negative,"[('OpenAI', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La ""hora feliz"" de las abuelas: la mujer que logró cambiar una ley en EE.UU. para permitir el alcohol en asilos","Grandmas' ""happy hour"": the woman who managed to change a law in the US to allow alcohol in nursing homes",0.0,neutral,"[('Grandmas', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué es polémico el acuerdo nuclear que firmaron EE.UU. y Arabia Saudita,Why the nuclear agreement signed by the US and Saudi Arabia is controversial,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Por qué Irán está arriesgando tanto por el estrecho de Ormuz?,Why is Iran risking so much for the Strait of Hormuz?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Tuvimos que sortear cadenillas de oro para pagar la atención médica de mi hija"": cómo el sistema de salud en Paraguay lleva a los pacientes a endeudarse","""We had to spend gold chains to pay for my daughter's medical care"": how the health system in Paraguay leads patients into debt",0.0,neutral,"[('Paraguay', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Encuentran muerto en París al reclutador de modelos vinculado con Jeffrey Epstein,Model recruiter linked to Jeffrey Epstein found dead in Paris,0.0,neutral,"[('Jeffrey Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Escribía versos entre entrega y entrega: el repartidor de comida que ganó uno de los mayores premios literarios de China,He wrote verses between deliveries: the food delivery man who won one of the biggest literary awards in China,-1.0,negative,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,धर्मेंद्र प्रधान का इस्तीफ़ा लेना क्या मोदी सरकार के लिए मुश्किल है?,Is it difficult for the Modi government to take Dharmendra Pradhan's resignation?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Dharmendra Pradhan's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,केंद्रीय मंत्री डॉ. जितेंद्र सिंह ने बातचीत के लिए सीजेपी को आमंत्रित किया","Live, Union Minister Dr. Jitendra Singh invites CJP for talks",0.0,neutral,"[('Jitendra Singh', 'PERSON'), ('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"युवाओं के आंदोलन के बीच पीएम मोदी ने की ये घोषणा, सीजेपी और राहुल गांधी ने दिया ये जवाब","PM Modi made this announcement amid youth movement, CJP and Rahul Gandhi gave this answer",0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सऊदी-अमेरिका परमाणु समझौता: पाकिस्तान को लेकर क्या जताई जा रही आशंकाएं,Saudi-America nuclear deal: What apprehensions are being expressed about Pakistan,0.0,neutral,"[('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,एक जैसे दिखने वाले 4 बच्चों के जन्म से मेडिकल दुनिया क्यों हैरान,Why the medical world is shocked by the birth of 4 identical looking children,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सलमान, आलिया और अरुंधति समेत ये दिग्गज सीजेपी के आंदोलन पर क्या बोले","What did these stalwarts including Salman, Alia and Arundhati say on CJP's movement?",-1.0,negative,"[('Salman', 'GPE'), ('Alia', 'GPE'), ('Arundhati', 'GPE'), ('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी का प्रोटेस्ट, अन्ना आंदोलन से कितना अलग?",How different is Cockroach Janata Party's protest from Anna movement?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Cockroach Janata Party's"", 'ORG'), ('Anna', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सीजेपी का प्रदर्शन ऐतिहासिक: अन्ना आंदोलन के साथ तुलना से लेकर आपातकाल तक पर क्या बोले योगेंद्र यादव,"CJP's performance is historic: From comparison with Anna movement to Emergency, what did Yogendra Yadav say?",0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Anna', 'NORP'), ('Yogendra Yadav', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सीजेआई बोले- 'वक़्त बर्बाद मत कीजिए', प्रदर्शनकारियों की पिटाई के मुद्दे पर जल्द सुनवाई से इनकार","CJI said - 'Don't waste time', refused to hear soon on the issue of beating of protesters",0.0,neutral,"[('CJI', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"महिलाओं से बदसलूकी के आरोप, सादी वर्दी वाले करते लाठीचार्ज: सीजेपी प्रदर्शन में पुलिस कार्रवाई पर उठते सवाल","Allegations of misbehavior with women, lathicharge by plainclothesmen: Questions raised on police action in CJP protest",0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O plano da China para se livrar da dependência do agro brasileiro (e por que isso assusta o Brasil),China's plan to free itself from dependence on Brazilian agriculture (and why it scares Brazil),0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Biquíni, 80 anos: como traje batizado por causa de bomba nuclear se tornou símbolo de brasilidade","Bikini, 80 years old: how an outfit named after a nuclear bomb became a symbol of Brazilianness",0.0,neutral,"[('Bikini', 'GPE'), ('80 years old', 'DATE'), ('Brazilianness', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que acordo histórico entre EUA e Arábia Saudita desperta receio de uma corrida nuclear no Oriente Médio,Why historic agreement between the US and Saudi Arabia raises fears of a nuclear race in the Middle East,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como nova tarifa contra o Brasil faz parte de estratégia maior de Trump para inimigos (e aliados),How the new tariff against Brazil is part of Trump's larger strategy for enemies (and allies),0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que novo tarifaço de Trump não deve decidir eleição a favor de Lula,Why Trump's new tariff should not decide the election in Lula's favor,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Criadora do ChatGPT diz que sua IA agiu por conta própria e lançou um ataque cibernético 'sem precedentes',ChatGPT creator says its AI acted on its own and launched an 'unprecedented' cyberattack,-1.0,negative,"[('ChatGPT creator', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como acidente de avião que teve destroços achados após 74 anos mudou para sempre a segurança aérea,How plane crash left wreckage found after 74 years changed aviation safety forever,0.0,neutral,"[('74 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Nicarágua virou a Coreia do Norte da América Latina': a reação diante do início do plano de Ortega para acabar com eleições no país,'Nicaragua became the North Korea of ​​Latin America': the reaction to the beginning of Ortega's plan to end elections in the country,0.0,neutral,"[('Nicaragua', 'GPE'), ('the North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Ortega', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Meu app de atividade física soube que eu estava grávida antes de mim','My fitness app knew I was pregnant before I did',0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A dama que 'macheava': o que diz o 1º poema homoerótico brasileiro,The lady who 'macheava': what the first Brazilian homoerotic poem says,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Евросоюз наконец согласовал ужесточение санкций против России. Греция добилась уступок в 21-м пакете,The European Union has finally agreed on tougher sanctions against Russia. Greece achieved concessions in the 21st package,0.0,neutral,"[('The European Union', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Greece', 'GPE'), ('21st', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Чем обернется «война городов и танкеров» между Москвой и Киевом?,How will the “war of cities and tankers” between Moscow and Kyiv turn out?,-1.0,negative,"[('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Лавров встретился с Рубио в Маниле, в пригороде Воронежа при атаке дронов погиб трехлетний ребенок","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Lavrov met with Rubio in Manila, a three-year-old child died in a drone attack in a suburb of Voronezh",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Manila', 'GPE'), ('three-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Voronezh', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Хуситы заявили об ударах по танкерам в Красном море. Это первая атака после начала объявленной ими блокады,The Houthis announced attacks on tankers in the Red Sea. This is the first attack since the start of the blockade they announced.,-1.0,negative,"[('Houthis', 'PERSON'), ('the Red Sea', 'LOC'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,США объявили о заключении соглашения с Саудовской Аравией в области атомной энергетики. Что оно предусматривает?,The United States announced an agreement with Saudi Arabia in the field of nuclear energy. What does it provide?,0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Искусственный интеллект компании OpenAI вышел из-под контроля и устроил кибератаку,OpenAI's artificial intelligence got out of control and launched a cyber attack,-1.0,negative,"[('OpenAI', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Студенческие протесты в Индии стали проблемой для Моди. Откуда взялось движение «тараканов»?,"Student protests in India have become a problem for Modi. Where did the ""cockroach"" movement come from?",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Modi', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Рекрутер девушек». Во Франции нашли мертвым модельного скаута Даниэля Сиада, связанного с Эпштейном","""Recruiter of girls."" Model scout Daniel Siad, linked to Epstein, found dead in France",0.0,neutral,"[('Daniel Siad', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Чем известен новый главком ВСУ Михаил Драпатый: штурм на БМП, меч королевы и сложнейшие участки фронта","What is the new commander-in-chief of the Armed Forces of Ukraine Mikhail Drapaty famous for: assault on an infantry fighting vehicle, the queen’s sword and the most difficult sectors of the front",0.0,neutral,"[('the Armed Forces of Ukraine', 'ORG'), ('Mikhail Drapaty', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Уехавших россиян, преследуемых в России, лишат консульских услуг и права распоряжаться имуществом. Какие еще вводятся запреты?",Russians who have left and are persecuted in Russia will be deprived of consular services and the right to dispose of property. What other prohibitions are being introduced?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russians', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、サウジアラビアとの画期的な原子力協定に署名　ウラン濃縮への懸念の声も,"US signs groundbreaking nuclear power agreement with Saudi Arabia, amid concerns over uranium enrichment",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、ロシアの通販大手の倉庫を相次ぎ攻撃　中小企業に打撃,Attacks on warehouses of major mail order companies in Ukraine and Russia hit small and medium-sized businesses one after another,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米オープンAI、自社AIが暴走し「前例のない」サイバー攻撃を仕掛けたと発表　セキュリティーテスト中に,"U.S. Open AI announces that its AI went out of control and launched an ""unprecedented"" cyber attack during a security test",-1.0,negative,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヒトラー生家に警察署を開設、ナチスの聖地化を防ごうと　オーストリア,Austria opens a police station at Hitler's birthplace to prevent it from turning into a holy site for the Nazis,0.0,neutral,"[('Austria', 'GPE'), ('Hitler', 'PERSON'), ('Nazis', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【分析】 イエメン近海でタンカーが相次ぎ急旋回、フーシ派の「海上封鎖」警告受け,"[Analysis] Tankers make sudden turns one after another near Yemen, receiving warning of Houthi ``maritime blockade''",-1.0,negative,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Yemen', 'GPE'), ('Houthi', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ政権の技術顧問、中国AIモデルが米競合から技術を盗んだと非難,Trump administration technology adviser accuses Chinese AI models of stealing technology from US rivals,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,マムダニNY市長、ネタニヤフ氏拘束に改めて言及　のちに権限ないと後退,"New York City Mayor Mamdani once again mentions Netanyahu's detention, but later retreats saying he lacks authority",0.0,neutral,"[('New York City', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ルーヴル美術館、宝飾品が盗まれたギャラリーの一般公開を再開　9カ月ぶり, 所要時間 0,37","Video, Louvre reopens gallery where jewelry was stolen to public for first time in 9 months, Duration 0,37",0.0,neutral,"[('Louvre', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('9 months', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,インドネシアで赤ちゃん売買組織の19人に有罪判決……子どもたちはどうなるのか, 所要時間 1,42","Video, 19 people convicted of baby trafficking ring in Indonesia...What will happen to the children? Duration: 1,42",0.0,neutral,"[('19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、イランを11夜連続で空爆　トランプ氏は地下核施設への攻撃を示唆,US airstrikes Iran for 11 consecutive nights; Trump hints at attacking underground nuclear facilities,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('11 consecutive nights', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Wahouthi wadai kuhusika na shambulio dhidi ya meli za mafuta baada ya Marekani kufanya mashambulizi zaidi dhidi ya Iran","Directly, the Houthis claim to be responsible for the attack on oil tankers after the United States carried out more attacks against Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('Houthis', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mojtaba Khamenei: Kwa nini kiongozi wa kidini wa Iran haonekani hadharani?,Mojtaba Khamenei: Why is the religious leader of Iran not seen in public?,0.0,neutral,"[('Mojtaba Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Mlima Ghazla Kalang; kituo cha Iran kilicho chini ya ardhi, cha siri, na chenye utata","Mount Ghazla Kalang; Iran's underground, secretive, and controversial facility",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Ndani ya 'dhehebu' la Epstein, na simulizi za wanawake aliowanyanyasa kwa miaka mingi","Inside Epstein's 'cult', and the accounts of the women he abused over the years",0.0,neutral,"[(""Inside Epstein's '"", 'PERSON'), ('the years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini makubaliano ya nyuklia yaliyotiwa saini na Marekani na Saudi Arabia yanazua utata?,Why the nuclear agreement signed by the United States and Saudi Arabia is controversial?,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Marekani yatumia zaidi ya dola bilioni 37 katika vita dhidi ya Iran,The US spends more than 37 billion dollars in the war against Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('more than 37 billion dollars', 'MONEY'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Alhamisi: Liverpool wana imani kubwa ya kumsajili Bradley Barcola,Football rumors Thursday: Liverpool are confident of signing Bradley Barcola,0.0,neutral,"[('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Bradley Barcola', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Lissu na Msigwa wakutana Mahakama Kuu huku kesi ya kikatiba ikiahirishwa,Lissu and Msigwa meet at the High Court while the constitutional case is postponed,0.0,neutral,"[('Lissu', 'ORG'), ('Msigwa', 'ORG'), ('the High Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwanini Iran inajihatarisha katika harakati za kuudhibiti Mlango Bahari wa Hormuz,Why is Iran taking risks in the process of controlling the Strait of Hormuz?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Beckham akawa sura ya Kombe la Dunia nchini Marekani?,Why did Beckham become the face of the World Cup in the United States?,0.0,neutral,"[('Beckham', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran, Houthis strike tankers as US bombing continues: What’s the latest?","Iran, Houthis strike tankers as US bombing continues: What’s the latest?",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Houthis', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"More than 2,300 Israelis storm Al-Aqsa Mosque in Jerusalem","More than 2,300 Israelis storm Al-Aqsa Mosque in Jerusalem",0.0,neutral,"[('More than 2,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israelis', 'NORP'), ('Al-Aqsa Mosque', 'ORG'), ('Jerusalem', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Indian activist Wangchuk sets conditions to end hunger strike,Indian activist Wangchuk sets conditions to end hunger strike,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Wangchuk', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘I have nowhere else to go’: Gaza’s shelter crisis,‘I have nowhere else to go’: Gaza’s shelter crisis,-1.0,negative,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,India’s Modi promises fast-track courts for exam fraud fuelling protests,India’s Modi promises fast-track courts for exam fraud fuelling protests,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Top US and Russian diplomats discuss Ukraine war in Manila,Top US and Russian diplomats discuss Ukraine war in Manila,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Manila', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Arsenal defender Saliba sidelined for ‘extended period’ due to back injury,Arsenal defender Saliba sidelined for ‘extended period’ due to back injury,0.0,neutral,"[('Saliba', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Between hope and fear: Yemenis react to Houthi blockade on Saudi Arabia,Between hope and fear: Yemenis react to Houthi blockade on Saudi Arabia,0.0,neutral,"[('Yemenis', 'NORP'), ('Houthi', 'ORG'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Thousands forced to evacuate as wildfires sweep across southern France,Thousands forced to evacuate as wildfires sweep across southern France,0.0,neutral,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel building earthen barrier in Gaza to entrench division of the enclave,Israel building earthen barrier in Gaza to entrench division of the enclave,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Houthis strike tankers in Red Sea; first since Saudi-linked shipping blockade via Bab el-Mandeb,Houthis strike tankers in Red Sea; first since Saudi-linked shipping blockade via Bab el-Mandeb,0.0,neutral,"[('Red Sea', 'LOC'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('Bab el-Mandeb', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Government to set up fast-track courts for paper leak cases, says PM Modi","Government to set up fast-track courts for paper leak cases, says PM Modi",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Commonwealth Games 2026: Lovlina assures India its first medal,Commonwealth Games 2026: Lovlina assures India its first medal,0.0,neutral,"[('Commonwealth Games 2026', 'ORG'), ('Lovlina', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,What is the Sabarimala gold ‘theft’ case? | Explained,What is the Sabarimala gold ‘theft’ case? | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Sabarimala', 'PERSON'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Sabarimala gold theft case: SIT arrests former TDB president P.S. Prasanth,Sabarimala gold theft case: SIT arrests former TDB president P.S. Prasanth,0.0,neutral,"[('Sabarimala', 'GPE'), ('P.S. Prasanth', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Meghalaya honeymoon murder: SC sets aside Sonam Raghuvanshi’s bail, gives her three weeks to surrender","Meghalaya honeymoon murder: SC sets aside Sonam Raghuvanshi’s bail, gives her three weeks to surrender",0.0,neutral,"[('Meghalaya', 'ORG'), ('Sonam Raghuvanshi’s', 'PERSON'), ('three weeks', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Parliament LIVE: Both Houses adjourned for the day amid Oppn protests,Parliament LIVE: Both Houses adjourned for the day amid Oppn protests,0.0,neutral,"[('the day', 'DATE'), ('Oppn', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,‘Jana Nayagan’ release: ‘Thalapathy’ Vijay pays tribute to MGR,‘Jana Nayagan’ release: ‘Thalapathy’ Vijay pays tribute to MGR,0.0,neutral,"[('Jana Nayagan', 'PERSON'), ('Vijay', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,All is not well: On the protests in Delhi,All is not well: On the protests in Delhi,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Buried questions: On the Sikkim tunnel accident,Buried questions: On the Sikkim tunnel accident,0.0,neutral,"[('Sikkim', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US signs landmark nuclear deal with Saudi Arabia,US signs landmark nuclear deal with Saudi Arabia,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Houthis claim attack on oil tankers as US launches more strikes on Iran,Houthis claim attack on oil tankers as US launches more strikes on Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Thousands evacuated in France fires,Thousands evacuated in France fires,0.0,neutral,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'I am still alive': Indian activist on hunger strike for 26 days loses 11kg,'I am still alive': Indian activist on hunger strike for 26 days loses 11kg,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('26 days', 'DATE'), ('11kg', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Tankers make sharp U-turns after Houthi shipping threat,Tankers make sharp U-turns after Houthi shipping threat,0.0,neutral,"[('Houthi', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Canada's 'powerful' dairy sector is in Trump's trade crosshairs,Canada's 'powerful' dairy sector is in Trump's trade crosshairs,0.0,neutral,"[('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Russia's businesses under strain from Ukraine's attacks on Wildberries,Russia's businesses under strain from Ukraine's attacks on Wildberries,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Google burning through cash with spiralling AI costs,Google burning through cash with spiralling AI costs,0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Fire kills 10 members of same family in Peru, police say","Fire kills 10 members of same family in Peru, police say",-1.0,negative,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,British woman jailed for blackmail after accusing banker of rape in Hong Kong,British woman jailed for blackmail after accusing banker of rape in Hong Kong,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘We Will All Die From Ebola Here’: Virus Stalks Crowded Camps in Congo,‘We Will All Die From Ebola Here’: Virus Stalks Crowded Camps in Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Why I Sought Out a Taliban Commander I Had Fought,Why I Sought Out a Taliban Commander I Had Fought,0.0,neutral,"[('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Oil-Rich Saudi Arabia Isn’t Short on Energy. Here’s Why It’s Going Nuclear.,Oil-Rich Saudi Arabia Isn’t Short on Energy. Here’s Why It’s Going Nuclear.,0.0,neutral,"[('Oil-Rich Saudi Arabia', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A New Target for Ukraine’s Long-Range Attacks: Russia’s Version of Amazon,A New Target for Ukraine’s Long-Range Attacks: Russia’s Version of Amazon,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A Russian Spy, Suddenly Cast Into the Spotlight, Flees Japan","A Russian Spy, Suddenly Cast Into the Spotlight, Flees Japan",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian Spy', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S.-Saudi Deal Prompts Fears of a Nuclear Arms Race,U.S.-Saudi Deal Prompts Fears of a Nuclear Arms Race,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Japan’s Leader Invokes Her Hero, Shinzo Abe, to Drive Nationalist Agenda","Japan’s Leader Invokes Her Hero, Shinzo Abe, to Drive Nationalist Agenda",0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Invokes Her Hero', 'PERSON'), ('Shinzo Abe', 'PERSON'), ('Drive Nationalist', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Military Presence in Jordan Makes It Iranian Target,U.S. Military Presence in Jordan Makes It Iranian Target,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Military Presence', 'ORG'), ('Jordan', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Israeli Banks Threaten to Cut Off Palestinian Economy,Israeli Banks Threaten to Cut Off Palestinian Economy,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Cut Off Palestinian Economy', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Dubai Firm Cuts Deal for New Port to Bypass Strait of Hormuz,Dubai Firm Cuts Deal for New Port to Bypass Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Dubai', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
