Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,¿Se está volviendo ingobernable Reino Unido?,Is the United Kingdom becoming ungovernable?,0.0,neutral,"[('United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La preocupación de los propietarios de hoteles en EE.UU. ante la poca cantidad de reservas antes del inicio del Mundial 2026,The concern of hotel owners in the US due to the low number of reservations before the start of the 2026 World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('the start of the', 'DATE'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué es lo que realmente une a China y Rusia y cómo se manifiesta en la inminente visita de Putin a Xi,What really unites China and Russia and how it manifests itself in Putin's imminent visit to Xi,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Xi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo 5 minutos de ejercicio al día pueden mejorar y alargar nuestras vidas,How 5 minutes of exercise a day can improve and lengthen our lives,1.0,positive,"[('5 minutes', 'TIME')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""La distancia de un padre con un hijo es querer hablar y sentir que el otro está a 300 kilómetros aunque estés cara a cara""","""The distance between a parent and a child is wanting to talk and feeling that the other is 300 kilometers away even though you are face to face""",0.0,neutral,"[('300 kilometers', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Hallan los cuerpos de los otros 4 buceadores italianos que se ahogaron mientras exploraban una cueva en Maldivas,They find the bodies of the other 4 Italian divers who drowned while exploring a cave in the Maldives,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Shakira gana su batalla de 8 años contra la Hacienda española, que deberá devolverle 60 millones de euros","Shakira wins her 8-year battle against the Spanish Treasury, which must return 60 million euros",1.0,positive,"[('8-year', 'DATE'), ('the Spanish', 'ORG'), ('Treasury', 'ORG'), ('60 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,3 ejemplos que evidencian cómo Delcy Rodríguez está desmantelando en Venezuela el modelo económico chavista,3 examples that show how Delcy Rodríguez is dismantling the Chavista economic model in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delcy Rodríguez', 'PERSON'), ('Chavista', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Díaz-Canel asegura que un ataque de EE.UU. en Cuba provocaría ""un baño de sangre de consecuencias incalculables""","Díaz-Canel assures that a US attack on Cuba would cause ""a bloodbath of incalculable consequences""",-1.0,negative,"[('Díaz-Canel', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Las luchas en Centroamérica contra las dictaduras nunca habrían sido posibles sin Costa Rica como lugar de refugio y libertad"": Sergio Ramírez, novelista y exvicepresidente de Nicaragua","""The struggles in Central America against dictatorships would never have been possible without Costa Rica as a place of refuge and freedom"": Sergio Ramírez, novelist and former vice president of Nicaragua",0.0,neutral,"[('Central America', 'LOC'), ('Costa Rica', 'GPE'), ('Sergio Ramírez', 'PERSON'), ('Nicaragua', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"फाल्टा सीट पर होने वाले चुनाव से पीछे हटे तृणमूल कांग्रेस के जहांगीर ख़ान, शुभेंदु अधिकारी ने क्या कहा?",What did Trinamool Congress's Jahangir Khan and Shubhendu Adhikari withdraw from the elections on Falta seat?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Trinamool Congress's"", 'ORG'), ('Jahangir Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Shubhendu Adhikari', 'PERSON'), ('Falta', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"भोपाल में ट्विशा शर्मा की मौत: परिवार ने कहा हत्या, ससुराल पक्ष ने मानसिक बीमारी का दावा किया","Twisha Sharma's death in Bhopal: Family said murder, in-laws claimed mental illness",-1.0,negative,"[(""Twisha Sharma's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,रूसी राष्ट्रपति पुतिन ने चीन यात्रा से पहले जारी किया वीडियो संदेश","Live, Russian President Putin released video message before his visit to China",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पीएम मोदी से सवाल के बाद फिर चर्चा में प्रेस फ़्रीडम, नॉर्वे कैसे बना दुनिया में नंबर वन?","After questioning PM Modi, press freedom again in discussion, how did Norway become number one in the world?",0.0,neutral,"[('Norway', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"आवारा कुत्तों पर सुप्रीम कोर्ट का बेहद सख़्त रवैया, कहा 'कुत्तों के डर के बिना जीना सबका हक़'","Supreme Court's very strict attitude on stray dogs, said 'Everyone has the right to live without fear of dogs'",0.0,neutral,"[(""Supreme Court's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'हो सकता है शायद आप आख़िरी बार मेरी आवाज़ सुन रहे हों', ईरान में राजनीतिक फांसी के मामले बढ़े","'Maybe you are hearing my voice for the last time', cases of political executions increase in Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नॉर्वे की पत्रकार ने पूछा, 'आपके प्रधानमंत्री मुश्किल सवालों के जवाब कब देंगे', भारत ने दिया ये जवाब","Norwegian journalist asked, 'When will your Prime Minister answer difficult questions', India gave this answer",0.0,neutral,"[('Norwegian', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अमेरिका: गौतम अदानी ने क्या सेटलमेंट किया जिसके बाद उन पर लगे आरोप हुए वापस,America: What settlement did Gautam Adani make after which the charges against him were withdrawn?,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Gautam Adani', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"केंद्रीय मंत्री बंडी संजय के बेटे ने सरेंडर किया या उन्हें गिरफ़्तार किया गया, पुलिस का क्या है कहना?","Has Union Minister Bandi Sanjay's son surrendered or been arrested, what does the police say?",0.0,neutral,"[(""Bandi Sanjay's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दिल्ली बस गैंगरेप मामला: सर्वाइवर का सवाल, 'मैं सेक्स वर्कर हूँ, क्या इसका मतलब यह है कि वे मेरा गैंगरेप करेंगे'","Delhi bus gangrape case: Survivor asks, 'I am a sex worker, does it mean they will gangrape me?'",0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Eduardo Paes sobre chance de ser governador do Rio: 'Se eu sair vivo e não terminar preso, já é uma vitória'","Eduardo Paes on the chance to be governor of Rio: 'If I get out alive and don't end up in prison, it's already a victory'",1.0,positive,"[('Eduardo Paes', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Ebola matou 131 em um país da África: por que é tão difícil impedir novo surto?,Ebola killed 131 in an African country: why is it so difficult to prevent another outbreak?,-1.0,negative,"[('131', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Canal do Panamá é o grande beneficiário da crise no estreito de Ormuz,Panama Canal is the main beneficiary of the crisis in the Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('Panama Canal', 'FAC'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Torcida do Brasil 'enlouqueceu' com 'conto de fadas' de Neymar, diz jornal","Brazil fans 'went crazy' with Neymar's 'fairy tale', says newspaper",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Neymar', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Não escolhemos Neymar por achar que é um bom reserva': os convocados por Ancelloti,'We didn't choose Neymar because we think he's a good substitute': those called up by Anceloti,1.0,positive,"[('Neymar', 'ORG'), ('Anceloti', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem foi convocado para a Copa, mas ficou de fora do álbum de figurinhas","Who was called up for the World Cup, but was left out of the sticker album",0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quanto custa completar o álbum da Copa no Brasil - e em outros países,How much does it cost to complete the World Cup album in Brazil - and in other countries,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Operação vai resgatar corpos de mergulhadores italianos mortos nas Maldivas,Operation will recover bodies of Italian divers killed in the Maldives,-1.0,negative,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quanto o filme sobre Bolsonaro precisaria ter de bilheteria para pagar investimento atribuído a Vorcaro,How much would the film about Bolsonaro need to make at the box office to pay for the investment attributed to Vorcaro?,0.0,neutral,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Vorcaro', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os bastidores da operação que levou a BYD à lista do trabalho escravo (e à demissão de secretário em Brasília),Behind the scenes of the operation that led BYD to the slave labor list (and the dismissal of its secretary in Brasília),0.0,neutral,"[('BYD', 'ORG'), ('Brasília', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«На мой день рождения пришла „Русская община“». Как выглядит новый русский национализм,“The Russian Community came to my birthday.” What does the new Russian nationalism look like?,0.0,neutral,"[('The Russian Community', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: удары по Черниговской и Сумской областям — четверо погибших","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: attacks on Chernihiv and Sumy regions - four dead",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Chernihiv', 'GPE'), ('Sumy', 'ORG'), ('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Лихорадка Эбола в ДР Конго: умер по меньшей мере 131 человек, среди заболевших — врач из США","Ebola fever in DR Congo: at least 131 people have died, including a US doctor",0.0,neutral,"[('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE'), ('at least 131', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Путин едет к Си Цзиньпину вслед за Трампом. Сможет ли он продать в Китай еще немного российского газа?,Putin goes to Xi Jinping after Trump. Can he sell some more Russian gas to China?,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В мечети Сан-Диего застрелены трое мужчин. Подозреваемые —подростки, их нашли мертвыми",Three men shot to death at a San Diego mosque. The suspects were teenagers and were found dead.,-1.0,negative,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('San Diego', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Садовые гномы вышли из бана: выставка цветов в Челси с участием короля Карла, Дэвида Бекхэма и Брайана Мэя","Garden gnomes out of ban: Chelsea Flower Show with King Charles, David Beckham and Brian May",0.0,neutral,"[('Chelsea Flower Show', 'ORG'), ('David Beckham', 'PERSON'), ('Brian May', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Беларусь и Россия начали учения по боевому применению ядерного оружия. Украина призывает партнеров к жесткому ответу,Belarus and Russia have begun exercises on the combat use of nuclear weapons. Ukraine calls on partners for a tough response,0.0,neutral,"[('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп заявил, что отменил новый удар по Ирану по просьбе лидеров Катара, Саудовской Аравии и ОАЭ","Trump said he called off a new strike on Iran at the request of the leaders of Qatar, Saudi Arabia and the UAE",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Спасатели обнаружили тела пяти итальянских дайверов, утонувших в подводных пещерах на Мальдивах. Во время их поисков погиб спасатель",Rescuers have discovered the bodies of five Italian divers who drowned in underwater caves in the Maldives. A rescuer died during their search.,0.0,neutral,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Суд отклонил громкий иск Илона Маска против компании OpenAI и ее главы Сэма Альтмана,The court rejected Elon Musk's high-profile lawsuit against OpenAI and its head Sam Altman,0.0,neutral,"[(""Elon Musk's"", 'PERSON'), ('OpenAI', 'ORG'), ('Sam Altman', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、19日に予定していた対イラン攻撃を「見送り」　湾岸諸国の要請で,Trump ``shuts off'' planned attack on Iran on the 19th at the request of Gulf countries,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the 19th', 'DATE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「僕の声を聞くのはこれが最後かもしれない」　イランで政治的処刑が急増、戦争開始後さらに,"``This may be the last time you hear my voice.'' Political executions increase rapidly in Iran, even more after war begins",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,レバノン、イスラエルの空爆による死者3000人超に　レバノン当局が発表,"More than 3,000 people killed in Israeli airstrikes in Lebanon, Lebanese authorities announce",-1.0,negative,"[('More than 3,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Lebanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米サンディエゴのイスラム教礼拝所で銃撃、容疑者少年2人含む5人死亡,"Shooting at Muslim church in San Diego kills 5 people, including 2 juvenile suspects",-1.0,negative,"[('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('San Diego', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エボラ出血熱、コンゴ民主での死者少なくとも118人に　当局が対策呼びかけ,At least 118 people killed in Ebola outbreak in Democratic Congo; authorities call for countermeasures,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 118', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ebola', 'GPE'), ('Democratic Congo', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ニホンザル「パンチ」のサル山に侵入、アメリカ国籍の男性2人を逮捕,Two American men arrested after invading Japanese macaque ``Punch'' monkey mountain,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('Punch', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】英与党・労働党、12時間の政局で首相が弱体化　3人の有力者はどう動いたのか,"[Commentary] Britain's ruling Labor Party, Prime Minister weakened after 12 hours of political turmoil. How did the three influential figures react?",0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Labor Party', 'ORG'), ('12 hours', 'TIME'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「21万円で転売」、客が殺到し販売中止も　スイスのコラボ時計めぐり世界各地で混乱, 所要時間 1,33","Video, ""Resale for 210,000 yen"", sale canceled due to rush of customers, Swiss collaboration watch causes confusion around the world, Required time 1,33",0.0,neutral,"[('210,000 yen', 'MONEY'), ('Swiss', 'NORP'), ('1,33', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,台湾総統、台湾は紛争を挑発しないが主権は手放さないと　トランプ氏の警告受け,Taiwanese president warns Taiwan not to provoke conflict but not give up sovereignty,-1.0,negative,"[('Taiwanese', 'NORP'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英労働党﻿党首選、実施なら「出馬する」とストリーティング氏　バーナム氏は党を「救う」,Streeting says he will run if UK Labor Party leadership election takes place; Burnham says he will 'save' the party,0.0,neutral,"[('UK Labor Party', 'ORG'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mgomo wa wahudumu wa usafiri wa umma wasitishwa Kenya","Directly, the strike of public transport operators should be called off in Kenya",0.0,neutral,"[('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Zaidi ya watu 3000 wamefariki nchini Lebanon kutokana na mashambulizi ya Israel,More than 3000 people have died in Lebanon due to Israeli attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('More than 3000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kutoka kukimbia ndoa ya utotoni na 'mzee' hadi kuwa mke wa rais,From running away from a childhood marriage with an 'old man' to becoming the wife of the president,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watu 118 wafariki kutokana na Ebola nchini DRC,118 people die from Ebola in DRC,0.0,neutral,"[('118', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ebola', 'GPE'), ('DRC', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ebola ni nini na kwa nini kuzuia mlipuko huu ni vigumu sana?,What is Ebola and why is preventing this outbreak so difficult?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini UAE ilipinga ziara ya Netanyahu nchini humo na kwa nini Israel iliitangaza?,Why did the UAE oppose Netanyahu's visit to the country and why did Israel announce it?,0.0,neutral,"[('UAE', 'ORG'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watu wanne wafariki dunia katika maandamano ya kupinga ongezeko la bei ya mafuta Kenya,Four people died in a protest against the increase in fuel prices in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Samia aunda Tume ya kuchunguza ghasia za uchaguzi mkuu 2025,Samia forms a Commission to investigate the violence of the 2025 general election,0.0,neutral,"[('Commission', 'ORG'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mlipuko wa Ebola nchini DR Congo unatia wasiwasi kiasi gani?,How worrying is the Ebola outbreak in DR Congo?,0.0,neutral,"[('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"CHADEMA vs Msajili, vita vya panzi au mgogoro wa mfumo?","CHADEMA vs Registrar, grasshopper war or system crisis?",-1.0,negative,"[('Registrar', 'ORG')]"
