Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Peor que empezar desde cero"": cuán grande es el reto de reconstruir a Gaza","""Worse than starting from scratch"": how big is the challenge of rebuilding Gaza",-0.13333333333333333,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Las operaciones encubiertas más conocidas de la CIA en América Latina,The CIA's best-known covert operations in Latin America,0.0,"[('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Con su guerra psicológica quieren atemorizar al pueblo, pero el pueblo está unido"": la respuesta de Maduro a la autorización de Trump para que la CIA opere en Venezuela","""With their psychological war they want to frighten the people, but the people are united"": Maduro's response to Trump's authorization for the CIA to operate in Venezuela",0.0,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Mi esposa me dice que busque otro trabajo"": el temor de los pescadores en Venezuela ante los ataques de EE.UU. contra embarcaciones en el Caribe","""My wife tells me to look for another job"": the fear of fishermen in Venezuela in the face of US attacks against vessels in the Caribbean",0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Uruguay aprueba la eutanasia: en qué otros países de América Latina se permite,Uruguay approves euthanasia: in which other Latin American countries it is allowed,-0.0625,"[('Latin American', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत रूस से तेल ख़रीदना बंद कर दे तो क्या होगा?,What will happen if India stops buying oil from Russia?,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,37 साल पहले स्वर्ण मंदिर में घुसे चरमपंथियों को कैसे सरेंडर करना पड़ा,How the extremists who entered the Golden Temple 37 years ago had to surrender,0.3,"[('the Golden Temple', 'FAC'), ('37 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,रिवाबा जडेजा भी बनीं गुजरात सरकार में मंत्री","Live, Rivaba Jadeja also becomes minister in Gujarat government",0.13636363636363635,"[('Rivaba Jadeja', 'PERSON'), ('Gujarat', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वेस्टर्न कपड़ों पर बहस के बाद मुस्कान शर्मा ने जीता मिस ऋषिकेश का ताज, एक हिंदू संगठन ने उठाई थी आपत्ति","Muskaan Sharma won the crown of Miss Rishikesh after the debate on western clothes, a Hindu organization had raised objection.",0.0,"[('Muskaan Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Miss Rishikesh', 'ORG'), ('Hindu', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'डिजिटल अरेस्ट': अब भारतीयों का इस्तेमाल अमेरिका और कनाडा में ठगी के लिए हो रहा है?,'Digital Arrest': Now Indians are being used for fraud in America and Canada?,-0.025,"[(""Digital Arrest'"", 'ORG'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ज़ेलेंस्की से मुलाक़ात के पहले ट्रंप ने की पुतिन से बात, बोले, 'हंगरी में हम मिलेंगे'","Trump spoke to Putin before meeting Zelensky, said, 'We will meet in Hungary'",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Hungary', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"देवबंद में तालिबान के मंत्री के स्वागत पर बहस, दारुल उलूम के प्रिंसिपल मौलाना मदनी ने दिया जवाब","Debate on welcoming Taliban minister in Deoband, Darul Uloom Principal Maulana Madani responded",0.0,"[('Taliban', 'ORG'), ('Deoband', 'ORG'), ('Maulana Madani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"गुजरात में मुख्यमंत्री को छोड़कर सभी मंत्रियों ने दिया इस्तीफ़ा, क्या है वजह?","In Gujarat, all the ministers except the Chief Minister resigned, what is the reason?",0.0,"[('Gujarat', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश में भारत और पाकिस्तान से भी महंगा क्यों है सोना?,Why is gold more expensive in Bangladesh than in India and Pakistan?,0.0,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A expectativa pelo último ato de Barroso no STF em favor do direito ao aborto,The expectation of Barroso's last act in the STF in favor of the right to abortion,0.14285714285714285,"[('Barroso', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Brasil deveria ter 'Petrobras das bebidas alcoólicas' para garantir qualidade após crise do metanol, diz professor da USP","Brazil should have 'Petrobras for alcoholic beverages' to guarantee quality after the methanol crisis, says USP professor",-0.25,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Petrobras', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Em 1ª reunião, chanceleres de Brasil e EUA acertam início de negociação de tarifa e reunião de Lula e Trump 'o mais cedo possível'","In 1st meeting, Brazilian and US foreign ministers agree to start tariff negotiations and meeting between Lula and Trump 'as soon as possible'",-0.0625,"[('1st', 'DATE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Operações secretas da CIA: tensão sem precedentes pode levar à guerra entre Venezuela e EUA?,CIA covert operations: could unprecedented tension lead to war between Venezuela and the US?,0.6,"[('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Uruguai aprova eutanásia: em quais outros países da América Latina procedimento é permitido,Uruguay approves euthanasia: in which other Latin American countries the procedure is allowed,-0.0625,"[('Latin American', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Brasil, Cuba, Chile: o histórico de intervenções da CIA na América Latina","Brazil, Cuba, Chile: the history of CIA interventions in Latin America",0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Chile', 'GPE'), ('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As 'operações secretas' da CIA na Venezuela que Trump autorizou,The CIA 'covert operations' in Venezuela that Trump authorized,0.0,"[('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Não posso me dar ao luxo de salvar os dois gêmeos': como guerra no Sudão deixou uma mãe com uma escolha impossível,'I can't afford to save both twins': How war in Sudan left a mother with an impossible choice,-0.3333333333333333,"[('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O fator Marco Rubio: quem é o secretário 'linha-dura' que Trump escolheu para negociar tarifa com Brasil,The Marco Rubio factor: who is the 'hardline' secretary that Trump chose to negotiate tariffs with Brazil,0.0,"[('Marco Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Резкий рост некрологов: что известно о потерях России в Украине за 1332 дня войны,"A sharp increase in obituaries: what is known about Russia’s losses in Ukraine over 1,332 days of war",-0.125,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('1,332 days', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Хуже, чем с нуля». Во что обойдется восстановление Газы","""Worse than starting from scratch."" How much will it cost to rebuild Gaza?",-0.06666666666666667,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Встретимся в Будапеште». Трамп и Путин впервые поговорили по телефону после саммита на Аляске и договорились о новой встрече,"""Meet me in Budapest."" Trump and Putin spoke on the phone for the first time since the summit in Alaska and agreed to meet again",0.25,"[('Budapest', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Alaska', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский прибыл в Вашингтон, сегодня он встретится с Трампом","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky arrived in Washington, today he will meet with Trump",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Экс-советнику Трампа Джону Болтону предъявили уголовные обвинения,Former Trump adviser John Bolton faces criminal charges,-0.2,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('John Bolton', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Во Франции задержали подозреваемых в подготовке покушения на основателя Gulagu.net,Suspects of plotting an assassination attempt on the founder of Gulagu.net were detained in France,0.0,"[('Gulagu.net', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Израиль хоронит погибших, требует возвращения тел и создает трибунал с правом смертного приговора участникам нападения 7 октября","Israel buries the dead, demands the return of the bodies and creates a tribunal with the power to sentence the participants of the October 7 attack to death.",-0.2,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('October 7', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Так громко и так жутко». Интенсивность ударов по Белгородской области за год выросла в четыре раза,“So loud and so creepy.” The intensity of strikes in the Belgorod region has quadrupled over the year,-0.2,"[('creepy', 'NORP'), ('Belgorod', 'NORP'), ('the year', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В посмертных мемуарах Вирджинии Джуффре вновь выдвигаются обвинения против принца Эндрю,Virginia Giuffre's posthumous memoir renews allegations against Prince Andrew,0.0,"[(""Virginia Giuffre's"", 'PERSON'), ('Prince Andrew', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Битва за железные дороги». Россия усиливает атаки на украинские поезда,"""Battle for the Railways"". Russia intensifies attacks on Ukrainian trains",0.0,"[('Battle for the Railways', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、プーチン氏とハンガリーでの会談で合意　ウクライナ和平への「非常に生産的な」電話協議で,Trump agrees to meet with Putin in Hungary after ``very productive'' telephone talks on peace in Ukraine,0.2,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インド、トランプ氏の主張に疑問呈す　モディ氏がロシア産石油の購入停止に同意との電話は「把握せず」,India questions Trump's claim: 'doesn't understand' Modi's call to agree to halt purchases of Russian oil,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Modi', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EUのドローン防衛システム、2027年末までの完全導入目指すと　対ロシア防衛を強化,EU drone defense system aims to be fully introduced by end of 2027 to strengthen defense against Russia,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('2027', 'DATE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国のためのスパイ疑惑めぐり英政界が紛糾、MI5長官は起訴取り下げに苦言,"British politics in turmoil over suspicion of spying for China, MI5 chief complains about dropping charges",0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ネタニヤフ首相、ハマスに圧力かけると決意表明　死亡した人質全員の発見に向け,Prime Minister Netanyahu expresses determination to put pressure on Hamas to find all dead hostages,-0.2,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【検証】 「ガザ人道財団」が援助物資の配布を停止　停戦合意の発効受け,[Verification] “Gaza Humanitarian Foundation” stops distributing aid supplies after ceasefire agreement takes effect,0.0,[]
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ボルトン元米大統領補佐官を起訴　第1次トランプ政権で解任、批判に転じる,"Former U.S. presidential aide John Bolton was indicted, dismissed during the first Trump administration, and turned to criticism",0.125,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('John Bolton', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,バングラデシュのハシナ前首相に死刑求刑、人道に対する罪　学生主導の反政府デモ弾圧で,Former Bangladeshi Prime Minister Hasina faces death penalty for crimes against humanity in suppressing student-led anti-government demonstrations,0.0,"[('Bangladeshi', 'PERSON'), ('Hasina', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アフガニスタンのタリバン政権とパキスタン、短期の停戦で合意,Afghanistan's Taliban and Pakistan agree to short-term ceasefire,0.0,"[('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('Taliban', 'ORG'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Buriani Raila Odinga: Ibada ya wafu ya mwili wa 'Baba' yaendelea uwanjani Nyayo","Live, Buriani Raila Odinga: The ritual of the dead body of 'Baba' continues at Nyayo Stadium",-0.03181818181818183,"[('Baba', 'PERSON'), ('Nyayo Stadium', 'FAC')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Buriani Raila Odinga: Wakenya wazidiwa na hisia katika ibada ya kumuaga Raila,Buriani Raila Odinga: Kenyans were overwhelmed with emotion at the farewell service for Raila,0.0,"[('Kenyans', 'NORP'), ('Raila', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Raila Odinga: Kutoka kushtakiwa kwa uhaini hadi mikataba na marais,Raila Odinga: From being accused of treason to deals with presidents,0.0,"[('Raila Odinga', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Jeshi kivuli' linavyomsaidia rais wa muda mrefu wa Uganda kusalia madarakani,How the 'shadow army' helps Uganda's long-time president stay in power,0.0,"[('Uganda', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu mchakato mzima wa uchaguzi Tanzania 2025,Know the entire process of the Tanzania 2025 elections,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Man United wanataka £40m kumruhusu Bruno Fernandes kuondoka,European football rumors Friday: Man United want £40m to let Bruno Fernandes leave,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('40', 'MONEY'), ('Bruno Fernandes', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, wajua Raila Odinga aliwahi kuwa 'Mtanzania'?",Did you know Raila Odinga was once a 'Tanzanian'?,0.0,"[('Raila Odinga', 'PERSON'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ndege iliyobeba mwili wa Raila Odinga ndiyo inayofuatiliwa zaidi duniani,The plane carrying Raila Odinga's body is the most tracked in the world,0.5,"[(""Raila Odinga's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ifahamu mikataba iliyomuweka Raila Odinga 'madarakani' licha ya urais kumponyoka,Find out about the agreements that put Raila Odinga 'in power' despite the presidency escaping him,0.0,"[(""Raila Odinga '"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kutoka Gerezani hadi Ikulu: Mfahamu mtawala mpya wa kijeshi nchini Madagascar?,From Prison to Palace: Do you know the new military ruler in Madagascar?,0.018181818181818174,"[('Madagascar', 'GPE')]"
