Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué a Venezuela le falta energía pese a su riqueza petrolera y cómo eso limita su recuperación económica,Why Venezuela lacks energy despite its oil wealth and how this limits its economic recovery,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Cómo se convirtió el expresidente iraní Ahmadineyad en uno de los misterios más extraños de la guerra en Irán?,How did former Iranian President Ahmadinejad become one of the strangest mysteries of the Iran war?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Ahmadinejad', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué nos dicen las nuevas amenazas de Rusia contra Ucrania sobre el estado de la guerra y el nerviosismo del gobierno de Moscú,What Russia's new threats against Ukraine tell us about the state of the war and the nervousness of the Moscow government,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El experimento de la reserva holandesa que pasó de ser un santuario de animales a un campo de muerte,The Dutch reserve experiment that went from being an animal sanctuary to a death camp,-1.0,negative,"[('Dutch', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las paradisíacas playas para turistas en el Caribe a las que los locales no pueden acceder,The paradisiacal beaches for tourists in the Caribbean that locals cannot access,0.0,neutral,"[('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cuál es la predicción del economista alemán que acertó el campeón del Mundial las tres últimas ediciones,What is the prediction of the German economist that the World Cup champion was right in the last three editions?,0.0,neutral,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Es una locura alucinante"": por qué esta semana se están pulverizando los récords de temperatura en Europa occidental","""It's mind-blowing madness"": why temperature records are being shattered in Western Europe this week",1.0,positive,"[('Western Europe', 'LOC'), ('this week', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué ha causado tanta polémica la presentación del primer auto eléctrico de Ferrari,Why has the presentation of Ferrari's first electric car caused so much controversy?,0.0,neutral,"[('Ferrari', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Jonathan Andic, hijo del fundador de Mango, se pronuncia por primera vez desde que fue acusado de la muerte de su padre","Jonathan Andic, son of the founder of Mango, speaks out for the first time since he was accused of his father's death",-1.0,negative,"[('Jonathan Andic', 'PERSON'), ('Mango', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué llegó a su fin el gasto de cientos de miles de millones de dólares de Arabia Saudita en ideas futuristas y extravagantes,"Why Saudi Arabia's spending hundreds of billions of dollars on futuristic, outlandish ideas has come to an end",0.0,neutral,"[(""Saudi Arabia's"", 'GPE'), ('hundreds of billions of dollars', 'MONEY')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"एसआईआर पर सुप्रीम कोर्ट का फ़ैसला, बीजेपी ने किया स्वागत, विपक्ष क्या बोला","Supreme Court's decision on SIR, BJP welcomed it, what did the opposition say?",0.0,neutral,"[(""Supreme Court's"", 'ORG'), ('SIR', 'ORG'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,पिनाराई विजयन के घर छापा मारने पहुंचे ईडी अधिकारियों की कार पर सीपीएम कार्यकर्ताओं का हमला","Live, CPM workers attack on the car of ED officers who came to raid Pinarayi Vijayan's house",-1.0,negative,"[('ED', 'ORG'), (""Pinarayi Vijayan's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वाराणसी गंगा इफ़्तार केस: आरोप, धाराएँ और क़ानूनी सवालों में उलझा मामला","Varanasi Ganga Iftar Case: Case entangled in charges, sections and legal questions",0.0,neutral,"[('Varanasi Ganga', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पुरुषों से ज़्यादा क्यों जीती हैं महिलाएं?,Why do women live longer than men?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,मोदी के प्रशंसक और सलाहकार रहे अर्थशास्त्री अब आलोचना करते हुए दे रहे ये तर्क,Economists who were fans and advisors of Modi are now giving these arguments while criticizing,0.0,neutral,"[('Modi', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ताइवान ने भारत को छोड़ा पीछे,  आगे की राह भी दिख रही मुश्किल","Taiwan left India behind, the path ahead also looks difficult",0.0,neutral,"[('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'बेख़ौफ़' पाटीदार के पास था गुजरात के ख़िलाफ़ ये प्लान, आरसीबी लगातार दूसरी बार फ़ाइनल में","'Fearless' Patidar had this plan against Gujarat, RCB in the final for the second consecutive time",0.0,neutral,"[('Patidar', 'PERSON'), ('Gujarat', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"मध्य प्रदेश: बारात लेकर पहुंच गए 42 दूल्हे लेकिन दुल्हनें नदारद, धोखाधड़ी के मामले में चार पर केस दर्ज","Madhya Pradesh: 42 grooms arrived with the wedding procession but brides were missing, case registered against four for fraud.",0.0,neutral,"[('Madhya Pradesh', 'PERSON'), ('42', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,जनभागीदारी से 'पानी कमाकर' सूखे को हराने वाले महाराष्ट्र के 23 गांवों की कहानी,Story of 23 villages of Maharashtra that defeated drought by 'earning water' through public participation,0.0,neutral,"[('23', 'CARDINAL'), ('Maharashtra', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पश्चिम बंगाल: 400 कैंटीनों में पाँच रुपये में मछली-भात, शुभेंदु अधिकारी ने और क्या कहा?","West Bengal: Fish and rice for five rupees in 400 canteens, what else did Shubhendu Adhikari say?",0.0,neutral,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('400', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shubhendu Adhikari', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Enquanto Brasil discute fim da escala 6x1, Argentina vai na contramão do mundo com reforma que retira direitos e permite jornada de até 12 horas por dia","While Brazil discusses the end of the 6x1 scale, Argentina goes against the world with a reform that removes rights and allows working hours of up to 12 hours a day",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the end of the', 'DATE'), ('6x1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('working hours', 'TIME'), ('up to 12 hours', 'TIME')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Crise de quê?': Flávio Bolsonaro aposta em Trump e debate sobre facções contra desgaste do caso Master,'Crisis of what?': Flávio Bolsonaro bets on Trump and debates about factions against erosion of the Master case,-1.0,negative,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Encontro com Trump é trunfo para Flávio Bolsonaro e acende alerta sobre papel da Casa Branca na eleição,Meeting with Trump is an asset for Flávio Bolsonaro and raises awareness about the role of the White House in the election,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que 'guru' da Copa prevê para o Brasil — e qual seleção será campeã,What World Cup 'guru' predicts for Brazil — and which team will win,1.0,positive,"[(""World Cup '"", 'EVENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Nasa revela seus planos para construir base lunar permanente até 2032,NASA reveals its plans to build a permanent lunar base by 2032,0.0,neutral,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('2032', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como a guerra no Irã afeta o real e outras moedas locais: veja quem são os ganhadores e os perdedores com o conflito,How the war in Iran affects the real and other local currencies: see who the winners and losers are from the conflict,-0.3333,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil ativa plano de contingência contra o Ebola; saiba o que isso quer dizer e por que o país nunca teve casos,Brazil activates contingency plan against Ebola; find out what this means and why the country has never had cases,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Ebola', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Hipersexualização dos seios traz ansiedade para mulheres': o que uma socióloga descobriu ao estudar o tema,'Hypersexualization of breasts causes anxiety for women': what a sociologist discovered when studying the topic,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_27,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"São Paulo é campeão de 'homicídios ocultos', apesar de ter menor taxa de assassinatos do país, aponta Atlas da Violência","São Paulo is champion of 'hidden homicides', despite having the lowest murder rate in the country, points out Atlas of Violence",0.0,neutral,"[('São Paulo', 'PERSON'), ('Atlas of Violence', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Британская разведка: Россия угрожает критической инфраструктуре и демократии,British intelligence: Russia threatens critical infrastructure and democracy,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: атаки на Запорожье и Чернигов, удары по Севастополю и Таганрогу","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: attacks on Zaporozhye and Chernigov, attacks on Sevastopol and Taganrog",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zaporozhye', 'ORG'), ('Chernigov', 'ORG'), ('Sevastopol', 'ORG'), ('Taganrog', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Большой сделки» США с Ираном пока не будет? Объясняет востоковед Руслан Сулейманов,Will there be a “Grand Deal” between the US and Iran yet? Orientalist Ruslan Suleymanov explains,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ruslan Suleymanov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Израиль объявил о гибели нового главы военного крыла ХАМАС в результате удара по Газе,Israel announces the death of the new head of Hamas's military wing in a strike on Gaza,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Обыски, аресты, суды: Париж потрясла волна сексуализированного насилия над детьми в садах и школах","Searches, arrests, trials: Paris was rocked by a wave of sexualized violence against children in kindergartens and schools",0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В НАСА рассказали о следующих шагах по созданию постоянной лунной базы,NASA spoke about the next steps to create a permanent lunar base,0.0,neutral,"[('NASA', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Китае казнен отравитель владельца империи видеоигр — правообладателя «Задачи трех тел»,"The poisoner of the owner of the video game empire - the copyright holder of the ""Three Body Problem"" - has been executed in China.",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Несоразмерная санкция». Госдума разрешила арестовывать имущество уехавших россиян за высказывания против войны и властей,"""Disproportionate sanction."" The State Duma allowed to seize the property of Russians who left for statements against the war and the authorities",-1.0,negative,"[('The State Duma', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Russians', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«У него два пути: тюрьма, фронт». Антивоенного активиста выдворяют из Финляндии в Россию","“He has two paths: prison, front.” Anti-war activist expelled from Finland to Russia",-1.0,negative,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Finland', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Эскалация ради эскалации? Как понимать новые угрозы России «системно бить по Киеву»,Escalation for the sake of escalation? How to understand Russia’s new threats to “systematically hit Kyiv”,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イラン、アメリカの空爆を非難　停戦合意への「重大な違反」と,"Iran condemns US airstrike, calling it 'serious violation' of ceasefire agreement",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリスの5月の最高気温、2日連続で更新　ロンドンで35度を超える,Highest temperature in May in the UK updated for 2nd consecutive day - over 35 degrees in London,0.0,neutral,"[('May', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('2nd consecutive day', 'DATE'), ('35 degrees', 'QUANTITY'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米NASA、月面基地建設計画を発表　中国との宇宙開発競争のなか,US NASA announces plans to build a moon base amid space competition with China,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('NASA', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアがイギリスの重要インフラや民主主義を「執拗に攻撃」　英情報トップが警告へ,Russia 'relentlessly attacks' UK critical infrastructure and democracy; UK intelligence chief warns,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエル、ハマス軍事部門トップを殺害と発表　ガザ市空爆で,Israel announces Hamas military chief killed in Gaza airstrike,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,レバノンで30人以上死亡、イスラエルが空爆を強化,"More than 30 killed in Lebanon, Israel ramps up airstrikes",-1.0,negative,"[('More than 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米軍、イラン南部を空爆　合意は「目前ではない」とイランが説明後,"US military launches airstrikes on southern Iran after Iran says agreement is ""not imminent""",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,教皇、AIの「武装解除」訴え　初の回勅は先端技術による搾取に焦点,"Pope calls for “disarmament” of AI, first encyclical focuses on exploitation by advanced technology",0.0,neutral,"[('Pope', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシア、キーウをさらに攻撃すると脅す　外国人に市外退避を呼びかけ,"Russia threatens further attacks on Kiv, asks foreigners to evacuate city",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Kiv', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,AIは人間の知性を低下させる？　英グリニッジ天文台が警告,Will AI reduce human intelligence? UK Greenwich Observatory warns,-1.0,negative,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Greenwich Observatory', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Israel yatangaza kumuua kamanda wa Hamas baada ya shambulizi la anga Gaza","Directly, Israel announces the killing of a Hamas commander after an airstrike in Gaza",-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini gari lako huenda linakusanya na kutoa taarifa zako binafsi?,Why might your car collect and release your personal information?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kuoga na maji ya barafu hadi kunywa maziwa ya lozi: Siri ya mafanikio ya Mohamed Salah Liverpool,From taking an ice bath to drinking almond milk: Mohamed Salah's secret to Liverpool's success,1.0,positive,"[(""Mohamed Salah's"", 'PERSON'), ('Liverpool', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Waislamu kote duniani wanaadhimisha sherehe za Eid al-Adha,Muslims around the world are celebrating Eid al-Adha,0.0,neutral,"[('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('Eid al-Adha', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,WARIDI WA BBC: 'Nilitokwa na haja ndogo bila kukoma kwa miaka minne',BBC Rose: 'I had non-stop bowel movements for four years',0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), (""four years'"", 'DATE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Rare Earth: Je, madini haya yataleta maajabu Tanzania?",Rare Earth: Will this mineral bring wonders to Tanzania?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Ndege za kivita za Marekani zaonekana karibu na Cuba, vita vinanukia?","American warplanes are seen near Cuba, does war smell?",-1.0,negative,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi Mahmoud Ahmadinejad alivyogeuka fumbo la vita Iran,How Mahmoud Ahmadinejad became a mystery of war in Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Mahmoud Ahmadinejad', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wanamichezo 10 wanaolipwa fedha nyingi zaidi Duniani 2026,10 highest paid sportsmen in the world 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mama mzazi wa aliyekuwa Rais wa Tanzania John Magufuli afariki dunia,The mother of the former President of Tanzania John Magufuli has passed away,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('John Magufuli', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ex-champ Fury sets Dublin fight before ‘Battle of Britain’ against Joshua,Ex-champ Fury sets Dublin fight before ‘Battle of Britain’ against Joshua,0.0,neutral,"[('Dublin', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Joshua', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US strike on alleged drug boat in Pacific kills one,US strike on alleged drug boat in Pacific kills one,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Pacific kills', 'LOC'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Sanctions fears as Krygyzstan shutters companies suspected of aiding Russia,Sanctions fears as Krygyzstan shutters companies suspected of aiding Russia,0.0,neutral,"[('Krygyzstan', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Aerial video shows ruptured chemical tank in Washington,Aerial video shows ruptured chemical tank in Washington,0.0,neutral,"[('Washington', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,German police clash with Crystal Palace and Vallecano fans at Europa final,German police clash with Crystal Palace and Vallecano fans at Europa final,0.0,neutral,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('Crystal Palace', 'FAC'), ('Vallecano', 'ORG'), ('Europa', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ken Paxton wins Texas primary election: Results and key takeaways,Ken Paxton wins Texas primary election: Results and key takeaways,1.0,positive,"[('Ken Paxton', 'PERSON'), ('Texas', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel claims head of Hamas military wing killed in Gaza strike,Israel claims head of Hamas military wing killed in Gaza strike,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israeli air attack kills at least two in southern Lebanon,Israeli air attack kills at least two in southern Lebanon,-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('at least two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Messi set for more tests ahead of World Cup but Argentina are optimistic,Messi set for more tests ahead of World Cup but Argentina are optimistic,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Supreme Court constitutes panel to draw up action plan to clean Yamuna,Supreme Court constitutes panel to draw up action plan to clean Yamuna,0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Yamuna', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Assam Assembly passes Uniform Civil Code Bill,Assam Assembly passes Uniform Civil Code Bill,0.0,neutral,"[('Assam Assembly', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Singapore court orders six-month jail term for Byju Raveendran over contempt,Singapore court orders six-month jail term for Byju Raveendran over contempt,0.0,neutral,"[('Singapore', 'GPE'), ('six-month', 'DATE'), ('Byju Raveendran', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,SC upholds SIR as an advancement towards free and fair elections,SC upholds SIR as an advancement towards free and fair elections,-1.0,negative,"[('SC', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,What Tamil Nadu CM Vijay really needs to see at Fort St. George,What Tamil Nadu CM Vijay really needs to see at Fort St. George,0.0,neutral,"[('Tamil Nadu CM Vijay', 'PERSON'), ('Fort St. George', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Will accord top priority to safety of women and children: T.N. tells Madras High Court,Will accord top priority to safety of women and children: T.N. tells Madras High Court,0.0,neutral,"[('T.N.', 'ORG'), ('Madras High Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Cabinet approves extension of SARTHAK-PDS scheme with central outlay of ₹25,530 crore","Cabinet approves extension of SARTHAK-PDS scheme with central outlay of ₹25,530 crore",0.0,neutral,"[('Cabinet', 'ORG'), ('SARTHAK', 'ORG'), ('25,530', 'MONEY')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Iran-Israel war LIVE: Iran Guards official says ‘low’ possibility of renewed war with U.S.,Iran-Israel war LIVE: Iran Guards official says ‘low’ possibility of renewed war with U.S.,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran Guards', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Govt. employees mandated to visit tourist spots every three months and file reports,Govt. employees mandated to visit tourist spots every three months and file reports,0.0,neutral,"[('every three months', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_27,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Bad fences: On Marco Rubio’s India visit,​Bad fences: On Marco Rubio’s India visit,0.0,neutral,"[('Marco Rubio’s', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Ebola-hit DR Congo faces 'catastrophic collision' of disease and conflict, WHO warns","Ebola-hit DR Congo faces 'catastrophic collision' of disease and conflict, WHO warns",-1.0,negative,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Israeli strike in Gaza City kills new head of Hamas's military wing,Israeli strike in Gaza City kills new head of Hamas's military wing,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza City', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Five people found alive after week trapped in flooded Laos cave,Five people found alive after week trapped in flooded Laos cave,0.0,neutral,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('week', 'DATE'), ('Laos', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Dozens killed in Lebanon as Israel intensifies strikes,Dozens killed in Lebanon as Israel intensifies strikes,-1.0,negative,"[('Dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Woman caught after 30 years on the run is jailed for armed robberies,Woman caught after 30 years on the run is jailed for armed robberies,0.0,neutral,"[('30 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,One killed and nine missing after chemical explosion at US paper mill,One killed and nine missing after chemical explosion at US paper mill,-1.0,negative,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Hotel that refused to give tourist tap water acted lawfully, Italian court rules","Hotel that refused to give tourist tap water acted lawfully, Italian court rules",0.0,neutral,"[('Italian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump-backed challenger beats veteran US senator in Texas primary,Trump-backed challenger beats veteran US senator in Texas primary,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Texas', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,South Korea detains dissident who fled China in rubber boat,South Korea detains dissident who fled China in rubber boat,0.0,neutral,"[('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Iran condemns US strikes as 'gross violation' of ceasefire,Iran condemns US strikes as 'gross violation' of ceasefire,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iran War Live Updates: Fighting Flares in Lebanon, Complicating U.S.-Iran Peace Talks","Iran War Live Updates: Fighting Flares in Lebanon, Complicating U.S.-Iran Peace Talks",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran War Live Updates: Fighting Flares', 'EVENT'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iranians Emerge From a ‘Black Hole’ as Internet Shutdown Eases,Iranians Emerge From a ‘Black Hole’ as Internet Shutdown Eases,0.0,neutral,"[('Iranians', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Nigel Farage’s Far-Right Party Is Now Central to British Politics,Nigel Farage’s Far-Right Party Is Now Central to British Politics,0.0,neutral,"[('Nigel Farage’s', 'PERSON'), ('Far-Right Party', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Where Time Is Always 15 Minutes Apart From Everywhere Else,Where Time Is Always 15 Minutes Apart From Everywhere Else,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Inventor of the Basque Cheesecake Plans to Retire. His Secret: He Prefers Chocolate,Inventor of the Basque Cheesecake Plans to Retire. His Secret: He Prefers Chocolate,0.0,neutral,"[('Retire', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Quiet Pacific Village Becomes China’s Security Testing Ground,A Quiet Pacific Village Becomes China’s Security Testing Ground,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,High-Level British Spy Warns of Expanding Russia Threat,High-Level British Spy Warns of Expanding Russia Threat,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Threat of Deportations Leads to Risky Childbirth for Haitian Mothers,Threat of Deportations Leads to Risky Childbirth for Haitian Mothers,0.0,neutral,"[('Haitian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Wars in Ukraine and Iran Are More Alike Than You May Think,The Wars in Ukraine and Iran Are More Alike Than You May Think,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_27,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iceland, Rattled by Trump’s Greenland Threats, Weighs Joining the E.U.","Iceland, Rattled by Trump’s Greenland Threats, Weighs Joining the E.U.",0.0,neutral,"[('Iceland', 'GPE'), ('Trump’s Greenland Threats', 'PERSON'), ('Weighs Joining', 'PERSON'), ('E.U.', 'GPE')]"
