Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El hombre que se infiltró en Auschwitz para revelar al mundo las atrocidades de Hitler y los nazis,The man who infiltrated Auschwitz to reveal to the world the atrocities of Hitler and the Nazis,0.0,"[('Auschwitz', 'PERSON'), ('Hitler', 'PERSON'), ('Nazis', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Trump declara el cierre total del espacio aéreo de Venezuela y el gobierno de Caracas califica el anuncio de ""amenaza colonialista""","Trump declares the total closure of Venezuelan airspace and the Caracas government describes the announcement as a ""colonialist threat""",0.0,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('Caracas', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Juan Orlando Hernández: quién es el expresidente de Honduras que será indultado por Trump y por qué la justicia de EE.UU. lo acusó de convertir a su país en un ""narcoestado""","Juan Orlando Hernández: who is the former president of Honduras who will be pardoned by Trump and why the US justice system accused him of turning his country into a ""narco-state""",0.0,"[('Juan Orlando Hernández', 'PERSON'), ('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué los ricos y poderosos no podían decirle 'no' a Jeffrey Epstein,Why the rich and powerful couldn't say 'no' to Jeffrey Epstein,0.3375,"[('Jeffrey Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué son las ingeniosas cajas de Ward y cómo transformaron la economía mundial,What are Ward's ingenious boxes and how did they transform the world economy?,0.5,"[('Ward', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सिंध, जो कई धर्मों और साम्राज्यों का गवाह रहा, भारत का हिस्सा क्यों नहीं बना?","Why did Sindh, which witnessed many religions and empires, not become a part of India?",0.5,"[('Sindh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'अच्छे कपड़े पहन रही हूं, मोदी जी से मिली हूं, यह सिर्फ़ क्रिकेट की वजह से', वर्ल्ड चैंपियन ब्लाइंड महिला क्रिकेटर्स की कहानी","'I am wearing nice clothes, I have met Modi ji, it is only because of cricket', the story of world champion blind women cricketers",0.033333333333333326,"[('Modi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,चक्रवाती तूफ़ान दित्वाह तमिलनाडु–पुदुचेरी से सिर्फ़ 70 किलोमीटर दूर","Live, Cyclone Ditvaah just 70 km away from Tamil Nadu-Puducherry",0.13636363636363635,"[('70 km', 'QUANTITY'), ('Tamil Nadu-Puducherry', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पीरियड ब्लड को चेहरे पर लगाने का ट्रेंड, डॉक्टर क्या कहते हैं?","Trend of applying period blood on face, what do doctors say?",0.0,[]
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दित्वाह तूफ़ान: श्रीलंका में तबाही के बाद भारत की ओर बढ़ा, कहां-कहां होगा कितना असर","Ditvah storm: After devastation in Sri Lanka, it moved towards India, where and how much impact will it have?",0.2,"[('Ditvah', 'PERSON'), ('Sri Lanka', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,आंखों के सामने छुपी हुई... मुंबई की आर्ट डेको शैली की इमारतों में क्या है ख़ास,Hidden before the eyes... what is special in the Art Deco style buildings of Mumbai?,0.09523809523809525,"[('the Art Deco', 'FAC'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,असम के विधायक अमीनुल इस्लाम को सात महीने जेल में क्यों गुज़ारने पड़े?,Why did Assam MLA Aminul Islam have to spend seven months in jail?,-0.1,"[('seven months', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुतिन की भारत यात्रा क्यों है अहम और विदेशी मीडिया इस पर क्या लिख रहा है,Why is Putin's visit to India important and what is the foreign media writing about it?,0.1375,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान: बारिश में आइसक्रीम की तलाश में निकली बच्ची 17 साल बाद यूं लौटी घर,Pakistan: The girl who went in search of ice cream in the rain returned home like this after 17 years,0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('17 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A 'reforma agrária' que ajudou imigrantes alemães e italianos a prosperarem no Sul do Brasil,The 'agrarian reform' that helped German and Italian immigrants prosper in southern Brazil,0.0,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Venezuela chama de 'ameaça colonialista' anúncio de Trump de fechar seu espaço aéreo,Venezuela calls Trump's announcement to close its airspace a 'colonialist threat',0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quem é o ex-presidente de Honduras condenado por narcotráfico que tem apoio de Trump para deixar prisão,Who is the former president of Honduras convicted of drug trafficking who has Trump's support to leave prison,0.0,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A 'pobreza' repentina que faz com que milhões de pessoas nos EUA dependam de ajuda para não passar fome,The sudden 'poverty' that leaves millions of people in the US dependent on aid to avoid going hungry,0.0,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Quando fiz 10 anos de casada, falei para meu marido: o que você acha da gente abrir o nosso casamento?'","'When I was 10 years married, I said to my husband: what do you think about us opening our marriage?'",0.25,"[('10 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que são as engenhosas caixas de Ward e como elas transformaram a economia mundial,What are Ward's ingenious boxes and how they transformed the world economy,0.5,"[('Ward', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Será que eu sou chato? O que meu comportamento diz sobre mim,Am I boring? What my behavior says about me,-1.0,[]
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que os ricos e poderosos não conseguiam dizer não a Epstein,Why the Rich and Powerful Couldn't Say No to Epstein,0.3375,[]
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que o mundo deveria viver como o Uruguai para frear a exploração dos recursos do planeta,Why the world should live like Uruguay to stop the exploitation of the planet's resources,0.13636363636363635,"[('Uruguay', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Тюрьма или смерть». В туннелях в секторе Газа блокированы сотни боевиков ХАМАС. Почему это стало тестом на прочность мирного плана Трампа?,"""Prison or death."" Hundreds of Hamas militants are blocked in the tunnels in the Gaza Strip. Why did this test the strength of Trump's peace plan?",0.0,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('the Gaza Strip', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сэр Том Стоппард: остроумный и веселый писатель с серьезными мыслями,Sir Tom Stoppard: a witty and funny writer with serious thoughts,0.1388888888888889,"[('Tom Stoppard', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,25 фаворитов на премию «Оскар» и где их смотреть,25 Oscar favorites and where to watch them,0.0,"[('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('Oscar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп объявил о закрытии воздушного пространства над Венесуэлой. В Венесуэле назвали это агрессией,Trump announced the closure of airspace over Venezuela. In Venezuela they called it aggression,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Макрон встретится с Зеленским в понедельник; Рубио примет участие во встрече во Флориде","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Macron to meet Zelensky on Monday; Rubio will attend the meeting in Florida",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Macron', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Фото: папа римский Лев XIV посетил Голубую мечеть в Стамбуле,Photo: Pope Leo XIV visited the Blue Mosque in Istanbul,0.0,"[('Leo XIV', 'PERSON'), ('the Blue Mosque', 'ORG'), ('Istanbul', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Британский драматург Том Стоппард скончался в возрасте 88 лет,British playwright Tom Stoppard dies at 88,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Tom Stoppard', 'PERSON'), ('88', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,США приостановили принятие всех решений об убежище после стрельбы в нацгвардейцев в Вашингтоне,US suspends all asylum decisions following shooting of National Guardsmen in Washington,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('National Guardsmen', 'ORG'), ('Washington', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Тысячам самолетов Airbus необходимо срочно обновить ПО. Причина — солнечное излучение,Thousands of Airbus aircraft are in urgent need of a software update. Cause: Solar radiation,0.0,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Airbus', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Действующие, спящие, потухшие вулканы: как понять, есть ли опасность извержения","Active, dormant, extinct volcanoes: how to understand whether there is a danger of eruption",-0.26666666666666666,[]
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、すべての亡命申請に対して決定停止　トランプ氏は途上国からの移民を「恒久的に停止」と,US suspends decisions on all asylum applications; Trump calls for ``permanently halting'' immigration from developing countries,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港の高層住宅群火災、死者少なくとも128人に　さらに８人を汚職容疑で逮捕,At least 128 people killed in Hong Kong high-rise housing fire; 8 more arrested on corruption charges,0.0,"[('At least 128', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('8', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏の側近、イェルマーク長官が辞任　汚職対策当局が自宅を強制捜査,Zelenskiy's close aide Yermak resigns; anti-corruption authorities raid his home,0.0,"[('Zelenskiy', 'ORG'), ('Yermak', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,同性婚認めない現行法の規定、東京高裁は「合憲」と　 ほか5件と判断分かれる,"The Tokyo High Court rules that the current law prohibiting same-sex marriage is constitutional, along with 5 other cases.",0.011666666666666667,"[('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,行方不明者の家族ら、苦しみのなか待ち続ける　香港高層住宅群火災,Families of missing people continue to wait in agony as fire breaks out in Hong Kong high-rise housing complex,-0.25,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル部隊、投降したとみられるパレスチナ人2人を殺害　映像が浮上,Video emerges of Israeli troops killing two Palestinians believed to have surrendered,0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ルーヴル美術館、欧州圏以外からの来場者の入場料を45％値上げへ　改修資金に,Louvre Museum to raise admission fee by 45% for visitors from outside Europe to fund renovations,0.0,"[('Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('45%', 'PERCENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米首都銃撃で負傷した州兵1人が死亡、容疑者は過去にアフガニスタンで米CIAと協力,One National Guard soldier injured in US capital shooting dies; suspect previously worked with US CIA in Afghanistan,-0.16666666666666666,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('National Guard', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,フランスが限定的な兵役を再導入へ、徴兵制廃止から25年,"France to reintroduce limited military service, 25 years after abolishing conscription",-0.08571428571428572,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('25 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Ukraine yashambulia meli za mafuta za Urusi katika Bahari Nyeusi","Directly, Ukraine attacks Russian oil tankers in the Black Sea",-0.022222222222222216,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanasoka wanawake watano Afrika wanaolipwa fedha nyingi zaidi 2025,Five female footballers in Africa who are paid the most money in 2025,0.25,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanyama wanaokwepa kifo kupitia uwezo wa kinga zao,Animals that avoid death through their immune system,0.0,[]
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumapili: Liverpool ni moja ya vilabu wanaomfukuzia Ndiaye,European football rumors on Sunday: Liverpool is one of the clubs chasing Ndiaye,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Ndiaye', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Papa leo avua viatu na kuingia msikitini Uturuki,The Pope today took off his shoes and entered the mosque in Turkey,0.0,"[('today', 'DATE'), ('Turkey', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini vita dhidi ya ukatili wa wanawake ni ya kipekee?,Why is the fight against violence against women unique?,0.375,[]
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, kinda wa Chelsea Estevao atafikia kiwango cha Yamal?",Will the young Chelsea Estevao reach the level of Yamal?,0.1,"[('Chelsea Estevao', 'ORG'), ('Yamal', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tanzania: Tunashughulikia azimio la Umoja wa Ulaya kidiplomasia,Tanzania: We are handling the EU resolution diplomatically,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Serikali ya Tanzania: Azimio la EU halina chembe ya ukweli,Government of Tanzania: The EU resolution has no grain of truth,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_30,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hatua ya bunge la Ulaya dhidi ya Tanzania ina maana gani?,What does the action of the European Parliament against Tanzania mean?,-0.07083333333333333,"[('the European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
