Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El gobierno de Venezuela extradita a EE.UU. al empresario colombiano Alex Saab, aliado y supuesto testaferro de Nicolás Maduro","The government of Venezuela extradites to the United States Colombian businessman Alex Saab, ally and alleged figurehead of Nicolás Maduro",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('Alex Saab', 'PERSON'), ('Nicolás', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué fue la Revolución Cultural de Mao Zedong y cómo marcó la historia de China hace 60 años,What was Mao Zedong's Cultural Revolution and how it marked the history of China 60 years ago,0.0,neutral,"[(""Mao Zedong's"", 'PERSON'), ('Cultural Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('60 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""En la ruina y profundamente endeudado"": así murió, hace 100 años, Mehmed VI, el último sultán del Imperio otomano","""In ruin and deeply in debt"": this is how Mehmed VI, the last sultan of the Ottoman Empire, died 100 years ago",0.0,neutral,"[('Mehmed VI', 'ORG'), ('the Ottoman Empire', 'GPE'), ('100 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Suiza abrirá sus archivos secretos sobre Joseph Mengele, pero ¿cuál es la relación del ""Ángel de la muerte nazi"" con ese país?","Switzerland will open its secret files on Joseph Mengele, but what is the relationship of the ""Nazi Angel of Death"" with that country?",-1.0,negative,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Joseph Mengele', 'PERSON'), ('the ""Nazi Angel of Death', 'LAW')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Muere un buzo que intentaba rescatar los cuerpos de los 5 italianos que se ahogaron en las Maldivas,A diver dies who was trying to rescue the bodies of the 5 Italians who drowned in the Maldives,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italians', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Trump advierte a Taiwán que no puede declarar su independencia y el gobierno taiwanés responde que es ""un país soberano""","Trump warns Taiwan that it cannot declare its independence and the Taiwanese government responds that it is ""a sovereign country""",-1.0,negative,"[('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('Taiwanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La trágica muerte de 5 buceadores italianos mientras exploraban unas cuevas en Maldivas,The tragic death of 5 Italian divers while exploring caves in the Maldives,-1.0,negative,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Con el 100% de las actas escrutadas, Keiko Fujimori y Roberto Sánchez se disputarán la presidencia de Perú el 7 de junio","With 100% of the minutes scrutinized, Keiko Fujimori and Roberto Sánchez will compete for the presidency of Peru on June 7",0.0,neutral,"[('100%', 'PERCENT'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('Peru', 'GPE'), ('June 7', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Un verdadero milagro"": rescatan a 11 personas con vida después de que su avión se estrellara en el Atlántico","""A true miracle"": 11 people rescued alive after their plane crashed in the Atlantic",0.0,neutral,"[('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('Atlantic', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué opinan los críticos de China dentro del movimiento MAGA sobre el viaje de Trump a Pekín,What China critics within the MAGA movement think about Trump's trip to Beijing,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('MAGA', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"चांदी के आयात को लेकर सरकार का बड़ा फ़ैसला, लेकिन सोने के लिए नहीं कोई शर्त","Government's big decision regarding import of silver, but no condition for gold",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,नीट पेपर लीक मामला: अभियुक्त मनीषा मंधारे को 14 दिन की सीबीआई हिरासत में भेजा गया","Live, NEET paper leak case: Accused Manisha Mandhare sent to 14-day CBI custody",0.0,neutral,"[('NEET', 'ORG'), ('14-day', 'DATE'), ('CBI', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"होर्मुज़ स्ट्रेट से 'एक्सिस ऑफ़ रेज़िस्टेंस' तक, ईरान और अमेरिका के बीच किन 5 मुद्दों पर बात अटकी है","From Hormuz Strait to 'Axis of Resistance', what are the 5 issues on which talks are stuck between Iran and America",0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अर्थव्यवस्था को संकट में तो नहीं डाल देगी किफ़ायत की प्रधानमंत्री की अपील? जानिए क्या कहते हैं विशेषज्ञ,Will the Prime Minister's appeal for austerity put the economy in trouble? Know what experts say,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,दिल्ली आ रही राजधानी एक्सप्रेस के एसी कोच में लगी आग, सभी यात्री सुरक्षित, अवधि 0,47","Video, Fire in AC coach of Rajdhani Express coming to Delhi, all passengers safe, duration 0,47",0.0,neutral,"[('AC', 'ORG'), ('Rajdhani Express', 'ORG'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सीबीएसई रिज़ल्टः इस बार इतना क्यों गिरा परीक्षा पास करने वाले छात्रों का प्रतिशत,CBSE Result: Why did the percentage of students passing the exam fall so much this time?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,कारीगरी के लिए मशहूर उत्तर प्रदेश के इन शहरों के हुनरबाज़ों के सामने कैसी चुनौतियां?, अवधि 10,12","Video, What challenges do the artisans of these cities of Uttar Pradesh, famous for their craftsmanship, face?, Duration 10,12",0.0,neutral,"[('Uttar Pradesh', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"आईपीएल 2026: कौन हैं महंगे खिलाड़ियों में से एक मथीशा पथिराना, जो पहले ही मैच में हो गए बाहर","IPL 2026: Who is Mathisha Pathirana, one of the expensive players, who was out in the very first match?",0.0,neutral,"[('Mathisha Pathirana', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भाव्या रंजन बिना कोचिंग ट्यूशन कैसे बनीं 12वीं सीबीएसई की नेशनल टॉपर,How Bhavya Ranjan became 12th CBSE national topper without coaching tuition,0.0,neutral,"[('Bhavya Ranjan', 'PERSON'), ('CBSE', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्या अमेरिका और इसराइल फिर से कर रहे हैं ईरान पर हमले की तैयारी?,Are America and Israel preparing to attack Iran again?,-1.0,negative,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que o governo da Índia pediu aos seus cidadãos que não comprem ouro durante um ano,Why the Indian government asked its citizens not to buy gold for a year,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('a year', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Havengate: o fundo na mira da PF que conecta Vorcaro, Flávio e Eduardo Bolsonaro","Havengate: the fund in the PF's sights that connects Vorcaro, Flávio and Eduardo Bolsonaro",0.0,neutral,"[('Vorcaro', 'ORG'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Eduardo Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Após visita à China, Trump alerta Taiwan contra independência","After visit to China, Trump warns Taiwan against independence",-1.0,negative,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que é a Armadilha de Tucídides, conceito que Xi Jinping usa para definir relação entre EUA e China","What is the Thucydides Trap, a concept that Xi Jinping uses to define the relationship between the USA and China",0.0,neutral,"[('the Thucydides Trap', 'PERSON'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A trágica morte de mergulhadores enquanto exploravam cavernas nas Maldivas,The tragic death of divers while exploring caves in the Maldives,-1.0,negative,"[('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Suíça vai divulgar arquivos secretos sobre Mengele, o 'Anjo da Morte' nazista que morreu no Brasil","Switzerland will release secret files on Mengele, the Nazi 'Angel of Death' who died in Brazil",-1.0,negative,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Mengele', 'PERSON'), ('Nazi', 'NORP'), (""Angel of Death'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como cuidar dos seus cabos de celular (certamente não da maneira como você está fazendo),How to take care of your cell phone cables (certainly not the way you're doing it),0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,3 formas divertidas de manter o cérebro jovem por mais tempo,3 fun ways to keep your brain young for longer,0.0,neutral,"[('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Após negar, Eduardo confirma ter assinado contrato de gestão financeira de filme de Bolsonaro; entenda","After denying, Eduardo confirms that he signed a financial management contract for Bolsonaro's film; understand",0.0,neutral,"[('Eduardo', 'ORG'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: власти сообщили об атаке дронов на НПЗ в Москве и трех погибших в Подмосковье","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: authorities reported a drone attack on a refinery in Moscow and three deaths in the Moscow region",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Болгария победила в финале 70-го «Евровидения» в Вене, Израиль занял второе место","Bulgaria won the final of the 70th Eurovision in Vienna, Israel took second place",0.0,neutral,"[('Bulgaria', 'GPE'), ('Vienna', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ВОЗ объявила вспышку Эболы в Африке ЧС международного значения,WHO declares Ebola outbreak in Africa a national emergency,0.0,neutral,"[('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Выиграть время до родов. Ученые разрабатывают новый метод лечения тяжелого осложнения беременности,Gain time before giving birth. Scientists are developing a new method for treating a severe pregnancy complication,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Новая гигантская карта Вселенной поможет понять природу темной энергии,New giant map of the Universe will help understand the nature of dark energy,0.0,neutral,"[('Universe', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В итальянской Модене машина въехала в толпу, ранены восемь человек","A car drives into a crowd in Modena, Italy, injuring eight people.",0.0,neutral,"[('Modena', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"ХАМАС подтвердил, что в Газе убит глава вооруженного крыла группировки. Израиль называл его «архитектором нападений 7 октября»","Hamas has confirmed that the head of the group's armed wing has been killed in Gaza. Israel called him ""the architect of the October 7 attacks""",-0.3333,negative,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('October 7', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Двойной протест в Лондоне. На улицы одновременно вышли крайне правые и пропалестинские активисты,Double protest in London. Far-right and pro-Palestinian activists took to the streets at the same time,0.0,neutral,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('pro-Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В подводных пещерах на Мальдивах утонули пять дайверов из Италии. Во время их поисков погиб спасатель,Five divers from Italy drowned in underwater caves in the Maldives. A rescuer died during their search.,0.0,neutral,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Убит «второй по значимости в мире» командир ИГИЛ,'World's second most powerful' ISIS commander killed,-1.0,negative,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('ISIS', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、イランの核開発停止「20年間で十分」　履行の保証があればと,"Trump says ``20 years is enough'' to halt Iran's nuclear program, as long as there is a guarantee that it will be implemented.",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,習氏との会談終えたトランプ氏、台湾の独立望んでいないと発言　合意の詳細は明かされず,"After meeting with Xi, Trump says he does not want independence for Taiwan, details of agreement not disclosed",1.0,positive,"[('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,レバノン、南部でイスラエルが救急隊員など6人殺害と発表　米はイスラエルとレバノンの停戦延長を発表,Israel announces killing of 6 people including emergency workers in southern Lebanon; US announces extension of ceasefire between Israel and Lebanon,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英与党、下院補選についてバーナム市長の出馬届を受理　党首選への道開く,"UK ruling party accepts Mayor Burnham's candidacy for House of Commons by-election, paving the way for leadership election",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('House of Commons', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 暑さが「選手を危険にさらす」　科学者らFIFAに対策見直し要求,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Heat 'puts players at risk', scientists urge FIFA to review measures",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('FIFA', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イラン、ホルムズ海峡近くで「浮体式武器庫」の船舶を拿捕か,Iran seizes 'floating weapons storage' ship near Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait of', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英労働党で党首選への動き加速　ストリーティング保健相が辞任、　バーナム市長は補選出馬へ,"Movement towards leadership election accelerates in UK Labor Party - Health Minister Streeting resigns, Mayor Burnham to run for election",-1.0,negative,"[('UK Labor Party - Health', 'ORG'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、習氏と2日目の会談を終える　北京から帰国の途に,"Mr. Trump finishes his second day of talks with Mr. Xi, on his way back from Beijing",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、習氏がホルムズ海峡開放への協力申し出たと　会談初日について米メディアに説明,Trump explains to US media about the first day of talks that Xi offered to cooperate in opening the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the first day', 'DATE'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,キーウの集合住宅にドローン攻撃、ロシアが攻撃強化, 所要時間 1,26","Video, Russia intensifies drone attack on Kiiv apartment complex, Duration 1,26",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Kiiv', 'PERSON'), ('1,26', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,WHO yatangaza mlipuko wa Ebola nchini DR Congo kuwa dharura ya kiafya duniani","Directly, WHO declares the Ebola outbreak in DR Congo as a global health emergency",0.0,neutral,"[('DR Congo', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Dangote: Wataalamu kuamua kiwanda kijengwe Tanzania au Kenya,Dangote: Experts decide whether the factory should be built in Tanzania or Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumapili:Juventus kuongeza juhudi kumnasa Silva,Football rumors Sunday: Juventus to increase efforts to capture Silva,0.0,neutral,"[('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Juventus', 'ORG'), ('Silva', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mmoja wa viongozi wakuu wa ISIS auawa na majeshi ya Marekani na Nigeria","Directly, one of the main leaders of ISIS was killed by the American and Nigerian forces",-1.0,negative,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('ISIS', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Nigerian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Njia tatu za kupunguza kasi ya kuzeeka kwa ubongo,Three ways to slow down brain aging,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini baadhi ya majengo huegama bila kuanguka?,Why do some buildings stand without falling?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nani aliyejenga Al-Kaaba?,Who built Al-Kaaba?,0.0,neutral,"[('Al-Kaaba', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Dunia inazidi kutajirika, lakini kwa nini vijana hawana furaha?","The world is getting richer, but why are young people unhappy?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uingereza yaunga mkono mpango wa haki za binadamu unaolenga kuondolewa kwa wahamiaji haramu,The UK supports a human rights initiative aimed at removing illegal immigrants,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kuanzia kwa makaribisho makubwa hadi mazungumzo magumu: China inataka nini kutoka kwa Trump?,From warm welcome to tough talks: What does China want from Trump?,-1.0,negative,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
