Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""En Afganistán estaba dispuesto a morir por los talibanes. Ahora que me fui espero poder evitar que otros se radicalicen""","""In Afghanistan I was willing to die for the Taliban. Now that I'm gone I hope to prevent others from becoming radicalized""",0.35,"[('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""He intentado estirar al máximo la poca comida que tengo"": los 40 millones de estadounidenses en riesgo de perder la ayuda con la que sobreviven","""I've tried to stretch the little food I have as much as possible"": the 40 million Americans at risk of losing the aid they survive on",-0.09375,"[('40 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Torturas, autos de lujo y vínculos con la policía: qué revela sobre Comando Vermelho la investigación de la Fiscalía que llevó al megaoperativo policial en Río de Janeiro","Torture, luxury cars and links with the police: what the Prosecutor's Office investigation that led to the mega police operation in Rio de Janeiro reveals about Comando Vermelho",0.0,"[(""the Prosecutor's Office"", 'ORG'), ('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE'), ('Comando Vermelho', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Una chica normal de una familia normal derrotó a un príncipe"": la reacción de la familia de Virginia Giuffre a la pérdida de estatus real de Andrés","""A normal girl from a normal family defeated a prince"": Virginia Giuffre's family's reaction to Andrés' loss of royal status",0.15,"[(""Virginia Giuffre's"", 'PERSON'), ('Andrés', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""La ambigüedad sexual le dio a Juan Gabriel en México una libertad que resonó en un pueblo acostumbrado a no decir las cosas""","""Sexual ambiguity gave Juan Gabriel in Mexico a freedom that resonated with a people accustomed to not saying things""",0.5,"[('Juan Gabriel', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव: बीजेपी के गढ़ में गणित के चर्चित टीचर केसी सिन्हा कितने मज़बूत,Bihar Elections: How strong is famous mathematics teacher KC Sinha in BJP's stronghold?,0.4666666666666667,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON'), ('KC Sinha', 'ORG'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,आंध्र प्रदेश के वेंकटेश्वर मंदिर में भगदड़, सीएम चंद्रबाबू नायडू ने क्या बताया","Live, stampede in Venkateswara temple of Andhra Pradesh, what did CM Chandrababu Naidu tell?",0.13636363636363635,"[('Venkateswara', 'PRODUCT'), ('Andhra Pradesh', 'PERSON'), ('Chandrababu Naidu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,देश के बड़े हिस्से में लागू हो रही एसआईआर प्रक्रिया, ये हो सकती हैं चुनौतियां- द लेंस, अवधि 34,08","Video, SIR process is being implemented in large parts of the country, these can be challenges - The Lens, Duration 34,08",0.21428571428571427,"[('SIR', 'ORG'), ('34,08', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अमेरिका और भारत के बीच रक्षा समझौते से दोनों देशों में से किसका ज़्यादा फ़ायदा,Which of the two countries will benefit more from the defense agreement between America and India?,0.5,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लिवर ट्रांसप्लांट कैसे होता है, जानिए कब और क्यों पड़ती है इसकी ज़रूरत","How is liver transplant done, know when and why it is needed.",0.0,[]
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मोकामा में दुलारचंद यादव की हत्या का आरोप अनंत सिंह पर, चुनावी रंजिश की ये है कहानी","Anant Singh accused of murder of Dularchand Yadav in Mokama, this is the story of election rivalry",0.0,"[('Anant Singh', 'PERSON'), ('Dularchand Yadav', 'ORG'), ('Mokama', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तूतनख़ामेन के अनदेखे खज़ाने मिस्र की ग्रैंड म्यूज़ियम में पहली बार दिखाए जाएंगे,Tutankhamen's unseen treasures to be shown for the first time in Egypt's Grand Museum,0.375,"[('Tutankhamen', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Grand Museum', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पत्नी के हिंदू होने पर दिए बयान के बाद जेडी वेंस बोले, 'वो ईसाई नहीं हैं, न धर्म बदलने की योजना है'","After his wife's statement about being a Hindu, JD Vance said, 'He is not a Christian, nor does he plan to change his religion.'",0.0,"[('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('JD Vance', 'PERSON'), ('Christian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जेमिमा रॉड्रिग्स की ये पारी आख़िर भारतीय क्रिकेट में क्यों नहीं भूली जा सकेगी,Why will this innings of Jemimah Rodrigues not be forgotten in Indian cricket?,0.0,"[('Jemimah Rodrigues', 'ORG'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Polícia divulga lista parcial de mortos; apoio à operação é majoritário no Brasil, no Rio e em favelas cariocas, diz pesquisa","Police release partial list of dead; Support for the operation is majority in Brazil, Rio and Rio favelas, says research",-0.15000000000000002,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Rio', 'ORG'), ('Rio', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Era o nosso filho, meu e dela. Ela pariu e eu criei': a espera no IML do Rio pelos corpos dos mortos na operação","'He was our son, mine and hers. She gave birth and I raised her': the wait at Rio's IML for the bodies of those killed in the operation",-0.2,"[('Rio', 'ORG'), ('IML', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Grupo de especialistas da ONU cobra investigação sobre operação no Rio,UN group of experts demands investigation into operation in Rio,0.0,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que experiência da Itália no combate à máfia pode ensinar ao Brasil na luta contra o crime organizado,What Italy's experience in fighting the mafia can teach Brazil in the fight against organized crime,0.0,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A jornada de dias a pé para fugir de violência no Sudão: 'Cenas brutais',The days-long journey on foot to escape violence in Sudan: 'Brutal scenes',-0.875,"[('days', 'DATE'), ('Sudan', 'GPE'), ('Brutal', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os americanos adotados que temem a deportação para um país do qual não se lembram,American adoptees who fear deportation to a country they don't remember,0.0,"[('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Irmão do rei Charles 3º, Andrew perde títulos e mansão por ligações com Epstein: 7 respostas sobre o caso","Brother of King Charles III, Andrew loses titles and mansion for links to Epstein: 7 answers about the case",-0.3,"[('Charles III', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que come o homem mais forte do mundo, com 148 kg? 'Consumo 6 mil calorias por dia'","What does the strongest man in the world, weighing 148 kg, eat? 'I consume 6 thousand calories a day'",0.0,"[('148 kg', 'QUANTITY'), ('6 thousand', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As pessoas com albinismo que viram alvo por superstição durante eleição: 'Muito medo',People with albinism who were targeted due to superstition during the election: 'Very afraid',-0.4525,[]
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Страна изменилась». Спустя год после трагедии в Нови-Саде сербские студенты из «поколения Z» продолжают протестовать,"""The country has changed."" A year after the tragedy in Novi Sad, Serbian students from Generation Z continue to protest",-0.5,"[('A year', 'DATE'), ('Novi Sad', 'PERSON'), ('Serbian', 'NORP'), ('Generation Z', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Пентагон одобрил поставку ракет Tomahawk, но окончательное решение за Трампом","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Pentagon approves supply of Tomahawk missiles, but Trump has final decision",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Pentagon', 'ORG'), ('Tomahawk', 'PRODUCT'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Больше не принц. Почему превращение Эндрю в «господина Маунтбеттена-Виндзора» — беспрецедентное событие для британской монархии,"No longer a prince. Why Andrew's transformation into ""Mr. Mountbatten-Windsor"" is an unprecedented event for the British monarchy",0.3,"[('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('Mountbatten-Windsor', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Беспорядки после выборов в Танзании: сообщается о сотнях погибших. Действующего президента объявили победителем,Post-election unrest in Tanzania: Hundreds of dead reported. The incumbent president was declared the winner,-0.2,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Россия применяет в Украине ракету 9М729, ставшую причиной выхода США из Договора о РСМД? Что известно","Russia uses the 9M729 missile in Ukraine, which became the reason for the US withdrawal from the INF Treaty? What is known",0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the INF Treaty', 'EVENT')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,СМИ: новые пользователи Telegram и WhatsApp в России при попытке регистрации не получают СМС или звонка. Полная блокировка близка?,Media: new users of Telegram and WhatsApp in Russia do not receive an SMS or call when they try to register. Is a complete lockdown near?,0.11212121212121212,"[('Telegram', 'ORG'), ('WhatsApp', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('SMS', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Они хотели нас казнить». Очевидцы рассказали об осаде города Эль-Фашир в Судане, где происходили массовые убийства","""They wanted to execute us."" Eyewitnesses spoke about the siege of the city of El Fasher in Sudan, where massacres took place",0.0,"[('El Fasher', 'ORG'), ('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«А тела всё несли и несли...» Рассказ фотографа о кровавом полицейском рейде в Рио-де-Жанейро,“And the bodies were carried and carried...” A photographer’s story about a bloody police raid in Rio de Janeiro,-0.8,"[('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп резко снизил число беженцев, которых примут США. Приоритет отдадут белым южноафриканцам",Trump has sharply reduced the number of refugees the US will accept. Priority will be given to white South Africans,-0.0625,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('South Africans', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Из пропавших — в погибшие: что  известно о потерях России в Украине к ноябрю,From missing to dead: what is known about Russia’s losses in Ukraine by November,-0.2,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('November', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】アンドリュー・マウントバッテン・ウィンザー氏はここがどん底なのか,[Commentary] Is this the lowest point for Andrew Mountbatten-Windsor?,0.0,"[('Andrew Mountbatten-Windsor', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 ジュフリー氏の回顧録には何が書かれているのか　アンドリュー氏やエプスティーン元被告からの性被害を訴えた女性,[Commentary] What is written in Mr. Giuffre's memoir? A woman who complained of sexual assault by Mr. Andrew and former defendant Epstein,0.06666666666666667,"[('Giuffre', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍の船舶攻撃は「国際法違反」と国連人権トップ　トランプ政権は麻薬密輸船だと主張,"U.S. military ship attack 'violates international law', UN human rights chief says, Trump administration claims it is a drug smuggling vessel",-0.03333333333333333,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,オランダ総選挙、中道リベラル政党が勝利を宣言　極右与党と接戦,Centrist liberal party declares victory in Dutch general election; close battle with far-right ruling party,0.05000000000000002,"[('Dutch', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タンザニアで選挙めぐり抗議デモ、弾圧で数百人死亡か,Hundreds killed in crackdown on election protests in Tanzania,-0.2,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ハリケーン「メリッサ」、ジャマイカで少なくとも19人死亡　BBC記者が被災地を取材, 所要時間 0,58","Video, Hurricane Melissa kills at least 19 people in Jamaica; BBC reporter covers affected area, Duration 0,58",-0.3,"[('Melissa', 'PERSON'), ('at least 19', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jamaica', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ政権に食料支援の継続を命令、米連邦2地裁　政府機関の閉鎖中であっても,Two US District Courts Order Trump Administration to Continue Food Assistance Even During Government Shutdown,0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 米中貿易戦争、「休戦」で合意も中国は長期戦の構え,"[Commentary] US-China trade war, ``truce'' agreed, but China is poised for a long war",-0.05,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 合意、譲歩、帰国間際の会談……トランプ氏のアジア歴訪を振り返る,"[Commentary] Agreements, concessions, talks just before returning home... Looking back on Trump's Asia trip",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Asia', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Matokeo ya Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Samia Suluhu Hassan atangazwa  mshindi wa uchaguzi wa urais,Tanzania Election Results 2025: Samia Suluhu Hassan has been declared the winner of the presidential election,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Hassan', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Wapinzani kukamatwa, vurugu na 'ushindi wa kihistoria'-matukio muhimu","Tanzania 2025 elections: Opposition arrested, violence and 'historic victory' - key events",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Dr. Hussein Ali Mwinyi aapishwa kuwa Rais wa Zanzibar kipindi cha Pili","Directly, Dr. Hussein Ali Mwinyi is sworn in as the President of Zanzibar for the second term",0.05,"[('Hussein Ali Mwinyi', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Serikali ya Tanzania: Hatuwezi kuthibitisha idadi ya watu waliouawa katika maandamano,Government of Tanzania: We cannot confirm the number of people killed in the protests,-0.2,[]
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Bunge la Ulaya laiomba INEC kutotangaza matokeo ya uchaguzi Tanzania,The European Parliament asks INEC not to announce the election results in Tanzania,0.0,"[('The European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hussein Mwinyi: Mfahamu zaidi rais mteule wa Zanzibar,Hussein Mwinyi: Get to know the president-elect of Zanzibar better,0.5,"[('Hussein Mwinyi', 'PERSON'), ('Zanzibar', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Iran yaitaja Marekani kuwa mzalishaji 'hatari zaidi' wa silaha za nyuklia duniani,Iran calls the US the 'most dangerous' producer of nuclear weapons in the world,-0.04999999999999999,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi  Tanzania 2025: Maandamano ya siku ya uchaguzi yana maanisha nini?,Tanzania Election 2025: What does the election day protest mean?,-0.3125,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE'), ('the election day', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Man City, Man United na Arsenal zamwania Carl Etta Eyong","Football rumors in Europe Friday: Man City, Man United and Arsenal for Carl Etta Eyong",0.0,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Man City', 'GPE'), ('Carl Etta', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ghasia zazuka  Namanga mpaka wa Kenya na Tanzania,"Riots broke out in Namanga, the border between Kenya and Tanzania",0.0,"[('Namanga', 'GPE'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
