Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Las imágenes de satélite que muestran que Israel ha destruido al menos 1.500 edificios en Gaza desde el inicio del alto el fuego,"Satellite images showing that Israel has destroyed at least 1,500 buildings in Gaza since the start of the ceasefire",-0.3,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('at least 1,500', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Jenifer de la Rosa, la sobreviviente de la tragedia de Armero que fue adoptada siendo bebé por una pareja española y conoció a su hermana décadas después","Jenifer de la Rosa, the survivor of the Armero tragedy who was adopted as a baby by a Spanish couple and met her sister decades later",0.0,"[('Jenifer de la Rosa', 'PERSON'), ('Armero', 'ORG'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('her sister decades later', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quiénes son los 5 millones de ""votantes obligados"" y cómo pueden incidir en las elecciones presidenciales de Chile","Who are the 5 million ""mandated voters"" and how can they influence the presidential elections in Chile?",0.0,"[('5 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Termina el cierre de gobierno más largo de la historia de EE.UU.: ¿qué consiguieron los demócratas?,The longest government shutdown in US history ends: what did the Democrats achieve?,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Democrats', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué los denisovanos pueden ayudarnos a comprender cómo llegamos a ser los únicos humanos en la Tierra,Why Denisovans can help us understand how we came to be the only humans on Earth,0.0,"[('Denisovans', 'NORP'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,बिहार चुनाव नतीजे: रुझानों में महागठबंधन के पिछड़ने के बाद आरजेडी सांसद ने लगाया ये आरोप","Live, Bihar election results: RJD MP made this allegation after the Grand Alliance lagged behind in the trends",0.07878787878787878,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('the Grand Alliance', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार विधानसभा चुनाव नतीजे 2025,Bihar Assembly Election Results 2025,0.0,"[('Bihar Assembly Election Results 2025', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"तेजस्वी को बढ़त और तेज प्रताप यादव पिछड़े, बिहार की बाकी हॉट सीटों पर कौन आगे और कौन पीछे","Tejashwi is ahead and Tej Pratap Yadav is behind, who is ahead and who is behind on other hot seats of Bihar",-0.16875,"[('Tejashwi', 'ORG'), ('Tej Pratap Yadav', 'PERSON'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नेहरू परमाणु कार्यक्रम को लेकर थे बेहद संजीदा, आज़ादी के बाद पहले पखवाड़े में लिया था अहम फ़ैसला","Nehru was very serious about the nuclear program, took an important decision in the first fortnight after independence.",0.07222222222222223,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अल-फ़लाह यूनिवर्सिटी की डॉक्टर शाहीन सईद के घर वालों ने क्या बताया?,What did the family members of Dr. Shaheen Saeed of Al-Falah University tell?,0.0,"[('Shaheen Saeed', 'PERSON'), ('Al-Falah University', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार में मतगणना, वे बातें जो आपको जानना ज़रूरी हैं","Counting of votes in Bihar, things you need to know",0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दुनिया की सबसे लंबी परीक्षा, 13 घंटे तक न लंच ब्रेक न डिनर ब्रेक","World's longest exam, no lunch break or dinner break for 13 hours",0.0,"[('13 hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'जितना भी तैरता, लगता जैसे एक ही जगह पर अटका हूँ': समुद्र में 26 घंटे तैरकर ऐसे बची शिवमुरुगन की जान","'No matter how much I swam, I felt as if I was stuck at one place': This is how Shivamurugan saved his life by swimming for 26 hours in the sea.",0.2,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shivamurugan', 'GPE'), ('26 hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अल फ़लाह यूनिवर्सिटी: दिल्ली ब्लास्ट के बाद चर्चा में आए इस संस्थान को चलाता कौन है?,Al Falah University: Who runs this institution which came into discussion after the Delhi blasts?,0.0,"[('Al Falah University', 'ORG'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Acordo provisório sobre tarifaço pode sair ainda em novembro, diz Mauro Vieira após nova reunião com Rubio","Provisional agreement on pricing could come out in November, says Mauro Vieira after new meeting with Rubio",0.13636363636363635,"[('November', 'DATE'), ('Mauro Vieira', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que se sabe sobre a operação militar Lança do Sul, anunciada pelos EUA contra narcotráfico na América Latina","What is known about the military operation South Spear, announced by the US against drug trafficking in Latin America",-0.1,"[('South Spear', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quanto dura popularidade de políticos 'linha-dura' contra as facções criminosas?,How long does the popularity of 'hard-line' politicians against criminal factions last?,-0.15,[]
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os netos dos primeiros protetores da Amazônia que agora renovam aliança contra mudanças climáticas,The grandchildren of the first protectors of the Amazon who now renew their alliance against climate change,0.25,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Vantagem de Lula cai: o que diz a última pesquisa Quaest sobre 2026,Lula's advantage falls: what the latest Quaest survey says about 2026,0.5,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('about 2026', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"BBC pede desculpas a Trump, mas rejeita pedido de indenização",BBC apologizes to Trump but rejects compensation claim,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que se sabe sobre novos e-mails de Epstein que citam Trump,What is known about Epstein's new emails that quote Trump,0.13636363636363635,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump sanciona projeto que encerra paralisação mais longa da história dos EUA,Trump sanctions bill that ends longest strike in US history,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Tank, um dos hackers mais procurados da história, revela da prisão como operam os cibercriminosos","Tank, one of the most wanted hackers in history, reveals from prison how cybercriminals operate",0.5,"[('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что нам известно о потерях России в Украине к ноябрю,What do we know about Russia's losses in Ukraine by November?,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('November', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в результате обстрела Киева есть погибшие; украинским ударом повреждена нефтебаза в Новороссийске","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: there are dead as a result of the shelling of Kyiv; Ukrainian strike damaged oil depot in Novorossiysk",-0.2,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Novorossiysk', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как ограничивали интернет в России в 2025 году и что будет дальше. Хроника,How the Internet was limited in Russia in 2025 and what will happen next. Chronicle,-0.03571428571428571,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Би-би-си принесла извинения Трампу за монтаж его речи, но отказалась платить компенсацию","BBC apologizes to Trump for editing his speech, but refuses to pay compensation",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Нью Гленн» отправился к Марсу. Blue Origin Джеффа Безоса успешно запустила ракету со спутниками НАСА,"""New Glenn"" went to Mars. Jeff Bezos' Blue Origin successfully launches rocket with NASA satellites",0.29545454545454547,"[('Mars', 'LOC'), (""Jeff Bezos'"", 'PERSON'), ('NASA', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Приговоры по «делу о дворовых чатах», литовские фуры застряли на границе. Главное в Беларуси за неделю","Verdicts in the “yard chat case”, Lithuanian trucks stuck at the border. The main things in Belarus in a week",0.16666666666666666,"[('Lithuanian', 'NORP'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Израиль идентифицировал тело заложника, переданное ХАМАС в четверг. Это Мэни Годдард, который был убит в возрасте 73 лет","Israel identified the body of a hostage handed over to Hamas on Thursday. This is Many Goddard, who was killed at the age of 73.",0.15,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Goddard', 'PERSON'), ('the age of 73', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Бывший глава «Укрэнерго»: мы не давали экс-министру энергетики Галущенко воровать и назначать своих людей,Former head of Ukrenergo: we did not allow ex-Minister of Energy Galushchenko to steal and appoint his own people,0.3,"[('Ukrenergo', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Тиктокер со стремянкой. Блогер из Украины Макс Клименко получил престижную премию на конкурсе TikTok,TikToker with a stepladder. Blogger from Ukraine Max Klimenko received a prestigious award at the TikTok competition,0.0,"[('TikToker', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Max Klimenko', 'PERSON'), ('TikTok', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Со дня трагедии в парижском «Батаклане» прошло 10 лет, но враг никуда не исчез","10 years have passed since the tragedy in the Paris Bataclan, but the enemy has not disappeared anywhere",0.0,"[('10 years', 'DATE'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 パリ連続襲撃事件から10年、いまだ消えない脅威,"[Commentary] 10 years after the Paris attacks, the threat still persists",0.0,"[('10 years', 'DATE'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,BBC、トランプ氏に謝罪も賠償は拒否　新たな「誤解編集映像」を英紙が指摘,BBC apologizes to Trump but refuses compensation; British newspaper points out new 'misunderstood edited footage',0.06818181818181818,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,独連立政権、新たな兵役制度導入でまとまる　兵力増強へ,German coalition government to strengthen military force by introducing new military service system,-0.015909090909090914,"[('German', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英王室アンドリュー氏は「ジュフリー氏と写真撮った」、エプスティーン元被告のメールに記述,"British royal Andrew ``took a photo with Giuffre,'' says Epstein in email",0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Andrew ``', 'PERSON'), ('Giuffre', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ボスニアへの「民間人狙撃ツアー」に多数参加と告発　イタリア当局が捜査着手,"Italian authorities launch investigation after accusations of multiple participation in ""civilian sniper tour"" to Bosnia",0.0,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Bosnia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国籍「暗号資産の女王」に禁錮11年超　逃亡先の英で豪邸住まい、押収額は「世界最大規模」,"Chinese national ``Queen of Cryptocurrency'' sentenced to over 11 years in prison, lives in mansion in UK, where seizure amount is ``world's largest''",0.0,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Queen of Cryptocurrency', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('11 years', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米政府閉鎖、過去最長の43日間で終了　トランプ氏がつなぎ予算案に署名,"US government shutdown ends after 43 days, longest on record; Trump signs bridge budget bill",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('43 days', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル入植者がパレスチナ人の農地を襲撃、倉庫などに放火　ヨルダン川西岸で攻撃急増,Israeli settlers attack Palestinian farmland and set fire to warehouses; attacks increase in West Bank,0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナで汚職の大規模捜査、ゼレンスキー氏の盟友ら巻き込み　2閣僚が辞任,Major corruption investigation in Ukraine involves Zelenskiy's allies; two ministers resign,0.0625,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskiy', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,BBC yamwomba Trump msamaha lakini yakataa kulipa fidia","Directly, the BBC apologized to Trump but refused to pay compensation",0.1,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mwigulu Nchemba: Kutoka kuchunga ng'ombe hadi Uwaziri Mkuu wa Tanzania,Mwigulu Nchemba: From herding cattle to the Prime Ministership of Tanzania,0.0,[]
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tunachojua kuhusu barua pepe mpya za Epstein zinazomtaja Trump,What we know about Epstein's new emails that mention Trump,0.13636363636363635,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Ujasusi, uharibifu na hujuma: Jinsi Urusi inavyotumia ""meli za mizimu"" kukwepa vikwazo vya Magharibi","Espionage, sabotage and sabotage: How Russia uses ""ghost ships"" to evade Western sanctions",0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Man United kumnunua Karim Adeyemi kutoka Borussia Dortmund,European football rumors Friday: Man United to buy Karim Adeyemi from Borussia Dortmund,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Karim Adeyemi', 'GPE'), ('Borussia Dortmund', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Zaidi ya Wakenya 200 wamesajiliwa katika jeshi la Urusi - waziri,More than 200 Kenyans are registered in the Russian army - minister,0.25,"[('More than 200', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenyans', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tamko la Umoja wa Mataifa dhidi ya madai ya mauaji ya Tanzania lina maana gani?,What is the meaning of the United Nations declaration against the alleged killing of Tanzania?,-0.1,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wapiganaji wa Hamas waliojificha kwenye mahandaki wawasilisha kikwazo kipya kuhusu kusitisha mapigano Gaza,Hamas fighters hiding in the trenches present a new obstacle to the ceasefire in Gaza,0.06818181818181818,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kuitunza amani wakati wa mageuzi changamoto na funzo Tanzania,Maintaining peace during the transition challenges and lessons in Tanzania,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nne kwa moja - mechi za mchujo za kufuzu kwa Kombe la Dunia kwa timu za Afrika hufanyikaje?,Four on one - how do the World Cup qualifiers for African teams take place?,0.0,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
