Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Islandia, el país ártico que nunca tuvo ejército y ahora tiene que replantearse su defensa","Iceland, the Arctic country that never had an army and now has to rethink its defense",0.0,neutral,"[('Iceland', 'GPE'), ('Arctic', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Uno de los mayores misterios sin resolver de la historia británica"": el conde que desapareció tras asesinar a la niñera de sus hijos","""One of the greatest unsolved mysteries in British history"": the earl who disappeared after murdering his children's nanny",1.0,positive,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Miles de muertos en la guerra en Irán y Líbano: por qué es tan difícil saber el balance real de víctimas,Thousands of dead in the war in Iran and Lebanon: why it is so difficult to know the real toll of victims,-1.0,negative,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué tipo de país representan De la Espriella y Cepeda, los antagónicos aspirantes a presidir Colombia","What type of country do De la Espriella and Cepeda, the antagonistic candidates to preside over Colombia, represent?",0.0,neutral,"[('De la Espriella and Cepeda', 'ORG'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Vas a recibir tu merecido"": los 'agentes' que amenazan a las modelos de OnlyFans y se quedan con la mitad de sus ganancias","""You're going to get what you deserve"": the 'agents' who threaten OnlyFans models and keep half of their earnings",0.0,neutral,"[('OnlyFans', 'NORP'), ('half', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Ni yo ni Italia suplicamos jamás"": Meloni niega haberle pedido a Trump hacerse una foto juntos como dijo el presidente de EE.UU.","""Neither I nor Italy ever begged"": Meloni denies having asked Trump to take a photo together as the US president said.",0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El capitán de Marruecos, Achraf Hakimi, será juzgado por violación en Francia",Morocco captain Achraf Hakimi to be tried for rape in France,0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('Achraf Hakimi', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Para qué sirvió la guerra?: la pregunta inevitable que plantea el acuerdo entre EE.UU. e Irán,What was the war for?: the inevitable question raised by the US-Iran deal,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Llenan de orgullo a todo México"": Sheinbaum y los hinchas festejan que el Tri sea el primer equipo en clasificarse para la siguiente fase del Mundial","""They fill all of Mexico with pride"": Sheinbaum and the fans celebrate that El Tri is the first team to qualify for the next phase of the World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Sheinbaum', 'ORG'), ('El Tri', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Mundial 2026: el ranking de la BBC de todos los equipos después de la primera ronda de partidos (con 3 latinoamericanos entre los 10 primeros),World Cup 2026: the BBC ranking of all teams after the first round of matches (with 3 Latin Americans in the top 10),0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Latin Americans', 'NORP'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिका-इसराइल की ईरान के साथ जंग में हज़ारों की मौत लेकिन सही आंकड़े क्या हैं?,"Thousands died in America-Israel's war with Iran, but what are the true figures?",-1.0,negative,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,अमित शाह बोले, 'अब कोई गुट बचा नहीं, शिवसेना एक हो गई'","Live, Amit Shah said, 'Now there is no group left, Shiv Sena has united'",0.0,neutral,"[('Shiv Sena', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भारत के विदेशी मुद्रा भंडार में गिरावट जारी, फिर कम हुआ क़रीब 10 अरब डॉलर, जानिए कारण","India's foreign exchange reserves continue to decline, again reduced by almost 10 billion dollars, know the reason",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('almost 10 billion dollars', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,शेखर सुमन का डिजिटल स्क्रीन पर डेब्यू किस वजह से है चर्चा में,Why is Shekhar Suman's debut on digital screen in discussion?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Shekhar Suman's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान-अमेरिका समझौता: पाकिस्तान की 'कूटनीतिक कामयाबी' पर विदेशी मीडिया में ऐसी चर्चा,Iran-America Agreement: Such discussion in foreign media on Pakistan's 'diplomatic success',1.0,positive,"[('Iran-America Agreement', 'EVENT'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"जेडी वेंस की सख़्ती पर इसराइल में तीखी बहस, वहाँ के मीडिया में इन कारणों पर चर्चा","Heated debate in Israel on JD Vance's strictness, these reasons discussed in the media there",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), (""JD Vance's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"उद्धव ठाकरे हुए भावुक,  पार्टी प्रमुख से इस्तीफ़े की पेशकश कर पूछे ये सवाल","Uddhav Thackeray became emotional, offered to resign from the party chief and asked these questions",0.0,neutral,"[('Uddhav Thackeray', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वीडियो,पाकिस्तान को क्या अंतरराष्ट्रीय मंचों पर अब ज़्यादा अहमियत मिलने लगी है?- द लेंस, अवधि 31,42","Video, Is Pakistan now getting more importance on international platforms? - The Lens, Duration 31,42",0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,खाद्य तेल में आत्मनिर्भर भारत दुनिया का सबसे बड़ा आयातक कैसे बना,How self-reliant India became the world's largest importer of edible oil?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ममता की तृणमूल कांग्रेस ताश के पत्तों की तरह कैसे बिखर गई, जानिए बीजेपी ने अपने में विलय क्यों नहीं किया","How Mamata's Trinamool Congress fell apart like a pack of cards, know why BJP did not merge with itself",0.0,neutral,"[('Mamata', 'GPE'), ('Trinamool Congress', 'ORG'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que caso Mariana Ferrer se tornou emblemático e será julgado de novo após decisão do STF,Why the Mariana Ferrer case became emblematic and will be tried again after the STF’s decision,0.0,neutral,"[('Mariana Ferrer', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Mais altos, mais rápidos, mais velhos: como o corpo dos melhores jogadores de futebol mudou nos últimos 50 anos","Taller, faster, older: how the bodies of the best football players have changed in the last 50 years",0.0,neutral,"[('Taller', 'PERSON'), ('the last 50 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Misantropia': a mensagem enviada com alerta pela Defesa Nacional após invasão hacker,'Misanthropy': the message sent with warning by National Defense after hacker invasion,-1.0,negative,"[('Misanthropy', 'PERSON'), ('National Defense', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil x Escócia: qual resultado a Seleção precisa para se classificar na liderança do grupo?,Brazil x Scotland: what result does the Seleção need to qualify at the top of the group?,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Seleção', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Os preços pagos pelos ultrarricos na Copa dos Estados Unidos: 'Dinheiro pode comprar praticamente qualquer coisa',The prices paid by the ultra-rich in the United States Cup: 'Money can buy practically anything',0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A homenagem histórica da camisa do Haiti que a Fifa decidiu proibir,The historic tribute on the Haiti shirt that FIFA decided to ban,0.0,neutral,"[('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('FIFA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Do terremoto ao vodu, brasileiro se apaixonou pelo Haiti, que enfrenta o Brasil na Copa do Mundo","From earthquake to voodoo, Brazilian fell in love with Haiti, which faces Brazil in the World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que aprendi fazendo 30 dias seguidos de ioga no outono paulistano,What I learned from doing 30 consecutive days of yoga in the autumn of São Paulo,0.0,neutral,"[('30 consecutive days', 'DATE'), ('São Paulo', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A troca de farpas entre Trump e Meloni por foto no G7: 'Nem eu nem a Itália imploramos nada. Trump inventou',The exchange of barbs between Trump and Meloni via photo at the G7: 'Neither Italy nor I beg for anything. Trump invented,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Meloni', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil vence Haiti por 3 a 0 e assume primeiro lugar do grupo,Brazil beats Haiti 3-0 and takes first place in the group,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Возвращение Белого Орла. Пять последствий отзыва президентом Польши награды у президента Украины,Return of the White Eagle. Five consequences of the President of Poland revoking an award from the President of Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('the White Eagle', 'ORG'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Наступил ли перелом в войне России с Украиной?,Has there been a turning point in the war between Russia and Ukraine?,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Два поезда столкнулись к северу от Лондона, пострадали десятки человек","Two trains collide north of London, injuring dozens",0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Почему каждый видит свою собственную радугу (а двух одинаковых не бывает)?,Why does everyone see their own rainbow (and no two are alike)?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский потребовал от Лукашенко убрать «технику, которая корректирует огонь»","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky demanded that Lukashenko remove “equipment that adjusts fire”",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Lukashenko', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Президент Польши лишил Зеленского высшего ордена из-за «Героев УПА» в названии части ВСУ,The President of Poland deprived Zelensky of the highest order because of “Heroes of the UPA” in the name of a unit of the Armed Forces of Ukraine,0.0,neutral,"[('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Heroes of the UPA', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the Armed Forces of Ukraine', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Атака на НПЗ в Москве: как «лучшее ПВО в России» пропустило удар по столице?,Attack on a refinery in Moscow: how did “the best air defense in Russia” miss the attack on the capital?,-1.0,negative,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Очереди из десятков автомобилей. Наблюдается ли в Москве дефицит бензина?,Queues of dozens of cars. Is there a gasoline shortage in Moscow?,0.0,neutral,"[('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Израиль и «Хезболла» договорились прекратить огонь,Israel and Hezbollah agree to ceasefire,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Джереми Боуэн: Трампу не избежать вопросов о том, ради чего он начал войну с Ираном",Jeremy Bowen: Trump will not avoid questions about why he went to war with Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Jeremy Bowen', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエルとヒズボラ、停戦で合意とアメリカが発表　発効後もレバノンでは空爆の報告相次ぐ,Israel and Hezbollah agree to ceasefire; US announces ceasefire; reports of airstrikes continue to occur in Lebanon even after it takes effect,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英与党の内部、スターマー首相に退任予定示すよう圧力高まる　閣僚や議員から,Pressure grows within Britain's ruling party on Prime Minister Starmer to announce plans to step down from ministers and MPs,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イタリア首相、トランプ氏が自分について「でまかせ」と反発　単発的な口論ではなく,"Italian Prime Minister criticizes Trump, calling him a ``fake'' It's not just a one-off argument",0.0,neutral,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イングランド中部で旅客列車同士が衝突　運転士1人死亡、89人負傷,"Passenger trains collide in central England; 1 driver killed, 89 injured",-1.0,negative,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('89', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】　いったい何のための戦争だったのか……米・イラン合意で浮かぶ避けがたい疑問　BBC国際編集長,[Commentary] What on earth was the war for? Unavoidable questions that arise in the US-Iran agreement BBC International Editor-in-Chief,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('BBC International', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカがイランの海上封鎖を解除　イラン最高指導者はトランプ氏が「絶望」して合意と,"US lifts naval blockade of Iran; Iran's supreme leader says Trump is ""desperate"" to agree",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英下院補選、労働党のバーナム市長が当選　党首選でスターマー首相への挑戦の道開く,"Labor Party's Mayor Burnham wins British House of Commons by-election, paving the way for challenge to Prime Minister Starmer in leadership race",1.0,positive,"[(""Labor Party's"", 'ORG'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('British House of Commons', 'ORG'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、モスクワに最大規模の攻撃で製油所直撃　地面や服に黒い染みと住民,"Ukraine's largest attack hits Moscow refinery, leaving residents with black stains on ground and clothes",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 米・イランは共に合意を「勝利」と主張、実際はどうなのか,"[Commentary] Both the US and Iran claim the agreement is a “victory”, but what is the reality?",1.0,positive,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本人サポーターがスタジアムを清掃、家でもやろうと女性から注文,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Japanese supporters clean stadium, woman orders to do it at home",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Mjumbe wa Trump, Waziri wa Iran waelekea Uswizi kwa mazungumzo","Directly, Trump's envoy, the Iranian minister is heading to Switzerland for talks",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la dunia 2026: Kanuni mpya za FIFA zatikisa hesabu za kufuzu,World Cup 2026: New FIFA rules shake up qualifying calculations,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Chanjo ya kwanza duniani iliyoundwa na akili unde (AI),The world's first artificial intelligence (AI) vaccine,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vifo takriban 30 katika kambi DRC vinaonyesha Ebola inaweza kuwa inaenea kwa kasi,About 30 deaths in camps in DRC suggest Ebola may be spreading rapidly,-1.0,negative,"[('About 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('DRC', 'ORG'), ('Ebola', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kisa cha mume kumlazimisha mkewe kushiriki ngono na wanaume 120,The case of a husband forcing his wife to have sex with 120 men,0.0,neutral,"[('120', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kutafuna chakula vizuri kunaimarisha ubongo wako - Utafiti,Chewing food well strengthens your brain - Research,1.0,positive,[]
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Spurs wamfukuzia Wharton,European Football Rumors: Spurs sack Wharton,0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors: Spurs', 'ORG'), ('Wharton', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, tunajua nini kuhusu fedha za Iran zilizozuiwa ugenini?",What do we know about Iranian funds held abroad?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ratiba, msimamo na matokeo","World Cup 2026: Schedule, standings and results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_20,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nahodha wa Morocco Hakimi kujibu mashtaka ya ubakaji,Moroccan captain Hakim to answer rape charges,0.0,neutral,"[('Moroccan', 'NORP'), ('Hakim', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup knockouts: Who has made it to the round of 32 stage?,World Cup knockouts: Who has made it to the round of 32 stage?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Two roadside bombs kill at least seven in northwestern Pakistan,Two roadside bombs kill at least seven in northwestern Pakistan,-1.0,negative,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('at least seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Family, including two daughters, killed in Israeli strikes on Gaza","Family, including two daughters, killed in Israeli strikes on Gaza",-1.0,negative,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Mona Khalil, Lebanon’s turtle advocate, dies after Israeli attack","Mona Khalil, Lebanon’s turtle advocate, dies after Israeli attack",-1.0,negative,"[('Mona Khalil', 'PERSON'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Australia pledges action on H5N1 after bird flu case confirmed,Australia pledges action on H5N1 after bird flu case confirmed,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('H5N1', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"US envoy headed for Switzerland, Israeli strikes on Lebanon threaten talks","US envoy headed for Switzerland, Israeli strikes on Lebanon threaten talks",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘We tasted the horrors of war’: Stories of refugees who returned home,‘We tasted the horrors of war’: Stories of refugees who returned home,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 113: Tehran presses US over Lebanon ceasefire,Iran war day 113: Tehran presses US over Lebanon ceasefire,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('113', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Turkiye knocked out of World Cup 2026 after 1-0 defeat to 10-man Paraguay,Turkiye knocked out of World Cup 2026 after 1-0 defeat to 10-man Paraguay,0.0,neutral,"[('Turkiye', 'GPE'), ('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel fetes Somaliland’s leader as it seeks to expand Red Sea influence,Israel fetes Somaliland’s leader as it seeks to expand Red Sea influence,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Somaliland', 'ORG'), ('Red Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Ex-Minister Padamsinh Patil, 7 others acquitted in 2006 murder of Congress leader Pawanraje Nimbalkar","Ex-Minister Padamsinh Patil, 7 others acquitted in 2006 murder of Congress leader Pawanraje Nimbalkar",0.0,neutral,"[('Padamsinh Patil', 'PERSON'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('2006', 'DATE'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Pawanraje Nimbalkar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Cockroach Janta Party protest LIVE | Protestors shout 'Go Pradhan, Go', while beating plates and spoons","Cockroach Janta Party protest LIVE | Protestors shout 'Go Pradhan, Go', while beating plates and spoons",0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janta Party', 'ORG'), ('Pradhan', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Kerala HC orders police protection for viral Kumbh Mela woman during Madhya Pradesh visit in abduction case,Kerala HC orders police protection for viral Kumbh Mela woman during Madhya Pradesh visit in abduction case,0.0,neutral,"[('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('Kumbh Mela', 'PERSON'), ('Madhya Pradesh', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Trump unveils new Air Force One, a gift from Qatar","Trump unveils new Air Force One, a gift from Qatar",0.0,neutral,"[('Air Force One', 'ORG'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Karnataka open to talks with Tamil Nadu on Mekedatu project, says Irrigation Minister Ramalinga Reddy","Karnataka open to talks with Tamil Nadu on Mekedatu project, says Irrigation Minister Ramalinga Reddy",0.0,neutral,"[('Karnataka', 'PERSON'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'PERSON'), ('Mekedatu', 'GPE'), ('Ramalinga Reddy', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,NEET UG re-exam: Nagpur student gets Abu Dhabi centre; NTA to correct ‘allotment error’,NEET UG re-exam: Nagpur student gets Abu Dhabi centre; NTA to correct ‘allotment error’,0.0,neutral,"[('Abu Dhabi', 'ORG'), ('NTA', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Abhishek Banerjee says armed individuals at airport posed security threat; Trinamool claims ‘murder bid’,Abhishek Banerjee says armed individuals at airport posed security threat; Trinamool claims ‘murder bid’,0.0,neutral,"[('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia war LIVE: 16 killed in Israeli strikes on south Lebanon despite ceasefire,West Asia war LIVE: 16 killed in Israeli strikes on south Lebanon despite ceasefire,-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Census 2027: The pressures of counting India,Census 2027: The pressures of counting India,0.0,neutral,"[('2027', 'DATE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Monsoon tracker LIVE | Heavy rain expected in 10 districts of  Tamil Nadu,Monsoon tracker LIVE | Heavy rain expected in 10 districts of  Tamil Nadu,0.0,neutral,"[('Heavy', 'NORP'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Several reported killed in Israeli strikes on Lebanon despite ceasefire,Several reported killed in Israeli strikes on Lebanon despite ceasefire,-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Zelensky stripped of highest Polish honour over WW2 name of army unit,Zelensky stripped of highest Polish honour over WW2 name of army unit,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Polish', 'NORP'), ('WW2', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Tourist dies in Dominican Republic luxury resort fire,Tourist dies in Dominican Republic luxury resort fire,0.0,neutral,"[('Dominican Republic', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Italy's Meloni says Trump 'made up' story that she 'begged' him for photo at G7,Italy's Meloni says Trump 'made up' story that she 'begged' him for photo at G7,0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Meloni', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('G7', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US to stop funding HIV programmes in South Africa,US to stop funding HIV programmes in South Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Watch: World Cup fans react to US defeating Australia to reach knockout round,Watch: World Cup fans react to US defeating Australia to reach knockout round,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Australia confirms first case of H5N1 bird flu as virus reaches every continent,Australia confirms first case of H5N1 bird flu as virus reaches every continent,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('H5N1', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,African and Caribbean nations call for formal apology for transatlantic slavery,African and Caribbean nations call for formal apology for transatlantic slavery,0.0,neutral,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"James Burrows, legendary director of Cheers and Friends, dies aged 85","James Burrows, legendary director of Cheers and Friends, dies aged 85",0.0,neutral,"[('James Burrows', 'PERSON'), ('Cheers', 'ORG'), ('Friends', 'ORG'), ('85', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Boy, 12, wins hearts after trying to check sick chicken into Ethiopian hospital","Boy, 12, wins hearts after trying to check sick chicken into Ethiopian hospital",1.0,positive,"[('12', 'DATE'), ('Ethiopian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Mideast Live Updates: Fighting Persists in Lebanon, Complicating Iran Peace Talks","Mideast Live Updates: Fighting Persists in Lebanon, Complicating Iran Peace Talks",1.0,positive,"[('Mideast Live Updates', 'ORG'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Complicating Iran Peace Talks', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A 175-Year-Old Shipwreck, Lots of Booze and a Korean Island’s Quest to Survive","A 175-Year-Old Shipwreck, Lots of Booze and a Korean Island’s Quest to Survive",0.0,neutral,"[('175-Year-Old Shipwreck', 'DATE'), ('a Korean Island’s Quest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Charles Kushner, U.S. Ambassador to France, Riles Paris With Trump Diplomacy","Charles Kushner, U.S. Ambassador to France, Riles Paris With Trump Diplomacy",0.0,neutral,"[('Charles Kushner', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Riles Paris', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,World Leaders Awaited Iran Deal for Months. Here’s Why They’re Still Wary.,World Leaders Awaited Iran Deal for Months. Here’s Why They’re Still Wary.,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Months', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Cape Verde Will Count on Vozinha Against Uruguay at the World Cup,Cape Verde Will Count on Vozinha Against Uruguay at the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘Game Changer’? Too Soon to Tell. But Ukraine Flexed in Striking Moscow.,‘Game Changer’? Too Soon to Tell. But Ukraine Flexed in Striking Moscow.,0.0,neutral,"[('Tell', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine Flexed', 'FAC'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Trump Called Iván Cepeda a ‘Radical Left Marxist.’ Can He Be Colombia’s President?,Trump Called Iván Cepeda a ‘Radical Left Marxist.’ Can He Be Colombia’s President?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump Called Iván Cepeda', 'ORG'), ('Marxist', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Abelardo De La Espriella, Right-Wing Outsider, Could Be Colombia’s Next President","Abelardo De La Espriella, Right-Wing Outsider, Could Be Colombia’s Next President",1.0,positive,"[('Abelardo De La Espriella', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Trains Collide in UK, Killing at Least One and Injuring Dozens of Others","Trains Collide in UK, Killing at Least One and Injuring Dozens of Others",-1.0,negative,"[('Trains Collide', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Killing', 'GPE'), ('at Least One', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_20,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mexico’s Laws Have a New Target: Journalists,Mexico’s Laws Have a New Target: Journalists,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico’s Laws Have a New Target', 'ORG')]"
