Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,4 grandes cambios en Reino Unido 10 años después del referendo sobre su salida de la Unión Europea (y qué tan posible es ahora su regreso al bloque),4 big changes in the United Kingdom 10 years after the referendum on its departure from the European Union (and how possible its return to the bloc is now),0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('the United Kingdom', 'GPE'), ('10 years', 'DATE'), ('the European Union', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué Starmer pasó de una victoria electoral aplastante a renunciar menos de dos años tras asumir como primer ministro de Reino Unido,Why Starmer went from a landslide election victory to resigning less than two years after taking over as UK Prime Minister,1.0,positive,"[('less than two years', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo hizo su fortuna De la Espriella y los cuestionados negocios del ganador de las elecciones en Colombia,How De la Espriella made his fortune and the questioned businesses of the winner of the elections in Colombia,1.0,positive,"[('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Hermanas de esperma"": descubrimos que teníamos el mismo padre donante después de haber cumplido 20 años","""Sperm sisters"": we discovered we had the same donor father after we turned 20",0.0,neutral,"[('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La historia de Alejandro Ojeda Carbajal, el fotógrafo mexicano que inmortalizó la ""mano de Dios"" de Maradona hace 40 años","The story of Alejandro Ojeda Carbajal, the Mexican photographer who immortalized Maradona's ""hand of God"" 40 years ago",0.0,neutral,"[('Alejandro Ojeda Carbajal', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Maradona', 'PERSON'), ('40 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El estrecho vínculo de Abelardo de la Espriella con EE.UU. (y las dudas que despierta que un estadounidense sea el presidente de Colombia),Abelardo de la Espriella's close ties with the US (and the doubts raised by an American being the president of Colombia),0.0,neutral,"[(""Abelardo de la Espriella's"", 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Los mapas y gráficos que muestran cómo se repartieron los votos en las elecciones en Colombia, según el preconteo","The maps and graphs that show how the votes were distributed in the elections in Colombia, according to the pre-count",0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué diferencias hay entre el preconteo y el escrutinio en las elecciones de Colombia y por qué la izquierda pide esperar antes de conceder la derrota,What differences are there between the pre-count and the scrutiny in the Colombian elections and why the left asks to wait before conceding defeat,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quién es Andy Burnham, el ""rey del norte"" que quiere suceder a Keir Starmer como primer ministro de Reino Unido","Who is Andy Burnham, the ""king of the north"" who wants to succeed Keir Starmer as Prime Minister of the United Kingdom",0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('Keir Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Es una alegría verlos jugar"": cómo Cabo Verde se ha convertido en la gran sensación del Mundial 2026","""It's a joy to watch them play"": how Cape Verde has become the great sensation of the 2026 World Cup",1.0,positive,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान से अमेरिकी प्रतिबंध हटने का फ़ायदा भारत को कितना होगा?,How much will India benefit from the lifting of US sanctions on Iran?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'दुनिया में शांति लाने के बाद अब पाकिस्तान के नेता अपने लोगों के आटे-दाल के बारे में सोचें': ब्लॉग,"'After bringing peace to the world, now the leaders of Pakistan should think about the welfare of their people': Blog",1.0,positive,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,भारत ने अमेरिका-ईरान समझौते पर कहा- 'हम सावधानी भरे आशावाद के साथ आगे बढ़ रहे हैं'","Live, India said on US-Iran agreement - 'We are moving forward with cautious optimism'",-1.0,negative,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,रहस्यमय 'डांसिंग गर्ल' पाकिस्तान से भारत कैसे पहुँची?,How did the mysterious 'dancing girl' reach India from Pakistan?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ममता बनर्जी को टीएमसी के बाग़ी विधायकों ने अध्यक्ष पद से हटाया, जानिए अब उनके पास क्या हैं विकल्प","Mamata Banerjee was removed from the post of President by rebel TMC MLAs, know what are her options now",0.0,neutral,"[('Mamata Banerjee', 'PERSON'), ('TMC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लखनऊ आग हादसा: 'पापा, आग लग गई है, मुझे बचा लो'","Lucknow fire accident: 'Papa, there is a fire, save me'",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वर्ल्ड कप फ़ुटबॉल 2026: मेसी ने रचा इतिहास और एम्बापे का करिश्मा, अगले दौर में पहुंचीं अर्जेंटीना और फ़्रांस","World Cup Football 2026: Messi created history and Mbappe's charisma, Argentina and France reached the next round.",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Football', 'EVENT'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Mbappe', 'ORG'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,नेतन्याहू इन 5 वजहों से अमेरिका-ईरान समझौते को लेकर हैं परेशान,Netanyahu is worried about the US-Iran agreement for these 5 reasons,0.0,neutral,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बेगूसराय में महिला का सामूहिक बलात्‍कार, प्राइवेट पार्ट से डॉक्‍टरों ने लकड़ी निकाली, अब तक क्‍या पता है","Gang rape of woman in Begusarai, doctors removed wood from private part, what is known till now",0.0,neutral,"[('Begusarai', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"क़तर के रास लाफ़ान इंडस्ट्रियल सिटी में धमाका, 12 भारतीयों की गई जान","Explosion in Qatar's Ras Laffan Industrial City, 12 Indians killed",-1.0,negative,"[('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('Ras Laffan Industrial City', 'FAC'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O movimento católico ultraconservador que desafia o papa e cresce no Brasil com missa em latim e padre de costas,The ultraconservative Catholic movement that defies the pope and grows in Brazil with Mass in Latin and a priest with his back,0.0,neutral,"[('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Latin', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como De la Espriella construiu sua fortuna e os negócios questionáveis envolvendo o vencedor das eleições na Colômbia,How De la Espriella built his fortune and the questionable deals involving the winner of the Colombian elections,1.0,positive,"[('Colombian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As dúvidas que pairam sobre o mais cotado para substituir Keir Starmer como primeiro-ministro do Reino Unido,The doubts that hang over the most likely candidate to replace Keir Starmer as Prime Minister of the United Kingdom,0.0,neutral,"[('Keir Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A explosão de cubanos pedindo refúgio no Brasil: 'Com o salário de psicólogo em Cuba não dava para comprar nem 30 ovos',"The explosion of Cubans asking for refuge in Brazil: 'With the salary of a psychologist in Cuba, I couldn't even buy 30 eggs'",0.0,neutral,"[('Cubans', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem o Brasil pode enfrentar no mata-mata da Copa do Mundo? Os cenários de cada resultado,Who can Brazil face in the World Cup knockout stages? The scenarios for each outcome,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A fantástica metamorfose de Messi: as cinco vidas do maior artilheiro da história das Copas,Messi's fantastic metamorphosis: the five lives of the greatest scorer in World Cup history,1.0,positive,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como a economia dos EUA continua superando seus rivais apesar de toda turbulência do governo Trump,How the US economy continues to outperform its rivals despite all the turmoil from the Trump administration,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Vídeo,Usar sapatos dentro de casa é falta de higiene? O que diz a Ciência, Duration 1,40","Video, Is wearing shoes indoors bad hygiene? What Science Says, Duration 1.40",0.0,neutral,"[('1.40', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Guerra' por ingressos de turnê do BTS vira pesadelo para fãs que caíram em golpes online,'War' for BTS tour tickets turns into nightmare for fans who fell for online scams,-1.0,negative,"[('BTS', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como é viver nos 5 países mais seguros do mundo em 2026,What it's like to live in the 5 safest countries in the world in 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,От «мистера Дарси» до «Мидаса наоборот». Почему ушел Кир Стармер?,"From ""Mr. Darcy"" to ""Reverse Midas"". Why did Keir Starmer leave?",0.0,neutral,"[('Darcy', 'PERSON'), ('Keir Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: трое погибших в результате ракетного удара по Кривому Рогу","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: three killed in a missile attack on Krivoy Rog",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Krivoy Rog', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Прогноз — выше 40°C. Во многих странах Европы объявлен красный уровень опасности из-за жары,The forecast is above 40°C. Many European countries have declared a red alert due to the heat.,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Гонка за «Золотой бутсой»: кто победит в исторической битве бомбардиров на ЧМ-2026?,Race for the Golden Boot: who will win the historic battle of goalscorers at the 2026 World Cup?,1.0,positive,"[('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Похитители Нэнси Гатри еще в феврале сообщили, что она умерла",Nancy Guthrie's kidnappers reported back in February that she had died.,0.0,neutral,"[(""Nancy Guthrie's"", 'PERSON'), ('February', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Долго так не может продолжаться». Как живут без топлива Крым и другие захваченные Россией территории,“This can’t go on for long.” How Crimea and other territories captured by Russia live without fuel,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Финансист-оберег. Умер Алан Гринспен, главный банкир США при четырех президентах","Financier-amulet. Alan Greenspan, chief US banker under four presidents, dies",0.0,neutral,"[('Alan Greenspan', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"США приостановили санкции против иранской нефти. Иран отрицает, что согласился допустить инспекторов к ядерным объектам",The US has suspended sanctions against Iranian oil. Iran denies agreeing to allow inspectors into nuclear sites,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трамп обвинил вандалов в порче Отражающего бассейна в Вашингтоне, позеленевшего после покраски в синий цвет","Trump blames vandals for damaging Washington's Reflecting Pool, which turned green after being painted blue.",0.0,neutral,"[('Washington', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Атака на Воронеж: серьезно поврежден военный завод, пять человек погибли","Attack on Voronezh: a military plant was seriously damaged, five people were killed",-1.0,negative,"[('five', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 バーナム氏、数週間後にも次期英首相になる可能性が濃厚　スターマー氏辞任で,[Commentary] There is a strong possibility that Mr. Burnham will become the next British Prime Minister in a few weeks due to Mr. Starmer's resignation.,0.0,neutral,"[('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('a few weeks', 'DATE'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 スターマー氏はなぜ辞任したのか、新指導者はどうやって決まるのか,[Explanation] Why did Starmer resign and how will a new leader be chosen?,0.0,neutral,"[('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、対イラン石油制裁を一時停止　核査察受け入れに同意したと主張するもイランは否定,"US suspends oil sanctions against Iran, claims it has agreed to nuclear inspections, but Iran denies",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ミャンマー軍、6カ月間で民間人700人超を殺害　国連報告,"Myanmar military kills over 700 civilians in 6 months, UN report",-1.0,negative,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE'), ('700', 'CARDINAL'), ('6 months', 'DATE'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 メッシ、さらに2ゴール　通算18得点で単独1位に,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Messi scores 2 more goals, ranking solo in first place with 18 total points",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('18', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,南米コロンビア大統領選、トランプ氏が支持した右派候補が勝利,Right-wing candidate supported by Trump wins Colombian presidential election in South America,1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('South America', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米オラクル、過去1年で2万人超を整理　AI投資で事業再編,"U.S. Oracle lays off over 20,000 employees in the past year, reorganizing business with AI investment",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Oracle', 'ORG'), ('over 20,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('the past year', 'DATE'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,英労働党にとって激動の1日、スターマー氏辞任からバーナム氏の下院復帰まで, 所要時間 1,46","Video, A turbulent day for the British Labor Party, from Starmer's resignation to Burnham's return to the House of Commons, Duration 1,46",0.0,neutral,"[('the British Labor Party', 'ORG'), ('Starmer', 'ORG'), ('Burnham', 'ORG'), ('the House of Commons, Duration 1,46', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,スターマー英首相、辞任発表　次の与党党首が決まるまでは留任,"British Prime Minister Starmer announces resignation, remains in office until new ruling party leader is chosen",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,【全訳】スターマー氏の辞任演説　次の総選挙へ向けた「党の答えを聞いた」, 所要時間 7,07","Video, [Full translation] Starmer's resignation speech: ``I heard the party's answer'' for the next general election, Duration 7,07",0.0,neutral,"[('Starmer', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yapunguza vikwazo vya mafuta huku Iran Ikikanusha madai ya Vance kuhusu wakaguzi wa nyuklia","Directly, US eases oil embargo as Iran denies Vance's claims about nuclear inspectors",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Vance', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Mbio za taji la mfungaji bora duniani - nani ataibuka kidedea?,World Cup 2026: The race for the world's top goalscorer title - who will come out on top?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wanawake wanaonufaika na utalii kupitia urithi wa utamaduni wao Zanzibar,Women who benefit from tourism through their cultural heritage in Zanzibar,0.0,neutral,"[('Zanzibar', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Syria inaweza kuchukua nafasi ya Israel kukabiliana na Hezbollah?,Syria can replace Israel to face Hezbollah?,0.0,neutral,"[('Syria', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Makubaliano ya Marekani na Iran yaibua maswali iwapo kulikuwa na haja yoyote ya vita,The US-Iran deal raises questions about whether there was any need for war,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Waziri Mkuu wa Uingereza Sir Keir Starmer ajiuzulu,British Prime Minister Sir Keir Starmer to resign,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Keir Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumanne: Morgan Rogers kujiunga na Arsenal,European football rumors Tuesday: Morgan Rogers to join Arsenal,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Rogers', 'ORG'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Duru ya kwanza ya mazungumzo ya Marekani na Iran yahitimishwa,The first round of negotiations between the United States and Iran is concluded,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Uingereza inabadilisha mawaziri wakuu kila mara?,Why does Britain keep changing prime ministers?,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Jinsi BBC inavyoziorodhesha timu zote baada ya mzunguko wa kwanza wa mechi,World Cup 2026: How the BBC ranks all the teams after the first round of matches,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran’s president lands in Pakistan after crucial talks with US,Iran’s president lands in Pakistan after crucial talks with US,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘I have never doped’: Vondrousova says after receiving four-year tennis ban,‘I have never doped’: Vondrousova says after receiving four-year tennis ban,0.0,neutral,"[('Vondrousova', 'ORG'), ('four-year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,What Israeli and Lebanese officials are saying before Washington talks,What Israeli and Lebanese officials are saying before Washington talks,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanese', 'NORP'), ('Washington', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Brexit 10 years on: What has changed in the UK explained in maps and charts,Brexit 10 years on: What has changed in the UK explained in maps and charts,0.0,neutral,"[('Brexit', 'PERSON'), ('10 years', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,England face Ghana: Can Three Lions roar to the World Cup knockouts?,England face Ghana: Can Three Lions roar to the World Cup knockouts?,0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('Ghana', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran says technical talks with US in Switzerland conclude successfully,Iran says technical talks with US in Switzerland conclude successfully,1.0,positive,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel’s deliberate targeting of Gaza children part of genocide: UN inquiry,Israel’s deliberate targeting of Gaza children part of genocide: UN inquiry,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,About 20 drown in France trying to escape heatwave sweeping much of Europe,About 20 drown in France trying to escape heatwave sweeping much of Europe,0.0,neutral,"[('About 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran war day 116: US eases Iran sanctions; Lebanon ceasefire holds,Iran war day 116: US eases Iran sanctions; Lebanon ceasefire holds,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('116', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,EU to hold migration meeting with Taliban officials in Brussels,EU to hold migration meeting with Taliban officials in Brussels,0.0,neutral,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Taliban', 'ORG'), ('Brussels', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"FCRA Rules tightened: NGOs must declare social media accounts, stick to specified activities","FCRA Rules tightened: NGOs must declare social media accounts, stick to specified activities",0.0,neutral,"[('FCRA Rules', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"TVK, DMK engage in heated debate in Tamil Nadu Assembly over CM Vijay’s remarks on ‘party funds’","TVK, DMK engage in heated debate in Tamil Nadu Assembly over CM Vijay’s remarks on ‘party funds’",0.0,neutral,"[('TVK', 'ORG'), ('DMK', 'ORG'), ('Tamil Nadu Assembly', 'ORG'), ('CM Vijay’s', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Explained: Meta’s $900 million investment in Cred and hiring of Kunal Shah as WhatsApp chief,Explained: Meta’s $900 million investment in Cred and hiring of Kunal Shah as WhatsApp chief,0.0,neutral,"[('Meta’s', 'ORG'), ('$900 million', 'MONEY'), ('Cred', 'ORG'), ('Kunal Shah', 'FAC'), ('WhatsApp', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Iran says UN watchdog will not be allowed to inspect bombed nuclear sites,Iran says UN watchdog will not be allowed to inspect bombed nuclear sites,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,IT Ministry asks CJP’s Dipke to be present for hearing on X account ban,IT Ministry asks CJP’s Dipke to be present for hearing on X account ban,0.0,neutral,"[('IT Ministry', 'ORG'), ('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,George Kurian resigns as Union Minister after his Rajya Sabha term ends,George Kurian resigns as Union Minister after his Rajya Sabha term ends,0.0,neutral,"[('George Kurian', 'PERSON'), ('Rajya Sabha', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Devastating building fire in Lucknow puts development authority’s actions under scrutiny,Devastating building fire in Lucknow puts development authority’s actions under scrutiny,0.0,neutral,"[('Lucknow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Two workers killed in susppected boiler blast at factory near Visakhapatnam’s Pharma City,Two workers killed in susppected boiler blast at factory near Visakhapatnam’s Pharma City,-1.0,negative,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Visakhapatnam', 'GPE'), ('Pharma City', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Google restores Telegram on Play Store in India, app starts functioning for some users","Google restores Telegram on Play Store in India, app starts functioning for some users",0.0,neutral,"[('Google', 'ORG'), ('Telegram', 'PRODUCT'), ('Play Store', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia war LIVE updates: Iran will determine usage of unfrozen assets, says Iranian Ambassador","West Asia war LIVE updates: Iran will determine usage of unfrozen assets, says Iranian Ambassador",-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Iran says no new commitments on nuclear sites after Vance says inspectors to be invited back,Iran says no new commitments on nuclear sites after Vance says inspectors to be invited back,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Vance', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump anticipates better relationship with Colombia under new leader,Trump anticipates better relationship with Colombia under new leader,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ransom note claims Nancy Guthrie died after abduction,Ransom note claims Nancy Guthrie died after abduction,0.0,neutral,"[('Ransom', 'PERSON'), ('Nancy Guthrie', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Montreal shooting leaves officer, civilian and suspect dead","Montreal shooting leaves officer, civilian and suspect dead",0.0,neutral,"[('Montreal', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Inquiry ordered after building fire kills 15 in north India city,Inquiry ordered after building fire kills 15 in north India city,-1.0,negative,"[('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Dettol apologises after ad to clean up 'toxic men' backfires in China,Dettol apologises after ad to clean up 'toxic men' backfires in China,0.0,neutral,"[('Dettol', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Myanmar army killed over 700 civilians in six months, UN says","Myanmar army killed over 700 civilians in six months, UN says",-1.0,negative,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE'), ('700', 'CARDINAL'), ('six months', 'DATE'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Russian troop build-up threatens city seen as key to seizing Ukraine's Donbas,Russian troop build-up threatens city seen as key to seizing Ukraine's Donbas,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Donbas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Tesla crash that killed a woman under US federal investigation,Tesla crash that killed a woman under US federal investigation,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,At least 13 killed and dozens injured after Qatar gas explosion,At least 13 killed and dozens injured after Qatar gas explosion,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 13', 'CARDINAL'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Mark Rutte of NATO Manages an Unpredictable Trump,How Mark Rutte of NATO Manages an Unpredictable Trump,0.0,neutral,"[('Mark Rutte', 'PERSON'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘A Terrible Inheritance’: Could Andy Burnham Succeed Where Starmer Failed?,‘A Terrible Inheritance’: Could Andy Burnham Succeed Where Starmer Failed?,-1.0,negative,"[('Andy Burnham Succeed', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran Makes Moves to Assert Control Over the Strait of Hormuz,Iran Makes Moves to Assert Control Over the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Soldier, Scholar and Symbol: Marc Bloch Is Elevated to France’s Panthéon","Soldier, Scholar and Symbol: Marc Bloch Is Elevated to France’s Panthéon",0.0,neutral,"[('Scholar', 'ORG'), ('Marc Bloch', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Those British Strawberries Are Being Picked by Central Asian Workers,Those British Strawberries Are Being Picked by Central Asian Workers,0.0,neutral,"[('Those British Strawberries Are Being Picked', 'ORG'), ('Central Asian Workers', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Delcy Rodríguez, Venezuela’s President, Struggles to Uphold Trump’s Narrative of Success","Delcy Rodríguez, Venezuela’s President, Struggles to Uphold Trump’s Narrative of Success",1.0,positive,"[('Delcy Rodríguez', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Uphold Trump’s Narrative of Success', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iranian Singer Sentenced to 74 Lashes for Performing Without Hijab,Iranian Singer Sentenced to 74 Lashes for Performing Without Hijab,0.0,neutral,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('74', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"At World Cup Soccer Game, Palestinian Emblems Abound","At World Cup Soccer Game, Palestinian Emblems Abound",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Soccer Game', 'EVENT'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Keir Starmer Resigns as UK Prime Minister,Keir Starmer Resigns as UK Prime Minister,0.0,neutral,"[('Keir Starmer Resigns', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_23,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Cuba’s Fuel Crisis Brings Schools to a Standstill,Cuba’s Fuel Crisis Brings Schools to a Standstill,-1.0,negative,"[('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
