Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,5 razones para mirar el futuro con optimismo,5 reasons to look at the future with optimism,0.0,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Fuegos artificiales y espectáculos de luces: las imágenes de las celebraciones  de Año Nuevo alrededor del mundo,Fireworks and light shows: images of New Year's celebrations around the world,0.2681818181818182,"[('Fireworks', 'PERSON'), (""New Year's"", 'EVENT')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo era el calendario maya que fue ""tan exacto incluso hasta en segundos"" y cómo se sigue usando hasta la actualidad","What was the Mayan calendar like that was ""so exact even down to seconds"" and how it is still used to this day",0.04722222222222221,"[('Mayan', 'NORP'), ('this day', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Trump necesita destruir algunos objetivos en Venezuela o parecerá débil"": John Feeley, exembajador de EE.UU. y experto en América Latina","""Trump needs to destroy some targets in Venezuela or he will look weak"": John Feeley, former US ambassador and Latin America expert",-0.19166666666666665,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('John Feeley', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Acoger ""la nada"", la idea del filósofo Jean-Paul Sartre que te puede resultar ""liberadora"" para iniciar el nuevo año","Welcome ""nothing"", the idea of ​​philosopher Jean-Paul Sartre that can be ""liberating"" to start the new year",0.4681818181818182,"[('Jean-Paul Sartre', 'PERSON'), ('the new year', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत के बारे में बांग्लादेश जमात-ए इस्लामी के अमीर ने ऐसा क्या कहा कि देनी पड़ी सफ़ाई,What did the Amir of Bangladesh Jamaat-e-Islami say about India that he had to clarify?,0.0,"[('Bangladesh Jamaat-e-Islami', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,स्विट्ज़रलैंड: पुलिस ने स्थानीय मीडिया को बताया, धमाके के वक़्त बार में 100 से ज़्यादा लोग थे मौजूद","Live, Switzerland: Police told local media, more than 100 people were present in the bar at the time of the blast.",0.1590909090909091,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('more than 100', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ख़ालिदा ज़िया को श्रद्धांजलि देने ढाका गए जयशंकर की इस तस्वीर की चर्चा पाकिस्तान और बांग्लादेश के मीडिया में,"This picture of Jaishankar, who went to Dhaka to pay tribute to Khaleda Zia, is being discussed in the media of Pakistan and Bangladesh.",0.0,"[('Jaishankar', 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka', 'ORG'), ('Khaleda Zia', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इंदौर, सबसे साफ़ शहर: 'मेरा बच्चा पाँच महीने का था, पानी ने जान ले ली', दूषित पानी से कई मौतें","Indore, the cleanest city: 'My child was five months old, water took his life', many deaths due to contaminated water",0.15833333333333333,"[('five months old', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ख़ालिदा ज़िया के पति ज़ियाउर रहमान की क़ब्र से शव निकाल दोबारा दफनाने की कहानी,The story of re-burying the body of Khaleda Zia's husband Ziaur Rehman from the grave.,0.0,"[(""Khaleda Zia's"", 'PERSON'), ('Ziaur Rehman', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अमेरिका: ज़ोहरान ममदानी ने न्यूयॉर्क के मेयर पद की ली शपथ,America: Zohran Mamdani takes oath as Mayor of New York,0.13636363636363635,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अरावली की पहाड़ी हर दिन टूट रही है लेकिन यहाँ रहने वाली आबादी के दुख का पहाड़ बढ़ता ही जा रहा,Aravali hills are breaking every day but the mountain of sorrow of the population living here is increasing.,0.0,"[('Aravali', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बैंकिंग और पैन संबंधी प्रावधानों में आज से बदलाव, आप पर क्या होगा असर","Changes in banking and PAN related provisions from today, what will be the impact on you",0.0,"[('PAN', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'ताऊ, तेरी छोरी की उम्र की हूं मैं', हरियाणा की अभिनेत्री के बयान के बाद किस मुद्दे पर बहस छिड़ी","'Tau, I am of your daughter's age', on which issue the debate started after the statement of the Haryana actress?",0.0,"[('Tau', 'PERSON'), ('Haryana', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,2025 foi o ano de Pernambuco?,Was 2025 the year of Pernambuco?,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('the year', 'DATE'), ('Pernambuco', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,O resgate de passageiros após acidente de trem perto de Machu Picchu: 'Vi gente no chão, chorando', Duration 0,41","Video,The rescue of passengers after a train accident near Machu Picchu: 'I saw people on the ground, crying', Duration 0.41",-0.05,"[('Machu Picchu', 'FAC'), ('0.41', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que se sabe sobre o acidente de trem que matou uma pessoa e deixou dezenas feridas em rota para Machu Picchu,What is known about the train accident that killed one person and injured dozens en route to Machu Picchu,-0.2,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Machu Picchu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Como evitar a ressaca — e quais alimentos podem piorar os sintomas, Duration 1,13","Video, How to avoid a hangover — and which foods can make symptoms worse, Duration 1.13",-0.4,"[('1.13', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro apresenta melhora em soluços e tem alta prevista para dia 1º: entenda,Bolsonaro presents improvement in hiccups and is scheduled to be discharged on the 1st: understand,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('the 1st', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Abraçar o 'nada': a ideia do filósofo Jean-Paul Sartre que pode ser libertadora para começar o ano,Embracing 'nothing': philosopher Jean-Paul Sartre's idea that can be liberating to start the year,0.0,"[(""Jean-Paul Sartre's"", 'PERSON'), ('the year', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Trump precisa explodir alguns alvos na Venezuela ou parecerá fraco', diz ex-embaixador dos EUA","'Trump needs to blow up some targets in Venezuela or he will look weak,' says former US ambassador",-0.1875,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Lula não deveria disputar reeleição por 'idade avançada' e políticas econômicas 'medíocres', diz Economist","Lula should not run for re-election due to 'advanced age' and 'mediocre' economic policies, says Economist",-0.006249999999999992,"[('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,'PF brasileiro tem 4 dos 5 alimentos que precisamos', diz Rita Lobo, Duration 1,38","Video,'Brazilian PF has 4 of the 5 foods we need', says Rita Lobo, Duration 1.38",0.0,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rita Lobo', 'PERSON'), ('1.38', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в новогоднюю ночь Россия выпустила по Украине ударные беспилотники; разведки США считают, что Киев не атаковал резиденцию Путина дронами, пишет WSJ","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: on New Year's Eve, Russia launched attack drones across Ukraine; US intelligence believes that Kyiv did not attack Putin’s residence with drones, writes WSJ",0.13636363636363635,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), (""New Year's Eve"", 'EVENT'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('WSJ', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Мир встречает новый 2026 год. Фотографии,The world is celebrating the new year 2026. Photos,0.13636363636363635,"[('the new year 2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Дьявол носит Prada», «Крик» и еще 18 самых ожидаемых кинопремьер 2026 года","“The Devil Wears Prada,” “Scream” and 18 more of the most anticipated film premieres of 2026",0.5,"[('The Devil Wears Prada', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп выводит войска из Чикаго, Лос-Анджелеса и Портленда","Trump withdraws troops from Chicago, Los Angeles and Portland",0.0,"[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('Los Angeles', 'GPE'), ('Portland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Израиль запретит деятельность 37 международных НПО в Газе. Британия и ЕС предупреждают о серьезных последствиях,Israel will ban the activities of 37 international NGOs in Gaza. Britain and EU warn of serious consequences,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('37', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Финская полиция задержала судно, подозреваемое в повреждении подводного кабеля по пути из России",Finnish police detained a ship suspected of damaging a submarine cable en route from Russia,0.0,"[('Finnish', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Гниют зубы, выпадают ногти»: дочь Джимми Лая рассказала Би-би-си о состоянии гонконгского диссидента в тюрьме","“Teeth is rotting, nails are falling out”: Jimmy Lai’s daughter told the BBC about the condition of the Hong Kong dissident in prison",0.0,"[('Jimmy Lai’s', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Брижит Бардо, Оззи Осборн, Роберт Редфорд... Вспоминаем, кого мир потерял в 2025 году","Brigitte Bardot, Ozzy Osbourne, Robert Redford... We remember who the world lost in 2025",0.0,"[('Brigitte Bardot', 'PERSON'), ('Ozzy Osbourne', 'PERSON'), ('Robert Redford', 'PERSON'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Саудовская Аравия призывает ОАЭ вывести войска из Йемена и бомбит привезенное оттуда оружие. Что происходит между союзниками?,Saudi Arabia calls on the UAE to withdraw troops from Yemen and bombs weapons brought from there. What's going on between the allies?,0.0,"[('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'ORG'), ('Yemen', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Платье из водорослей, плащ из комбучи. Как биоматериалы могут изменить моду","Seaweed dress, kombucha raincoat. How biomaterials can change fashion",0.0,[]
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【写真で見る】 2026年を迎えた各地の様子　花火と黙祷,[See photos] Various locations celebrating 2026 with fireworks and silence,0.0,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU外交トップ、ウクライナがプーチン氏公邸を攻撃したとするロシアの主張を否定　和平プロセスへの妨害と非難,"EU diplomat denies Russia's claim that Ukraine attacked Putin's residence, accuses it of interfering with peace process",0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米議会、スミス元特別検察官の証言を公開　トランプ氏の起訴について,U.S. Congress releases former special counsel Smith's testimony regarding Trump's indictment,0.17857142857142858,"[('U.S. Congress', 'ORG'), ('Smith', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,世界各地で花火やダンス、2026年の始まり祝う,Fireworks and dances around the world celebrate the start of 2026,0.0,"[('Fireworks', 'PERSON'), ('the start of 2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ユーロスターの運行復旧　電力障害で大混乱の後,Eurostar service restored after power outage caused chaos,0.0,"[('Eurostar', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米首都のケネディ・センター公演、中止相次ぐ　トランプ氏の名前入れた改称にアーティストから異議,Performances at the Kennedy Center in the US capital are canceled one after another; artists object to name change to include Trump's name,-0.1,"[('the Kennedy Center', 'FAC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ドイツで銀行金庫から3000万ユーロ盗まれる　ドリル使用か,A drill was used to steal 30 million euros from a bank safe in Germany,0.5,"[('30 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,40以上の戦争を取材してきた、しかし2025年のような年は見たことがない――シンプソンBBC世界情勢編集長,"I've covered more than 40 wars, but I've never seen a year like 2025 - BBC World Affairs Editor-in-Chief Simpson",0.5,"[('more than 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国軍、台湾周辺で軍事演習　「分離主義勢力」への警告と,"Chinese military conducts military exercises near Taiwan as a warning to ""separatist forces""",-0.025,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,2026 Tusikubali tofauti za kiitikadi zitugawe- Samia","Live, 2026 Let's not allow ideological differences to divide us - Samia",0.13636363636363635,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Dunia yasheherekea mwaka mpya 2026,The world celebrates the new year 2026,0.13636363636363635,"[('the new year 2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ndoto zako za mwaka 2026 unazianzaje?,How do you start your dreams for 2026?,0.0,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"AFCON 2025: Sahau 16 bora, haya ni mafanikio mengine 5 ya Tanzania","AFCON 2025: Forget the top 16, here are 5 more successes for Tanzania",0.5,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Alhamisi: Man U, Bayern Munich na PSG wanamtaka Yan Diomande","European Football Rumors Thursday: Man U, Bayern Munich and PSG want Yan Diomande",0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Yan Diomande', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Sherehe za mwaka mpya katika picha,New year celebrations in pictures,0.13636363636363635,"[('New year', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi 10 tajiri zaidi duniani mwaka 2025,The 10 richest countries in the world in 2025,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Arsenal kuwa mabingwa msimu huu?,Arsenal to be champions this season?,0.0,"[('this season', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Matukio ya kukumbukwa Tanzania mwaka 2025,Memorable events in Tanzania in 2025,0.5,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu waliotawala mijadala mitandaoni 2025 nchini Tanzania,Find out who dominated online discussions in 2025 in Tanzania,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
