Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Somalilandia, el territorio que declaró su independencia hace más de 30 años y que hoy solo Israel reconoce como nación soberana","Somaliland, the territory that declared its independence more than 30 years ago and that today only Israel recognizes as a sovereign nation",0.25,"[('more than 30 years ago', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Invitamos a un hombre a casa para Navidad y se quedó con nosotros 45 años""","""We invited a man home for Christmas and he stayed with us for 45 years""",0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('45 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""No ha sido una reparación porque los culpables siguen libres"": Azul Rojas, la mujer trans que logró una sentencia histórica tras ser torturada por 3 policías en Perú","""It has not been a reparation because the culprits are still free"": Azul Rojas, the trans woman who achieved a historic sentence after being tortured by 3 police officers in Peru",0.2,"[('Azul Rojas', 'PERSON'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué pasa cuando dejas las inyecciones para perder peso,What happens when you stop weight loss injections,0.0,[]
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,10 de las imágenes más sorprendentes de 2025,10 of the most surprising images of 2025,0.6,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सोमालिया के भीतर अलग सोमालीलैंड देश को मान्यता इसराइल ने क्यों दी? तुर्की, सऊदी समेत कई देश ख़फ़ा",Why did Israel recognize the separate country of Somaliland within Somalia? Many countries including Türkiye and Saudi are angry,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Somaliland', 'GPE'), ('Somalia', 'GPE'), ('Türkiye', 'GPE'), ('Saudi', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,उन्नाव रेप सर्वाइवर ने कहा- 'वो मुझे फूलन देवी बनने को मजबूर कर रहे हैं',Unnao rape survivor said- 'They are forcing me to become Phoolan Devi',0.0,"[('Unnao', 'GPE'), (""Phoolan Devi'"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,एशेज़ सिरीज़: चौथे टेस्ट में दूसरे दिन ही इंग्लैंड ने ऑस्ट्रेलिया को चार विकेट से हराया","Live, Ashes series: England beats Australia by four wickets on the second day of the fourth test",0.04545454545454545,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('the second day', 'DATE'), ('fourth', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"उत्तराखंड: अंकिता भंडारी केस में 'वीआईपी' से जुड़े नए आरोप, पिता ने मांगा इंसाफ़","Uttarakhand: New allegations related to 'VIP' in Ankita Bhandari case, father demands justice",0.06818181818181818,"[('Uttarakhand', 'ORG'), ('Ankita Bhandari', 'FAC')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तमिलनाडु: निजी ज़मीन पर बनी 220 फीट लंबी दीवार को 'छुआछूत' से जोड़ने का विवाद - ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट,Tamil Nadu: Controversy linking 220 feet long wall built on private land to 'untouchability' - Ground Report,-0.025,"[('Tamil Nadu', 'PERSON'), ('220 feet', 'QUANTITY')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत में क्रिसमस सेलिब्रेशन के दौरान तोड़फोड़ की घटनाओं की चर्चा अंतरराष्ट्रीय मीडिया में ऐसे हुई,This is how incidents of vandalism during Christmas celebrations in India were discussed in the international media.,0.0,"[('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"विजय हजारे ट्रॉफ़ी: विराट के बल्ले से फिर निकले रन, लेकिन रोहित नहीं चले, किस टीम ने किसे हराया","Vijay Hazare Trophy: Virat scored runs again but Rohit did not, which team defeated whom?",0.0,"[('Vijay Hazare Trophy', 'PERSON'), ('Virat', 'NORP'), ('Rohit', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश में भारत क्या चूक गया? आईसीजी की रिपोर्ट और एक्सपर्ट्स से समझिए,What did India miss in Bangladesh? Understand from ICG report and experts,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('ICG', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वक़्त की धारा में हँसिए की धार, भारतीय कम्युनिस्ट पार्टी के 100 साल","The edge of the sickle in the stream of time, 100 years of the Communist Party of India",0.0,"[('100 years', 'DATE'), ('the Communist Party of India', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Fuga ao Paraguai com pitbull, passaporte falso e carta sobre câncer: como ex-diretor da PRF foi preso e o que acontece agora","Escape to Paraguay with pitbull, fake passport and letter about cancer: how former PRF director was arrested and what happens now",-0.25,"[('Escape', 'PERSON'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('PRF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os bolsonaristas que fugiram do Brasil para evitar prisão,The Bolsonarists who fled Brazil to avoid arrest,-0.05,"[('Bolsonarists', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As 10 imagens mais surpreendentes de 2025,The 10 most surprising images of 2025,0.6,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Após propaganda controversa, Sydney Sweeney diz que quer fazer filmes 'que salvem vidas'","After controversial advertising, Sydney Sweeney says she wants to make films 'that save lives'",0.375,"[('Sydney Sweeney', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Trump decidiu bombardear o Estado Islâmico na Nigéria,Why Trump decided to bomb the Islamic State in Nigeria,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A atriz de 'O Agente Secreto' que começou no cinema aos 72 e chegou ao radar do Oscar,The actress from 'The Secret Agent' who started in cinema at 72 and reached the Oscar radar,-0.4,"[(""The Secret Agent'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('72', 'DATE'), ('Oscar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Médica venezuelana condenada a 30 anos por criticar Maduro em áudio no WhatsApp deixa a prisão,Venezuelan doctor sentenced to 30 years for criticizing Maduro in audio on WhatsApp leaves prison,0.0,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('WhatsApp', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Onda de calor: por que 8 Estados do Brasil enfrentam 'alerta vermelho' por temperaturas extremas?,Heat wave: why are 8 states in Brazil facing 'red alert' for extreme temperatures?,-0.0625,"[('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Mega da Virada: por que você pode ganhar R$ 1 bilhão e ainda assim ir à falência?,Mega da Virada: why can you earn R$1 billion and still go bankrupt?,0.0,"[('Mega da Virada', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: массированная атака на Киев перед визитом Зеленского в США","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: massive attack on Kyiv before Zelensky’s visit to the USA",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Камбоджа и Таиланд договорились о немедленном прекращении огня,Cambodia and Thailand agree to immediate ceasefire,0.0,"[('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('Thailand', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Твардовский, память и правда в СССР и в современной России","Tvardovsky, memory and truth in the USSR and in modern Russia",0.2,"[('Tvardovsky', 'PERSON'), ('USSR', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Израиль первым в мире признал независимость Сомалиленда, отколовшегося от Сомали","Israel was the first in the world to recognize the independence of Somaliland, which broke away from Somalia.",0.25,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Somaliland', 'PRODUCT'), ('Somalia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трое братьев из Дагестана в «Манчестер Юнайтед» и один в MMA: история семьи Ибрагимовых,Three brothers from Dagestan to Manchester United and one to MMA: the story of the Ibragimov family,0.0,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Dagestan', 'GPE'), ('Manchester United', 'PERSON'), ('Ibragimov', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Признак значительного прогресса». Зеленский заявил, что встретится с Трампом 28 декабря во Флориде","""A sign of significant progress."" Zelensky said he will meet with Trump on December 28 in Florida",0.375,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('December 28', 'DATE'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сколько еще Украина сможет удерживать города Покровск и Мирноград в Донецкой области,How much longer can Ukraine hold the cities of Pokrovsk and Mirnograd in the Donetsk region?,0.2,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Pokrovsk', 'GPE'), ('Mirnograd', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Лицо, известное многим как „Юра Унитаз“». Кто может возглавить российские беспилотные войска","""The face known to many as 'Yura Toilet'."" Who can lead Russian unmanned troops",0.15555555555555556,"[(""Yura Toilet'"", 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что мы знаем о потерях России в Украине в 2025 году?,What do we know about Russian losses in Ukraine in 2025?,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Взрыв в алавитской мечети в Сирии: восемь погибших и 18 раненых,Explosion in an Alawite mosque in Syria: eight dead and 18 wounded,-0.2,"[('Alawite', 'NORP'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('18', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、トランプ氏と近くフロリダで会談予定と表明　戦争終結に向け,Zelenskiy announces plans to meet with Trump in Florida soon to end the war,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエルがソマリランドを承認、世界初　ソマリアや近隣国は非難,"Israel recognizes Somaliland, world's first, Somalia and neighboring countries condemn",0.25,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Somaliland', 'PRODUCT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Somalia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル北部で襲撃事件、2人死亡　容疑者はパレスチナ人と当局,Two killed in attack in northern Israel; suspects are Palestinians and authorities,-0.2,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,シリアのモスクで金曜礼拝中に爆発、少なくとも8人死亡,Explosion at Syrian mosque during Friday prayers kills at least 8 people,-0.3,"[('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('at least 8', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍、ナイジェリアの「イスラム国」に「強力な」攻撃実施　トランプ氏が発表,"U.S. military launches ""strong"" attack on Islamic State in Nigeria, Trump announces",0.16666666666666663,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Islamic State', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トルコ、「イスラム国」メンバー115人を拘束　年末年始の攻撃を計画した疑い,Türkiye detains 115 Islamic State members suspected of planning year-end and New Year attacks,0.13636363636363635,"[('Türkiye', 'ORG'), ('115', 'CARDINAL'), ('Islamic', 'NORP'), ('year-end', 'DATE'), ('New Year', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,教皇レオ、ウクライナでの戦争を終わらせる「勇気」促す　初のクリスマス演説,Pope Leo urges “courage” to end war in Ukraine in first Christmas speech,0.25,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英国王、分断された世界での結束を呼びかける　クリスマス恒例メッセージ,British King's annual Christmas message calls for unity in a divided world,0.0,"[(""British King's"", 'ORG'), ('annual', 'DATE'), ('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 アメリカ人教皇とアメリカ政府、仲たがいしているのか,[Commentary] Are the American Pope and the US government at odds?,0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Zelensky kukutana na Trump Jumapili kwa mazungumzo ya kukomesha vita","Directly, Zelensky to meet with Trump on Sunday for talks to end the war",0.1,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini awamu ya pili ya usitishaji mapigano Gaza imekwama?,Why is the second phase of the cease-fire in Gaza stalled?,0.0,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,AFCON 2025: Uganda vs Tanzania katika dabi ya msiba harusini,AFCON 2025: Uganda vs Tanzania in a wedding disaster,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Uganda', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Man Utd inafikiria kumsajili Garner,European Football Rumors: Man Utd are considering signing Garner,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Garner', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mzaha kuhusu upara wangu ulivyobadilisha maisha yangu,How a joke about my baldness changed my life,0.0,[]
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Marekani yafanya shambulizi Nigeria,  dhidi ya nani na kwa nini?","The United States is attacking Nigeria, against whom and why?",0.0,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Muonekano wa Yesu ulikuwa vipi, Wanahistoria wanasema nini?","What was the appearance of Jesus, what do Historians say?",0.0,"[('Jesus', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Habari 10 zilizosomwa sana BBC mwaka 2025,10 most read BBC news in 2025,0.5,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Netanyahu anajiandaa kuishambulia tena Iran?",Is Netanyahu preparing to attack Iran again?,0.0,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu Jiji la Uswizi linalokuruhusu kulipia vitu vingi kwa sarafu ya Bitcoin,Discover the Swiss City that allows you to pay for many things with Bitcoin currency,0.5,"[('the Swiss City', 'GPE'), ('Bitcoin', 'NORP')]"
