Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Mapas coloniales y un templo antiguo: la historia detrás del sangriento conflicto entre Tailandia y Camboya,Colonial maps and an ancient temple: the story behind the bloody conflict between Thailand and Cambodia,-0.6000000000000001,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Al menos 2 muertos y 9 heridos en un tiroteo en la Universidad de Brown en Rhode Island,At least 2 dead and 9 injured in shooting at Brown University in Rhode Island,-0.25,"[('At least 2', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brown University', 'ORG'), ('Rhode Island', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Los diamantes de Amberes: cómo fueron descubiertos los protagonistas del ""robo del siglo"" gracias a un palo de escoba, una comadreja y un sándwich de salami","The Antwerp diamonds: how the protagonists of the ""robbery of the century"" were discovered thanks to a broomstick, a weasel and a salami sandwich",0.2,"[('Antwerp', 'GPE'), ('the century', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Bebés vikingos"": por qué el esperma danés domina el mercado de las donaciones","""Viking babies"": why Danish sperm dominates the donation market",0.0,"[('Danish', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Aficionados indignados lanzan sillas y botellas en un evento de Messi en la India,Outraged fans throw chairs and bottles at Messi event in India,-0.9,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नोबेल शांति पुरस्कार विजेता को वेनेजु़एला से निकालने के सीक्रेट मिशन की पूरी कहानी,The complete story of the secret mission to evacuate the Nobel Peace Prize winner from Venezuela,-0.15000000000000002,"[('the Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,असम में भारतीय वायु सेना के रिटायर्ड अधिकारी गिरफ़्तार, पाकिस्तानी एजेंटों के साथ संबंधों के आरोप","Live, Retired Indian Air Force officer arrested in Assam, accused of links with Pakistani agents",0.13636363636363635,"[('Indian Air Force', 'ORG'), ('Assam', 'GPE'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"केरल स्थानीय चुनाव में यूडीएफ़ की जीत, लेकिन तिरुवनंतपुरम में एनडीए को बढ़त के मायने क्या?","UDF's victory in Kerala local elections, but what does NDA's lead in Thiruvananthapuram mean?",-0.15625,"[('UDF', 'ORG'), ('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('NDA', 'ORG'), ('Thiruvananthapuram', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,शैलेंद्र के वे गीत जो ज़िंदगी के विरोधाभास से भरे हैं,Those songs of Shailendra which are full of contradictions of life,0.35,"[('Shailendra', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,इंडिगो संकट ने किसकी नाकामी को उजागर किया?,Whose failure did the Indigo crisis expose?,-0.3166666666666667,"[('Indigo', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत के मिडिल क्लास के सपनों को पहिए देने वाली मारुति की कहानी,"The story of Maruti, which gave wheels to the dreams of India's middle class.",0.0,"[('Maruti', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पंकज चौधरी हो सकते हैं यूपी बीजेपी के अगले अध्यक्ष, उनके चेहरे के पीछे क्या है पार्टी की रणनीति?","Pankaj Chaudhary can be the next president of UP BJP, what is the party's strategy behind his face?",-0.2,"[('Pankaj Chaudhary', 'ORG'), ('UP BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"राजस्थान में एथेनॉल फ़ैक्ट्री को लेकर क्यों हुई हिंसा, अब कैसे हैं हालात - ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट","Why was there violence over ethanol factory in Rajasthan, how is the situation now - Ground Report",0.0,"[('Rajasthan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मेसी के कोलकाता कार्यक्रम में बवाल, ममता बनर्जी ने जांच समिति बनाई तो बीजेपी ने साधा निशाना","Uproar in Messi's Kolkata event, when Mamata Banerjee formed an investigation committee, BJP targeted",0.0,"[('Messi', 'GPE'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE'), ('Mamata Banerjee', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como se comparam 'Bolsonaro chileno' e candidata comunista que disputam presidência do Chile neste domingo,How do 'Chilean Bolsonaro' compare to the communist candidate running for president of Chile this Sunday,0.0,"[(""Chilean Bolsonaro'"", 'PERSON'), ('communist', 'NORP'), ('Chile', 'GPE'), ('this Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que se sabe sobre ataque que deixou mortos e feridos em universidade nos EUA,What is known about the attack that left dead and injured at a university in the USA,-0.1,"[('USA', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Humanos são monogâmicos? O que revela nova 'escala romântica' dos animais,Are humans monogamous? What reveals new 'romantic scale' of animals,0.06818181818181818,[]
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os novos detalhes do dia da prisão de Luigi Mangione revelados por câmeras corporais,The new details of the day of Luigi Mangione's arrest revealed by body cameras,0.043181818181818175,"[('the day', 'DATE'), (""Luigi Mangione's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como microssessões de exercício podem ajudar a viver mais,How exercise microsessions can help you live longer,0.13636363636363635,[]
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump está deixando Bolsonaro 'à deriva', diz analista americano","Trump is leaving Bolsonaro 'adrift', says American analyst",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Governo Trump retira sanções contra Alexandre de Moraes e esposa pela Lei Magnitsky,Trump administration lifts sanctions against Alexandre de Moraes and his wife under the Magnitsky Act,0.0,"[('Alexandre de Moraes', 'PERSON'), ('the Magnitsky Act', 'LAW')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como a pobreza afeta milhões de pessoas no Reino Unido,How poverty affects millions of people in the UK,0.0,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por dentro da operação secreta que tirou opositora da Venezuela e a levou à Noruega para receber Nobel,Inside the secret operation that took an opponent out of Venezuela and took her to Norway to receive the Nobel Prize,-0.4,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('the Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Босния 30 лет спустя. Чем закончилась самая кровавая война 1990-х?, Продолжительность 14,15","Video, Bosnia 30 years later. How did the bloodiest war of the 1990s end?, Duration 14.15",0.0,"[('Bosnia', 'GPE'), ('30 years later', 'DATE'), ('the 1990s end', 'DATE'), ('14.15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Здесь полный хаос»: как детей в Марселе втягивают в наркоторговлю — и часто убивают,“It’s complete chaos here”: how children in Marseille are drawn into the drug trade - and often killed,-0.05,"[('Marseille', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Стрельба в одном из старейших университетов США: погибли двое студентов,Shooting at one of the oldest US universities: two students killed,-0.2,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Лукашенко освободил Колесникову, Бабарико, Беляцкого и еще более 100 человек после отмены санкций США на калий","Lukashenko released Kolesnikova, Babariko, Byalyatsky and more than 100 people after the lifting of US sanctions on potassium",0.5,"[('Lukashenko', 'PERSON'), ('Kolesnikova', 'PERSON'), ('Babariko', 'PERSON'), ('Byalyatsky', 'PERSON'), ('more than 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Двое американских военных и переводчик погибли при нападении в Сирии,Two American soldiers and a translator died in an attack in Syria,0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Syria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский анонсировал «много событий» на встрече в Берлине","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky announced “many events” at a meeting in Berlin",0.5,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Berlin', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Украина ликвидирует интернациональные легионы: зачем и к чему это может привести?,Ukraine is liquidating international legions: why and what could this lead to?,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Момент, когда люди впервые добыли огонь: обнаружено самое раннее свидетельство",The moment humans first made fire: Earliest evidence discovered,0.25,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Европа прикрывает границы. Борьба с мигрантами набирает обороты перед решающим 2026 годом,Europe is closing its borders. The fight against migrants is gaining momentum ahead of the decisive year 2026,0.0,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the decisive year 2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Таиланд и Камбоджа продолжили столкновения на границе после заявления Трампа о прекращении огня,Thailand and Cambodia continue border clashes after Trump ceasefire announcement,0.0,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU、ロシア資産の無期限凍結で合意　対ウクライナ融資計画への活用を念頭,"EU agrees to indefinitely freeze Russian assets, with consideration for use in loan plans for Ukraine",0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,チャールズ英国王、がん治療順調と　新年から治療を軽減へ,King Charles' cancer treatment is going well; treatment will be reduced in the new year,0.13636363636363635,"[('the new year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,2023年ノーベル平和賞の人権活動家モハンマディ氏、イランで拘束　支持者が発表,"2023 Nobel Peace Prize winner human rights activist Mohammadi detained in Iran, supporters announce",0.0,"[('2023', 'DATE'), ('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Mohammadi', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,韓国大学入試の英語、異常なほど難しいと批判噴出　責任者が辞任,"The person in charge of the Korean university entrance exam, which is criticized for being unusually difficult in English, resigns.",-0.25,"[('Korean', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告めぐる新写真を米民主党議員が公開　トランプ氏などさまざまな著名人の姿,"US Democratic Party member releases new photos of former defendant Epstein, featuring various celebrities including Trump",0.04545454545454545,"[('US Democratic Party', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インドネシアを襲ったサイクロンと洪水、オランウータンにも大きな被害か,"Cyclones and floods hit Indonesia, causing great damage to orangutans",0.8,"[('Cyclones', 'GPE'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米移民当局が再拘束のアブレゴ＝ガルシア氏、連邦地裁が釈放を命じ新たな拘束を禁止　政府は反発,"Abrego-Garcia, who was re-detained by US immigration authorities, is released by a federal judge and prohibited from being detained again; the government protests",0.0,"[('Abrego-Garcia', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイとカンボジアが戦闘停止に合意とトランプ米大統領,"Thailand and Cambodia agree to cease fighting, US President Trump says",0.0,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「自分が最も役立つ場所に身を置く」とノーベル平和賞のマチャド氏　BBC単独インタビュー, 所要時間 8,51","Video, ""Place yourself in the place where you can be most useful,"" says Nobel Peace Prize winner Machado in exclusive BBC interview, duration 8,51",0.4,"[('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Machado', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Israel yamlenga afisa mkuu wa Hamas katika shambulio baya la Gaza","Directly, Israel has targeted a senior Hamas official in a deadly Gaza attack",-0.05,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumapili: West Ham yavutiwa na Sargent,Sunday football rumours: West Ham interested in Sargent,0.25,"[('Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu aina ya vyakula ambavyo ukivila vinakufanya unukie vizuri,Know the types of foods that make you smell good when you eat them,0.7,[]
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Mashambulizi ya jeshi la anga la Sudan yaua mamia katika miji, masoko na shule - Ripoti","Sudanese air force strikes kill hundreds in towns, markets and schools - Report",0.0,"[('Sudanese', 'NORP'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kombe la Mataifa ya Afrika 2025: Ratiba na nyakati za mechi 52 za ​​AFCON nchini Morocco,Africa Cup of Nations 2025: Schedule and times for the 52 AFCON matches in Morocco,0.0,"[('Africa Cup', 'EVENT'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('52', 'CARDINAL'), ('AFCON', 'ORG'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi Venezuela inavyotumia 'meli za mapepo' kukwepa vikwazo vya mafuta,How Venezuela uses 'ghost ships' to evade oil embargoes,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Wahamiaji wote wanapaswa kumlipa msafirishaji haramu... lakini wanawake wanalazimika kutoa huduma za ngono','All migrants have to pay the trafficker... but women are forced to provide sex services',-0.30000000000000004,[]
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi 10 zenye madeni makubwa zaidi Afrika,10 countries with the biggest debts in Africa,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wimbi la vifo vya wapinzani linavyoongezeka duniani,The wave of death of opponents is increasing in the world,0.0,[]
2025_12_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mahakama ya Kenya imesitisha mpango wa msaada wa afya wa Marekani kutokana na masuala ya faragha,A Kenyan court has suspended the US health aid program due to privacy concerns,-0.125,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
