Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién fue la Lady Godiva real, la jinete desnuda que se convirtió en un símbolo de resistencia","Who was the real Lady Godiva, the naked rider who became a resistance symbol",0.1,"[('Lady Godiva', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ट्रंप इसराइल को नाराज़ करने का रिस्क लेकर क़तर के लिए इस हद तक क्यों जा रहे हैं?,Why are Trump going to this extent for Qatar with the risk of making Israel angry?,-0.5,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्रिकेट के वो 10 रिकॉर्ड जो पुरुषों से पहले महिलाओं ने बनाए,10 records of cricket that women made before men,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सेना प्रमुख जनरल उपेंद्र द्विवेदी के भूगोल वाले बयान पर बोली पाकिस्तान की सेना,Pakistan's army spoke on the geography statement of Army Chief General Upendra Dwivedi,0.05000000000000002,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Army', 'ORG'), ('Upendra Dwivedi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ग़ज़ा पीस प्लान से लेकर पाकिस्तान से नज़दीकी तक: भारत समेत दुनिया को ट्रंप क्या दिखाना चाहते हैं?,From Gaza Peace Plan to Pakistan to close: What do you want to show Trump to the world including India?,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ऐसे 'छोटे दिमाग़' वैज्ञानिकों ने बनाए जो कर सकते हैं बहुत कुछ,Scientists made such 'small minds' who can do a lot,-0.125,[]
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump prometeu retaliar inimigos — até onde ele pode ir?,Trump promised to retaliate enemies - how far can he go?,0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump diz que 'não tolerará demora' do Hamas no acordo de paz com Israel,Trump says 'won't tolerate Hamas' delay in the peace agreement with Israel,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As religiões são machistas?,Are religions macho?,0.0,[]
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O teste rápido e barato que detecta metanol e pode salvar vidas, mas que ainda espera investimento","The quick and cheap test that detects methanol and can save lives, but still expects investment",0.3666666666666667,[]
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Intoxicação por metanol: por dentro do mercado clandestino de lacres falsos, tampas e garrafas de bebidas alcoólicas","Methanol intoxication: inside the clandestine market of fake seals, lids and bottles of alcohol",-0.5,"[('Methanol', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que falta para que Lula e Trump conversem de novo?,What is missing for Lula and Trump to talk again?,-0.2,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os perigos de deixar que a IA organize sua próxima viagem,The dangers of letting the IA organize your next trip,0.0,"[('IA', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A mulher que se casou com um detento que conheceu enquanto visitava seu filho na prisão,The woman who married a detainee she met while visiting her son in prison,0.25,[]
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O office-boy que se tornou o primeiro rosto humano da história a aparecer na TV,Office-boy who became the first human face in history to appear on TV,0.125,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: атака на Львовскую область стала крупнейшей с начала войны, при попадании в дом погибла семья из четырех человек","Livelive, War in Ukraine: The attack on the Lviv region became the largest from the beginning of the war, when it entered the house, a family of four died",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Lviv', 'LOC'), ('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Массированный удар по Украине: Польша поднимала авиацию по тревоге, Россия выпустила более 50 ракет и около 500 дронов","A massive blow to Ukraine: Poland raised alarm aviation, Russia produced more than 50 missiles and about 500 drones",0.25,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('more than 50', 'CARDINAL'), ('about 500', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нобель для президента. Как воинственный американский лидер уговорил Россию подписать договор и получил премию мира,Nobel is for the president. How a warlike American leader persuaded Russia to sign an agreement and received a world award,0.0,"[('Nobel', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Расизм, любовь к насилию и женоненавистничество. Что выявила скрытая съемка в полицейском участке Лондона","Racism, love of violence and femininity. What was revealed hidden shooting in the police station London",0.16666666666666669,"[('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Дроны, язык жестов и попытки «выглядеть как американец»: как иммигранты в США пытаются перехитрить агентов ICE","Drones, gestures and attempts to “look like an American”: how immigrants in the United States are trying to outwit ICE agents",0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Столкновения в Тбилиси после муниципальных выборов: демонстранты попытались штурмовать президентский дворец,Clashes in Tbilisi after municipal elections: demonstrators tried to storm the presidential palace,0.0,"[('Tbilisi', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп санкционировал отправку в Чикаго 300 военнослужащих Национальной гвардии,Trump authorized the sending to Chicago 300 troops of the National Guard,0.0,"[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('the National Guard', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Пропалестинские акции в Европе: в Риме четверть миллиона человек прошли маршем мимо Колизея, в Лондоне почти 500 арестованных","Rosmostinsky actions in Europe: in Rome, a quarter of a million people passed a march past the Coliseum, in London almost 500 arrested",-0.25,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Rome', 'GPE'), ('a quarter', 'CARDINAL'), ('million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Coliseum', 'LOC'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('almost 500', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Нетаньяху пообещал освобождение заложников в ближайшие дни, Трамп призвал ХАМАС поторопиться","Netanyahu promised the release of hostages in the coming days, Trump called on Hamas to hurry",0.0,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('the coming days', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Результаты выборов в Чехии: партия евроскептика Бабиша лидирует, но самостоятельно создать правительство не сможет","Elections in the Czech Republic: the Babish euroskeptic party is the leader, but the government will not be able to create",0.5,"[('the Czech Republic', 'GPE'), ('Babish', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ネタニヤフ氏、「近日中」に人質解放発表を期待　ハマスの武装解除も実現させると表明,"Netanyahu hopes to announce hostage release ""coming soon""; Hamas will also be disarmed",0.0,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日本の「鉄の女」、自民党の高市早苗新総裁とは,"Who is Japan's ""Iron Woman"" and new president of the LDP Takaichi Sanae",0.13636363636363635,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Iron Woman', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the LDP Takaichi Sanae', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、シカゴへの州兵派遣を承認　300人規模,Trump approves 300 people to send National Guard to Chicago,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('300', 'CARDINAL'), ('National Guard', 'ORG'), ('Chicago', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロンドンで「パレスチナ・アクション」支持の抗議、500人近く逮捕,Nearly 500 people arrested in London for protesting against Palestinian Action,0.1,"[('Nearly 500', 'CARDINAL'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Palestinian Action', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,高市早苗氏、自民党の新総裁に選出　日本初の女性首相となる見通し,Takaichi Sanae is expected to become Japan's first female prime minister as new president of the LDP,0.0715909090909091,"[('Takaichi Sanae', 'PERSON'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('LDP', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ハマス、人質の解放に同意　トランプ氏はイスラエルにガザ攻撃停止を要求,Hamas agrees to release hostages; Trump demands Israel to stop attack on Gaza,0.0,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英カンタベリー大主教に初の女性、マラーリー氏指名　約1年の空席経て,"Marary is the first woman to become the Archbishop of Canterbury, and has been vacant for about a year",0.25,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('about a year', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英マンチェスターのシナゴーグ襲撃、襲撃犯はレイプ容疑で逮捕後に保釈中と警察発表,"Police announce that attacker in synagogue in Manchester, UK, is on bail after arrest on suspicion of rape",-0.05,"[('Manchester', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,独ミュンヘン空港にまたドローン飛来、24時間以内で2度目の一時閉鎖,"Drones fly back to Munich Airport, Germany, closing for the second time within 24 hours",0.26666666666666666,"[('Munich Airport', 'FAC'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('24 hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Netanyahu asema anatarajia kutangaza kuachiliwa kwa mateka katika 'siku zijazo'","Directly, Netanyahu says he hopes to announce the release of captives in 'future'",0.05,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mbappe mdogo atokeza kwenye kivuli cha kaka yake,Little Mbappe comes out of his brother's shadow,-0.1875,[]
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Putin aionya Marekani dhidi ya kuipatia Ukraine makombora ya Tomahawk,Putin warns the United States against giving Ukraine to Tomahawk missiles,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Tomahawk', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini mlo wenye chumvi kidogo una athari sawa na wenye chumvi nyingi?,Why does a low salt diet have the same effect as high salt?,0.05333333333333334,[]
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mabeki wa siku hizi sio wazuri kama ilivyokuwa wakati wangu - Rooney,Today's defenders are not as good as it was in my time - Rooney,0.7,"[('Today', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Trump asema 'hatavumilia ucheleweshaji wowote' kutoka kwa Hamas kuhusu makubaliano ya amani na Israel,Trump says 'he will not tolerate any delay' from Hamas about the peace agreement with Israel,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumapili: Real Madrid yamtaka Rodri wa Man City,Soccer Sunday Sunday: Real Madrid Wants Rodri of Man City,0.2,"[('Sunday Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Man City', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kundi la kanisa Anglikana la kihafidhina lashutumu uchaguzi wa Askofu Mkuu wa kike wa Canterbury,Anglican conservative group condemns the election of the archbishop of Canterbury,0.0,"[('Anglican', 'NORP'), ('Canterbury', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Sean 'Diddy' Combs ahukumiwa kifungo cha zaidi ya miaka minne jela,Sean 'Diddy' Combs is sentenced to more than four years in prison,0.5,"[('Sean', 'NORP'), ('Diddy', 'ORG'), ('more than four years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Takaichi, Waziri mkuu wa kwanza mwanamke mtarajiwa Japan","Takaichi, the first prime minister to be prospective Japan",0.25,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
