Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Vendí a mi hija de 5 años para que recibiera tratamiento médico"": las familias que se enfrentan a decisiones imposibles en Afganistán",'I sold my 5-year-old daughter for medical treatment': Families facing impossible decisions in Afghanistan,0.0,neutral,"[('5-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Al menos 90 personas murieron en una explosión en una mina de carbón en China, según medios estatales","At least 90 people died in a coal mine explosion in China, according to state media",0.0,neutral,"[('At least 90', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Lo que los británicos realmente quieren decir cuando dicen ""sorry""","What Brits Really Mean When They Say ""Sorry""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo es el Jardín de los Venenos, que alberga más de 100 plantas tóxicas (incluida la más venenosa del mundo)","What is the Garden of Poisons like, which houses more than 100 toxic plants (including the most poisonous in the world)",0.0,neutral,"[('the Garden of Poisons', 'FAC'), ('more than 100', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Los buceadores italianos que murieron en Maldivas carecían de equipos adecuados, según un rescatista","Italian divers who died in Maldives lacked proper equipment, rescuer says",0.0,neutral,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El director ejecutivo de un banco pide disculpas tras describir a sus trabajadores como ""capital humano de menor valor""","Bank CEO apologizes after describing his workers as ""lower value human capital""",0.0,neutral,"[('Bank', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El gobierno de Trump exigirá a la mayoría de los inmigrantes que solicitan la residencia que abandonen primero EE.UU.,The Trump administration will require most immigrants who apply for residency to leave the US first.,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Panamá no es un país inventado por EE.UU. para hacer un canal""","""Panama is not a country invented by the US to make a canal""",0.0,neutral,"[('Panama', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Rodrigo Rey Rosa y su novela inspirada en la megacárcel de Bukele: ""Con el giro a la derecha en el mundo, estos centros de detención pueden volverse la norma""","Rodrigo Rey Rosa and his novel inspired by Bukele's megaprison: ""With the shift to the right in the world, these detention centers can become the norm""",0.0,neutral,"[('Rodrigo Rey Rosa', 'PERSON'), ('Bukele', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El proyecto fruto de la Segunda Guerra Mundial que hace que los japoneses sufran cada vez más alergias,The project resulting from the Second World War that causes the Japanese to suffer more and more allergies,-1.0,negative,"[('the Second World War', 'EVENT'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्यूबा के पूर्व राष्ट्रपति राउल कास्त्रो का हाल भी क्या मादुरो जैसा होगा,Will the condition of former Cuban President Raul Castro be like that of Maduro?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cuban', 'NORP'), ('Raul Castro', 'PERSON'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अभिजीत दीपके ने कहा- सरकार ने 'कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी' की वेबसाइट बंद कर दी","Live, Abhijeet Deepke said- Government has closed the website of 'Cockroach Janata Party'",0.0,neutral,"[('Abhijeet Deepke', 'PERSON'), (""'Cockroach Janata Party'"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,खाड़ी के देशों में काम करने गईं कुछ भारतीय महिलाओं की आपबीती,Ordeal of some Indian women who went to work in Gulf countries,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'काश मैंने ये सर्जरी पहले कराई होती', ब्रेस्ट रिडक्शन सर्जरी के ट्रेंड बढ़ने की कहानी","'I wish I had done this surgery earlier', the story of increasing trend of breast reduction surgery",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,मार्को रुबियो ने दिल्ली आने से पहले जो कहा क्या वह भारत की उलझन बढ़ाता है?,Does what Marco Rubio said before coming to Delhi add to India's confusion?,0.0,neutral,"[('Marco Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी के संस्थापक अभिजीत दीपके के माता-पिता क्या चाहते हैं?,What do the parents of Cockroach Janata Party founder Abhijeet Deepke want?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG'), ('Abhijeet Deepke', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"गोवा से मुँह मोड़ रहे हैं विदेशी पर्यटक, श्रीलंका से मिल रही है कड़ी चुनौती","Foreign tourists are turning away from Goa, facing tough challenge from Sri Lanka",0.0,neutral,"[('Goa', 'PERSON'), ('Sri Lanka', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"तुलसी गबार्ड ने अचानक दिया इस्तीफ़ा, ट्रंप ने उनके इस्तीफ़े पर की ये टिप्पणी","Tulsi Gabbard suddenly resigned, Trump made this comment on her resignation",0.0,neutral,"[('Tulsi Gabbard', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भोजशाला पर फ़ैसले के बाद पहला शुक्रवारः 'हम जीत गए' और 'हमसे छीन लिया गया' के बीच धार,First Friday after the decision on Bhojshala: The edge between 'we won' and 'it was snatched from us',0.0,neutral,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Bhojshala', 'GPE'), ('us', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'बच्चे कहते हैं, बाबा रोटी दो... मैं कहां से दूं?': अपने बच्चों को बेचने के लिए मजबूर अफ़गान परिवार","'Children say, Baba give me bread... where should I give it from?': Afghan families forced to sell their children",0.0,neutral,"[('Baba', 'PERSON'), ('Afghan', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'O STF é um tribunal que julga muito e acaba sempre desagradando alguém', diz ex-ministro Luis Barroso","'The STF is a court that judges a lot and always ends up displeasing someone', says former minister Luis Barroso",0.0,neutral,"[('STF', 'ORG'), ('Luis Barroso', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Em reviravolta, Carla Zambelli é solta na Itália após Justiça anular extradição ao Brasil","In a twist, Carla Zambelli is released in Italy after the court annuls her extradition to Brazil",0.0,neutral,"[('Carla Zambelli', 'PERSON'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Lula descola de Flávio Bolsonaro e abre 4 pontos em eventual 2º turno, aponta Datafolha","Lula takes off from Flávio Bolsonaro and gains 4 points in the eventual 2nd round, points out Datafolha",0.0,neutral,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('2nd', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A disparada do custo de vida e dos imóveis em João Pessoa com chegada de jovens que buscam 'desacelerar' e 'investir',The soaring cost of living and real estate in João Pessoa with the arrival of young people looking to 'slow down' and 'invest',0.0,neutral,"[('João Pessoa', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Vacina britânica contra Ebola pode ficar pronta para testes em meses,British Ebola vaccine could be ready for testing in months,0.0,neutral,"[('British Ebola', 'ORG'), ('months', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Timing do escândalo com Vorcaro foi bom para Flávio Bolsonaro, dará tempo de se recuperar', diz Marcos Nobre","'Timing of the scandal with Vorcaro was good for Flávio Bolsonaro, it will give him time to recover', says Marcos Nobre",1.0,positive,"[('Vorcaro', 'ORG'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Marcos Nobre', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Mega-Sena faz 30 anos e paga R$ 300 milhões: os maiores prêmios da história e o que dá para comprar com eles,Mega-Sena turns 30 and pays R$300 million: the biggest prizes in history and what you can buy with them,0.0,neutral,"[('Mega-Sena', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Quando as pessoas ouvem a mesma música, nossos corações e nossa atividade cerebral se sincronizam'","'When people listen to the same music, our hearts and brain activity synchronize'",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Saía de casa pensando que podia ser atacado por uma feminista': como jovem escapou da machosfera,'I left the house thinking I might be attacked by a feminist': how a young man escaped the machosphere,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Casal é preso por abandonar dois meninos menores de 5 anos à beira de estrada em Portugal,Couple arrested for abandoning two boys under 5 years old on the side of the road in Portugal,0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('under 5 years old', 'DATE'), ('Portugal', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: МЧС России сообщило о 10 погибших в Старобельске; в Новороссийске после атаки дронов загорелась нефтебаза","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Russian Emergency Situations Ministry reported 10 dead in Starobelsk; in Novorossiysk, an oil depot caught fire after a drone attack",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Starobelsk', 'GPE'), ('Novorossiysk', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Голод или жадность: сколько еды класть себе в тарелку?,Hunger or greed: how much food should you put on your plate?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Участницы британского реалити-шоу «Женаты с первого взгляда»  заявили, что их насиловали экранные мужья",Participants in the British reality show Married at First Sight said they were raped by their on-screen husbands,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Около 90 рабочих погибли при взрыве на угольной шахте в Китае,About 90 workers died in a coal mine explosion in China,0.0,neutral,"[('About 90', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,SpaceX провела беспилотный испытательный полет самой большой в истории ракеты Starship V3,"SpaceX conducted an unmanned test flight of the largest rocket in history, Starship V3.",0.0,neutral,"[('SpaceX', 'PERSON'), ('Starship V3', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Директор национальной разведки США Талси Габбард подала в отставку,US Director of National Intelligence Tulsi Gabbard tenders her resignation,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Судья прекратил уголовное дело против Килмара Абрего Гарсии. Его депортация стала символом споров вокруг миграционной политики Трампа,A judge has dismissed the criminal case against Kilmar Abrego Garcia. His deportation became a symbol of the controversy surrounding Trump's immigration policies.,0.0,neutral,"[('Kilmar Abrego Garcia', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Путин приказал Минобороны «представить предложения» после атаки на колледж в Старобельске, ВСУ заявили об ударе по военным целям","Putin ordered the Ministry of Defense to “submit proposals” after the attack on the college in Starobelsk, the Ukrainian Armed Forces announced a strike on military targets",-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('the Ministry of Defense', 'ORG'), ('Starobelsk', 'GPE'), ('the Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Месси стал футболистом-миллиардером — как Роналду,Messi became a billionaire footballer - just like Ronaldo,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Ronaldo', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Освобожденные активисты «флотилии Газы» заявили о сексуализированном насилии после задержания в Израиле,Freed Gaza flotilla activists report sexualized violence after being detained in Israel,0.0,neutral,"[('Freed Gaza', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ポーランドに米兵追加配備すると発表　NATO会合の最中に,Trump announces deployment of additional US troops to Poland during NATO meeting,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エボラ出血熱のリスク、WHOが「非常に高い」に引き上げ　コンゴ民主共和国について,WHO raises Ebola risk to 'very high' for Democratic Republic of Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('Democratic Republic of Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン氏、ウクライナが学生寮を攻撃と非難　報復誓う,"Putin accuses Ukraine of attacking student dormitory, vows retaliation",-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ギャバード米国家情報長官、6月末に辞任へ　夫のがんが判明と,US Director of National Intelligence Gabbard to resign at the end of June after her husband was diagnosed with cancer,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('National Intelligence Gabbard', 'ORG'), ('the end of June', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米深夜番組「ザ・レイト・ショー」が終了　最後のゲストはマッカートニー氏,"US late-night show ""The Late Show"" ends with McCartney as the final guest",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('late-night', 'TIME'), ('The Late Show', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('McCartney', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 アメリカのカストロ元議長起訴、キューバで何が起こり得るのか,[Commentary] What could happen in Cuba after the indictment of former US President Castro?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアと中国、キューバ元指導者を起訴した米国を非難　米長官はキューバは「安全保障上の脅威」,"Russia, China criticize US for indicting former Cuban leader; US Secretary of State calls Cuba a 'security threat'",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuban', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、台湾への武器売却を一時停止　イランとの戦争が理由と,US suspends arms sales to Taiwan due to war with Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トイレ・更衣室は生物学的性別に基づく利用を、ジェンダー中立空間の必要性も明記　英平等委が新指針,"British Equality Commission's new guidelines specify that toilets and changing rooms should be used based on biological sex, and that gender-neutral spaces are required.",0.0,neutral,"[(""British Equality Commission's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「ノーの意味はノー」　グリーンランド住民、新しい米領事館前でトランプ氏に抗議,'No means no': Greenlanders protest against Trump in front of new US consulate,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Rubio ajaribu kutuliza Nato juu ya mabadililo ya wanajeshi wake kupelekwa Ulaya","Directly, Rubio tries to appease Nato on the change of its soldiers to be sent to Europe",0.0,neutral,"[('Nato', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Utaratibu usio wa kawaida nyuma ya mafanikio ya Salah,The unusual mechanism behind Salah's success,1.0,positive,"[('Salah', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hatari ya Ebola yaongezeka hadi 'juu zaidi' nchini DR Congo,Ebola risk rises to 'very high' in DR Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nadharia tatu kuhusu uwezekano wa kutokea mwisho wa dunia,Three theories about the possibility of the end of the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hadithi ya msichana aliyebakwa na sheikh aliyekuwa 'akimtibu',The story of a girl who was raped by a sheikh who was 'treating' her,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marekani yamuwekea vikwazo Mafwele kwa madai ya 'kuwatesa' wanaharakati wa haki za binadamu,The United States has imposed sanctions on Mafele for allegedly 'torturing' human rights activists,0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Mafele', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Masuala yanayokwaza mazungumzo kati ya Marekani na Iran,Issues hindering negotiations between the United States and Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Marekani imepata hasara kiasi gani katika vita vya Iran, kuanzia ndege za kivita hadi droni?","How much has the US lost in the Iran war, from warplanes to drones?",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('the Iran war', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi ya kuzuia picha zako za faragha zisivuje,How to prevent your private photos from being leaked,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wasanii wa Afrika Mashariki wanavyoishi katikati ya vita ya Marekani na Iran,East African artists live in the middle of the US-Iran war,-1.0,negative,"[('East African', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
