Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""He informado sobre más de 40 guerras y nunca he visto un año tan preocupante como 2025""","""I have reported on more than 40 wars and I have never seen a year as worrying as 2025""",0.5,"[('more than 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo el miedo a la deportación aumentó la cantidad de dinero que los hondureños en EE.UU. envían a su país,How fear of deportation increased the amount of money Hondurans in the US send home,0.0,"[('Hondurans', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los niños con cáncer a los que estafaron millones de dólares en América Latina y en el resto del mundo con los fondos recaudados en campañas para sus tratamientos,Children with cancer who were defrauded of millions of dollars in Latin America and the rest of the world with funds raised in campaigns for their treatments,0.0,"[('millions of dollars', 'MONEY'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El misterio de Mercurio, el planeta que los científicos creen que no debería existir","The mystery of Mercury, the planet that scientists believe should not exist",0.0,"[('Mercury', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""A menudo las personas se enferman en Navidad porque es el momento de hacer un diagnóstico de su relación con su familia""","""Often people get sick at Christmas because it is the time to make a diagnosis of their relationship with their family""",-0.7142857142857143,"[('Christmas', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बांग्लादेश: ढाका में ख़ालिदा ज़िया के बेटे से मिले जयशंकर, भारत क्या दे रहा है संकेत?","Bangladesh: Jaishankar met Khaleda Zia's son in Dhaka, what signal is India giving?",0.0,"[('Jaishankar', 'PERSON'), (""Khaleda Zia's"", 'PERSON'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,बांग्लादेश: भारत से एस जयशंकर और पाकिस्तान से सरदार अयाज़ सादिक़ ढाका पहुचे","Live, Bangladesh: S Jaishankar from India and Sardar Ayaz Sadiq from Pakistan reached Dhaka.",-0.05681818181818182,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Sardar Ayaz Sadiq', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Dhaka', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,गिग वर्कर्स के विरोध की कमान संभालने वाले शेख़ सलाउद्दीन को जानिए,"Know Sheikh Salahuddin, who led the protest of gig workers",0.0,"[('Salahuddin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश में जमात-ए इस्लामी और एनसीपी के साथ आने को भारत के हक़ में क्यों नहीं देखा जा रहा है?,Why is the coming together of Jamaat-e-Islami and NCP in Bangladesh not being seen in India's favor?,0.0,"[('Jamaat-e-Islami', 'GPE'), ('NCP', 'ORG'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ताबूत में 61 दिनों तक 'ज़िंदा दफ़्न' रहने वाले शख़्स की कहानी,The story of a man who was 'buried alive' in a coffin for 61 days,0.1,"[('61 days', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सऊदी अरब और यूएई में तनातनी, दोनों देशों में टकराव कितना गंभीर है?","Tension between Saudi Arabia and UAE, how serious is the conflict between the two countries?",-0.3333333333333333,"[('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सिंधु घाटी सभ्यता कैसे ख़त्म हुई थी, नई रिसर्च में जानिए वजह","How did the Indus Valley Civilization end, know the reason in new research",0.13636363636363635,"[('the Indus Valley Civilization', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सलमान ख़ान की 'बैटल ऑफ़ गलवान' फ़िल्म से चीन का सरकारी मीडिया क्यों हुआ नाराज़,Why was China's government media angry with Salman Khan's 'Battle of Galwan' film?,-0.5,"[('China', 'GPE'), (""Salman Khan's"", 'PERSON'), (""Battle of Galwan'"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'मैं बेहद ग़ुस्से में हूं': ट्रंप ने पुतिन के घर पर 'हमले' के बाद कहा, पीएम मोदी और शरीफ़ ने भी दी प्रतिक्रिया","'I am very angry': Trump said after 'attack' on Putin's house, PM Modi and Sharif also reacted",-0.65,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('PM Modi', 'ORG'), ('Sharif', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Mortes de soldados russos crescem no maior ritmo desde o início da guerra da Ucrânia,Russian soldier deaths rise at fastest rate since Ukraine war began,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Banco Master: depoimentos de Vorcaro e de diretor do BC abrem novo capítulo da investigação no STF,Banco Master: statements by Vorcaro and the BC director open a new chapter in the investigation at the STF,0.06818181818181818,"[('Banco Master', 'ORG'), ('Vorcaro', 'ORG'), ('BC', 'ORG'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Caso tenha problema com exageros, dê uma olhada nisso, porque a vida é muito melhor': a mensagem de Anthony Hopkins após 50 anos sem beber álcool","'If you have a problem with overindulging, take a look at this, because life is so much better': Anthony Hopkins' message after 50 years without drinking alcohol",0.5,"[(""Anthony Hopkins'"", 'PERSON'), ('50 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A ação dos ladrões para roubar 30 milhões de euros de banco na Alemanha: 'É como no filme 'Onze Homens e um Segredo'',The thieves' action to steal 30 million euros from a bank in Germany: 'It's like the movie 'Ocean's Eleven'',0.1,"[('30 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), (""Ocean's"", 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump afirma que EUA destruíram instalações para drogas na Venezuela,Trump says US destroyed drug facilities in Venezuela,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Como facções transformaram destinos turísticos do Nordeste em um grande negócio, Duration 2,59","Video, How factions turned tourist destinations in the Northeast into big business, Duration 2.59",0.0,"[('Northeast', 'LOC'), ('2.59', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,'Convidamos um homem para o Natal e ele ficou por 45 anos': o ato de bondade que mudou a vida de um sem-teto, Duration 1,37","Video, 'We Invited a Man to Christmas and He Stayed for 45 Years': The Act of Kindness That Changed a Homeless Man's Life, Duration 1.37",0.0,"[(""45 Years': The Act of Kindness That Changed a Homeless Man's Life, Duration"", 'DATE'), ('1.37', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Vídeo mostra casamento de mulher com personagem criado pelo ChatGPT, Duration 1,27","Video,Video shows a woman's wedding with a character created by ChatGPT, Duration 1.27",0.0,"[('1.27', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro faz terceiro procedimento  contra crise persistente de soluços: entenda,Bolsonaro undergoes third procedure against persistent hiccups: understand,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в результате российского удара по Одессе повреждены многоэтажки, есть пострадавшие","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: as a result of the Russian strike on Odessa, high-rise buildings were damaged, there were casualties",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Odessa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Ветеран Би-би-си Джон Симпсон: «Я работал на 40 войнах, но такого, как в 2025-м, не припомню»","BBC veteran John Simpson: ""I've worked in 40 wars, but I don't remember anything like the one in 2025""",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('John Simpson', 'PERSON'), ('40', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Почему имя Чайковского убрали из названия Национальной музыкальной академии Украины?,Why was Tchaikovsky's name removed from the name of the National Music Academy of Ukraine?,0.0,"[('Tchaikovsky', 'GPE'), ('the National Music Academy of Ukraine', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нападение не только на Путина. Как российская пропаганда реагирует на заявления об «атаке» на резиденцию президента России,The attack is not only on Putin. How Russian propaganda reacts to claims of an “attack” on the residence of the Russian President,-0.025,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Сомали прошли демонстрации против признания Израилем Сомалиленда. США защищают Израиль, но следовать его примеру не торопятся","Demonstrations took place in Somalia against Israel's recognition of Somaliland. The US defends Israel, but is in no hurry to follow its example",0.0,"[('Somalia', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Somaliland', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Правое крыло Франции призывает проводить кинозвезду Брижит Бардо с почестями национального уровня,France's right wing calls for film star Brigitte Bardot to be given national honors,0.2857142857142857,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Brigitte Bardot', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Плохой мир не устроит около 10% украинцев. Будет ли новый майдан?» Украинский социолог рассказал, какое мирное соглашение готовы принять украинцы",“A bad world will not suit about 10% of Ukrainians. Will there be a new Maidan? Ukrainian sociologist told what kind of peace agreement Ukrainians are ready to accept,0.059090909090909124,"[('about 10%', 'PERCENT'), ('Ukrainians', 'NORP'), ('Maidan', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainians', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Два года блокады. Когда откроется главный морской путь между Европой и Азией?,Two years of blockade. When will the main sea route between Europe and Asia open?,0.08333333333333333,"[('Two years', 'DATE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Asia', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Ученые предупреждают: средиземноморская большая белая акула может исчезнуть,Scientists warn: Mediterranean great white shark may become extinct,0.13333333333333333,"[('Mediterranean', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Итоги 2025 года на фронте | Военное время, Продолжительность 13,15","Video, Results of 2025 at the front | Wartime, Duration 13.15",0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('13.15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ユーロスター大規模運休　英仏海峡トンネルで電力トラブル,Massive suspension of Eurostar services due to power problems in the Channel Tunnel,-0.0625,"[('Eurostar', 'ORG'), ('the Channel Tunnel', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米首都のケネディ・センター公演、中止相次ぐ　トランプ氏の名前入れた改称にアーティストから異議,Performances at the Kennedy Center in the US capital are canceled one after another; artists object to name change to include Trump's name,-0.1,"[('the Kennedy Center', 'FAC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ドイツで銀行金庫から3000万ユーロ盗まれる　ドリル使用か,A drill was used to steal 30 million euros from a bank safe in Germany,0.5,"[('30 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,40以上の戦争を取材してきた、しかし2025年のような年は見たことがない――シンプソンBBC世界情勢編集長,"I've covered more than 40 wars, but I've never seen a year like 2025 - BBC World Affairs Editor-in-Chief Simpson",0.5,"[('more than 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナ、プーチン氏公邸へのドローン攻撃を否定,Ukraine denies drone attack on Putin's official residence,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国軍、台湾周辺で軍事演習　「分離主義勢力」への警告と,"Chinese military conducts military exercises near Taiwan as a warning to ""separatist forces""",-0.025,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,豪ビーチで銃撃犯と格闘の男性　罪のない人たちの犠牲を防ぎたかった,Man struggles with gunman on Australian beach - wanted to prevent innocent casualties,0.25,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,バングラデシュ初の女性首相、カレダ・ジア氏が死去　80歳,"Khaleda Zia, Bangladesh's first female prime minister, dies at the age of 80",0.125,"[('Khaleda Zia', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the age of 80', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ガザ停戦の第2段階へ「素早く」移行したいと　ネタニヤフ首相と会談,"Trump wants to move ""quickly"" to Phase 2 of ceasefire in Gaza, talks with Prime Minister Netanyahu",0.26666666666666666,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yazuia pesa za malezi ya watoto Minnesota kufuatia madai ya ulaghai","Directly, the United States freezes child care funds in Minnesota following allegations of fraud",0.05,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Minnesota', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu waliotawala mijadala mitandaoni 2025 nchini Tanzania,Find out who dominated online discussions in 2025 in Tanzania,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"AFCON 2025: Tanzania yaweka historia, yatinga 16 bora","AFCON 2025: Tanzania makes history, making it to the top 16",0.5,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Masuala magumu yanayotishia kuvuruga makubaliano ya amani ya Urusi na Ukraine,Difficult issues that threaten to derail the Russia-Ukraine peace agreement,-0.5,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,“Tuna lengo moja tu: kushinda vita” – M23,"""We have only one goal: to win the war"" - M23",0.4,[]
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatano: Marc Guehi anataka kuhamia Real Madrid,European Football Rumors Wednesday: Marc Guehi wants to move to Real Madrid,0.13333333333333333,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Marc Guehi', 'PERSON'), ('Real Madrid', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,MQ-9A Reaper: Ndege isiyo na rubani hatari zaidi duniani,MQ-9A Reaper: The world's deadliest drone,0.0,[]
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Mapinduzi hadi maandamano, 2025 ulikuwa mwaka mgumu kwa demokrasia Afrika","Revolution to protest, 2025 was a difficult year for democracy in Africa",-0.5,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('a difficult year', 'DATE'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini 2025 wasanii wa Tanzania hawatausahau?,Why will Tanzanian artists not forget 2025?,0.0,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_31,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Beyoncé atangazwa kuwa bilionea na Forbes,Beyoncé has been declared a billionaire by Forbes,0.0,"[('Beyoncé', 'ORG'), ('Forbes', 'ORG')]"
