Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Tropas extranjeras, dinero ruso confiscado y el apoyo de China: qué necesita Ucrania para que Putin ponga fin a la guerra","Foreign troops, confiscated Russian money and Chinese support: what Ukraine needs for Putin to end the war",-0.041666666666666664,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Trump ordena el bloqueo ""total y completo"" de todos los petroleros sancionados que entren y salgan de Venezuela","Trump orders the ""total and complete"" blockade of all sanctioned oil tankers entering and leaving Venezuela",0.05,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué es y cuánto poder tiene el Clan del Golfo, el grupo armado que EE.UU. designó como organización terrorista en Colombia","What is it and how much power does the Clan del Golfo have, the armed group that the US designated as a terrorist organization in Colombia",0.2,"[('the Clan del Golfo', 'FAC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Sentimos un profundo orgullo por su valentía"": Boris y Sofía, la pareja que murió al tratar de detener a los atacantes en la playa Bondi Beach de Australia","""We feel deep pride in their bravery"": Boris and Sofía, the couple who died while trying to stop the attackers on Bondi Beach in Australia",0.0,"[('Boris', 'PERSON'), ('Sofía', 'ORG'), ('Bondi Beach', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es Nick Reiner y cuáles son los cargos que enfrenta por el asesinato de sus padres, el cineasta Rob Reiner y la fotógrafa Michele Singer Reiner","Who is Nick Reiner and what charges he faces for the murder of his parents, filmmaker Rob Reiner and photographer Michele Singer Reiner",0.0,"[('Nick Reiner', 'PERSON'), ('Rob Reiner', 'PERSON'), ('Michele', 'PERSON'), ('Reiner', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'जी राम जी' बिल पर विवाद- जानिए, मनरेगा ने गांवों में कैसे बदली रोज़गार की तस्वीर",Controversy over 'Jee Ram Ji' bill - Know how MNREGA changed the picture of employment in villages,0.0,"[(""Jee Ram Ji'"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बोंडी बीच हमला: ऑस्ट्रेलिया के मीडिया में भारतीय नागरिक साजिद अकरम और उनके बेटे नवीद के बारे में क्या कहा जा रहा है?,Bondi Beach attack: What is being said in Australian media about Indian citizen Sajid Akram and his son Navid?,0.0,"[('Bondi Beach', 'GPE'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Sajid Akram', 'PERSON'), ('Navid', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,दिल्ली में वायु प्रदूषण गंभीर, दिल्ली सरकार ने सभी दफ़्तरों में 50% वर्क फ़्रॉम होम अनिवार्य किया","Live, Air pollution in Delhi is serious, Delhi government made 50% work from home mandatory in all offices.",-0.09848484848484848,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('50%', 'PERCENT')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,फैट लॉस ड्रग्स: क्या हैं ये दवाएं और कैसे काम करती हैं?,Fat Loss Drugs: What are these drugs and how do they work?,0.0,"[('Fat Loss Drugs', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बीजेपी में राष्ट्रीय अध्यक्ष की जगह कार्यकारी अध्यक्ष क्यों नियुक्त किया गया?,Why was the working president appointed instead of the national president in BJP?,0.0,"[('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"आक़िब, प्रशांत और कार्तिक को आईपीएल नीलामी में ऐसा क्या मिला कि सभी हैरान","What did Aaqib, Prashant and Karthik get in the IPL auction that surprised everyone?",0.1,[]
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश: हसनत अब्दुल्लाह ने 'सेवन सिस्टर्स' को भारत से अलग-थलग करने की दी चेतावनी,Bangladesh: Hasnat Abdullah warns of isolating 'Seven Sisters' from India,0.0,"[('Hasnat Abdullah', 'PERSON'), ('Seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sisters', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"राणा बलाचौरिया कौन थे, मूसेवाला हत्याकांड से जुड़े होने के दावों पर पुलिस ने क्या कहा?","Who was Rana Balachauria, what did the police say on his claims of being linked to the Moosewala murder case?",0.0,"[('Rana Balachauria', 'PERSON'), ('Moosewala', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तानी पायलट सरेंडर से बचने के लिए कैसे ढाका से भागे थे?,How did Pakistani pilots flee Dhaka to avoid surrender?,0.0,"[('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('Dhaka', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,São Paulo anuncia que vai romper contrato com Enel: o que se sabe e o que falta esclarecer?,São Paulo announces that it will break its contract with Enel: what is known and what remains to be clarified?,0.0,[]
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump ordena bloqueio 'total' de todos os petroleiros sancionados que entrem e saiam da Venezuela,Trump orders 'total' blockade of all sanctioned oil tankers entering and leaving Venezuela,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Parlamento Europeu aprova salvaguardas e abre caminho para acordo com Mercosul,European Parliament approves safeguards and paves the way for agreement with Mercosur,0.0,"[('European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Mercosur', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Donald Trump está processando a BBC?,Why is Donald Trump suing the BBC?,0.0,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Diretor americano de filme sobre Bolsonaro fala pela primeira vez sobre seu papel no projeto,American director of film about Bolsonaro speaks for the first time about his role in the project,0.125,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Polêmica Zezé di Camargo x SBT: as relações pragmáticas que Silvio Santos mantinha com a política,Zezé di Camargo x SBT controversy: the pragmatic relationships that Silvio Santos maintained with politics,0.0,"[('Zezé di Camargo', 'ORG'), ('Silvio Santos', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Não culpamos nosso pai pela morte de nossa mãe; ele estava doente','We don't blame our father for our mother's death; he was sick',-0.7142857142857143,[]
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Atirador de ataque terrorista na Austrália acorda do coma; polícia investiga viagem às Filipinas para suposto 'treinamento militar',Australia terrorist attack shooter wakes up from coma; police investigate trip to the Philippines for alleged 'military training',-0.10000000000000002,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('coma', 'GPE'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Eles estavam prestes a se tornar americanos – até Trump cancelar suas cerimônias de cidadania,They were about to become Americans – until Trump canceled their citizenship ceremonies,0.0,"[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Бензиновая война в Мали. Потеряет ли Кремль еще одного союзника?,Gasoline war in Mali. Will the Kremlin lose another ally?,0.0,"[('Mali', 'GPE'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Дело археолога. Что значит задержание Александра Бутягина в Польше по запросу Украины,The case of an archaeologist. What does the detention of Alexander Butyagin in Poland at the request of Ukraine mean?,-0.3125,"[('Alexander Butyagin', 'PERSON'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Глава аппарата Белого дома заявила, что ее резкие отзывы о Трампе, Вэнсе и Маске в Vanity Fair вырваны из контекста","White House Chief of Staff Says Her Harsh Reviews of Trump, Vance and Musk in Vanity Fair Are Taken Out of Context",0.16666666666666666,"[('White House', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Vance', 'PERSON'), ('Vanity Fair Are Taken Out', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп объявил морскую нефтяную блокаду Венесуэлы. Она будет касаться танкеров под санкциями,Trump declared a naval oil blockade of Venezuela. It will concern tankers under sanctions,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Верховный суд России вынес решение в пользу Полины Лурье по резонансному делу о квартире певицы Ларисы Долиной,The Supreme Court of Russia ruled in favor of Polina Lurie in the high-profile case regarding the apartment of singer Larisa Dolina,0.0,"[('The Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Polina Lurie', 'ORG'), ('Larisa Dolina', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Переговоры о мире в Украине: главные вопросы, на которые нет ответа",Peace negotiations in Ukraine: the main unanswered questions,0.033333333333333326,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский сообщил, что США проинформируют Россию о переговорах по мирному плану","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky said that the US will inform Russia about negotiations on a peace plan",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Он был очень вреден для страны». Трамп не стал извиняться и продолжил критиковать убитого режиссера-демократа Райнера,“He was very harmful to the country.” Trump did not apologize and continued to criticize the murdered Democratic director Reiner,0.2,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Reiner', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В итальянских горах обнаружены тысячи следов динозавров, которым более 200 млн лет",Thousands of dinosaur tracks dating back more than 200 million years have been discovered in the Italian mountains.,0.16666666666666666,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 200 million years', 'MONEY'), ('Italian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Власти Британии намерены расследовать иностранное вмешательство в политику страны,British authorities intend to investigate foreign interference in the country's politics,-0.0625,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヴェネズエラ出入港の制裁対象タンカーを「全面封鎖」、トランプ氏が命じる,Trump orders 'total blockade' of sanctioned tankers entering and exiting Venezuelan ports,0.0,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,豪ビーチ銃撃事件で殺害された夫婦、直前に容疑者と格闘　ドライブレコーダーに映像,Couple killed in Australian beach shooting incident struggles with suspect moments before - footage captured on dashcam,-0.1,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロブ・ライナー監督の息子、両親に対する殺人罪で訴追　検察が発表,"Director Rob Reiner's son charged with murder of parents, prosecutors announce",0.0,"[(""Rob Reiner's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,BBC、トランプ氏と「争う」方針　番組での演説編集めぐる名誉毀損訴訟で,BBC plans to ``fight'' with Trump in defamation lawsuit over edited speech on program,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU、ガソリン車とディーゼル車の新車販売禁止を見直し　2035年以降も1割可に,EU reviews ban on sales of new gasoline and diesel cars; 10% will be allowed after 2035,0.13636363636363635,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('10%', 'PERCENT'), ('2035', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告、出所後も繰り返し渡英　虐待被害を訴える英国人と一緒だったことも＝BBC調査,"Ex-defendant Epstein repeatedly traveled to the UK after being released from prison, sometimes with a British man who had complained of abuse - BBC investigation",-0.15,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ブラウン大学銃撃、容疑者の捜索続く　当局が新たな映像を公開,"Search continues for suspect in Brown University shooting, authorities release new footage",0.13636363636363635,"[('Brown University', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、ウクライナに「強力な」安全の保証を提供する意向示す　領土問題は解決せず,"US indicates intention to provide 'strong' security guarantees to Ukraine, territorial issue remains unresolved",0.4333333333333333,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「我々は平和と戦争のはざまにいる」　英MI6新長官が初の公開演説, 所要時間 0,51","Video, ""We are between peace and war"", the new British MI6 chief gives his first public speech, duration 0,51",0.09659090909090909,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump aamuru kuzuiwa meli za mafuta zilizowekewa vikwazo kuingia na kutoka Venezuela","Directly, Trump orders the blocking of restricted oil tankers entering and leaving Venezuela",0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,BBC itapinga kesi ya kashfa ya Donald Trump: Tutegemee nini?,The BBC will challenge Donald Trump's defamation case: What should we expect?,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), (""Donald Trump's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanamgambo wa RSF wanaficha mauaji ya halaiki huko el-Fasher-Watafiti,RSF militants cover up the genocide in el-Fasher-Watafiti,0.0,"[('el-Fasher-Watafiti', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Watoto wenye saratani waibiwa mamilioni ya pesa za matibabu yao, BBC yafichua","Children with cancer are being robbed of millions for their treatment, the BBC has revealed",0.0,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatano: Vilabu vitano vya EPL vinamfukuzia Semenyo,European Football Rumors Wednesday: Five EPL clubs are chasing Semenyo,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('EPL', 'ORG'), ('Semenyo', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mzozo wa DRC: M23 wadai kujiondoa Uvira baada ya kuudhibiti wiki jana,DRC conflict: M23 demands to withdraw from Uvira after controlling it last week,0.0,"[('M23', 'GPE'), ('Uvira', 'GPE'), ('last week', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Waziri Mkuu wa Australia: Shambulio la Sydney linachochewa na ""itikadi ya IS""","Australian PM: Sydney attack inspired by ""IS ideology""",0.0,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ardhi yao yenye utajiri wa almasi ilichukuliwa: Sasa wanataka irudishwe,Their diamond-rich land was taken: Now they want it back,0.0,[]
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Mimi ni Muislamu lakini ninaadhimisha Shabbat','I am Muslim but I observe Shabbat',0.0,"[('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Shabbat', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_17,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi mkakati mpya wa usalama wa Trump unavyobadili sera ya kigeni ya Marekani,How Trump's new security strategy is changing US foreign policy,0.005681818181818177,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
