Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué el origen de la madre de Kim Jong-un podría poner en peligro la legitimidad del régimen de Corea del Norte,Why the origin of Kim Jong-un's mother could endanger the legitimacy of the North Korean regime,0.0,neutral,"[(""Kim Jong-un's"", 'PERSON'), ('North Korean', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Estás completamente loco"": la tensa llamada telefónica entre Trump y Netanyahu que complica las conversaciones con Irán","""You are completely crazy"": the tense phone call between Trump and Netanyahu that complicates talks with Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Toda mi vida estudié cómo los virus evolucionan y sobreviven, y ahora aplico eso ante el agresivo cáncer cerebral que tengo""","""All my life I studied how viruses evolve and survive, and now I apply that to the aggressive brain cancer I have""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"María Montserrat Alvarado, la mexicana que el Papa nombró como jefa de comunicación y se convertirá en la primera mujer laica en dirigir un ""ministerio"" del Vaticano","María Montserrat Alvarado, the Mexican whom the Pope appointed as head of communications and will become the first lay woman to head a Vatican ""ministry""",0.0,neutral,"[('María Montserrat Alvarado', 'ORG'), ('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Vatican', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La indignación por el caso del joven que murió esposado por la policía mientras se desangraba tras ser apuñalado en Reino Unido,The outrage over the case of the young man who died handcuffed by the police while bleeding to death after being stabbed in the United Kingdom,-1.0,negative,"[('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué Venezuela llegó a tener uranio altamente enriquecido y cómo fue la reciente operación secreta para entregárselo a EE.UU.,Why Venezuela came to have highly enriched uranium and what was the recent secret operation to deliver it to the United States like?,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cuándo comienza el Mundial 2026 y otras preguntas sobre la primera Copa del Mundo con 48 selecciones,When does the 2026 World Cup begin and other questions about the first World Cup with 48 teams,0.0,neutral,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('48', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los miles de marineros estresados ​​y exhaustos tras más de 3 meses atrapados por el bloqueo del estrecho de Ormuz,The thousands of sailors stressed and exhausted after more than 3 months trapped by the blockade of the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 3 months', 'DATE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La película que el famoso director Wim Wenders retirará por una escena en la que aparece en topless la actriz Nastassja Kinski con 13 años,The film that the famous director Wim Wenders will withdraw due to a scene in which the 13-year-old actress Nastassja Kinski appears topless,0.0,neutral,"[('Wim Wenders', 'PERSON'), ('13-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Nastassja Kinski', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué revela sobre nuestra salud el dolor de cabeza que nos da cuando comemos helado,What the headache we get when we eat ice cream reveals about our health,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ममता बनर्जी के क़रीबी सहयोगी फिरहाद हकीम कौन हैं, जिन्होंने कोलकाता का मेयर पद छोड़ा","Who is Mamta Banerjee's close aide Firhad Hakim, who left the post of Mayor of Kolkata?",0.0,neutral,"[(""Mamta Banerjee's"", 'PERSON'), ('Firhad Hakim', 'PERSON'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,उत्तर प्रदेश: एक इंटर कॉलेज में बच्ची का एडमिशन कराने के लिए टॉयलेट सीट लेकर क्यों पहुंचे अभिभावक?,Uttar Pradesh: Why did parents arrive with a toilet seat to get their child admitted in an inter college?,0.0,neutral,"[('Uttar Pradesh', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी के प्रवक्ता बोले, 'हम किसी भी हिंसा का समर्थन नहीं करते'","Live, Cockroach Janata Party spokesperson said, 'We do not support any violence'",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,एग्ज़िट बंद थे और खिड़कियां सील... आग से 21 ज़िंदगियां लेने वाले इस होटल में थीं कई खामियां,Exits were closed and windows sealed... There were many flaws in this hotel which took 21 lives in the fire.,1.0,positive,"[('21', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'बांग्लादेश में हत्या' से जुड़े ममता बनर्जी के बयान पर पड़ोसी देश के राजनीतिक दलों ने क्या कहा?,What did the political parties of the neighboring country say on Mamata Banerjee's statement related to 'murder in Bangladesh'?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Mamata Banerjee's"", 'ORG'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,मवेशी चराने निकले युवक के 'प्यार' में एलओसी पार कर जम्मू-कश्मीर पहुँचने का क्या है मामला,What is the matter of a young man out for grazing cattle crossing LOC and reaching Jammu and Kashmir in 'love'?,0.0,neutral,"[('LOC', 'ORG'), ('Jammu', 'GPE'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ट्रंप की नेतन्याहू के साथ 'तल्ख़ बातचीत' ने ईरान वार्ता को और उलझाया,Trump's 'tough talk' with Netanyahu further complicates Iran talks,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सूर्यकुमार यादव की टी20 कप्तानी पर क्यों लगाई जा रहीं अटकलें,Why is there speculation on Suryakumar Yadav's T20 captaincy?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Suryakumar Yadav's"", 'PERSON'), ('T20', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ममता को अब भी अपना नेता बताने वाले ऋतब्रत कैसे बने उनके सियासी करियर का 'सबसे बड़ा संकट',"How did Ritabrata, who still calls Mamata his leader, become the 'biggest crisis' of his political career?",-1.0,negative,"[('Ritabrata', 'PERSON'), ('Mamata', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी के तीन प्रवक्ता कौन हैं, जानिए उनके बारे में?","Who are the three spokespersons of Cockroach Janata Party, know about them?",0.0,neutral,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Por que Padre Zezinho está (de novo) na mira de católicos tradicionalistas: 'Sou agredido todos os dias, falam que sou um câncer para a Igreja'","Why Father Zezinho is (again) in the crosshairs of traditionalist Catholics: 'I am attacked every day, they say I am a cancer for the Church'",-1.0,negative,"[('Zezinho', 'PERSON'), ('Catholics', 'NORP'), ('Church', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que prevê o acordo de cessar-fogo entre Israel e Líbano — e o que esperar a partir de agora,What the ceasefire agreement between Israel and Lebanon predicts — and what to expect from now on,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Câmara dos EUA aprova resolução que limita poderes de Trump: os avanços na tentativa de encerrar as guerras no Irã e no Líbano,US House approves resolution limiting Trump's powers: progress in trying to end wars in Iran and Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('US House', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'O Pix não sofre nenhuma ameaça', diz ex-diretor da OMC sobre relatório dos EUA","'Pix is ​​not under any threat', says former WTO director about US report",0.0,neutral,"[('WTO', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Simone Tebet diz que ministros do STF podem sofrer impeachment se houver 'denúncias sérias e comprovação': 'Ninguém está acima da lei',Simone Tebet says that STF ministers could be impeached if there are 'serious allegations and proof': 'No one is above the law',0.0,neutral,"[('Simone Tebet', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Presos pelo bloqueio do estreito de Ormuz há quase 100 dias: 'Só existe uma saída',Trapped by the blockade of the Strait of Hormuz for almost 100 days: 'There is only one way out',0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('almost 100 days', 'DATE'), ('only one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,EUA ameaçam taxar Brasil por trabalho forçado na pecuária e governo Lula diz que pode adotar reciprocidade,USA threatens to tax Brazil for forced labor in livestock farming and Lula government says it can adopt reciprocity,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O adolescente com superdotação que passou no vestibular aos 12 anos e sonha estudar no MIT,The gifted teenager who passed the entrance exam at age 12 and dreams of studying at MIT,0.0,neutral,"[('age 12', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Ameaças ao Pix e de novo tarifaço expõem Flávio e podem dar vitória a Lula em eleição apertada, dizem analistas","Threats to Pix and new tariffs expose Flávio and could give Lula victory in a tight election, analysts say",1.0,positive,"[('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Эрнст и Неизвестный: как подделывали скульптуры  знаменитого нонконформиста, чьим творчеством увлечен популярный конформист","Ernst and Neizvestny: how the sculptures of the famous nonconformist, whose work the popular conformist is passionate about, were forged",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Германия впервые не смогла получить место в Совете Безопасности ООН и винит в этом Россию,Germany failed to get a seat on the UN Security Council for the first time and blames Russia for this,-1.0,negative,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('the UN Security Council', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Пожар на «Бойком» подтверждают спутниковые снимки. Насколько опасным может быть удар по корвету в доке?,The fire at Boykoy is confirmed by satellite images. How dangerous could it be to hit a corvette while docked?,0.0,neutral,"[('Boykoy', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Палата представителей США пытается запретить Трампу продолжать войну в Иране без разрешения Конгресса,The US House of Representatives is trying to block Trump from continuing the war in Iran without Congressional authorization.,-1.0,negative,"[('The US House of Representatives', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Congressional', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Израиль и Ливан договорились о прекращении огня. Главным условием остается отказ «Хезболлы» от обстрелов,Israel and Lebanon agreed to a ceasefire. The main condition remains Hezbollah’s refusal to fire,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"За операцией по задержанию инкассаторов украинского «Ощадбанка» мог стоять Виктор Орбан, следует из расследования венгерских журналистов","Viktor Orban could have been behind the operation to detain collectors of the Ukrainian Oschadbank, follows from an investigation by Hungarian journalists",0.0,neutral,"[('Viktor Orban', 'PERSON'), ('the Ukrainian Oschadbank', 'ORG'), ('Hungarian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Великобритания, Франция и Германия разрабатывают план по вовлечению России в переговоры с Украиной, пишет Bloomberg","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Britain, France and Germany are developing a plan to involve Russia in negotiations with Ukraine, writes Bloomberg",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Bloomberg', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Один погибший и десятки раненых в результате ударов иранских дронов по аэропорту Кувейта,One dead and dozens injured in Iranian drone strikes at Kuwait airport,0.0,neutral,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В самопровозглашенной ДНР заявили о восьми погибших при ударе по рейсовому автобусу. Что известно,The self-proclaimed DPR announced that eight people were killed when a regular bus was hit. What is known,-1.0,negative,"[('eight', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"ВОЗ: вспышка Эболы приобрела серьезную форму — сотни зараженных, десятки умерших","WHO: Ebola outbreak has become serious - hundreds of infected, dozens of deaths",-1.0,negative,"[('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナがロシア・サンクトペテルブルクを攻撃、経済フォーラム開幕のなか,"Ukraine attacks St. Petersburg, Russia as economic forum opens",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエルとレバノン、停戦の履行で合意　ヒズボラによる攻撃停止が条件,"Israel and Lebanon agree to ceasefire, conditional on Hezbollah stopping attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、日本など60カ国・地域に最大12.5％の追加関税を検討　強制労働への懸念を理由に,Considering additional tariffs of up to 12.5% ​​on 60 countries and regions including the United States and Japan due to concerns about forced labor,0.0,neutral,"[('up to 12.5%', 'PERCENT'), ('60', 'CARDINAL'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,中国のスパイ、求人サイトから政府や軍関係者に接触　英MI5など5カ国の情報機関が警告,"Chinese spy contacts government and military personnel through recruitment site; intelligence agencies in five countries, including British MI5, warn",-1.0,negative,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,映画監督ヴェンダース氏、1975年の作品を公開中止に　当時10代俳優の裸のシーンめぐり,Film director Wenders cancels release of 1975 film over nude scene of then-teenage actor,0.0,neutral,"[('Wenders', 'PERSON'), ('1975', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏の対イラン戦争の権限制限、米下院が決議案を可決,US House of Representatives passes resolution to limit Trump's war powers against Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('US House of Representatives', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イランがクウェートの空港をドローン攻撃か、1人死亡　米イランの交渉は停滞,One person killed in Iran drone attack on Kuwait airport; US-Iran negotiations stalled,-1.0,negative,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ドイツ、国連安保理・非常任理事国選で落選　「苦い敗北」の原因はロシアと,Germany loses election as a non-permanent member of the UN Security Council; the cause of the “bitter defeat” is Russia.,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('the UN Security Council', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ政権、「反武器化基金」を断念　与党の一部も強く抵抗,Trump administration abandons “anti-weaponization fund”; some members of the ruling party also strongly resist,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_04,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 プーチン氏、ウクライナでの戦争で妥協を拒み続ける　ロシアの世論はどうなのか,[Commentary] Mr. Putin continues to refuse to compromise on the war in Ukraine.What is the opinion of Russian public opinion?,-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Israel na Lebanon zakubaliana kusitisha mapigano","Immediately, Israel and Lebanon agreed to cease fighting",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"""Una wazimu"" Simu ya mzozo kati ya Trump na Netanyahu yavuruga mazungumzo na Iran","""You're crazy"" Trump-Netanyahu conflict phone call derails talks with Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump-Netanyahu', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kutoka kivuli hadi alama ya nguvu duniani, Putin alijengaje taswira yake?","From a shadow to a symbol of power in the world, how did Putin build his image?",0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moto wafufua mjadala wa CCTV mashuleni, usalama kwanza au faragha?","Fire revives the discussion of CCTV in schools, security first or privacy?",0.0,neutral,"[('CCTV', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwanini Kim Jong-un huwa hamzungumzii mama yake?,Why doesn't Kim Jong-un talk to his mother?,0.0,neutral,"[('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tunachojua kuhusu mashambulizi mapya kati ya Marekani na Iran,What we know about the new attacks between the United States and Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,CCM kuna Yuda au ni homa ya urais 2030?,CCM is there Judah or is it 2030 presidential fever?,0.0,neutral,"[('CCM', 'ORG'), ('Judah', 'PERSON'), ('2030', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vita vya 'kisiri' vinavyohatarisha usalama wa ndege duniani,The 'secret' war that threatens the safety of the world's aviation,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tanzania inatafuta nini Urusi?,What is Tanzania looking for in Russia?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini ngome hii yenye miaka 900 ni muhimu katika vita vya Israel-Hezbollah?,Why is this 900-year-old fortress important in the Israel-Hezbollah war?,-1.0,negative,"[('900-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Argentina erupts in protest against gender violence after teen murder,Argentina erupts in protest against gender violence after teen murder,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ireland’s Black community opens up about racism after ‘George Floyd moment’,Ireland’s Black community opens up about racism after ‘George Floyd moment’,0.0,neutral,"[('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('George Floyd', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US House votes to end Trump’s Iran war: Does it matter?,US House votes to end Trump’s Iran war: Does it matter?,-1.0,negative,"[('US House', 'ORG'), ('Trump’s Iran', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Did Germany lose its UNSC seat because of support for Israel?,Did Germany lose its UNSC seat because of support for Israel?,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('UNSC', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Nepali Mount Everest guide found alive after being missing for six days,Nepali Mount Everest guide found alive after being missing for six days,0.0,neutral,"[('Nepali Mount Everest', 'LOC'), ('six days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Who is Khalilur Rahman, Bangladesh FM who beat Cyprus to UNGA presidency?","Who is Khalilur Rahman, Bangladesh FM who beat Cyprus to UNGA presidency?",0.0,neutral,"[('Khalilur Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Cyprus', 'PRODUCT'), ('UNGA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup 2026: All the key dates from opening game to final,World Cup 2026: All the key dates from opening game to final,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,China bans four New Zealand lawmakers over visit to Taiwan,China bans four New Zealand lawmakers over visit to Taiwan,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,NBA finals: Jalen Brunson sparks Knicks’ rally past Spurs in opener,NBA finals: Jalen Brunson sparks Knicks’ rally past Spurs in opener,0.0,neutral,"[('NBA', 'ORG'), ('Jalen Brunson', 'PERSON'), ('Knicks', 'ORG'), ('Spurs', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Sabalenka ‘mentally off track’ as French Open exit made her want to ‘quit’,Sabalenka ‘mentally off track’ as French Open exit made her want to ‘quit’,0.0,neutral,"[('French Open', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Iran's Khamenei says dealt enemies 'decisive blow' in West Asia war | LIVE,Iran's Khamenei says dealt enemies 'decisive blow' in West Asia war | LIVE,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('West Asia', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"After Maoism, the next battle is for Adivasi trust","After Maoism, the next battle is for Adivasi trust",0.0,neutral,"[('Adivasi', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Kerala’s UDF govt requests CBI probe into controversial death of Kannur ADM Naveen Babu,Kerala’s UDF govt requests CBI probe into controversial death of Kannur ADM Naveen Babu,-1.0,negative,"[('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('UDF', 'ORG'), ('CBI', 'ORG'), ('Kannur ADM Naveen', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Kohli set to be ruled out of Afghanistan ODI series,Kohli set to be ruled out of Afghanistan ODI series,0.0,neutral,"[('Kohli', 'PERSON'), ('Afghanistan ODI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Census fieldwork contradicts government data, enumerators asked to revisit, review data","Census fieldwork contradicts government data, enumerators asked to revisit, review data",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Tamil Nadu receives surplus Cauvery water for yet another year,Tamil Nadu receives surplus Cauvery water for yet another year,0.0,neutral,"[('Tamil Nadu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Search ends in tragedy: 8 of family killed in Delhi hotel fire,Search ends in tragedy: 8 of family killed in Delhi hotel fire,-1.0,negative,"[('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Brazil takes a historic HDI leap with focused planning and public spending,Brazil takes a historic HDI leap with focused planning and public spending,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Satire | Application for ‘Chogada Taara’ garba dance in Strait of Hormuz,Satire | Application for ‘Chogada Taara’ garba dance in Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_04,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Base and framework: On the latest Index of Industrial Production,​Base and framework: On the latest Index of Industrial Production,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Israel and Lebanon agree to implement ceasefire if Hezbollah stops attacks,Israel and Lebanon agree to implement ceasefire if Hezbollah stops attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US House delivers rebuke to Trump as it votes to halt Iran war,US House delivers rebuke to Trump as it votes to halt Iran war,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('House', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'Crazy' phone call between Trump and Netanyahu complicates Iran talks,'Crazy' phone call between Trump and Netanyahu complicates Iran talks,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Grab what you can while you can: The new reality in the South China Sea,Grab what you can while you can: The new reality in the South China Sea,0.0,neutral,"[('the South China Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Missing Sherpa guide found on Mount Everest after 'miracle' self-rescue,Missing Sherpa guide found on Mount Everest after 'miracle' self-rescue,0.0,neutral,"[('Mount Everest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ukraine accused of killing four in occupied Crimea,Ukraine accused of killing four in occupied Crimea,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Crimea', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Heavy gunfire in Somali capital as row over election delay escalates,Heavy gunfire in Somali capital as row over election delay escalates,0.0,neutral,"[('Somali', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump to nominate Blanche for attorney general on permanent basis,Trump to nominate Blanche for attorney general on permanent basis,0.0,neutral,"[('Blanche', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Indian film union drops boycott call against Bollywood star Ranveer Singh,Indian film union drops boycott call against Bollywood star Ranveer Singh,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Bollywood', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Germany blames Russia for 'bitter defeat' in UN Security Council bid,Germany blames Russia for 'bitter defeat' in UN Security Council bid,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('UN Security Council', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: Israel and Lebanon Renew Cease-Fire,Iran War Live Updates: Israel and Lebanon Renew Cease-Fire,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates', 'EVENT'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Hezbollah’s Fiber-Optic Drones Expose Cracks in Israeli Defenses,Hezbollah’s Fiber-Optic Drones Expose Cracks in Israeli Defenses,0.0,neutral,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Fiber-Optic Drones Expose Cracks', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Defenses', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Ireland, Seen as a Weak Link in Europe’s Defense, Is Trying to Bulk Up","Ireland, Seen as a Weak Link in Europe’s Defense, Is Trying to Bulk Up",0.0,neutral,"[('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Seen', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Marjane Satrapi, Author of ‘Persepolis,’ Dies at 56","Marjane Satrapi, Author of ‘Persepolis,’ Dies at 56",0.0,neutral,"[('56', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Amid War, Iran’s Soccer Leader Works to Get His Team to the World Cup","Amid War, Iran’s Soccer Leader Works to Get His Team to the World Cup",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Works', 'PERSON'), ('Get His Team', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Can Abelardo De La Espriella, a U.S. Citizen, Become Colombia’s President?","Can Abelardo De La Espriella, a U.S. Citizen, Become Colombia’s President?",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Priest’s Ebola Death Stirs Fear an Doubt in Congolese Town,Priest’s Ebola Death Stirs Fear an Doubt in Congolese Town,-1.0,negative,"[('Priest’s Ebola Death Stirs Fear', 'ORG'), ('Congolese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Four New Zealand Lawmakers Banned From China After Taiwan Trip,Four New Zealand Lawmakers Banned From China After Taiwan Trip,0.0,neutral,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Colombia’s Yellow World Cup Jersey, Once a Symbol of Unity, Becomes a Political Statement","Colombia’s Yellow World Cup Jersey, Once a Symbol of Unity, Becomes a Political Statement",0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Yellow World Cup Jersey', 'EVENT'), ('Once a Symbol of Unity', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_04,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,South Korea’s Governing Democratic Party Sweeps Local Elections but Faces Setback in Seoul Mayor’s Race,South Korea’s Governing Democratic Party Sweeps Local Elections but Faces Setback in Seoul Mayor’s Race,0.0,neutral,"[('South Korea’s', 'GPE'), ('Governing Democratic Party Sweeps Local Elections', 'ORG'), ('Faces Setback', 'PERSON')]"
