Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El desafío de Irán a EE.UU. al aumentar el área del estrecho de Ormuz sobre la que reclama control militar,Iran's challenge to the US by increasing the area of ​​the Strait of Hormuz over which it claims military control,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('​​the Strait of', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El trágico caso de Yulixa Toloza, la mujer que apareció muerta en una cuneta después de someterse a un procedimiento estético en Colombia","The tragic case of Yulixa Toloza, the woman who was found dead in a ditch after undergoing a cosmetic procedure in Colombia",0.0,neutral,"[('Yulixa Toloza', 'ORG'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Marco Rubio afirma que Cuba es una amenaza para EE.UU. y ve poco probable un acuerdo diplomático,Marco Rubio affirms that Cuba is a threat to the US and sees a diplomatic agreement unlikely,0.0,neutral,"[('Marco Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El esperanzador ensayo pionero sobre la preeclampsia, la complicación del embarazo que mata a medio millón de bebés al año","The hopeful pioneering trial on preeclampsia, the pregnancy complication that kills half a million babies a year",0.0,neutral,"[('preeclampsia', 'GPE'), ('half a million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La historia de amor de las dos jóvenes que iban a ser monjas y acabaron casándose: ""Dios fue nuestro Cupido""","The love story of the two young women who were going to be nuns and ended up getting married: ""God was our Cupid""",0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cupid', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Por qué México importa más del 50% de la gasolina que consume, pese a ser uno de los mayores productores de petróleo de América Latina","Why Mexico imports more than 50% of the gasoline it consumes, despite being one of the largest oil producers in Latin America",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('more than 50%', 'PERCENT'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""EE.UU. se beneficia de la estabilidad en América Latina, que se produce mediante el desarrollo y las clases medias. Debería promover eso en lugar de intervenciones""","""The US benefits from stability in Latin America, which comes through development and the middle classes. It should promote that instead of interventions""",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,¿Qué significa que Rusia haya desplegado sus fuerzas nucleares estratégicas en sus mayores ejercicios militares hasta la fecha?,What does it mean that Russia has deployed its strategic nuclear forces in its largest military exercises to date?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,3 formas en que podría evolucionar la crisis en Cuba tras la acusación penal de EE.UU. contra Raúl Castro,3 ways the crisis in Cuba could evolve after the US criminal indictment against Raúl Castro,-1.0,negative,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Air France y Airbus son declaradas culpables de homicidio involuntario por el accidente aéreo más letal de Francia ocurrido en 2009,Air France and Airbus found guilty of involuntary manslaughter for France's deadliest plane crash in 2009,0.0,neutral,"[('Air France', 'ORG'), ('Airbus', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('2009', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"जेल से भागकर मुंबई में एक्टर बन गया गुजरात का एक हत्यारा, 12 साल बाद ऐसे पकड़ा गया","A murderer from Gujarat escaped from jail and became an actor in Mumbai, caught like this after 12 years",0.0,neutral,"[('Gujarat', 'GPE'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('12 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,त्विषा शर्मा केसः दूसरा पोस्टमार्टम दिल्ली एम्स के डॉक्टरों से कराने का आदेश","Live, Tvisha Sharma case: Order to conduct second post-mortem from Delhi AIIMS doctors",0.0,neutral,"[('Tvisha Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी की चर्चा विदेशी मीडिया में भी, जानिए इसे वहाँ कैसे देखा जा रहा है?","Cockroach Janata Party is being discussed in foreign media also, know how it is being seen there?",0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ईरान: बच्चे की देखभाल करती महिला की इस तस्वीर पर क्यों छिड़ा विवाद,Iran: Why controversy erupted over this picture of a woman taking care of a child?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,हरदोई में शादी से इनकार करने पर युवक ने युवती के ब्रेस्ट को नुक़सान पहुंचाया,"In Hardoi, a young man damaged a girl's breast after refusing to marry her.",0.0,neutral,"[('Hardoi', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,त्विषा शर्मा केस: मध्य प्रदेश सरकार ने सीबीआई जांच की सिफ़ारिश की,Tvisha Sharma case: Madhya Pradesh government recommends CBI investigation,0.0,neutral,"[('Tvisha Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Madhya Pradesh', 'ORG'), ('CBI', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'कॉकरोच से छुटकारा नहीं मिलेगा': 'सीजेपी इज़ बैक' पर क्या कह रहे हैं लोग,'Can't get rid of cockroaches': What people are saying on 'CJP is back',0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी का जन्म तो मीम से हुआ लेकिन ये गंभीर बदलाव की शुरुआत हो सकती है ': योगेंद्र यादव,'Cockroach Janata Party was born from a meme but this can be the beginning of serious change': Yogendra Yadav,0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG'), ('Yogendra Yadav', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बस पांच मिनट की कसरत से लंबा जीना संभव, जानिए क्या है एक्सरसाइज़ स्नैकिंग","It is possible to live longer with just five minutes of exercise, know what exercise snacking is",0.0,neutral,"[('just five minutes', 'TIME')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पश्चिम बंगाल: मदरसों में वंदे मातरम को अनिवार्य करने वाले आदेश पर क्या बोला विपक्ष?,West Bengal: What did the opposition say on the order making Vande Mataram mandatory in madrassas?,0.0,neutral,"[('Vande Mataram', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Timing do escândalo com Vorcaro foi bom para Flávio Bolsonaro, dará tempo de se recuperar', diz Marcos Nobre","'Timing of the scandal with Vorcaro was good for Flávio Bolsonaro, it will give him time to recover', says Marcos Nobre",1.0,positive,"[('Vorcaro', 'ORG'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Marcos Nobre', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Acordo com a PGR e delação unilateral: os possíveis caminhos de Daniel Vorcaro após ter proposta recusada pela PF,Agreement with the PGR and unilateral denunciation: Daniel Vorcaro's possible paths after having a proposal rejected by the PF,1.0,positive,"[('PGR', 'ORG'), (""Daniel Vorcaro's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Ameaça à segurança nacional', drones, Raúl Castro indiciado: os sinais de que Cuba está na mira dos Estados Unidos","'Threat to national security', drones, Raúl Castro indicted: signs that Cuba is in the crosshairs of the United States",-1.0,negative,"[('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Como EUA e Cuba se envolveram numa disputa histórica, Duration 12,18","Video,How the US and Cuba got involved in a historic dispute, Duration 12.18",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('12.18', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Como foi o último 'The Late Show', de Stephen Colbert, que pôs fim a décadas de programa, com Paul McCartney","How was the last 'The Late Show', by Stephen Colbert, which ended decades of the program, with Paul McCartney",0.0,neutral,"[(""'The Late Show'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Stephen Colbert', 'PERSON'), ('decades', 'DATE'), ('Paul McCartney', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Receita abre consulta ao 1º lote de restituição do Imposto de Renda; veja esta e outras datas importantes do IR,Revenue opens consultation on the 1st batch of Income Tax refunds; see this and other important IR dates,0.0,neutral,"[('the 1st', 'DATE'), ('Income Tax', 'ORG'), ('IR', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Aumento de câncer em jovens: o que estudo do Reino Unido descobriu e como resultados espelham a realidade brasileira,Increase in cancer in young people: what a UK study found and how results mirror the Brazilian reality,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que a Rússia faz o maior exercício militar com arsenal nuclear das últimas décadas,Why Russia is carrying out the largest military exercise with a nuclear arsenal in recent decades,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('recent decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As praias paradisíacas 'para turistas' onde o acesso de moradores é restrito,Paradisiacal beaches 'for tourists' where access for locals is restricted,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Perguntamos às IAs em quem votar — veja o que elas responderam, mesmo proibidas de se posicionar","We asked the AIs who to vote for — see what they responded, even though they were prohibited from taking a stand",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Исчерпала ли себя российская модель войны с Украиной?,Has the Russian model of war with Ukraine exhausted itself?,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"США направят в Польшу 5 тысяч военных, заявил Трамп","The US will send 5 thousand troops to Poland, Trump said",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('5 thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Механизм против неудобных». Как Минюст России лишает адвокатуру самоуправления и чем это грозит обычным людям,"""Mechanism against the inconvenient."" How the Russian Ministry of Justice is depriving the legal profession of self-government and how this threatens ordinary people",-1.0,negative,"[('the Russian Ministry of Justice', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Рубио заявил, что Куба представляет угрозу для США, Гавана обвинила его во лжи","Rubio said Cuba poses a threat to the US, Havana accused him of lying",-1.0,negative,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Havana', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: атака на Ярославскую область; в самопровозглашенной ЛНР заявили о погибших при ударе по колледжу","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: attack on the Yaroslavl region; in the self-proclaimed Luhansk People's Republic they announced that they were killed in an attack on a college",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Yaroslavl', 'NORP'), (""Luhansk People's Republic"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Литве объявили тревогу из-за летящего со стороны Беларуси дрона, Арина Соболенко высказалась против войны в Украине. Главное в Беларуси за неделю","In Lithuania, an alarm was declared due to a drone flying from Belarus; Arina Sabalenko spoke out against the war in Ukraine. The main things in Belarus in a week",-1.0,negative,"[('Lithuania', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('Arina Sabalenko', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Запуск ракеты Starship Илона Маска перенесен на пятницу из-за неполадок на старте,Elon Musk's Starship launch postponed to Friday due to problems at launch,0.0,neutral,"[(""Elon Musk's Starship"", 'PERSON'), ('Friday', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Если выход завалит — все!» Почему Подмосковье оказалось не готово к атакам беспилотников,"“If the exit is blocked, that’s it!” Why the Moscow region was not ready for drone attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Авиакомпании Air France и Airbus признаны виновными в непредумышленном убийстве в связи с авиакатастрофой 2009 года,Air France and Airbus found guilty of manslaughter in connection with 2009 plane crash,0.0,neutral,"[('Air France', 'ORG'), ('Airbus', 'ORG'), ('2009', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"История рокового авиаудара, ставшего поводом для обвинения Рауля Кастро",The story of the fatal airstrike that led to the indictment of Raul Castro,0.0,neutral,"[('Raul Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 アメリカのカストロ元議長起訴、キューバで何が起こり得るのか,[Commentary] What could happen in Cuba after the indictment of former US President Castro?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアと中国、キューバ元指導者を起訴した米国を非難　米長官はキューバは「安全保障上の脅威」,"Russia, China criticize US for indicting former Cuban leader; US Secretary of State calls Cuba a 'security threat'",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuban', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、台湾への武器売却を一時停止　イランとの戦争が理由と,US suspends arms sales to Taiwan due to war with Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エールフランスとエアバス、2009年の旅客機墜落事故で逆転有罪判決　過失致死罪で仏裁判所,Air France and Airbus reconvicted in French court for manslaughter in 2009 passenger plane crash,0.0,neutral,"[('Air France', 'ORG'), ('Airbus', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('2009', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「ノーの意味はノー」　グリーンランド住民、新しい米領事館前でトランプ氏に抗議,'No means no': Greenlanders protest against Trump in front of new US consulate,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トイレ・更衣室は生物学的性別に基づく利用を、ジェンダー中立空間の必要性も明記　英平等委が新指針,"British Equality Commission's new guidelines specify that toilets and changing rooms should be used based on biological sex, and that gender-neutral spaces are required.",0.0,neutral,"[(""British Equality Commission's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エボラ治療の病院で怒った群衆がテントに放火　コンゴ民主共和国,Angry crowd sets tent on fire at Ebola hospital in Democratic Republic of Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('Democratic Republic of Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエルの極右閣僚、拘束されたガザ支援船の活動家あざける　国内外で非難噴出,"Israeli far-right minister mocks detained Gaza aid boat activist, sparking criticism at home and abroad",0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏がIRSと和解、自らと家族などに対する税務調査を禁止する条項を追加,"Trump settles with IRS, adds clause barring tax audits of himself and family members",0.0,neutral,"[('IRS', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,牛乳や卵などの価格を引き下げるよう英政府が圧力、スーパー側は「上限」設定には反発,"British government pressures to lower prices of milk, eggs, etc., with supermarkets resisting the idea of ​​setting a 'cap'",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marekani yamuwekea vikwazo Mafwele kwa madai ya 'kuwatesa' wanaharakati wa haki za binadamu,The United States has imposed sanctions on Mafele for allegedly 'torturing' human rights activists,0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Mafele', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maseneta waishinikiza Marekani kutathmini upya uhusiano na Tanzania,Senators pressured the United States to reevaluate relations with Tanzania,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Cuba ni tishio kwa usalama wa Marekani - Marco Rubio","Directly, Cuba is a threat to the security of the United States - Marco Rubio",-1.0,negative,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Marekani imepata hasara kiasi gani katika vita vya Iran, kuanzia ndege za kivita hadi droni?","How much has the US lost in the Iran war, from warplanes to drones?",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('the Iran war', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi ya kuzuia picha zako za faragha zisivuje,How to prevent your private photos from being leaked,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wasanii wa Afrika Mashariki wanavyoishi katikati ya vita ya Marekani na Iran,East African artists live in the middle of the US-Iran war,-1.0,negative,"[('East African', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Polisi Tanzania inachunguza tukio la kutekwa kwa msaidizi wa Lissu,The Tanzanian police are investigating the incident of the abduction of Lissu's assistant,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('Lissu', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Raúl Castro akabiliwa na mashataka ya uhalifu lakini chanzo cha migogoro kati ya Cuba na Marekani ni nini?,Raúl Castro faces criminal charges but what is the source of the conflict between Cuba and the United States?,-1.0,negative,"[('Raúl Castro', 'PERSON'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,DR Congo yafunga kambi ya mazoezi ya Kombe la Dunia kufuatia mlipuko wa Ebola,DR Congo closes the World Cup training camp following the Ebola outbreak,1.0,positive,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Hii inaweza kuwa mara ya mwisho kusikia sauti yangu': Mauaji ya kisiasa yaongezeka Iran,'This may be the last time I hear my voice': Political killings on the rise in Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
