Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,BBC Mundo en territorio de las maras en Guatemala: cómo operan y qué las diferencia de las organizaciones criminales en otros países de la región,BBC Mundo in gang territory in Guatemala: how they operate and what differentiates them from criminal organizations in other countries in the region,-0.2625,"[('BBC Mundo', 'ORG'), ('Guatemala', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué se juegan Milei, la oposición y Trump en las elecciones legislativas de Argentina","What Milei, the opposition and Trump are at stake in Argentina's legislative elections",0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El anuncio con la voz de Ronald Reagan que enfureció a Trump y por el que terminó las negociaciones comerciales con Canadá,The announcement with Ronald Reagan's voice that angered Trump and ended trade negotiations with Canada,-0.75,"[(""Ronald Reagan's"", 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo Madrid desbancó en los últimos años a Cataluña como la región más rica de España,How Madrid overtook Catalonia as the richest region in Spain in recent years,0.0,"[('Madrid', 'GPE'), ('Catalonia', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('recent years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Mi hija adolescente fue víctima de un grupo satánico en línea y me sentí impotente para ayudarla""","""My teenage daughter was a victim of a satanic group online and I felt helpless to help her""",-0.037500000000000006,[]
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वो रहस्यमय शख़्स कौन है, जिसे बताया जा रहा है 14 अरब डॉलर के क्रिप्टो घोटाले का मास्टरमाइंड","Who is that mysterious person, who is said to be the mastermind of the $14 billion crypto scam?",0.0,"[('$14 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,ब्रिटेन के दौरे पर ज़ेलेंस्की- फ़्रांस और ब्रिटेन ने रूस को दी चेतावनी","Live, Zelensky on Britain's visit - France and Britain warned Russia",0.13636363636363635,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अफ़ग़ानिस्तान और पाकिस्तान के बीच संघर्ष में पाकिस्तानी तालिबान की क्या भूमिका है?,What is the role of Pakistani Taliban in the conflict between Afghanistan and Pakistan?,0.0,"[('Pakistani Taliban', 'ORG'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'नेता नहीं, बेटा बनने आया हूं': क्या खेसारी लाल यादव बीजेपी के 'गढ़' छपरा में दे पाएंगे चुनौती","'I have come to become a son, not a leader': Will Khesari Lal Yadav be able to challenge BJP's stronghold Chapra?",0.5,"[('Will Khesari Lal Yadav', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Chapra', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'सब कुछ फ़िल्मी था...'  तालिबान के राज में मुसलमान लड़के और यहूदी लड़की की प्रेम कहानी,'Everything was filmy...' Love story of Muslim boy and Jewish girl under Taliban rule,0.25,"[('Love', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"रूस पर सख़्त हुए ट्रंप, लेकिन क्या पुतिन को झुका पाएंगे","Trump becomes tough on Russia, but will he be able to bend Putin?",0.05555555555555555,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,महिला वर्ल्ड कप: एक-एक मैच बाक़ी फिर भी भारत सेमीफ़ाइनल में और न्यूज़ीलैंड बाहर क्यों,"Women's World Cup: One match left, yet why is India in the semi-finals and New Zealand out?",0.06818181818181818,"[(""Women's World Cup"", 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,कर्नाटक के आलंद में वोटर लिस्ट से नाम हटाने की एसआईटी जाँच रिपोर्ट में क्या बात सामने आई,"What was revealed in the SIT investigation report on removal of names from voter list in Aaland, Karnataka?",0.0,"[('SIT', 'ORG'), ('Aaland', 'GPE'), ('Karnataka', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दुनिया के ये चार देश, जो रहने के लिहाज से हैं सबसे बेहतर",These four countries of the world are the best to live in,0.5681818181818181,"[('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como viagem de Lula à Ásia para rebater efeito Trump pode acabar selando paz entre os dois,How Lula's trip to Asia to counter Trump's effect could end up sealing peace between the two,0.0,"[('Asia', 'LOC'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A luta de médicos em Gaza para investigar 'sinais de tortura' em corpos devolvidos por Israel,Gaza doctors struggle to investigate 'signs of torture' in bodies returned by Israel,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A corrida científica para encontrar planeta 'irmão' da Terra,The scientific race to find Earth's 'sister' planet,0.0,"[('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que missa em latim virou campo de batalha entre tradicionalistas e progressistas — e teste para Leão 14,Why the Latin Mass became a battleground between traditionalists and progressives — and a test for Leo 14,0.0,"[('Latin', 'NORP'), ('Leo 14', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,50 anos sem Vladimir Herzog: a pouco conhecida trajetória do jornalista na BBC News Brasil,50 years without Vladimir Herzog: the journalist's little-known trajectory at BBC News Brasil,0.0,"[('50 years', 'DATE'), ('Vladimir Herzog', 'PERSON'), ('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que a queda dos preços nem sempre é tão boa quanto parece,Why falling prices aren't always as good as they seem,0.7,[]
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Empresa alemã que fabrica escada elevatória usada no roubo ao Louvre faz propaganda: 'Movimento rápido e silencioso',German company that manufactures elevator ladder used in the Louvre robbery advertises: 'Quick and silent movement',0.1111111111111111,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Quando eu vi ele entrando, senti que ia ser atacada': o relato da brasileira vítima de agressão sexual em Paris","'When I saw him coming in, I felt like I was going to be attacked': the story of the Brazilian victim of sexual assault in Paris",0.2125,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As incríveis imagens de leões que abandonaram deserto para caçar na praia,The incredible images of lions that abandoned the desert to hunt on the beach,0.9,[]
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Спецпосланник Путина прилетел в США сразу после первых санкций Трампа в отношении России. Что известно о визите Кирилла Дмитриева?,Putin’s special envoy flew to the United States immediately after Trump’s first sanctions against Russia. What is known about the visit of Kirill Dmitriev?,0.3035714285714286,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Kirill Dmitriev', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Стармер на встрече «коалиции желающих» заявил, что Путин — единственный, кто не хочет прекращать эту войну","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: Starmer at a meeting of the “coalition of the willing” said that Putin is the only one who does not want to stop this war",0.125,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Суд в Лондоне вынес приговоры за поджог складов с помощью для Украины по заказу ЧВК «Вагнер»,A court in London handed down sentences for setting fire to warehouses with aid for Ukraine ordered by the Wagner PMC.,-0.15555555555555556,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Визит Зеленского в Лондон: приём у короля Карла III, встреча со Стармером и «коалицией желающих»","Zelensky's visit to London: reception with King Charles III, meeting with Starmer and the “coalition of the willing”",0.25,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Charles III', 'PERSON'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Борьба с наркоторговлей или свержение Мадуро — чего Трамп добивается в Венесуэле?,The fight against drug trafficking or the overthrow of Maduro - what is Trump trying to achieve in Venezuela?,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Мой доктор прописал мне белый». Как российских музыкантов учат искать пропаганду наркотиков в своих треках,“My doctor prescribed me white.” How Russian musicians are taught to look for drug propaganda in their tracks,-0.03333333333333333,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Дроны, авианалеты, парапланы. Как хунта Мьянмы с помощью Китая отвоевывает города у повстанцев","Drones, air raids, paragliders. How Myanmar's junta, with Chinese help, is retaking cities from rebels",0.0,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Грузии предъявили обвинение экс-премьеру Ираклию Гарибашвили,Former Prime Minister Irakli Garibashvili was charged in Georgia,0.0,"[('Irakli Garibashvili', 'PERSON'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Россия против НАТО: возможна ли война на Балтике? | Военное время, Продолжительность 15,02","Video, Russia versus NATO: is war possible in the Baltic? | Wartime, Duration 15.02",0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Baltic', 'LOC'), ('15.02', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ЕС отложил передачу замороженных российских активов Киеву,EU postpones transfer of frozen Russian assets to Kyiv,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU、ウクライナへのロシア凍結資産使った24兆円融資案見送り　支援継続は約束,"EU postpones proposed 24 trillion yen loan to Ukraine using frozen Russian assets, promises continued support",0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('24 trillion yen', 'MONEY'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、カナダとの貿易交渉「打ち切る」と発表　関税に関する広告めぐり,Trump announces ``terminus'' of trade negotiations with Canada over tariff ads,0.0,"[('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,NBAスター選手と監督やマフィアら数十人を逮捕　違法賭博の取り締まりで,"Dozens of NBA stars, managers and mafia members arrested in crackdown on illegal gambling",-0.5,"[('Dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,チャールズ英国王とローマ教皇が並んで祈る　16世紀からの溝を修復, 所要時間 0,38","Video, King Charles and the Pope pray side by side, repairing a 16th-century ditch, Duration 0,38",0.0,"[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('16th-century', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,上司に「できません」と言いにくい時、どう言えばいい,"What to say when it's difficult to say ""I can't"" to your boss",-0.5,[]
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヨルダン川西岸併合に向けた法案、イスラエル議会で1回目の可決　米副大統領ら批判,"Bill for West Bank annexation passed first time in Israeli parliament, criticized by US vice president and others",0.25,"[('Bill', 'PERSON'), ('West Bank', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,仏ルーヴル美術館から機械式リフトで降りる2人の映像　逃亡する宝石強盗団か, 所要時間 0,32","Video, Footage of two people descending from France's Louvre Museum in a mechanical lift. Could it be a gang of jewel thieves on the run? Duration: 0,32",0.0,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('jewel', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロンドン警視庁、警官3人を免職　BBCが潜入取材で報じた問題行為を認定,"London Metropolitan Police dismisses three officers, recognizing problematic behavior reported by BBC in undercover reporting",0.0,"[('London Metropolitan Police', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イギリス国王とローマ教皇、並んで祈り歴史を作る,British King and Pope make history by praying side by side,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Pope', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: EAC yapeleka waangalizi wa uchaguzi Tanzania,Tanzania 2025 elections: EAC sends election observers to Tanzania,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('EAC', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, safu ya ulinzi ya Arsenal inaweza kuwasaidia  kushinda ubingwa?",Can Arsenal's defense help them win the title?,0.8,[]
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Meli za kivita, ndege za kivita na CIA – lengo la Trump nchini Venezuela ni lipi?","Warships, warplanes and the CIA - what is Trump's goal in Venezuela?",0.0,"[('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Matamanio ya Watanzania ughaibuni kuhusu uchaguzi wa nyumbani,Desires of Tanzanians abroad regarding local elections,0.0,"[('Tanzanians', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maamuzi ya Raila Odinga ambayo yaliwaacha wengi vinywa wazi,Raila Odinga's decisions that left many speechless,0.25,"[(""Raila Odinga's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,John Heche hajulikani alipo - Ndugu,John Heche's whereabouts are unknown - Brother,-0.1,"[(""John Heche's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchambuzi: Trump aachana na mbinu ya kumbembeleza Putin juu ya vita vya Ukraine,Analysis: Trump abandons the approach of flattering Putin on the war in Ukraine,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Marcus Rashford anataka kusalia Barcelona,European Football Rumors Friday: Marcus Rashford wants to stay at Barcelona,0.1,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Marcus Rashford', 'PERSON'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wasomi Chuo Kikuu Tanzania wataka utekaji kuchunguzwa,Academics at the University of Tanzania want the abduction to be investigated,0.0,"[('the University of Tanzania', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_24,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marekani yaonya dhidi ya unyakuzi wa ukingo wa Magharibi,The United States warns against the annexation of the West Bank,0.0,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('the West Bank', 'GPE')]"
