Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Delcy Rodríguez invita a Trump y a EE.UU. a trabajar conjuntamente ""en una agenda de cooperación""","Delcy Rodríguez invites Trump and the US to work together ""on a cooperation agenda""",0.0,"[('Delcy Rodríguez', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El gobierno de La Habana informó que 32 cubanos murieron en los ataques de EE.UU. en Venezuela,The Havana government reported that 32 Cubans died in the US attacks in Venezuela,0.0,"[('Havana', 'GPE'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cubans', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué le taparon los ojos y los oídos a Maduro al detenerlo,Why did they cover Maduro's eyes and ears when detaining him?,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Análisis: lo que suceda ahora en Venezuela puede definir el legado de Trump y el rol de Estados Unidos en el mundo,Analysis: what happens now in Venezuela can define Trump's legacy and the role of the United States in the world,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo es el MDC de Brooklyn, el centro de detención en Nueva York donde se encuentra Maduro tras ser capturado por EE.UU.","What the Brooklyn MDC is like, the detention center in New York where Maduro is held after being captured by the US.",0.018181818181818174,"[('the Brooklyn MDC', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,राष्ट्रपति को पकड़ा और न्यूयॉर्क ले आए... क्या वेनेज़ुएला के ख़िलाफ़ अमेरिका ऐसा कर सकता है?,Caught the President and brought him to New York... Can America do this against Venezuela?,0.13636363636363635,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,बांग्लादेश ने आईपीएल मैचों के प्रसारण को लेकर किया ये फ़ैसला",Bangladesh took this decision regarding broadcasting IPL matches live.,0.13636363636363635,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,उमर ख़ालिद और शरजील इमाम को सुप्रीम कोर्ट से नहीं मिली ज़मानत,Omar Khalid and Sharjeel Imam did not get bail from the Supreme Court,0.0,"[('Omar Khalid', 'PERSON'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वेनेज़ुएला के बाद ट्रंप ने कहा उन्हें ग्रीनलैंड चाहिए, डेनमार्क की कड़ी प्रतिक्रिया","After Venezuela, Trump said he wants Greenland, Denmark gave strong reaction",0.31666666666666665,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Greenland', 'GPE'), ('Denmark', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बीई और बीटेक क्या अलग होते हैं और क्या इससे करियर पर पड़ता है असर?,What is the difference between BE and B.Tech and does it affect your career?,0.0,"[('BE', 'ORG'), ('B.Tech', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'मैं उसकी मां हूं. मैं वह वीडियो देख ही नहीं सकती' दीपू दास की मां ने बीबीसी से कहा,'I am his mother. I can't watch that video' Dipu Das's mother told BBC,0.0,"[(""Dipu Das's"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"निकोलस मादुरो की पत्नी सिलिया फ़्लोरेस कौन हैं, जो रहीं वेनेज़ुएला की 'फ़र्स्ट वॉरियर'","Who is Nicolas Maduro's wife Cilia Flores, who was Venezuela's 'First Warrior'?",0.25,"[(""Nicolas Maduro's"", 'PERSON'), ('Cilia Flores', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वेनेज़ुएला पर भारत बोला- गहरी चिंता की बात, वहीं मुस्लिम देशों के भी आए बयान","India said on Venezuela - a matter of deep concern, statements from Muslim countries also came",0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,टी20 वर्ल्ड कप खेलने के लिए भारत का दौरा नहीं करेगी बांग्लादेश की क्रिकेट टीम,Bangladesh cricket team will not tour India to play T20 World Cup,0.0,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('T20 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem é Delcy Rodríguez, a poderosa sucessora de Maduro com trânsito nos EUA, na China e entre empresários","Who is Delcy Rodríguez, Maduro's powerful successor with a presence in the USA, China and among businesspeople",0.3,"[('Delcy Rodríguez', 'PERSON'), ('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"AO VIVO,Após derrubada de Maduro, Trump ameaça Colômbia; Delcy fala em 'cooperação' com EUA; acompanhe ao vivo","LIVE,After Maduro's overthrow, Trump threatens Colombia; Delcy talks about 'cooperation' with the USA; follow live",0.13636363636363635,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Delcy', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump diz que presidente interina 'pagará preço muito alto' se 'não fizer o certo' na Venezuela; o que aconteceu até agora,Trump says interim president 'will pay a very high price' if he 'doesn't do the right thing' in Venezuela; what happened so far,0.19790476190476192,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Ataque à Venezuela lembra invasão ao Iraque, diz ex-subsecretária de Defesa dos EUA","Attack on Venezuela resembles invasion of Iraq, says former US Undersecretary of Defense",0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Iraq', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que cobriram os olhos e os ouvidos de Maduro durante sua captura,Why did they cover Maduro's eyes and ears during his capture,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Ação de Trump na Venezuela pode criar um precedente para potências autoritárias no mundo','Trump's action in Venezuela could create a precedent for authoritarian powers around the world',0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A fascinante história do irlandês que passou 61 dias enterrado em um caixão,The fascinating story of the Irishman who spent 61 days buried in a coffin,0.3,"[('Irishman', 'NORP'), ('61 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O mistério de Mercúrio, o planeta que cientistas dizem que não deveria existir","The mystery of Mercury, the planet scientists say shouldn't exist",0.0,"[('Mercury', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Imagens de satélite mostram estragos em complexo militar em Caracas após ação dos EUA,Satellite images show damage to military complex in Caracas after US action,-0.10000000000000002,"[('Caracas', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Мадуро и его супруга предстанут перед судом в Нью-Йорке, Трамп грозит мерами против Родригес","LIVELive,Maduro and his wife will appear in court in New York, Trump threatens measures against Rodriguez",0.13636363636363635,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Rodriguez', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Трамп сказал, что не верит в атаку дронов на госрезиденцию Путина","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Trump said he doesn't believe there will be a drone attack on Putin's state residence",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Прецедент Мадуро. Решатся ли последовать примеру Трампа авторитарные лидеры по всему миру?,Maduro's precedent. Will authoritarian leaders around the world decide to follow Trump's example?,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Новая эра и удар по Путину. Политолог — о причинах и последствиях свержения Мадуро в подкасте Би-би-си «Что это было?»,A new era and a blow to Putin. Political scientist talks about the causes and consequences of the overthrow of Maduro in the BBC podcast “What was that?”,0.06818181818181818,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Операция США в Венесуэле. Почему у них получилось,US operation in Venezuela. Why did they succeed?,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Премьер-министр Дании призвала Трампа прекратить угрозы в адрес Гренландии,Danish Prime Minister calls on Trump to stop threats against Greenland,0.0,"[('Danish', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Greenland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп хочет добывать нефть в Венесуэле. Насколько это реально и кому она достанется?,Trump wants to extract oil in Venezuela. How realistic is this and who will get it?,0.18333333333333335,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как мир реагирует на военную операцию США в Венесуэле,How the world is reacting to the US military operation in Venezuela,-0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп сверг Мадуро, но пока оставил у власти его режим. Что будет дальше?",Trump overthrew Maduro but kept his regime in power for now. What's next?,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Анализ: операция США в Венесуэле может определить наследие Трампа и место Америки в мире,Analysis: US operation in Venezuela could define Trump's legacy and America's place in the world,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ヴェネズエラ暫定大統領に警告　米国に従わなければマドゥロ氏と同じ運命と,"Trump warns Venezuelan interim president: If you don't follow the US, you will face the same fate as Maduro",0.0,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 トランプ氏の行動は世界中の権威主義国家にとって前例となる可能性　BBC国際編集長,[Commentary] Trump's actions could set a precedent for authoritarian countries around the world BBC International Editor-in-Chief,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('BBC International', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,【検証】ヴェネズエラに対するトランプ米大統領の動き　主なポイントは, 所要時間 3,32","Video, [Verification] U.S. President Trump's moves toward Venezuela, main points, time required 3,32",0.16666666666666666,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('3,32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,デンマーク首相、グリーンランドへの「脅し」やめるようトランプ氏に要求,Denmark's prime minister asks Trump to stop 'threatening' Greenland,0.0,"[('Denmark', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Greenland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スイスのバー火災、犠牲者全40人の身元特定　現地警察,All 40 victims of Swiss bar fire identified by local police,0.0,"[('40', 'CARDINAL'), ('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、「我々がヴェネズエラを運営する」　マドゥロ氏はNYに到着,Trump: ``We will run Venezuela'' Maduro arrives in New York,0.13636363636363635,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,アメリカのヴェネズエラ攻撃と大統領拘束、これまでの経緯と市民の反応, 所要時間 1,37","Video, U.S. attack on Venezuela and capture of president, history and citizen reaction, Duration 1,37",0.0,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,シャンパンボトルの手持ち花火が原因か、スイスのバー火災で多数死亡,Many killed in Swiss bar fire possibly caused by hand-held fireworks from champagne bottles,0.075,"[('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,マスク氏のAI「Grok」に服をデジタルで消された……「人間性を奪われた」と被害女性,Victim says her clothes were digitally erased by Musk's AI ``Grok''... ``My humanity was taken away'',-0.037500000000000006,"[('Victim', 'PERSON'), ('Grok', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump amuonya kiongozi mpya wa Venezuela, Maduro akitarajiwa kufikishwa mahakamani","Directly, Trump warned the new leader of Venezuela, Maduro is expected to be brought to court",0.04545454545454545,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ni nani anaongoza Venezuela sasa na kipi kitakachofuata?,Who is leading Venezuela now and what will happen next?,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchambuzi: Hatua ya Trump Venezuela inazisafishia njia tawala za kiimla duniani,Analysis: Trump's action in Venezuela clears the way for totalitarian regimes in the world,0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"AFCON 2025: Tanzania yafa kiume Morocco, haitasahau matukio haya 4","AFCON 2025: Tanzania dies in Morocco, will not forget these 4 events",0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"'Huonekani, hupo' - maisha bila cheti cha kuzaliwa","'You are not seen, you are not there' - life without a birth certificate",0.0,[]
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Real Madrid yajiunga na mbio za kumsaka Wharton,European Football Rumors Monday: Real Madrid join race for Wharton,0.1,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Wharton', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Jehanamu Duniani': Watu mashuhuri waliowahi kuzuiliwa kituo cha Brooklyn aliko Maduro,'Hell on Earth': Celebrities who were detained in the Brooklyn detention center where Maduro is,-0.1,"[('Earth', 'LOC'), ('Brooklyn', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kuishi kwa hofu ya Lakurawa - kundi la wanamgambo lililoshambuliwa na Trump nchini Nigeria,Living in fear of Lakurawa - the militant group attacked by Trump in Nigeria,0.0,"[('Lakurawa', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maduro ni nani na kwanini Marekani imemkamata?,Who is Maduro and why has the United States arrested him?,0.0,"[('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanasiasa maarufu Tanzania walioaga dunia 2025,Famous Tanzanian politicians who passed away in 2025,0.5,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
