Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Los resultados preliminares de las presidenciales en Honduras muestran una ajustada contienda entre el conservador Asfura, apoyado por Trump, y el centrista Nasralla","The preliminary results of the presidential elections in Honduras show a tight contest between the conservative Asfura, supported by Trump, and the centrist Nasralla",-0.17857142857142858,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('Asfura', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Nasralla', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cuál es el estado de los vuelos en Venezuela tras los anuncios de Trump y su gobierno sobre el cierre del espacio aéreo del país caribeño,What is the status of flights in Venezuela after the announcements by Trump and his government about the closure of the Caribbean country's airspace?,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"En qué países de América Latina ha estado presente Lev Tahor, la secta ultraortodoxa judía acusada de abuso infantil y recientemente detectada en Colombia","In which Latin American countries has Lev Tahor, the ultra-Orthodox Jewish sect accused of child abuse and recently detected in Colombia, been present?",0.0,"[('Latin American', 'NORP'), ('Lev Tahor', 'PERSON'), ('ultra-Orthodox', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Es como viajar al fin de la civilización"": una aventura por la desafiante Carretera Austral de Chile","""It's like traveling to the end of civilization"": an adventure along Chile's challenging Carretera Austral",0.5,"[('Chile', 'GPE'), ('Carretera Austral', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué son las ingeniosas cajas de Ward y cómo transformaron la economía mundial,What are Ward's ingenious boxes and how did they transform the world economy?,0.5,"[('Ward', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नीट में कामयाबी ना मिले तो मेडिकल के ये कोर्स बन सकते हैं 'प्लान बी',"If you do not get success in NEET, these medical courses can become 'Plan B'",0.15,"[('NEET', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,यूक्रेन जंग ख़त्म करने को लेकर चल रही वार्ता के बारे में मार्को रूबियो ने क्या बताया","Live, what Marco Rubio told about the ongoing talks to end the Ukraine war",0.13636363636363635,"[('Marco Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,विराट कोहली ने शतक ठोंककर एक साथ कितने सवालों के जवाब दे दिए,How many questions did Virat Kohli answer at once by scoring a century?,0.5,"[('Virat Kohli', 'ORG'), ('a century', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"संसद का शीतकालीन सत्र: लोकसभा में एसआईआर पर फिर हंगामा, दोपहर 2 बजे तक कार्यवाही स्थगित","Winter session of Parliament: Uproar again over SIR in Lok Sabha, proceedings adjourned till 2 pm",0.0,"[('Winter', 'TIME'), ('Parliament', 'ORG'), ('SIR', 'ORG'), ('Lok Sabha', 'PERSON'), ('2 pm', 'TIME')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"भारत में कैसे मिला था एड्स का पहला मामला, राजीव गांधी को दी गई थी जानकारी","How the first case of AIDS was found in India, information was given to Rajiv Gandhi",0.25,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Rajiv Gandhi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नेतन्याहू ने राष्ट्रपति को पत्र लिखकर क्यों लगाई माफ़ी की गुहार, उनके ख़िलाफ़ क्या हैं आरोप?","Why did Netanyahu write a letter to the President asking for pardon, what are the allegations against him?",0.0,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,वॉशिंगटन में नेशनल गार्ड्स पर हमलाः पूर्व बाइडन सरकार की नीति पर क्यों उठ रहे सवाल,Attack on National Guards in Washington: Why questions are being raised on the policy of the former Biden government,0.0,"[('National Guards', 'ORG'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Biden', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सऊदी की महिला क्रिकेट लीग में बरसेंगे पैसे, फिर भी कुछ खिलाड़ी क्यों दुविधा में हैं?","Money will pour into Saudi Women's Cricket League, yet why are some players in a dilemma?",0.0,"[(""Saudi Women's"", 'ORG'), ('Cricket League', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लॉर्ड डलहौज़ी, जिनकी रजवाड़ों को निगलने की नीति 1857 के विद्रोह का कारण बनी","Lord Dalhousie, whose policy of absorbing the princely states led to the rebellion of 1857",0.2,"[('Dalhousie', 'PERSON'), ('1857', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Vaca Muerta: a nova riqueza do boom do petróleo da Argentina,Vaca Muerta: the new wealth of Argentina's oil boom,0.13636363636363635,"[('Vaca Muerta', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A situação dos voos na Venezuela após anúncios de Trump sobre o fechamento do espaço aéreo do país,The situation with flights in Venezuela after Trump's announcements about the closure of the country's airspace,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que a compra de uma seguradora para agentes do serviço secreto dos EUA revela sobre a onda de investimentos da China no Ocidente,What the purchase of an insurance company for US Secret Service agents reveals about China's wave of investment in the West,-0.4,"[('US Secret Service', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Anúncios com IA e imagens falsas levaram consumidores a acreditar que essas lojas ficavam na Inglaterra — mas elas estavam na Ásia,AI ads and fake images led consumers to believe these stores were in England — but they were in Asia,-0.5,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('Asia', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'O Paradoxo do Terror': Como assistir a filmes de terror pode acalmar a ansiedade e ajudar a lidar com situações difíceis,'The Horror Paradox': How Watching Horror Movies Can Calm Anxiety and Help You Cope With Difficult Situations,-0.09999999999999998,[]
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'É como dirigir até o limite da civilização': uma aventura pela desafiante Carretera Austral do Chile,'It's like driving to the edge of civilization': an adventure along Chile's challenging Carretera Austral,0.5,"[('Chile', 'GPE'), ('Carretera Austral', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O jovem que passa horas por dia consertando notas de dinheiro velhas e rasgadas em Gaza,The young man who spends hours a day repairing old and torn banknotes in Gaza,0.1,"[('hours a day', 'DATE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A música acalma os animais?,Does music calm animals?,0.30000000000000004,[]
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os macabros assassinatos para vender partes humanas para rituais de magia,The macabre murders to sell human parts for magic rituals,0.25,[]
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Уиткофф в понедельник отправится в Москву после встречи с украинской делегацией во Флориде","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Witkoff will travel to Moscow on Monday after meeting with the Ukrainian delegation in Florida",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Грузинская полиция могла использовать химоружие времен Первой мировой для разгона протестов. Расследование Би-би-си,Georgian police may have used World War I-era chemical weapons to disperse protests. BBC investigation,0.0,"[('Georgian', 'NORP'), ('World War I', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Украина атаковала дронами танкеры «теневого флота» России в Черном море и терминал в Новороссийске. Казахстан и Турция протестуют,Ukraine attacked tankers of Russia’s “shadow fleet” in the Black Sea and a terminal in Novorossiysk with drones. Kazakhstan and Türkiye protest,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('the Black Sea', 'LOC'), ('Novorossiysk', 'GPE'), ('Kazakhstan', 'GPE'), ('Türkiye', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Продуктивные переговоры, но работа еще остается». Делегации Украины и США обсудили мирный план на встрече во Флориде","“Productive negotiations, but work remains.” Delegations of Ukraine and the United States discussed a peace plan at a meeting in Florida",0.0,"[('Delegations of Ukraine', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,25 фаворитов на премию «Оскар» и где их смотреть,25 Oscar favorites and where to watch them,0.0,"[('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('Oscar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Тюрьма или смерть». В туннелях в секторе Газа блокированы сотни боевиков ХАМАС. Почему это стало тестом на прочность мирного плана Трампа?,"""Prison or death."" Hundreds of Hamas militants are blocked in the tunnels in the Gaza Strip. Why did this test the strength of Trump's peace plan?",0.0,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('the Gaza Strip', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нетаньяху попросил президента Израиля помиловать его по делу о коррупции,Netanyahu asked Israeli President to pardon him in corruption case,0.0,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Первые результаты выборов парламента Кыргызстана: сторонники президента получают большинство,First results of the parliamentary elections in Kyrgyzstan: supporters of the president receive a majority,0.25,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('Kyrgyzstan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Число жертв наводнения в Индонезии достигло 442,Indonesian flood death toll reaches 442,0.0,"[('Indonesian', 'NORP'), ('442', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Число погибших при пожаре в Гонконге выросло до 146, пропавшими без вести остаются более 40 человек","Death toll from fire in Hong Kong rises to 146, more than 40 people remain missing",0.15,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('146', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 40', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ガザ地区の死者が7万人超す　停戦以降に350人以上、直近は幼い兄弟2人,"More than 70,000 people have died in Gaza; more than 350 since ceasefire, most recently two young brothers",0.32,"[('More than 70,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('more than 350', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナとの協議、「生産的」だったが作業の継続必要と　米国務長官,US Secretary of State says talks with Ukraine were 'productive' but work needs to continue,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スリランカ、洪水と土砂崩れで死者330人超　非常事態を宣言,Sri Lanka declares state of emergency as floods and landslides kill more than 330 people,0.5,"[('Sri Lanka', 'PERSON'), ('more than 330', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インドネシア、大洪水の死者500人超す　行方不明も500人以上,"More than 500 dead in Indonesia, more than 500 missing in severe floods",0.15000000000000002,"[('More than 500', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indonesia', 'GPE'), ('more than 500', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港の高層住宅群火災、死者146人に　多数の市民集まり犠牲者悼む,146 people killed in Hong Kong high-rise residential fire; large number of citizens gather to mourn victims,0.007142857142857131,"[('146', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,続く協議にウクライナ側は　前軍総司令官の英紙投稿が注目されるなか, 所要時間 3,52","Video, Ukraine side engages in subsequent talks as former army commander's post in British newspaper attracts attention, time required: 3,52",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('3,52', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,今年の単語は「レイジ・ベイト」に、英オックスフォード英語辞典　意図的に「炎上」狙うコンテンツの意味,"This year's word is ""rage bait,"" according to the Oxford English Dictionary, meaning content that intentionally aims to cause a stir.",0.0,"[('year', 'DATE'), ('English Dictionary', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日本の音楽イベント、上海で相次ぎ中止　「ONE PIECE」主題歌は公演途中で,"Japanese music events are canceled one after another in Shanghai; ""ONE PIECE"" theme song is still being performed",0.0,"[('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('Shanghai', 'GPE'), ('ONE', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スイスの尊厳死団体の創設者、医師の支援を受けて死去　92歳,Founder of Switzerland's Death with Dignity organization dies at age 92 with help from doctors,0.0,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Death with Dignity', 'ORG'), ('age 92', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mazungumzo ya kumaliza vita vya Ukraine yanakwenda vyema - asema Rubio","Directly, the negotiations to end the war in Ukraine are going well - says Rubio",0.1,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maelfu ya watu wanadhaniwa kuathiriwa na kemikali hatari wakati wa maandamano ya kupinga serikali Georgia,Thousands of people are thought to have been exposed to dangerous chemicals during anti-government protests in Georgia,-0.6,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"""Niliwaona wakikanyaga watu waliojeruhiwa kwa magari yao"" -ukimbizi wa kutisha kutoka vitani nchini Sudan","""I saw them trampling wounded people with their cars"" - a terrible escape from the war in Sudan",-1.0,"[('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumatatu: Liverpool yapanga kutoa ofa kwa Camavinga,Football rumors Monday: Liverpool are planning to make an offer for Camavinga,0.0,"[('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool', 'ORG'), ('Camavinga', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Benjamin Netanyahu amuomba rais wa Israel amsamehe,Benjamin Netanyahu asked the president of Israel to forgive him,0.0,"[('Benjamin Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Museveni hatahudhuria mdahalo wa wagombea urais Uganda,President Museveni will not attend the Ugandan presidential candidates' debate,0.0,"[('Museveni', 'PERSON'), ('Ugandan', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Hofu ya utekaji inatutia wasiwasi hatuwezi kuzungumza' - Wanavijiji Nigeria,'The fear of kidnapping worries us we can't talk' - Villagers in Nigeria,0.0,"[('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ukraine yashambulia meli za Urusi katika Bahari Nyeusi,Ukraine attacks Russian ships in the Black Sea,-0.08333333333333333,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanasoka wanawake watano Afrika wanaolipwa fedha nyingi zaidi 2025,Five female footballers in Africa who are paid the most money in 2025,0.25,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_01,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanyama wanaokwepa kifo kupitia uwezo wa kinga zao,Animals that avoid death through their immune system,0.0,[]
