Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,¿Qué está frenando la segunda fase del cese el fuego entre Israel y Hamás impulsado por EE.UU.?,What is holding back the second phase of the US-driven ceasefire between Israel and Hamas?,0.0,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Trump enfurece al gobierno de Dinamarca al nombrar a un enviado especial para Groenlandia,Trump angers Danish government by appointing special envoy to Greenland,0.35714285714285715,"[('Danish', 'NORP'), ('Greenland', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La desgarradora foto de la madre a la que entregaron el cuerpo de su bebé en una caja de cartón (y qué dice de la crisis de salud de Ecuador),The heartbreaking photo of the mother to whom her baby's body was delivered in a cardboard box (and what it says about Ecuador's health crisis),0.0,"[('Ecuador', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,9 de los viajes en tren más inolvidables del mundo (y cuáles son en América Latina y España),9 of the most unforgettable train trips in the world (and which ones are in Latin America and Spain),0.65,"[('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Latin America', 'LOC'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué tus fotos de principios de los 2000 pueden haberse perdido para siempre (y varios consejos para conservar las que tienes ahora),Why your photos from the early 2000s may be lost forever (and tips for preserving the ones you have now),0.1,"[('the early 2000s', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश में रूस के राजदूत ने बढ़ती तनातनी पर भारत को लेकर क्या कहा?,What did the Russian Ambassador to Bangladesh say about India on the increasing tension?,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,राहुल गांधी के जर्मनी में दिए बयानों पर बीजेपी हमलावर","Live, BJP attacks Rahul Gandhi's statements in Germany",0.13636363636363635,"[('BJP', 'ORG'), (""Rahul Gandhi's"", 'PERSON'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार के नवादा में मुसलमान फेरीवाले को पीट कर मार डालने का पूरा मामला-ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट,"The entire case of Muslim hawker being beaten to death in Nawada, Bihar - ground report",0.0,"[('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Nawada', 'GPE'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश में 25 दिसंबर को ऐसा क्या होना है कि जर्मन दूतावास रहेगा बंद और अमेरिकी दूतावास ने जारी की एडवाइज़री,What is to happen in Bangladesh on 25th December that the German Embassy will remain closed and the US Embassy issued advisory,-0.05,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('25th December', 'DATE'), ('the German Embassy', 'ORG'), ('the US Embassy', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अरावली पहाड़ियों को लेकर उत्तर भारत के कई राज्यों में प्रदर्शन क्यों हो रहे?,Why are there protests in many states of North India regarding the Aravalli Hills?,0.5,"[('North India', 'LOC'), ('the Aravalli Hills', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बांग्लादेश के मीडिया में भारत के बारे में क्या-कुछ कहा जा रहा है?,What is being said about India in the media of Bangladesh?,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बोंडी बीच पर हमला करने वालों ने कैसे की थी तैयारी?,How did those who attacked Bondi Beach prepare?,0.0,"[('Bondi Beach', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,टॉय गन से जहाज़ अग़वा करने वाले हाईजैकर्स जो बाद में विधायक बने,Hijackers who hijacked ships with toy guns later became MLAs,0.0,"[('Hijackers', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"फ़ैसल करीम मसूद कौन हैं, जिनकी उस्मान हादी हत्या मामले में बांग्लादेश पुलिस को है तलाश","Who is Faisal Karim Masood, whom Bangladesh Police is looking for in the Osman Hadi murder case?",0.0,"[('Faisal Karim Masood', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh Police', 'ORG'), ('Osman Hadi', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Moraes autoriza prisão domiciliar do general Augusto Heleno por diagnóstico de Alzheimer,Moraes authorizes house arrest of General Augusto Heleno due to Alzheimer’s diagnosis,-0.041666666666666664,"[('Moraes', 'ORG'), ('Augusto Heleno', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que China e Rússia parecem ter abandonado Maduro em meio à escalada da tensão com EUA?,Why do China and Russia appear to have abandoned Maduro amid escalating tension with the US?,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Qual o futuro do 'fenômeno' Michelle Bolsonaro?,What is the future of the 'phenomenon' Michelle Bolsonaro?,0.0,"[('Michelle Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Novo enviado de Trump afirma que irá trabalhar para que Groenlândia passe a fazer parte dos EUA,Trump's new envoy says he will work to make Greenland part of the US,0.13636363636363635,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Greenland', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O 'iceberg de gordura' pesando 100 toneladas achado no esgoto de Londres,'Fat iceberg' weighing 100 tonnes found in London sewer,0.0,"[('100 tonnes', 'QUANTITY'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como uma mala antiga revelou uma fortuna familiar perdida sob o nazismo,How an old suitcase revealed a family fortune lost under Nazism,0.1,"[('Nazism', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os nomes de criança mais populares no Brasil em 2025,The most popular children's names in Brazil in 2025,0.55,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que nova campanha da Havaianas levou grupos de direita a pedirem boicote à marca,Why Havaianas' new campaign led right-wing groups to call for a boycott of the brand,0.13636363636363635,"[('Havaianas', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Foto de Trump é reinserida nos arquivos de Epstein após acusações de 'acobertamento',Trump photo reinserted into Epstein files after 'cover-up' accusations,0.0,"[('Epstein', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: новый ночной обстрел, известно о двух погибших","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: new night shelling, two dead known",-0.03181818181818183,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«„Красный человек“ стреляет в Украине». Светлана Алексиевич рассказала Би-би-си о жизни в Берлине и своей следующей книге,"""The 'Red Man' shoots in Ukraine."" Svetlana Alexievich spoke to the BBC about life in Berlin and her next book",0.0,"[(""The 'Red Man'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Svetlana Alexievich', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Berlin', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В сирийском Алеппо произошли столкновения правительственных сил с курдскими формированиями,Clashes between government forces and Kurdish forces occurred in Syrian Aleppo,0.0,"[('Kurdish', 'NORP'), ('Syrian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Москве в результате подрыва автомобиля погиб начальник управления Генштаба,"In Moscow, the head of the General Staff department died as a result of a car explosion",0.05000000000000002,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('General Staff', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Новый спецпосланник Трампа по Гренландии пообещал работать над ее присоединением к США. Дания возмущена,Trump's new special envoy for Greenland has promised to work toward its annexation to the United States. Denmark is outraged,-0.1354978354978355,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Greenland', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Denmark', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В центре Лондона появились два новых произведения Бэнкси. Они совершенно одинаковые,Two new Banksy pieces have appeared in central London. They are exactly the same,0.09659090909090909,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Умер британский певец Крис Ри, автор хита The Road to Hell","British singer Chris Rea, author of the hit The Road to Hell, has died",0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Chris Rea', 'PERSON'), ('The Road to Hell', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Цены на золото и серебро взлетели на рекордную высоту: инвесторы ищут спасения от нестабильности в мировой экономике,Gold and silver prices soar to record highs as investors seek refuge from global economic instability,0.1,[]
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Самодельные бомбы и тренировки на стрельбище. Австралийская полиция раскрыла подробности нападения на Бонди-Бич,Homemade bombs and training at the shooting range. Australian police reveal details of Bondi Beach attack,0.0,"[('Homemade', 'NORP'), ('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Bondi Beach', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Мы добьемся его избрания 48-м президентом США». Вдова и сторонники Чарли Кирка поддержали Джей Ди Вэнса,“We will get him elected as the 48th President of the United States.” Charlie Kirk's widow and supporters support J.D. Vance,0.0,"[('48th', 'ORDINAL'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), (""Charlie Kirk's"", 'PERSON'), ('J.D. Vance', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシア、ウクライナの要衝オデーサ州への攻撃強める,Russia intensifies attacks on Ukraine's key Odesa region,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、グリーンランド担当特使を任命　アメリカが「所有しなければならない」と,"Trump appoints special envoy for Greenland, saying the US “must own it”",0.47857142857142854,"[('Greenland', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロンドンにバンクシー氏の新作、空を眺める子どもの壁画,Banksy's new mural of a child looking at the sky in London,0.13636363636363635,"[('Banksy', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,【検証】 アメリカがヴェネズエラ沖で追う石油タンカー、何が問題になっているのか, 所要時間 1,53","Video, [Verification] What's wrong with the oil tanker being chased by the US off the coast of Venezuela? Duration: 1,53",-0.5,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('1,53', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米大統領、「トランプ級」軍艦からなる「黄金艦隊」構想を発表,US President announces 'Gold Fleet' concept consisting of 'Trump-class' warships,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), (""Gold Fleet'"", 'ORG')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,モスクワで車爆発、ロシア軍幹部が死亡と当局発表,"Russian military officer killed in car explosion in Moscow, authorities say",-0.10000000000000002,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米司法省、「エプスティーン・ファイル」から一部資料を削除　写真少なくとも13点,U.S. Department of Justice deletes some documents from 'Epstein File' - at least 13 photos,-0.3,"[('U.S. Department of Justice', 'ORG'), (""Epstein File'"", 'PERSON'), ('at least 13', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカがヴェネズエラ沖で石油タンカーを拿捕、今月2度目　3隻目を追跡中と当局者,"The US has seized an oil tanker off the coast of Venezuela for the second time this month, officials say they are tracking a third tanker.",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('this month', 'DATE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,バーボン「ジム・ビーム」、米主力製造拠点が来年1年閉鎖へ,Jim Beam bourbon's main manufacturing base in the US to close next year,-0.21111111111111114,"[('Jim Beam', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('next year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Gridi ya maji ya taifa, muarobaini wa tatizo la maji Tanzania?","The national water grid, the root of Tanzania's water problem?",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Urusi yaongeza mashambulizi katika eneo la Odesa, Ukraine","Directly, Russia increases attacks in Odesa, Ukraine",0.1,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Odesa', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,AFCON 2025: Tanzania kuishangaza Nigeria leo?,AFCON 2025: Tanzania to surprise Nigeria today?,0.0,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Man United wamgeukia Conor Gallagher,European football rumours: Man United turn to Conor Gallagher,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Conor Gallagher', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, M23 wamejiondoa Uvira kweli? Hali ilivyo sasa Mashariki mwa DRC",Have M23 really pulled out of Uvira? The current situation in Eastern DRC,0.1,"[('M23', 'GPE'), ('Uvira', 'GPE'), ('Eastern DRC', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Vijana 8 wa kiafrika walioacha alama mwaka 2025,8 young Africans who left a mark in 2025,0.05,"[('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africans', 'PERSON'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watu maarufu duniani waliofariki 2025,Famous people in the world who died in 2025,0.5,"[('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi 10 za Afrika ambazo hazijawahi kushiriki fainali za AFCON,10 African countries that have never participated in the AFCON finals,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('AFCON', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Faili za Epstein: Waathirika na mashaka kuhusu kutolewa kwa nyaraka zilizobaki za Epstein,Epstein files: Victims and doubts about release of remaining Epstein documents,0.0,"[('Epstein', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Benin yamuweka kizuizini kiongozi wa upinzani kwa tuhuma za mapinduzi,Benin detains an opposition leader on suspicion of coup,0.0,"[('Benin', 'PERSON')]"
