Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué ha pasado en Gaza desde el alto el fuego (y por qué el conflicto no ha terminado),What has happened in Gaza since the ceasefire (and why the conflict is not over),0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Quiénes forman el círculo de poder en torno a Nicolás Maduro en Venezuela,Who forms the circle of power around Nicolás Maduro in Venezuela,0.0,"[('Nicolás Maduro', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Es un mensaje horrible"": las dudas que despierta el indulto de Trump a Juan Orlando Hernández mientras EE.UU. acusa a Maduro de narcotráfico","""It's a horrible message"": the doubts raised by Trump's pardon for Juan Orlando Hernández while the US accuses Maduro of drug trafficking",-1.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Juan Orlando Hernández', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Trump llama ""basura"" a los somalíes antes de lanzar una operación contra los migrantes de la nación africana en Minneapolis","Trump calls Somalis ""garbage"" before launching an operation against migrants from the African nation in Minneapolis",0.0,"[('Somalis', 'NORP'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('Minneapolis', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Alejandro Carranza, el colombiano que presuntamente murió en un ataque de EE.UU. en el Caribe y cuya familia denunció su caso ante la CIDH","Alejandro Carranza, the Colombian who allegedly died in a US attack in the Caribbean and whose family reported his case to the IACHR",-0.1,"[('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('IACHR', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुतिन के भारत दौरे पर क्या कह रहे हैं दोनों देशों के एक्सपर्ट,What are experts from both countries saying about Putin's visit to India?,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,भीमा कोरेगांव केस: दिल्ली यूनिवर्सिटी के पूर्व प्रोफ़ेसर हनी बाबू को मिली ज़मानत","Live, Bhima Koregaon case: Former Delhi University professor Honey Babu gets bail",0.06818181818181818,"[('Bhima Koregaon', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi University', 'ORG'), ('Honey Babu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत का सुप्रीम कोर्ट दलित अधिकारों को लेकर सचेत है लेकिन उसकी भाषा में पूर्वाग्रह- स्टडी,Supreme Court of India is conscious about Dalit rights but there is bias in its language – study,0.1,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Dalit', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इंडिगो की 100 से ज़्यादा उड़ानें रद्द और दर्जनों में घंटों की देरी से यात्री नाराज़, पायलटों की कमी बताई जा रही है वजह","More than 100 Indigo flights canceled and dozens are delayed by hours, passengers angry, shortage of pilots being cited as the reason",0.0,"[('More than 100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indigo', 'ORG'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुत‍िन का भारत दौरा: दोनों देशों के संबंधों में जो मुश्किलें आती हैं आड़े,Putin's visit to India: Difficulties that come in the way in the relations between the two countries,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मारक्रम के आगे कोहली-गायकवाड़ की पारी फ़ेल, दक्षिण अफ़्रीका ने भारत को चार विकेट से हराया","Kohli-Gaikwad's innings failed in front of Markram, South Africa defeated India by four wickets",-0.5,"[(""Kohli-Gaikwad's"", 'ORG'), ('Markram', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"जेम्स वेब टेलीस्कोप के सहारे भारतीय शोधकर्ताओं ने खोजी आकाशगंगा, अलकनंदा रखा नाम","With the help of James Webb Telescope, Indian researchers discovered the galaxy and named it Alaknanda.",0.0,"[('James Webb Telescope', 'PERSON'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Alaknanda', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पुतिन के दौरे से पहले रूस ने भारत के पाले में डाली गेंद, भारत क्या करेगा फ़ैसला?","Before Putin's visit, Russia put the ball in India's court, what will India decide?",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मोबाइल ऐप्स क्या आपका पर्सनल डेटा चुरा सकते हैं, आप ख़ुद को सुरक्षित कैसे रख सकते हैं?","Can mobile apps steal your personal data, how can you keep yourself safe?",0.25,[]
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que revela o novo mapa das facções e milícias do Rio de Janeiro,What the new map of factions and militias in Rio de Janeiro reveals,0.13636363636363635,"[('Rio de Janeiro', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Gilmar Mendes altera lei e veta Senado de pedir impeachment de ministros do Supremo,Gilmar Mendes changes the law and vetoes the Senate from calling for impeachment of Supreme Court ministers,0.0,"[('Gilmar Mendes', 'PERSON'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O fator Michelle Bolsonaro: a aposta que irrita os filhos de ex-presidente,The Michelle Bolsonaro factor: the bet that irritates the former president's children,0.0,"[('Michelle Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Otan discute próximos passos após Putin rejeitar acordo de paz para a Ucrânia: 'Enfrentamos perigos reais',NATO discusses next steps after Putin rejects Ukraine peace deal: 'We face real dangers',0.1,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que revelam as imagens inéditas da ilha onde Jeffrey Epstein cometeu seus crimes sexuais,What the never-before-seen images of the island where Jeffrey Epstein committed his sexual crimes reveal,0.5,"[('Jeffrey Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Governo Trump paralisa processos de residência e cidadania para imigrantes de Cuba, Venezuela e outros 17 países","Trump administration halts residency and citizenship processes for immigrants from Cuba, Venezuela and 17 other countries",-0.125,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('17', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O novo alerta sobre perigos da harmonização facial e outros preenchimentos — e como se proteger,The new warning about the dangers of facial harmonization and other fillers — and how to protect yourself,0.0037878787878787845,[]
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Minha melhor amiga me prometeu aos 15 anos que teria meu bebê e agora sou mãe graças a ela','My best friend promised me at 15 that she would have my baby and now I'm a mother thanks to her',0.6,"[('15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As palavras que você não pode dizer na internet,The words you can't say on the internet,0.0,[]
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Едины в похвалах Трампу. Как в НАТО реагируют на американские мирные инициативы по Украине,United in praise of Trump. How NATO reacts to American peace initiatives in Ukraine,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Путин и Трамп прокомментировали переговоры в Москве, Уиткофф и Кушнер снова встретятся с Умеровым в США","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Putin and Trump commented on negotiations in Moscow, Witkoff and Kushner will meet again with Umerov in the USA",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Witkoff', 'GPE'), ('Kushner', 'ORG'), ('Umerov', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Нефть, оружие и геополитика. Зачем Путин отправляется с госвизитом в Индию","Oil, weapons and geopolitics. Why is Putin going on a state visit to India?",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Не могу сказать, что выйдет». Трамп хвалит переговоры Уиткоффа в Кремле, но не уверен в их успехе; делегация Украины снова летит в Майами","“I can’t say what will happen.” Trump praises Witkoff's negotiations in the Kremlin, but is not confident in their success; Ukrainian delegation flies to Miami again",0.024999999999999994,"[('Witkoff', 'PERSON'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Miami', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,«Скоро тут будет Кавказская Америка». Как выглядит «дорога Трампа» на границе Ирана, Армении, Турции и Азербайджана | Репортаж Би-би-си, Продолжительность 10,15","Video, “Caucasian America will be here soon.” What does the “Trump Road” look like on the border of Iran, Armenia, Turkey and Azerbaijan | BBC report, Duration 10.15",0.0,"[('Caucasian America', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Trump Road', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Armenia', 'GPE'), ('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Azerbaijan', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('10.15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Виноват больше всех». Врач, поставлявший кетамин актеру Мэтью Перри, получил 2,5 года тюрьмы","""Most guilty."" The doctor who supplied actor Matthew Perry with ketamine received 2.5 years in prison.",0.0,"[('Matthew Perry', 'PERSON'), ('2.5 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Обман на 112 млн рублей. Что в деле Ларисы Долиной пошло не так и как в России разрешаются подобные споры?,Fraud of 112 million rubles. What went wrong in Larisa Dolina’s case and how are such disputes resolved in Russia?,-0.25,"[('112 million rubles', 'MONEY'), ('Larisa Dolina’s', 'FAC'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Израиль заявил, что скоро откроет КПП «Рафах», чтобы позволить палестинцам покинуть Газу через Египет",Israel says it will soon open the Rafah crossing to allow Palestinians to leave Gaza through Egypt,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Rafah', 'PERSON'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Egypt', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Кенийский парламент обвинил британских военных в сексуальном насилии и убийствах, происходивших на протяжении десятилетий",Kenyan parliament accuses British military of decades of sexual abuse and killings,0.13333333333333333,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Итальянская Prada купила модный дом Versace — со скидкой,Italian Prada bought the fashion house Versace - at a discount,0.0,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Prada', 'ORG'), ('Versace - at', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナとアメリカ、和平案めぐりフロリダで協議へ　ホワイトハウスが明らかに,"Ukraine and US to hold talks in Florida over peace plan, White House reveals",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 プーチン氏は今どんな心境なのか　直近のウクライナ和平協議からわかること,[Commentary] What is Mr. Putin's current state of mind? What we can learn from the latest Ukraine peace talks,0.25,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港当局、足場用ネットの撤去を改修現場に命じる　大規模火災受け,Hong Kong authorities order renovation site to remove scaffolding nets following large-scale fire,0.0,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告が所有した島、未公開画像を公開　米民主党議員,US Democratic lawmaker releases unreleased images of Epstein's island,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,豪のSNS禁止措置、60秒で解説　メタは16歳未満のアカウント無効化を開始, 所要時間 1,00","Video, Australia's SNS ban explained in 60 seconds Meta starts disabling accounts for people under 16, Required time 1,00",0.0,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('SNS', 'ORG'), ('60 seconds', 'TIME'), ('Meta', 'ORG'), ('under 16', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米国防長官、「シグナル」チャットで部隊を危険にさらした可能性　監視機関が指摘,"US Defense Secretary may have put troops at risk with 'Signal' chats, watchdog says",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Signal', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル軍が避難民キャンプを攻撃、子供含む5人死亡と医療関係者が証言,"Israeli military attacks camp for displaced people, killing 5 people, including children, medical personnel say",-0.05,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米国防長官、生存者は目にしていなかったと主張　「麻薬船」追撃で,US Secretary of Defense claims he didn't see any survivors in pursuit of 'drug ship',0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ドイツ軍に納入予定の弾薬、輸送車から盗まれる　約2万発分か,"Approximately 20,000 rounds of ammunition stolen from a transport vehicle scheduled to be delivered to the German military",-0.16666666666666666,"[('Approximately 20,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('German', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Wajumbe wa Ukraine na Marekani kukutana Florida baada ya mazungumzo ya Moscow - Whitehouse","Directly, the representatives of Ukraine and the United States meet in Florida after the talks in Moscow - Whitehouse",0.1,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Alhamisi: Palace wanaweza kupokea ofa kwa Mateta,Football rumors Thursday: Palace could receive bid for Mateta,0.0,"[('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Palace', 'ORG'), ('Mateta', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, yalikuwa mapinduzi ya 'uongo'? Kilicho nyuma ya uvamizi wa kijeshi Guinea-Bissau",Was it a 'fake' revolution? What is behind the military invasion of Guinea-Bissau,-0.3333333333333333,"[('Guinea-Bissau', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi Wasomali watakavyoathirika kutokana na shutuma za Rais Trump,How Somalis will be affected by President Trump's accusations,0.0,"[('Somalis', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Urusi yakataa baadhi ya masharti ya mpango wa amani ya Ukraine,Russia rejects some of the terms of the Ukraine peace plan,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,UN yashutumu kuongezeka kwa ukandamizaji dhidi ya upinzani Uganda,The UN condemns the increase in repression against the opposition in Uganda,0.0,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Uganda', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais alimuua babu yangu na sasa anataka kumuua baba yangu,The president killed my grandfather and now he wants to kill my father,0.0,[]
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Serikali yamburuza Mahakamani mwanaharakati Mange Kimambi,Protests in Tanzania: The government drags activist Mange Kimambi to court,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Mange Kimambi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tanzania kwenye mzani wa nani 'beberu' nani mfadhili,Tanzania on the scale of who is the 'imperialist' who is the benefactor,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_04,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Samia -Nguvu Iliyotumika Oktoba 29 ilistahili,President Samia - The power used on October 29 was deserved,0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON'), ('October 29', 'DATE')]"
