Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Es una vergüenza que esta misión tenga que existir"": Greta Thunberg y otros 170 activistas de la flotilla que llevaba ayuda humanitaria a Gaza son deportados por Israel","""It is a shame that this mission has to exist.""",0.0,[]
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान ट्रंप की ग़ज़ा योजना को समर्थन देकर क्या ख़ुद को फँसा हुआ पा रहा है?,Is Pakistan able to get itself trapped by supporting Trump's Gaza Yojana?,0.18333333333333335,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Yojana', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,लालू यादव की सोशल मीडिया पोस्ट पर सम्राट चौधरी बोले- '14 तारीख़ को पता चल जाएगा'","On the social media post of Live, Lalu Yadav, Emperor Chaudhary said- '14 date will be known'",0.08484848484848484,"[(""'14"", 'DATE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारतीय टैलेंट को अमेरिका से वापस बुलाना इतना मुश्किल क्यों?,Why is it so difficult to recall Indian talent from America?,-0.5,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सुप्रीम कोर्ट में चीफ़ जस्टिस पर हमले की कोशिश, पीएम मोदी ने कहा, 'घटना से हर भारतीय आक्रोशित'","Attempt to attack Chief Justice in Supreme Court, PM Modi said, 'Every Indian is angry with the incident'",-0.5,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('PM Modi', 'ORG'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान के ख़िलाफ़ छा जाने वाली क्रांति गौड़ जिन्हें क्रिकेट खिलाने के लिए उनकी मां को गहने बेचने पड़े,"Kranti Gaur, who became famous against Pakistan, had to sell her jewelery to her mother to feed her cricket",0.5,"[('Kranti Gaur', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump diz a Lula que EUA 'estão sentindo falta' do café brasileiro: o efeito do tarifaço no bolso americano,Trump tells Lula that the USA 'are missing' Brazilian coffee: the effect of tariff on the American pocket,-0.1,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,'Não podemos ignorar esse genocídio transmitido ao vivo', diz Greta Thunberg sobre Gaza, Duration 1,28","Video, 'We can't ignore this live genocide,' says Greta Thunberg about Gaza, Duration 1.28",0.13636363636363635,"[('Greta Thunberg', 'PERSON'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('1.28', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Marco Rubio pode ser um obstáculo para a aproximação entre Lula e Trump,Why Marco Rubio can be an obstacle to the approach between Lula and Trump,0.0,"[('Marco Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula pede fim do tarifaço e Trump diz que dois países vão 'se dar bem juntos'; o que se sabe da conversa,Lula asks for the end of the tariff and Trump says two countries will 'get along together'; What is known about the conversation,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,José Dirceu: 'Bolsonaro não tem condições de ir para a prisão comum',José Dirceu: 'Bolsonaro is unable to go to the common prison',-0.4,"[('José Dirceu', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Três mortes por intoxicação de metanol em São Paulo: o que o governo sabe e o que ainda não sabe,Three deaths from methanol poisoning in São Paulo: what the government knows and what it does not yet know,0.0,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('São Paulo', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Intoxicação por metanol: mundo já teve 40 mil casos e 14 mil mortes nos últimos 27 anos, indica levantamento","Methanol Poisoning: World has had 40,000 cases and 14,000 deaths in the last 27 years, indicates a survey",0.0,"[('40,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('14,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('the last 27 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como proteger seus joelhos de problemas futuros,How to protect your knees from future trouble,-0.1,[]
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As células que são 'agentes de segurança' do sistema imunológico e renderam Nobel de Medicina de 2025 aos descobridores,Cells that are 'security agents' of the immune system and yielded Nobel Medicine of 2025 to discoverers,0.0,"[('Nobel Medicine', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Израиле вспоминают жертв нападения ХАМАС 7 октября 2023 года. Фото,"Israel remembers the victims of the Hamas attack on October 7, 2023. Photo",0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('October 7, 2023', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Трамп заявил, что почти принял решение о поставке ракет Tomahawk Киеву","Livelive, War in Ukraine: Trump said that he had almost decided to supply Tomahawk missiles to Kyiv",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Tomahawk', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Предварительные итоги выборов в Сирии: в новый парламент прошли несколько женщин,Preliminary election results in Syria: several women entered the new parliament,0.06818181818181818,"[('Syria', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"ВОЗ встревожена числом курящих электронные сигареты, в том числе детей","WHO is alarmed by the number of smokers of electronic cigarettes, including children",0.0,[]
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Израиль и ХАМАС начали переговоры. В чем главные проблемы мирного плана Трампа?,Israel and Hamas began negotiations. What are the main problems of Trump's peaceful plan?,0.20833333333333331,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Во Франции опять нет премьер-министра. Почему это случилось и что будет дальше,"In France, there is no prime minister again. Why did this happen and what will happen next",0.0,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нобелевскую премию по медицине и физиологии присудили за открытия в области иммунитета,The Nobel Prize for Medicine and Physiology was awarded for discoveries in the field of immunity,0.0,"[('The Nobel Prize for Medicine and Physiology', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Лидер суданского ополчения осужден за военные преступления в Дарфуре 20 лет спустя,The leader of the Sudanese militia was convicted of war crimes in Darfur 20 years later,0.0,"[('Sudanese', 'NORP'), ('Darfur', 'GPE'), ('20 years later', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что изменилось во Франции спустя год после процесса по делу Жизель Пелико,What changed in France a year after the process in the case of Giselle Pelico,0.0,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Giselle Pelico', 'FAC')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нобель для президента. Как воинственный американский лидер уговорил Россию подписать договор и получил премию мира,Nobel is for the president. How a warlike American leader persuaded Russia to sign an agreement and received a world award,0.0,"[('Nobel', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノーベル生理学・医学賞、坂口志文氏ら3人に　免疫反応抑える「制御性T細胞」を発見,"Nobel Prize in Physiology and Medicine, Sakaguchi Shifumi, discovered ""regulatory T cells"" that suppress immune responses",0.0,"[('Nobel Prize in Physiology and Medicine', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Sakaguchi Shifumi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ルコルニュ首相が辞任、就任からわずか26日　フランス政界は新たな混乱に,"Prime Minister Le Corgne resigns, only 26 days after taking office, French politics is in new turmoil",0.04545454545454545,"[('Le Corgne', 'PERSON'), ('only 26 days', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、トゥーンベリ氏ら活動家170人を国外追放　拘束中に不当な扱い受けたと活動家たち,"Israeli deported 170 activists including Thunberg, and activists said they were wronged while detained",0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('170', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thunberg', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,20年間亡命の政治家、来年2月の総選挙に向け帰国へ　バングラデシュ,"Politician in exile for 20 years returns to Japan for the general election in February next year, Bangladesh",0.02500000000000001,"[('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('February next year', 'DATE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアのミサイルとドローン、イギリスや日本など外国製の部品を使用とゼレンスキー氏,"Zelensky uses Russian missiles and drones, foreign-made parts such as the UK and Japan.",0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ米大統領とブラジルのルラ大統領が電話協議、「友好的な」雰囲気と両政府,"US President Trump and Brazilian President Lula talks about telephone talks, ""Friendly"" atmosphere and both governments",0.375,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米連邦最高裁、マックスウェル受刑者の上告を却下　エプスティーン事件の共犯者,U.S. Supreme Court dismisses appeal of Maxwell inmates; accomplices in Epstein,0.0,"[('U.S. Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Maxwell', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エヴェレストの吹雪から避難したハイカー、低体温症の恐怖語る　救助活動続く,Hikers evacuated from Everest snowstorm speak of fear of hypothermia; rescue efforts continue,0.0,"[('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mazungumzo ya amani Gaza kuendelea, Trump asema nafasi ya makubaliano ni 'nzuri sana'","Directly, Gaza Peace talks continue, Trump says the position of agreement is 'very good'",0.505,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Maaskofu wa Katoliki DRC wapinga hukumu ya kifo dhidi ya Joseph Kabila,","Catholic bishops DRC oppose the death sentence against Joseph Kabila,",0.0,"[('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Joseph Kabila', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mtanzania aliyekuwa Israel: ‘Kupiga ng'ombe kuliniepusha kuuawa na Hamas Oktoba 7’,Israeli Tanzanian: 'Beating cows avoided killing Hamas on October 7',0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), (""October 7'"", 'DATE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, mwisho wa vita Gaza wakaribia?",Is the end of the war Gaza near?,0.1,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumanne: Bayern inamfukuzia Marc Guehi Crystal Palace,European football rumors on Tuesday: Bayern is chasing Marc Guehi Crystal Palace,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Marc Guehi Crystal Palace', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Humphrey Polepole: Familia yathibitisha 'katekwa na wasiojulikana',Humphrey Slowly: Family Confirms 'captured by anonymous',-0.30000000000000004,"[(""Humphrey Slowly: Family Confirms '"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Samia ameshindwa kukamilisha mageuzi kwa namna na kiwango alichoahidi?,Why has Samia failed to complete the reform in the form and level he promised?,-0.2,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Vita vya Oktoba 1973: Kwa nini Washington iliimarisha tahadhari ya nyuklia?,October 1973 War: Why did Washington enhance nuclear attention?,0.0,"[('October 1973', 'DATE'), ('Washington', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Nitaenda kusherehekea na Ferguson na Wenger' - Guardiola,'I'm going to celebrate with Ferguson and Wenger' - Guardiola,0.0,"[('Ferguson', 'PERSON'), ('Wenger', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi VVU vilivyoongezeka kwa zaidi ya 1000% katika taifa hili dogo la  pasifiki,How HIV has increased by more than 1000% in this small Pacific nation,0.125,"[('more than 1000%', 'PERCENT'), ('Pacific', 'LOC')]"
