Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La opositora venezolana María Corina Machado no irá en persona a recibir el premio Nobel de la Paz,Venezuelan opposition figure María Corina Machado will not go in person to receive the Nobel Peace Prize,0.0,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('María Corina Machado', 'ORG'), ('the Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué China y Rusia parecen haber abandonado a Nicolás Maduro en plena escalada con EE.UU.,Why China and Russia seem to have abandoned Nicolás Maduro in the midst of an escalation with the US.,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Nicolás Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es Alejandro Gil, el exministro de economía de Cuba condenado a cadena perpetua por corrupción y espionaje en un juicio rodeado de secretismo","Who is Alejandro Gil, the former Cuban economy minister sentenced to life imprisonment for corruption and espionage in a trial surrounded by secrecy",0.0,"[('Alejandro Gil', 'PERSON'), ('Cuban', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El experimento de dar una paga a más de 100 millones de mujeres por su trabajo como amas de casa (y los resultados que arroja),The experiment of paying more than 100 million women for their work as housewives (and the results it shows),0.5,"[('more than 100 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los secretos de un peligroso río de la Amazonía que una comunidad indígena empieza a revelar,The secrets of a dangerous river in the Amazon that an indigenous community begins to reveal,-0.6,"[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,गोवा नाइट क्लब हादसा: अभियुक्त लूथरा ब्रदर्स को थाईलैंड से भारत लाना कितना चुनौतीपूर्ण?,Goa Night Club Incident: How challenging is it to bring accused Luthra Brothers from Thailand to India?,0.5,"[('Goa Night Club Incident', 'ORG'), ('Luthra Brothers', 'ORG'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,दीपावली को यूनेस्को ने धरोहरों की इस सूची में किया शामिल","Live, Diwali included in UNESCO's list of heritage sites",0.13636363636363635,"[('Diwali', 'NORP'), ('UNESCO', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'धुरंधर' में अक्षय खन्ना का निभाया किरदार रहमान डकैत असल ज़िंदगी में कितना ख़तरनाक था,"How dangerous was Dacoit Rahman, the character played by Akshay Khanna in 'Dhurandhar' in real life?",-0.19999999999999998,"[('Dacoit Rahman', 'PERSON'), ('Akshay Khanna', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,हार्दिक पांड्या और जसप्रीत बुमराह की 'सेंचुरी' की दक्षिण अफ्रीका पर जीत के बीच कैसी चर्चा,What kind of discussion is there between Hardik Pandya and Jasprit Bumrah's 'century' in the victory over South Africa?,0.6,"[('Hardik Pandya', 'PERSON'), (""Jasprit Bumrah's"", 'PERSON'), (""'century'"", 'DATE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'प्राइवेट पार्ट पकड़ना रेप नहीं', अदालत की ऐसी टिप्पणियों पर सख़्त सुप्रीम कोर्ट","'Holding private parts is not rape', Supreme Court is strict on such comments of the court",0.0,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'11 साल की मोहब्बत की जगह लोगों को हमारा रंग दिखा',"'Instead of 11 years of love, people saw our colors'",0.5,"[('11 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सीरिया: असद के जाने से राहें हुईं आसान लेकिन अब नई मुसीबतें सामने,Syria: Assad's departure made things easier but now new problems have emerged,0.13636363636363635,"[('Syria', 'GPE'), ('Assad', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'भारत किसी भ्रम में न रहे': पाकिस्तान सेना के प्रमुख आसिम मुनीर ने और क्या कहा?,'India should not be under any illusion': What else did Pakistan Army Chief Asim Munir say?,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan Army', 'ORG'), ('Asim Munir', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्या आप बच्चों को सोशल मीडिया से दूर रख सकते हैं? ऑस्ट्रेलिया में बैन से पहले ही बच्चों ने ढूंढ लिए नए रास्ते,Can you keep children away from social media? Children found new ways even before the ban in Australia,0.08484848484848484,"[('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Redução de penas que beneficia Bolsonaro e condenados pelo 8 de janeiro é aprovada após noite de confusão na Câmara,Reduction of sentences that benefits Bolsonaro and those convicted of January 8th is approved after a night of confusion in the Chamber,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('January 8th', 'DATE'), ('a night', 'TIME')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Deputado Glauber Braga ocupa Mesa Diretora da Câmara e é retirado à força pela Polícia Legislativa,Deputy Glauber Braga occupies the Board of Directors of the Chamber and is forcibly removed by the Legislative Police,0.5,"[('Glauber Braga', 'PERSON'), ('the Board of Directors', 'ORG'), ('Chamber', 'ORG'), ('the Legislative Police', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,PL da dosimetria pode colocar Bolsonaro em liberdade? Entenda o que está em jogo na votação da Câmara,Can dosimetry PL set Bolsonaro free? Understand what is at stake in the Chamber’s vote,0.4,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Chamber', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Flávio visita Bolsonaro na prisão e diz que candidatura à Presidência é 'irreversível', Duration 0,41","Video, Flávio visits Bolsonaro in prison and says that running for President is 'irreversible', Duration 0.41",0.0,"[('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('0.41', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os países e territórios do Caribe que estão ajudando os EUA nas operações militares contra barcos venezuelanos,The Caribbean countries and territories that are assisting the US in military operations against Venezuelan boats,-0.1,"[('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A escalada da tensão entre Venezuela e EUA, dia a dia: bombardeios no Caribe, porta-aviões e ameaça direta de ataque","The escalation of tension between Venezuela and the USA, day by day: bombings in the Caribbean, aircraft carriers and direct threat of attack",0.1,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O novo tratamento que vem salvando pacientes com leucemia: 'Ficção científica alguns anos atrás',The new treatment that has been saving leukemia patients: 'Science fiction a few years ago',-0.03181818181818183,"[(""a few years ago'"", 'DATE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que está por trás da disputa entre Netflix e Paramount pela Warner,What's behind the dispute between Netflix and Paramount over Warner,-0.4,"[('Netflix', 'ORG'), ('Paramount', 'ORG'), ('Warner', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que muda com as novas regras para tirar a CNH?,What changes with the new rules for obtaining a driver's license?,0.13636363636363635,[]
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Центр патриотов». Как в России вербовщики грабят завербованных,"""Center of Patriots"" How in Russia recruiters rob those recruited",-0.1,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Зеленский заявил о готовности к выборам в Украине и рассказал о деталях мирного плана по прекращению войны,Zelensky announced his readiness for elections in Ukraine and spoke about the details of the peace plan to end the war,0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский готов к «энергетическому перемирию» и выборам, обновленный мирный план Киев передаст США завтра","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky is ready for an “energy truce” and elections, Kyiv will hand over the updated peace plan to the US tomorrow",0.2,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Французские феминистки возмущены комментариями Брижит Макрон об активистках,French feminists outraged by Brigitte Macron's comments about activists,-0.45,"[('French', 'NORP'), (""Brigitte Macron's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Литва объявила режим чрезвычайной ситуации из-за шаров с контрабандой из Беларуси,Lithuania declared a state of emergency due to balloons containing contraband from Belarus,-0.125,"[('Lithuania', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Это довольно простое дело». Главный конструктор Fire Point — о создании «Фламинго» и об украинской баллистической ракете,"""It's a pretty simple matter."" The chief designer of Fire Point talks about the creation of Flamingo and the Ukrainian ballistic missile",0.125,"[('Fire Point', 'ORG'), ('Flamingo', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Австралии вступил в силу запрет на социальные сети для детей младше 16 лет,Australia bans social media for children under 16,0.03333333333333333,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('under 16', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Новейший метод генной терапии позволил британским врачам спасти пациентов от прежде неизлечимой формы лейкемии,A new gene therapy method has allowed British doctors to save patients from a previously incurable form of leukemia,-0.12121212121212122,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Возмущаются, но тихо». Как школьников и родителей в России вынуждают установить госмессенджер Max","“They are outraged, but quietly.” How schoolchildren and parents in Russia are forced to install the state messenger Max",-0.4000000000000001,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Max', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Под Иваново разбился военный Ан-22 — самый большой турбовинтовой самолет в мире,"A military An-22, the largest turboprop aircraft in the world, crashed near Ivanovo",0.0,"[('Ivanovo', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、欧州諸国は「衰退している」と　欧州首脳は「弱い」とも批判,"Trump says European countries are ""in decline"" and criticizes European leaders as ""weak""",-0.125,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイとカンボジアの衝突続く　アメリカは戦闘停止を要求,Clashes between Thailand and Cambodia continue; US calls for cessation of fighting,0.0,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ジャカルタのオフィスビルで火災、少なくとも22人死亡と警察　日本企業も入居,"At least 22 people killed in fire at office building in Jakarta, police say Japanese companies also moved in",-0.16666666666666666,"[('At least 22', 'CARDINAL'), ('Jakarta', 'GPE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏への「FIFA平和賞」授与、「政治的中立」の内規に違反と人権団体,"Human rights group says award of FIFA Peace Prize to Trump violates internal rule of ""political neutrality""",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,フランス首相、重要な社会保障予算案の採決で勝利　次は本予算案,French Prime Minister wins vote on important social security budget; next budget bill,0.14666666666666667,"[('French', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナでイギリス軍の一員が事故死,British military member dies in accident in Ukraine,-0.05,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 アサド政権の重圧が消えシリアは前より軽やかな印象、しかし今では新しい問題がある　BBC国際編集長,"[Commentary] With the pressure of the Assad regime gone, Syria feels lighter than before, but now there are new problems - BBC International Editor-in-Chief",0.06818181818181818,"[('Assad', 'PERSON'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('BBC International', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英仏独ウクライナの4首脳、ロンドンで会談　ゼレンスキー氏は領土問題に懸念,"Four leaders of Britain, France, Germany and Ukraine meet in London; Mr. Zelenskiy is concerned about territorial issues",0.0,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskiy', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,アサド政権崩壊から1年、シリアの人々が語る思い, 所要時間 1,41","Video, One year since the fall of the Assad regime, thoughts expressed by Syrian people, Duration 1,41",0.0,"[('One year', 'DATE'), ('Assad', 'PERSON'), ('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('1,41', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Kwanini Disemba 9 yameshindikana?,Protests in Tanzania: Why did December 9 fail?,-0.5,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('December 9', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Viongozi wa Ulaya ni dhaifu - Trump","Directly, European leaders are weak - Trump",-0.1875,"[('European', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kwa nini China na Urusi zinaonekana kumtenga Maduro, wakati huu akivutana na Marekani?","Why do China and Russia seem to isolate Maduro, this time he is fighting with the United States?",0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Salah kutimkia Saudi Arabia Januari,European football rumours: Salah to go to Saudi Arabia in January,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Salah', 'NORP'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('January', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hali ya usalama wa nchi ni shwari - Polisi Tanzania,The country's security situation is stable - Tanzania Police,0.0,[]
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mataifa gani yanapigiwa chapuo kubeba kombe la dunia 2026?,Which countries are being beaten to carry the 2026 world cup?,0.0,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Maandamano Tanzania: Disemba 9 yaanza kwa utulivu, ulinzi ukiimarishwa","Protests in Tanzania: December 9 begins quietly, security being strengthened",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('December 9', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mwaka mmoja bila Assad na Putin. Ni viongozi gani wanaoongoza Syria na nini kitatokea baadaye?,One year without Assad and Putin. Who are the leaders of Syria and what will happen next?,0.0,"[('One year', 'DATE'), ('Assad', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Syria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Mapinduzi yaliyofeli nchini Benin: Je, kiongozi wa putsch ni nani?",The failed coup in Benin: Who is the leader of the putsch?,-0.5,"[('Benin', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Siasa za Afrika upinzani au uadui?,African politics opposition or hostility?,0.0,"[('African', 'NORP')]"
