Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué el declive de población deja al descubierto las antiguas divisiones de Alemania,Why population decline exposes Germany's ancient divisions,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Ya no quiero ser pediatra. La mirada de esos niños se queda con uno para siempre"": el dolor de los médicos que asisten a los heridos del terremoto en Venezuela","""I no longer want to be a pediatrician. The look of those children stays with you forever"": the pain of the doctors who assist those injured in the earthquake in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,España alcanza las segundas semifinales del Mundial de su historia y habrá choque estelar con Francia,Spain reaches the second World Cup semi-finals in its history and there will be a stellar clash with France,0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Llevamos el almuerzo al trabajo durante 10 años y pudimos jubilarnos a los 35 y 40 años""","""We brought lunch to work for 10 years and were able to retire at ages 35 and 40""",0.0,neutral,"[('10 years', 'DATE'), ('ages 35 and 40', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Cuál es el origen del ""tacofredag"", la tradición noruega de comer tacos los viernes","What is the origin of ""tacofredag"", the Norwegian tradition of eating tacos on Fridays?",0.0,neutral,"[('Norwegian', 'NORP'), ('Fridays', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Mikel Merino, el héroe de la Roja que con otro gol in extremis metió a España en las semifinales del Mundial 2026","Mikel Merino, the hero of La Roja who with another goal in extremis put Spain in the semifinals of the 2026 World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('Merino', 'PERSON'), ('La Roja', 'FAC'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Al menos 12 muertos y 23 desaparecidos en el incendio más letal de las últimas décadas en España en medio de la ola de calor,At least 12 dead and 23 missing in the deadliest fire in recent decades in Spain amid the heat wave,0.0,neutral,"[('At least 12', 'CARDINAL'), ('23', 'CARDINAL'), ('recent decades', 'DATE'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La ""transformación milagrosa"" de Corea del Norte: cómo logró Kim Jong-un paliar la situación económica de su país","The ""miraculous transformation"" of North Korea: how Kim Jong-un managed to alleviate the economic situation of his country",0.0,neutral,"[('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quién es Lise Klaveness, la dirigente del exitoso fútbol de Noruega que critica a la FIFA, Trump e Israel","Who is Lise Klaveness, the leader of Norway's successful soccer team who criticizes FIFA, Trump and Israel",1.0,positive,"[('Lise Klaveness', 'PERSON'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La locura de los argentinos por las ""cábalas"", los rituales con los que buscan traerle buena suerte a su equipo durante el Mundial","The Argentinians' madness for ""cabalas"", the rituals with which they seek to bring good luck to their team during the World Cup",1.0,positive,"[('Argentinians', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बांकीपुर उप चुनाव: बीजेपी उम्मीदवार के नाम वापस लेने के पीछे क्या ये वजह है,Bankipur by-election: Is this the reason behind withdrawal of name of BJP candidate?,0.0,neutral,"[('Bankipur', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वाई-फ़ाई स्लो है? घर में रखे माइक्रोवेव समेत ये 4 चीजें रोक सकती हैं स्पीड,Is Wi-Fi slow? These 4 things including microwave kept in the house can stop the speed,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,मध्य प्रदेश: नरोत्तम मिश्रा का टिकट कटने पर बोली कांग्रेस- बीजेपी यूज़ एंड थ्रो करती है","Live, Madhya Pradesh: On denial of ticket to Narottam Mishra, Congress said - BJP uses and throws.",0.0,neutral,"[('Narottam Mishra', 'PERSON'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"होर्मुज़ बना नाक का सवाल, ट्रंप ने कहा-ईरान ग़लती माने या नतीजा भुगतने के लिए तैयार रहे","Hormuz became a big issue, Trump said - Iran should accept its mistake or be ready to face the consequences.",0.0,neutral,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'बावी' से फिलीपींस में 15 लोगों की मौत, ताइवान-जापान में अलर्ट, किस-किस देश को ख़तरा","15 people died in Philippines due to 'Bavi', alert in Taiwan-Japan, which countries are in danger",0.0,neutral,"[('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('Bavi', 'PERSON'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बॉलीवुड अभिनेता राजपाल यादव को तीन महीने की जेल, कहा था- पांच बार जेल जाने को तैयार लेकिन एक पैसा भी नहीं देंगे","Bollywood actor Rajpal Yadav jailed for three months, had said - ready to go to jail five times but will not pay even a single penny",0.0,neutral,"[('Rajpal Yadav', 'PERSON'), ('three months', 'DATE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('a single penny', 'MONEY')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अली ख़ामेनेई : मौत के 132 दिन बाद क्यों दफ़नाया गया शव, देरी पर उठ रहे कैसे सवाल","Ali Khamenei: Why was the body buried 132 days after death, why questions are being raised on the delay",-1.0,negative,"[('Ali Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('132 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बांकीपुर उपचुनाव: बीजेपी उम्मीदवार के नाम वापस लेने पर क्या बोले प्रशांत किशोर,Bankipur by-election: What did Prashant Kishor say on withdrawal of name of BJP candidate?,0.0,neutral,"[('Bankipur', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"दिल्ली में यमुना किनारे क्यों चले बुलडोज़र, क्या आगे और भी इलाक़े आएंगे ज़द में?: ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट","Why did bulldozers run on the banks of Yamuna in Delhi, will more areas be affected in the future?: Ground report",0.0,neutral,"[('Yamuna', 'GPE'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Ground', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भारत अपना अहम हथियार ब्रह्मोस कई देशों को क्यों बेच रहा है, क्या रूस की परमिशन ज़रूरी है?","Why is India selling its important weapon BrahMos to many countries, is Russia's permission necessary?",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('BrahMos', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Quantos bilhões custará reconstruir a Venezuela após terremotos, e quem pagará a conta?","How many billions will it cost to rebuild Venezuela after earthquakes, and who will foot the bill?",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que PF e Flávio Dino apontam presidente do PL como suspeito de indicar emendas irregularmente,Why PF and Flávio Dino point to PL president as suspected of irregularly indicating amendments,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Dino', 'PERSON'), ('PL', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como profissionais de IA estão inflacionando os imóveis na Califórnia - e expulsando famílias de suas casas,How AI Pros Are Inflating California Real Estate — and Evicting Families From Their Homes,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Haaland: nascido na Inglaterra, artilheiro da Noruega está prestes a ver 'seus mundos colidirem'","Haaland: England-born, Norway's top scorer is about to see 'his worlds collide'",0.0,neutral,"[('Haaland', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A Copa dos pênaltis perdidos — a 'paradinha' virou um problema?,The World Cup of missed penalties — did the 'break' become a problem?,0.0,neutral,"[('The World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que 'Moana' em live-action foi duramente criticado por especialistas: 'Poderia ter sido IA',Why live-action 'Moana' was harshly criticized by experts: 'It could have been AI',0.0,neutral,"[('Moana', 'PERSON'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Produtora de filme sobre Bolsonaro funcionava em casa de sócio em subúrbio dos Estados Unidos,Film production company about Bolsonaro operated out of a partner's house in a suburb of the United States,0.0,neutral,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Espanha bate Bélgica e enfrenta França na semifinal — como De la Fuente criou uma seleção quase imbatível,Spain beats Belgium and faces France in the semi-final – how De la Fuente created an almost unbeatable team,0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('De la Fuente', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Regina Casé encara os haters: 'Tem períodos mais difíceis, outros melhoram, e a gente vai lidando'","Regina Casé faces the haters: 'There are more difficult periods, others get better, and we cope'",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_11,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A sangrenta imagem de 1770 que alimentou a Independência dos EUA,The bloody image of 1770 that fueled US Independence,0.0,neutral,"[('1770', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Викинг против англосакса: Эрлинг Холанд и Гарри Кейн выводят Норвегию и Англию на решающий бой,Viking vs Anglo-Saxon: Erling Haaland and Harry Kane lead Norway and England to decisive battle,0.0,neutral,"[('Harry Kane', 'PERSON'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Россия атаковала Киев баллистическими ракетами; среди пострадавших — 11-летний мальчик, сообщил Кличко","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Russia attacks Kyiv with ballistic missiles; Among the victims is an 11-year-old boy, Klitschko said.",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('11-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Klitschko', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп заявил о готовности нанести ракетный удар по Ирану в случае покушения на него,Trump announced his readiness to launch a missile strike on Iran in the event of an assassination attempt,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Анализ: как долго Россия сможет обстреливать столицу Украины баллистическими ракетами?,Analysis: How long can Russia bombard the Ukrainian capital with ballistic missiles?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Испания обыграла Бельгию и вышла в полуфинал чемпионата мира по футболу,Spain beat Belgium to reach the World Cup semi-finals,0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Принц Гарри все же привез семью в Англию. Король Карл повидал младших внуков,Prince Harry still brought his family to England. King Charles met his younger grandchildren,0.0,neutral,"[('Harry', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('King Charles', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Жара в Европе: погибшие и пропавшие без вести в Испании, обширные пожары, тысячи эвакуированных","Heat in Europe: dead and missing in Spain, extensive fires, thousands of evacuees",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Пассажира Ryanair чуть не засосало в иллюминатор во время полета. Что произошло?,A Ryanair passenger was nearly sucked out of a window during a flight. What happened?,1.0,positive,"[('Ryanair', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,СМИ: Китай впервые успешно вернул на Землю многоразовую ракету. Что это значит для глобальной космической гонки?,Media: China successfully returned a reusable rocket to Earth for the first time. What does this mean for the global space race?,1.0,positive,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Earth', 'LOC'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Историческое возвращение: гобелен из Байё привезли в Великобританию впервые за почти тысячу лет,Historic return: Bayeux Tapestry brought to Britain for the first time in almost a thousand years,0.0,neutral,"[('Bayeux Tapestry', 'ORG'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('almost a thousand years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、ホルムズ海峡での船舶攻撃の停止を誓うようイランに要求,US asks Iran to pledge to stop attacking ships in Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米移民当局ICE、テキサスで出勤途中の男性を射殺　取締作戦の対象者ではなかったと国土安全保障省,US immigration agency ICE fatally shoots man on his way to work in Texas; Department of Homeland Security says he was not the target of an enforcement operation,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('Department of Homeland Security', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 スペイン、ベルギー破りベスト4　メリノが土壇場決勝ゴール,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Spain defeats Belgium in the final four; Merino scores last-minute winning goal,1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Merino', 'PERSON'), ('last-minute', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米アップル、オープンAIと従業員を提訴　企業秘密を盗んだと主張,"Apple sues OpenAI and employees, claiming they stole trade secrets",0.0,neutral,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('OpenAI', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,スペイン、山火事で12人死亡　南欧で熱波続く,12 people killed in wildfires in Spain; heatwave continues in southern Europe,-1.0,negative,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、クリミア沖で燃料輸送中のロシア船を攻撃　燃料供給網への攻撃強化,"Ukraine attacks a Russian ship transporting fuel off the coast of Crimea, intensifying attacks on the fuel supply network",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Crimea', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,バーナム氏、次のイギリス首相になる見通し　労働党議員322人が党首指名投票で支持,Burnham expected to become the next British Prime Minister; 322 Labor Party MPs support him in leadership nomination vote,0.0,neutral,"[('Burnham', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('322', 'CARDINAL'), ('Labor Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ガザでW杯観戦会を開催の活動家、イスラエル軍に殺される　パレスチナ人から悼む声,Activist holding World Cup watching party in Gaza killed by Israeli army; voices of mourning from Palestinians,-1.0,negative,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英野党ファラージ党首の議員辞職に伴う補欠選挙の実施確定　主要政党はボイコット表明,By-election confirmed following UK opposition leader Farage's resignation as MP; major political parties announce boycott,1.0,positive,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Farage', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,イギリスの選挙常連候補「顔がごみ箱伯爵」とは？　補選でファラージ氏に挑戦, 所要時間 0,48","Video, Who is the regular British election candidate, ``The Count of the Garbage Can''? Challenging Mr. Farage in by-election, time required 0,48",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), (""The Count of the Garbage Can''"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Farage', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yaitaka Iran kusitisha mashambulizi katika mlango bahari wa Hormuz","Directly, the United States wants Iran to stop attacks in the Strait of Hormuz",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tunafanya mazungumzo na Iran ila usitishaji mapigano umefutiliwa mbali - Trump,We are negotiating with Iran but the ceasefire has been scrapped - Trump,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Uturuki iliwazawadia viongozi wa NATO bastola zenye risasi sita?,Why did Turkey reward NATO leaders with six-shot pistols?,-1.0,negative,"[('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('six', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"VAR ni nini, na kwa nini inaleta utata mkubwa katika Kombe la Dunia?","What is VAR, and why is it so controversial in the World Cup?",0.0,neutral,"[('VAR', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Zifahamu tawala 10 za kimabavu Afrika,Know the 10 authoritarian regimes in Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Majengo 10 marefu zaidi Afrika Mashariki 2026,10 tallest buildings in East Africa 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('East Africa', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vita vya Ukraine vilivyobadili uhusiano kati ya Putin na matajiri wa Urusi,The war in Ukraine changed the relationship between Putin and Russia's rich,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Mbappe, Dembele waiongoza Ufaransa kwenye nusu fainali ya Kombe la Dunia","Mbappe, Dembele lead France to the semi-finals of the World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Hali iko vipi katika miji mitano yenye ubora wa juu wa maisha 2026?,How is the situation in the five cities with the highest quality of life in 2026?,0.0,neutral,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Tottenham yawasilisha ombi la kumsajili Randal Kolo Muani,European football rumors Friday: Tottenham submit a request to sign Randal Kolo Muani,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Tottenham', 'ORG'), ('Randal Kolo Muani', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Indonesia’s anti-graft prosecutor quits after police seize gold and cash,Indonesia’s anti-graft prosecutor quits after police seize gold and cash,0.0,neutral,"[('Indonesia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Sealed in blood’: Where does the China-North Korea alliance stand today?,‘Sealed in blood’: Where does the China-North Korea alliance stand today?,0.0,neutral,"[('the China-North Korea', 'FAC'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Trump threatens Iran after chants for his death erupted at Khamenei funeral,Trump threatens Iran after chants for his death erupted at Khamenei funeral,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Report: Spurs sign Victor Wembanyama for 5 years, $252M in NBA","Report: Spurs sign Victor Wembanyama for 5 years, $252M in NBA",0.0,neutral,"[('Victor Wembanyama', 'PERSON'), ('5 years', 'DATE'), ('$252M', 'MONEY'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup Day 31: What to know as Haaland, Kane and Messi chase the semis","World Cup Day 31: What to know as Haaland, Kane and Messi chase the semis",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day', 'EVENT'), ('31', 'CARDINAL'), ('Haaland', 'GPE'), ('Kane', 'PERSON'), ('Messi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Eyes on the prize: Can stuttering Argentina get past Switzerland?,Eyes on the prize: Can stuttering Argentina get past Switzerland?,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Venezuelan doctors convert restaurant into a clinic after earthquake,Venezuelan doctors convert restaurant into a clinic after earthquake,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Meta backtracks on AI-image feature for Instagram due to privacy backlash,Meta backtracks on AI-image feature for Instagram due to privacy backlash,0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('Instagram', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Argentina’s Scaloni: Messi will be the best as long as he wants to be,Argentina’s Scaloni: Messi will be the best as long as he wants to be,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Messi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘We are the lost generation of Sudan’: Students in exile,‘We are the lost generation of Sudan’: Students in exile,0.0,neutral,"[('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Wildflower season is here: From Kaas Plateau to Dzukou Valley, where to trek this season","Wildflower season is here: From Kaas Plateau to Dzukou Valley, where to trek this season",0.0,neutral,"[('Kaas Plateau', 'PERSON'), ('Dzukou Valley', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The uncertain flight of Parandur airport,The uncertain flight of Parandur airport,0.0,neutral,"[('Parandur', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Where to eat in Boston before the FIFA World Cup 2026 quarterfinal,Where to eat in Boston before the FIFA World Cup 2026 quarterfinal,0.0,neutral,"[('Boston', 'GPE'), ('the FIFA World Cup 2026', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Death of 14 Juang girls from Odisha in TN ammonia gas leak exposes tribe’s socio-economic struggle,Death of 14 Juang girls from Odisha in TN ammonia gas leak exposes tribe’s socio-economic struggle,-1.0,negative,"[('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('Odisha', 'GPE'), ('TN', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Balcony design trends: How outdoor spaces are becoming extensions of home,Balcony design trends: How outdoor spaces are becoming extensions of home,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"'India-NZ Waka' ready to embark on new voyage together, says Modi at diaspora event | LIVE","'India-NZ Waka' ready to embark on new voyage together, says Modi at diaspora event | LIVE",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Modi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"UN Special Rapporteurs raise concerns over SIR, use of AI-driven models for exclusion of minorities","UN Special Rapporteurs raise concerns over SIR, use of AI-driven models for exclusion of minorities",0.0,neutral,"[('UN Special Rapporteurs', 'ORG'), ('SIR', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,A future of financial health for every Indian,A future of financial health for every Indian,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Born in Sri Lanka, brought up in India, residing in the US: IT employee faces threat of being declared ‘stateless’","Born in Sri Lanka, brought up in India, residing in the US: IT employee faces threat of being declared ‘stateless’",0.0,neutral,"[('Sri Lanka', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Datia byelection: Narottam Mishra's supporters clash with M.P. Police, block highway after BJP ticket snub","Datia byelection: Narottam Mishra's supporters clash with M.P. Police, block highway after BJP ticket snub",0.0,neutral,"[(""Narottam Mishra's"", 'PERSON'), ('M.P. Police', 'ORG'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US wants Iran to pledge to stop shooting at ships in Strait of Hormuz,US wants Iran to pledge to stop shooting at ships in Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Spain battles to contain one of its deadliest wildfires as at least 12 killed,Spain battles to contain one of its deadliest wildfires as at least 12 killed,-1.0,negative,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('at least 12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Meet the crypto billionaires building a world where money buys you a vote,Meet the crypto billionaires building a world where money buys you a vote,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,East Asia braces for destructive typhoon as landslides kill 15 in Philippines,East Asia braces for destructive typhoon as landslides kill 15 in Philippines,-1.0,negative,"[('East Asia', 'LOC'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,The photo that shows who's really on top in Le Pen's party,The photo that shows who's really on top in Le Pen's party,0.0,neutral,"[(""Le Pen's"", 'FAC')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Apple sues OpenAI, its employees claiming theft of trade secrets","Apple sues OpenAI, its employees claiming theft of trade secrets",0.0,neutral,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('OpenAI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,New dinosaur species as long as cricket pitch discovered in Thailand,New dinosaur species as long as cricket pitch discovered in Thailand,0.0,neutral,"[('Thailand', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Russia trains sights on schools, offices and buses in busy Ukrainian city","Russia trains sights on schools, offices and buses in busy Ukrainian city",0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Meta pulls new AI image feature after days of backlash,Meta pulls new AI image feature after days of backlash,0.0,neutral,"[('Meta', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'GPE'), ('days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_11,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Small plane crash in Bahamas kills 10 people,Small plane crash in Bahamas kills 10 people,-1.0,negative,"[('Bahamas', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Israel Struck an Iranian Steel Facility. Was It a Valid Military Target?,Israel Struck an Iranian Steel Facility. Was It a Valid Military Target?,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel Struck', 'PERSON'), ('an Iranian Steel Facility', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Man Arrested in Killing of U.K. Ex-Lawmaker Is Released,Man Arrested in Killing of U.K. Ex-Lawmaker Is Released,-1.0,negative,"[('Killing', 'GPE'), ('U.K. Ex-Lawmaker Is Released', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"England and Norway, Old Friends, Resurrect a Rivalry for the World Cup","England and Norway, Old Friends, Resurrect a Rivalry for the World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Old Friends', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘They Don’t Need People’: The Workers Left Behind by China’s Robot Drive,‘They Don’t Need People’: The Workers Left Behind by China’s Robot Drive,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Citizen Tests Positive for Ebola in Democratic Republic of Congo,U.S. Citizen Tests Positive for Ebola in Democratic Republic of Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Democratic Republic of Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"After Being Delayed by Trump, a Canada-U.S. Bridge is Set to Open","After Being Delayed by Trump, a Canada-U.S. Bridge is Set to Open",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iran’s Supreme Leader Remains Absent, a Void at the Top of the Regime","Iran’s Supreme Leader Remains Absent, a Void at the Top of the Regime",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Remains Absent', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,At Least 12 People Die in Southern Spain Wildfire,At Least 12 People Die in Southern Spain Wildfire,0.0,neutral,"[('At Least 12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"After Venezuela Earthquakes, a Youth Baseball League Counts the Dead","After Venezuela Earthquakes, a Youth Baseball League Counts the Dead",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela Earthquakes', 'PERSON'), ('Youth Baseball League Counts the Dead', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_11,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Moscow Still Has Art and Culture. Just Don’t Say ‘Ukraine.’,Moscow Still Has Art and Culture. Just Don’t Say ‘Ukraine.’,0.0,neutral,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
