Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Hogares reducidos a escombros y precios exorbitantes: así es la vida de dos mujeres gazatíes a un mes del cese el fuego con Israel,Homes reduced to rubble and exorbitant prices: this is the life of two Gazan women one month after the ceasefire with Israel,0.0,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gazan', 'GPE'), ('one month', 'DATE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Chile está extremadamente atemorizado. Pero está lejos de ser el país con el mayor problema por crimen y violencia""","""Chile is extremely frightened. But it is far from being the country with the biggest problem with crime and violence""",-0.012499999999999997,"[('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,USS Gerald R. Ford: el mayor buque de guerra del mundo se une al despliegue de EE.UU. en el Caribe y Maduro eleva la alerta militar en Venezuela,USS Gerald R. Ford: the largest warship in the world joins the US deployment in the Caribbean and Maduro raises the military alert in Venezuela,-0.1,"[('USS Gerald R. Ford', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"¿Por qué el Papa quiere ""corregir"" la devoción a la virgen María, la madre de Jesús?","Why does the Pope want to ""correct"" devotion to the Virgin Mary, the mother of Jesus?",0.0,"[('the Virgin Mary', 'GPE'), ('Jesus', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Me perdonó la vida"": el impresionante relato del mexicano que sobrevivió a la mordida de un tiburón en la cabeza","""He forgave my life"": the impressive story of the Mexican who survived a shark bite on the head",0.5,"[('Mexican', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अफ़ग़ानिस्तान से भागी 'बालिका वधू' यूरोप में कैसे बन गई बॉडीबिल्डिंग चैंपियन,How a 'girl bride' who fled from Afghanistan became a bodybuilding champion in Europe,0.0,"[('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दिल्ली में धमाके से पहले गिरफ़्तार हुए तीन डॉक्टरों के बारे में अब तक क्या पता है?,What is known so far about the three doctors arrested before the Delhi blasts?,0.1,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,तुर्की का सैन्य कार्गो प्लेन क्रैश, कम से कम 20 लोग सवार थे","Live, Turkish military cargo plane crashes, at least 20 people were on board",-0.08787878787878789,"[('Turkish', 'NORP'), ('at least 20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"धर्मेंद्र को अस्पताल से घर ले जाया गया, डॉक्टर ने और क्या-क्या बताया","Dharmendra was taken home from the hospital, what else did the doctor tell?",0.0,"[('Dharmendra', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,एग्ज़िट पोल: बिहार में किसकी बन सकती है सरकार,Exit Poll: Who can form the government in Bihar?,0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"गोविंदा की तबीयत बिगड़ी, अस्पताल में भर्ती कराया गया","Govinda's health deteriorated, admitted to hospital",0.0,"[('Govinda', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बाग़ी से व्हाइट हाउस तक: सीरिया के राष्ट्रपति अहमद अल-शरा की नई पहचान,From rebel to White House: The new identity of Syrian President Ahmed al-Sharaa,0.06818181818181818,"[('White House', 'ORG'), ('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('Ahmed al-Sharaa', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,धर्मेंद्र ने जब बीबीसी से कहा था, ""मैं मिट्टी का बेटा हूँ, अपनी जड़ों से दूर नहीं हो सकता"", अवधि 5,54","Video, When Dharmendra told BBC, ""I am a son of the soil, I cannot move away from my roots"", duration 5,54",0.0,"[('Dharmendra', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('5,54', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इस्लामाबाद कोर्ट धमाके में 12 की मौत, शहबाज़ शरीफ़ ने भारत पर लगाया यह आरोप","12 killed in Islamabad court blast, Shehbaz Sharif blames India for this",-0.2,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Islamabad', 'GPE'), ('Shehbaz Sharif', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que imposto sobre bets é mais baixo no Brasil do que em outros países,Why tax on bets is lower in Brazil than in other countries,-0.125,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,COP30: manifestantes entram em confronto com seguranças da ONU em Belém,COP30: protesters clash with UN security guards in Belém,0.0,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Belém', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O Brasil está à beira de se tornar um narcoestado?,Is Brazil on the verge of becoming a narcostate?,0.45,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Rainha das criptomoedas: a chinesa acusada de fraude que fugiu para mansão em Londres,Queen of cryptocurrencies: the Chinese woman accused of fraud who fled to a mansion in London,0.0,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem é Derrite, ex-secretário de Tarcísio à frente de projeto contra facções que pode mexer com a PF","Who is Derrite, Tarcísio's former secretary heading a project against factions that could affect the PF",0.0,"[('Derrite', 'PERSON'), ('Tarcísio', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump ameaça processar a BBC em US$ 1 bilhão por edição de discurso em documentário,Trump threatens to sue BBC for $1 billion over editing speech in documentary,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('$1 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Eu queria que o ChatGPT me ajudasse. Por que ele me aconselhou a me matar?','I wanted ChatGPT to help me. Why did he advise me to kill myself?',0.0,[]
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O Nobel que caiu em desgraça por defender que negros são menos inteligentes sem respaldo científico,The Nobel laureate who fell into disgrace for arguing that black people are less intelligent without scientific support,0.15555555555555559,"[('Nobel', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Bandido bom é bandido morto': a origem da expressão e como ela se popularizou,'A good criminal is a dead criminal': the origin of the expression and how it became popular,0.05999999999999998,[]
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Карлсон» и его «Шлагбаум». Кто такой Тимур Миндич и что нужно знать о коррупционном скандале в окружении Зеленского,"""Carlson"" and his ""Barrier"". Who is Timur Mindich and what you need to know about the corruption scandal surrounding Zelensky",0.0,"[('Barrier', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Timur Mindich', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: дроны второй раз за две недели атаковали ставропольский Буденновск","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: drones attacked Stavropol Budennovsk for the second time in two weeks",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Stavropol', 'GPE'), ('Budennovsk', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('two weeks', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Деньгами не наешься». Представители коренных народов  Амазонии прорвались на климатический саммит в Бразилии, требуя остановить вырубку лесов","“You can’t get enough of money.” Representatives of indigenous peoples of the Amazon stormed the climate summit in Brazil, demanding a stop to deforestation",0.0,"[('Amazon', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Противостояние США и Венесуэлы: авианосная группа американского ВМФ прибыла в Карибское море,Confrontation between the USA and Venezuela: an aircraft carrier group of the US Navy arrived in the Caribbean Sea,0.0,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the US Navy', 'ORG'), ('the Caribbean Sea', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Грузии разбился турецкий самолет C-130, летевший из Азербайджана, погибли 20 военнослужащих","A Turkish C-130 plane flying from Azerbaijan crashed in Georgia, killing 20 servicemen",0.0,"[('Turkish', 'NORP'), ('Azerbaijan', 'GPE'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,5 млрд фунтов в биткоинах. Бежавшая в Лондон с деньгами китайских пенсионеров криптокоролева получила почти 12 лет тюрьмы,£5 billion in Bitcoin. The crypto queen who fled to London with the money of Chinese pensioners received almost 12 years in prison,0.0,"[('£5 billion', 'MONEY'), ('Bitcoin', 'NORP'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('almost 12 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Австралии нашли пчелу с рогами — и назвали ее Люцифером,A bee with horns was found in Australia and they named it Lucifer,0.0,"[('bee', 'ORG'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Lucifer', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Разрушенные дома и заоблачные цены. Жители Газы рассказывают о жизни в первый месяц перемирия,Destroyed houses and sky-high prices. Gaza residents talk about life in the first month of the truce,0.25,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('the first month', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Из уличных музыкантов в политзэки. Участников «Стоптайм» в Петербурге арестовали в третий раз,From street musicians to political prisoners. Stoptime participants in St. Petersburg were arrested for the third time,0.0,"[('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что такое технологический сбор и как он скажется на экономике России. Объясняем в 100 и 500 словах,What is a technological fee and how will it affect the Russian economy. We explain in 100 and 500 words,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('500', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英与党でスターマー首相下ろしの動き　「首相は対抗する」と支持者ら,Britain's ruling party moves to remove Prime Minister Starmer; supporters say ``the Prime Minister will fight back'',0.0,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,辞任表明のBBC会長、BBC報道の意義強調　下院では与野党の意見割れる, 所要時間 3,18","Video, BBC chairman announces resignation, emphasizes significance of BBC reporting, ruling and opposition parties are divided in the House of Commons, Duration 3,18",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('the House of Commons, Duration', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,BBCは信頼回復のために「奮闘しなくてはならない」と英文化相　トランプ氏演説映像の編集問題で,"BBC must 'fight' to restore trust, says UK Culture Secretary over editing issue with footage of Trump's speech",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,【解説】BBCの危機は今に始まったものではない、トランプ氏の演説編集めぐりトップ辞任, 所要時間 4,44","Video, [Commentary] The crisis at the BBC is not new; the top official resigns over Trump's speech editing, Duration 4,44",0.2159090909090909,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,COP30、ブラジルで始まる　2日目に抗議者らが会場へと乱入,"COP30 begins in Brazil, protesters storm venue on second day",0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('second day', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,パキスタン首都で自動車爆発、自爆攻撃で12人死亡と内相,"12 killed in car explosion and suicide bomb attack in Pakistan's capital, interior minister says",-0.2,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 高市首相の台湾をめぐる発言、なぜ中国を怒らせたのか,[Commentary] Why did Prime Minister Takaichi's comments regarding Taiwan anger China?,-0.7,"[('Takaichi', 'PERSON'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インド・デリーの世界遺産近くで車両が爆発、少なくとも8人死亡,"At least 8 people killed in car explosion near world heritage site in Delhi, India",-0.13333333333333333,"[('At least 8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ルーヴル美術館の盗難事件、謎の「ソフト帽の男」が話題に　探偵ファンの10代と判明,"The mysterious ``man in a fedora'' becomes a hot topic after the Louvre Museum theft incident, revealed to be a teenager who is a detective fan",0.125,"[('the Louvre Museum', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tanzania inahitaji maridhaino ya aina gani?,What kind of approval does Tanzania need?,0.6,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Wanajeshi wa Marekani wawasili katika visiwa Caribbean","Directly, American soldiers arrive in the Caribbean islands",0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Trump dhidi ya BBC: Je, ni vikwazo gani vinavyokabili kesi ya rais huyo?",Trump vs. BBC: What are the obstacles facing the president's case?,-0.05,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Vilabu vinne vinamfukuzia Myles Lewis-Skelly,European football rumours: Four clubs are chasing Myles Lewis-Skelly,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Myles Lewis-Skelly', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Umoja wa Mataifa waitaka Tanzania kuchunguza mauaji ya siku ya uchaguzi,The United Nations wants Tanzania to investigate the election day killings,0.2,"[('The United Nations', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('the election day', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Ahmed Sharia Ikulu; Je, wanajeshi wa Marekani kuelekea Damascus?",Ahmed Sharia Palace; Are American troops heading to Damascus?,0.0,"[('Ahmed Sharia Palace', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Damascus', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"""Kazi yetu ni kuua tu""","""Our job is just to kill""",0.0,[]
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Zungu Spika Mpya wa Bunge la Tanzania,Zungu is the new Speaker of the Parliament of Tanzania,0.13636363636363635,"[('Zungu', 'ORG'), ('the Parliament of Tanzania', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mfahamu Mussa Azzan Zungu,Know Mussa Azzan Zungu,0.0,[]
2025_11_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Rais Samia anatupiwa lawama?,Why is President Samia being blamed?,0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
