Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La estrecha relación forjada por Trump y Gianni Infantino que cuestiona la neutralidad política de la FIFA antes del Mundial,The close relationship forged by Trump and Gianni Infantino that questions the political neutrality of FIFA before the World Cup,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gianni Infantino', 'PERSON'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo logró Perú convertir uno de los desiertos más áridos del mundo en un gran centro de producción de alimentos,How Peru managed to turn one of the driest deserts in the world into a major food production center,-0.018750000000000003,"[('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué ha pasado en Gaza desde el alto el fuego (y por qué el conflicto no ha terminado),What has happened in Gaza since the ceasefire (and why the conflict is not over),0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es ""Rosita"", la DJ e influencer venezolana a la que EE.UU. y México sancionaron por sus presuntos vínculos con el Tren de Aragua","Who is ""Rosita"", the Venezuelan DJ and influencer whom the US and Mexico sanctioned for her alleged links with the Aragua Train",-0.1,"[('Rosita', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('the Aragua Train', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Las imágenes inéditas de la isla privada en el Caribe en la que Jeffrey Epstein cometió sus crímenes sexuales,The unpublished images of the private island in the Caribbean where Jeffrey Epstein committed his sexual crimes,0.25,"[('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('Jeffrey Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुतिन के भारत दौरे को चीन कैसे देख रहा है?,How is China viewing Putin's visit to India?,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'उन्हें गंदे पैंट वाली बात नहीं कहना चाहिए थी', जया बच्चन के बयान पर पैपराज़ी बिरादरी में ग़ुस्सा","'She should not have said the dirty pants thing', paparazzi fraternity angry over Jaya Bachchan's statement",-0.55,"[(""Jaya Bachchan's"", 'FAC')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,पीएम मोदी ने राष्ट्रपति पुतिन की यात्रा को इसलिए 'ऐतिहासिक' बताया","Live, PM Modi called President Putin's visit 'historic'",0.06818181818181818,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पुतिन की दो बेटियां कौन हैं, उनके परिवार के बारे में हम क्या जानते हैं?","Who are Putin's two daughters, what do we know about their family?",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'भारत ख़ुशकिस्मत है कि उन्हें मोदी जैसा नेता मिला': व्लादिमीर पुतिन,'India is lucky to have a leader like Modi': Vladimir Putin,0.3333333333333333,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Modi', 'PERSON'), ('Vladimir Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"अयोध्याः राम मंदिर का निर्माण पूरा, लेकिन जहां मस्जिद बननी थी वहां क्या हाल है?","Ayodhya: Construction of Ram temple completed, but what is the condition where the mosque was to be built?",0.0,[]
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्या दिल्ली हवाई अड्डे पर जीपीएस स्पूफिंग 'साइबर' हमला था?,Was GPS spoofing a 'cyber' attack on Delhi airport?,0.0,"[('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दिल्ली पहुंचे रूसी राष्ट्रपति पुतिन, पीएम मोदी ने गले लगाकर किया स्वागत","Russian President Putin reached Delhi, PM Modi welcomed him with a hug",0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('PM Modi', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत के ये परिवार रूस से क्या उम्मीद लगाए बैठे हैं?,What are these Indian families expecting from Russia?,0.0,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quem são os foragidos do 8 de janeiro que podem ser extraditados da Argentina?,Who are the January 8 fugitives who could be extradited from Argentina?,0.0,"[('January 8', 'DATE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Gilmar Mendes: o que diz cada lado em crise sobre mudança em impeachment de ministros do STF,Gilmar Mendes: what each side in crisis says about changes in impeachment of STF ministers,0.0,"[('Gilmar Mendes', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Freada na economia do Brasil pode ser positiva?,Can braking in Brazil's economy be positive?,0.22727272727272727,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que se sabe sobre as acusações contra Lulinha na CPMI do INSS,What is known about the accusations against Lulinha at the INSS CPMI,0.0,"[('the INSS CPMI', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que nossas fotos da lua geralmente ficam horríveis,Why Our Moon Photos Often Look Horrible,-1.0,[]
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como será o sorteio da Copa do Mundo de 2026 e quem são os possíveis adversários do Brasil,What will be the draw for the 2026 World Cup and who are Brazil's possible opponents,0.0,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"TCP e CV em expansão, recuo das milícias: o novo retrato do crime organizado no Rio","TCP and CV expanding, militias retreating: the new portrait of organized crime in Rio",0.13636363636363635,"[('TCP', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'GPE'), ('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O mofo preto de Chernobyl que parece 'se alimentar de radiação',Chernobyl's black mold that appears to 'feed on radiation',-0.16666666666666666,"[('Chernobyl', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A nova orientação do papa sobre sexo no casamento,The pope's new guidance on sex in marriage,0.13636363636363635,[]
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Вязки». Как принудительная фиксация в российской психиатрии калечит и убивает,"""Matings."" How forced fixation in Russian psychiatry maims and kills",-0.15000000000000002,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Умеров снова проводит переговоры в США; украинские дроны повредили порт в Темрюке","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Umerov holds talks in the USA again; Ukrainian drones damaged the port in Temryuk",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Temryuk', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сергей Тихановский недоволен офисом своей жены. Белорусы не верят в демократическое будущее. Главное в Беларуси за неделю,Sergei Tikhanovsky is dissatisfied with his wife’s office. Belarusians do not believe in a democratic future. The main things in Belarus in a week,0.08333333333333333,"[('Sergei Tikhanovsky', 'PERSON'), ('Belarusians', 'NORP'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Ровно в тот момент». Ирландия расследует полет неизвестных дронов около маршрута самолета Зеленского,"""Exactly at that moment."" Ireland is investigating the flight of unknown drones near the route of Zelensky's plane",0.08333333333333333,"[('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Защита перебежчиков и охота на российских шпионов. Какие уроки спецслужбы Британии извлекли из отравления Скрипаля,Protecting defectors and hunting Russian spies. What lessons did Britain's intelligence services learn from the Skripal poisoning?,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Skripal', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Это просто предательство!» Как в Украине реагируют на переезд в Россию чемпионки по прыжкам в воду Софии Лыскун,“This is just betrayal!” How Ukraine reacts to diving champion Sofia Lyskun’s move to Russia,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Sofia Lyskun’s', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Газе убит лидер выступавшей против ХАМАС палестинской группировки Ясир Абу Шабаб,Anti-Hamas Palestinian leader Yasser Abu Shabab killed in Gaza,-0.2,"[('Anti-Hamas', 'NORP'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Yasser Abu Shabab', 'PERSON'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Израиль остается на «Евровидении». В ответ Нидерланды, Испания, Ирландия и Словения отказались от участия в конкурсе","Israel remains at Eurovision. In response, the Netherlands, Spain, Ireland and Slovenia refused to participate in the competition",0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Netherlands', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Slovenia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Вывод британского общественного расследования: моральную ответственность за отравление Дон Стерджесс «Новичком» несет Путин,Conclusion of the British public inquiry: Putin bears moral responsibility for the poisoning of Dawn Sturgess with Novichok,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Dawn Sturgess', 'PERSON'), ('Novichok', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Великобритания и Норвегия создают объединенный флот для отслеживания российских подлодок,UK and Norway create joint fleet to track Russian submarines,0.0,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン氏、ウクライナ軍撤退なければドンバスを「武力で掌握」と警告,"Putin warns that if Ukrainian troops do not withdraw, he will seize Donbas by force",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Donbas', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヘグセス米長官は「全員殺せ」と命令していないと海軍提督　連邦議員たちに証言,Navy admiral tells federal lawmakers that US Secretary of State Hegseth did not give order to kill everyone,0.0,"[('Navy', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,欧州歌合戦「ユーロヴィジョン」、来年のイスラエルの出場認める　アイルランドなど4カ国がボイコット表明,"Four countries, including Ireland, announce boycott of European singing competition ``Eurovision'' to allow Israel to participate next year",0.0,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Eurovision', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('next year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】石油、防衛、地政学……なぜプーチン氏はモディ氏に会いにデリーを訪れたのか,"[Commentary] Oil, defense, geopolitics... Why did Mr. Putin visit Delhi to meet Mr. Modi?",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Modi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,アザラシの赤ちゃんがバーに侵入、ニュージーランド, 所要時間 1,12","Video, Baby seal breaks into bar, New Zealand, Duration 1,12",0.13636363636363635,"[('Baby', 'ORG'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「典型的な酔っ払い」、アライグマが酒で目を回し……「トラブルに巻き込まれるのが好き」と米動物管理官, 所要時間 0,33","Video, ``Typical drunk'' raccoon rolls its eyes due to alcohol... ``Likes to get into trouble,'' says US animal control officer, Duration 0,33",-0.24791666666666667,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ストーカーの位置情報をリアルタイムで表示、韓国当局がアプリの開発進める,South Korean authorities are developing an app that displays stalkers' location information in real time,0.2,"[('South Korean', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米連邦最高裁、テキサス州の連邦議会選挙区割りの変更を承認,U.S. Supreme Court approves Texas congressional redistricting changes,0.0,"[('U.S. Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Texas', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,猫が人間の友達になったのは……思われていたよりずっと後,Cats became friends with humans... much later than we thought.,0.0,[]
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Balozi 16 za nchi za magharibi zataka uchunguzi huru wa matukio ya Octoba 29,Protests in Tanzania: 16 embassies of western countries want an independent investigation of the events of October 29,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('October 29', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,DRC na Rwanda watia saini mkataba wa amani","Directly, DRC and Rwanda sign a peace treaty",0.1,"[('DRC', 'ORG'), ('Rwanda', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ukatili mtandaoni: Jinsi wanawake wanavyokabiliwa na hatari kubwa na namna wanavyoweza kujilinda,Cyberbullying: How women are at greater risk and how they can protect themselves,0.5,[]
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Meta yajibu sababu za kufungia akaunti za wanaharakati wawili wa Tanzania,Meta answers the reasons for freezing the accounts of two Tanzanian activists,0.0,"[('Meta', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, miamba ya ajabu inayopatikana kwenye sayari ni ishara ya uhai?",Are the strange rocks found on the planet a sign of life?,-0.05,[]
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ijumaa: Salah huenda akaelekea Saudia,Football rumors Friday: Salah may be heading to Saudi Arabia,0.0,"[('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Salah', 'PERSON'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Marekani kutathmini upya uhusiano wake na taifa hilo,Protests in Tanzania: The United States should reassess its relationship with the country,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('The United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Putin asema Urusi itachukua eneo lote la Ukraine la Donbas kwa nguvu,Putin says Russia will take all of Ukraine's Donbas region by force,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Donbas', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Trump kuongoza utiaji saini wa makubaliano ya amani kati ya DRC na Rwanda,Trump to lead the signing of a peace agreement between the DRC and Rwanda,0.0,"[('DRC', 'ORG'), ('Rwanda', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tume ya Vatican yapiga kura dhidi ya kuwaruhusu wanawake kuwa mashemasi wa Kikatoliki,The Vatican Commission votes against allowing women to become Catholic deacons,0.0,"[('The Vatican Commission', 'ORG'), ('Catholic', 'NORP')]"
