Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Trump anuncia la suspensión de subsidios y pagos a Colombia después de que Petro acusara al gobierno de EE.UU. de cometer un asesinato y violar la soberanía colombiana,Trump announces the suspension of subsidies and payments to Colombia after Petro accused the US government of committing murder and violating Colombian sovereignty,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Petro', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Colombian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Un robo de joyas de ""valor incalculable"" obliga a cerrar el museo del Louvre de París mientras la policía se lanza a la caza de los ladrones","A theft of ""priceless"" jewels forces the Louvre museum in Paris to close as police hunt for the thieves",1.0,"[('the Louvre museum', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Israel lanza ataques aéreos en Gaza tras acusar a Hamás de una ""flagrante violación"" del alto el fuego",Israel launches airstrikes in Gaza after accusing Hamas of 'flagrant violation' of ceasefire,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Lo más ingenioso desde el caballo de Troya"": la pieza de arte con la que los soviéticos espiaron a EE.UU.","""The most ingenious thing since the Trojan horse"": the piece of art with which the Soviets spied on the United States",0.5,"[('Trojan', 'PERSON'), ('Soviets', 'NORP'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quiénes son Rodrigo Paz y Tuto Quiroga, los aspirantes a presidente de Bolivia (y por quién se decantará el voto de izquierda tras casi 20 años en el poder)","Who are Rodrigo Paz and Tuto Quiroga, the candidates for president of Bolivia (and who will the leftist vote choose after almost 20 years in power)",-0.05,"[('Rodrigo Paz', 'PERSON'), ('Tuto Quiroga', 'ORG'), ('Bolivia', 'GPE'), ('almost 20 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दुनिया के सबसे बड़े म्यूज़ियम में सात मिनट में बेशक़ीमती गहनों की चोरी कैसे हुई?,How were precious jewels stolen from the world's largest museum in seven minutes?,0.5,"[('seven minutes', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,दिल्ली-एनसीआर में एयर क्वालिटी ख़राब होने के बाद ग्रैप स्टेज-2 लागू किया गया","Live, Grape Stage-2 implemented after poor air quality in Delhi-NCR",-0.13181818181818183,"[('Delhi-NCR', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जय शाह पर पाकिस्तान क्यों लगा रहा क्रिकेट को नुक़सान पहुंचाने का आरोप,Why is Pakistan accusing Jai Shah of harming cricket?,0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Jai Shah', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'जब अदालत ने बरी कर दिया तो श्रद्धांजलि की अनुमति क्यों नहीं?',"'When the court acquitted, why not allow tribute?'",0.0,[]
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ऑस्ट्रेलिया ने पहले वनडे में भारत को हराया, नहीं चला रोहित-कोहली का बल्ला","Australia defeated India in the first ODI, Rohit-Kohli's bat did not work",0.25,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('ODI', 'ORG'), (""Rohit-Kohli's"", 'ORG')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सर सैयद अहमद खाँ जिन्होंने तीखे विरोध के बीच की थी अलीगढ़ मुस्लिम यूनिवर्सिटी की स्थापना - विवेचना,"Sir Syed Ahmed Khan, who established Aligarh Muslim University amidst strong opposition - Discussion",0.43333333333333335,"[('Syed Ahmed Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Aligarh Muslim University', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"खाने-पीने की कुछ चीज़ें भी बना सकती हैं किडनी स्टोन, डॉक्टर की सलाह जानिए","Some food items can also cause kidney stones, know doctor's advice",0.0,[]
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,प्रशांत किशोर बिहार चुनाव क्यों नहीं लड़ना चाह रहे?,Why does Prashant Kishor not want to contest Bihar elections?,0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"क्रिकेटर प्रतिका रावल, जिन्होंने तोड़ा 28 साल पुराना रिकॉर्ड","Cricketer Pratika Rawal, who broke 28 years old record",0.1,"[('Cricketer Pratika Rawal', 'ORG'), ('28 years old', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Geração Z está derrubando governos — mas protestos nas redes sociais geram mudanças duradouras?,Generation Z is overthrowing governments — but do protests on social media create lasting change?,0.016666666666666666,[]
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como ultrassom inaugura nova era de tratamento de câncer sem cirurgias,How ultrasound ushers in a new era of cancer treatment without surgery,0.13636363636363635,[]
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Israel ataca Gaza enquanto IDF e Hamas se acusam mutuamente de violar cessar-fogo,Israel attacks Gaza as IDF and Hamas accuse each other of violating ceasefire,-0.125,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('IDF', 'ORG'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Rodrigo Paz e Tuto Quiroga: quem são os candidatos à presidência da Bolívia e o futuro do voto da esquerda,Rodrigo Paz and Tuto Quiroga: who are the candidates for president of Bolivia and the future of the left vote,0.0,"[('Rodrigo Paz', 'PERSON'), ('Tuto Quiroga', 'ORG'), ('Bolivia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Roubo no Louvre: o que se sabe sobre o crime no museu de Paris,Robbery at the Louvre: what is known about the crime at the Paris museum,0.0,"[('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Pior do que começar do zero': por que reconstrução em Gaza é tão desafiadora,'Worse than starting from scratch': why reconstruction in Gaza is so challenging,0.033333333333333326,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Protestos contra Trump levam multidão às ruas nos EUA,Protests against Trump bring crowds to the streets in the USA,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A revolução discreta da cidade italiana que virou alternativa ao turismo excessivo de Veneza,The discreet revolution of the Italian city that became an alternative to the excessive tourism of Venice,-0.125,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Venice', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O edifício desenhado para combater a solidão reconhecido com prestigiado prêmio de arquitetura,The building designed to combat loneliness recognized with prestigious architecture award,0.0,[]
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Из музея Лувр в Париже средь бела дня украли драгоценности. Часть уже найдена,Jewels were stolen from the Louvre Museum in Paris in broad daylight. Part has already been found,0.0625,"[('the Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Израиль обвинил ХАМАС в «грубом нарушении перемирия» и нанес авиаудары по Газе,"Israel accused Hamas of ""gross violation of the truce"" and launched airstrikes in Gaza",0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Как Украина разворачивает «шахеды» назад в Россию, а «Кинжалы» падают в полях. Интервью с главой службы РЭБ Украины","How Ukraine deploys “martyrs” back to Russia, and “Daggers” fall in the fields. Interview with the head of the electronic warfare service of Ukraine",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как гормоны могут управлять вашим сознанием?,How can hormones control your mind?,0.0,[]
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Нет королям!». Миллионы американцев участвовали в акциях протеста против Трампа,"""No to kings!"" Millions of Americans took part in anti-Trump protests",0.0,"[('Millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: украинские беспилотники нанесли удар по Оренбургскому газоперерабатывающему и Новокуйбышевскому НПЗ","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Ukrainian drones attacked the Orenburg gas processing plant and the Novokuybyshevsk oil refinery",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Orenburg', 'GPE'), ('Novokuybyshevsk', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Что пишут о переговорах Трампа и Зеленского западные СМИ,What Western media write about the Trump-Zelensky negotiations,0.0,[]
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Армия Израиля заявила, что получила останки еще двух заложников из Газы",The Israeli army said it had received the remains of two more Gaza hostages.,0.5,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Зеленский и Трамп обсудили военную помощь Киеву, но о конкретных результатах ничего не сказали","Zelensky and Trump discussed military assistance to Kyiv, but said nothing about specific results",-0.05,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Что будет делать Трамп, если в Венгрии Путин не пойдет на перемирие?, Продолжительность 0,34","Video, What will Trump do if Putin does not agree to a truce in Hungary?, Duration 0.34",0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('0.34', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ゼレンスキー氏と直接会談　長距離ミサイル供与には慎重姿勢,Trump talks directly with Zelensky; cautious stance on providing long-range missiles,0.1,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英王室のアンドリュー王子、ヨーク公爵など称号返上,British royal family's Prince Andrew relinquishes titles including Duke of York,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('Duke of York', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル軍、ヨルダン川西岸で10歳パレスチナ少年を射殺,Israeli army shoots dead 10-year-old Palestinian boy in West Bank,-0.2,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('10-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、詐欺で服役中のサントス元共和党議員を減刑　「素晴らしい人生を！」と祝う,Trump commutes sentence of former Republican congressman Santos serving time for fraud; congratulates him on ``Have a wonderful life!'',0.5,"[('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Santos', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、プーチン氏とハンガリーでの会談で合意　ウクライナ和平への「非常に生産的な」電話協議で,Trump agrees to meet with Putin in Hungary after ``very productive'' telephone talks on peace in Ukraine,0.2,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ガザで死亡した人質の遺体、赤十字がさらに1体収容　イスラエル発表,"Red Cross collects one more body of hostage killed in Gaza, Israel announces",0.075,"[('Red Cross', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インド、トランプ氏の主張に疑問呈す　モディ氏がロシア産石油の購入停止に同意との電話は「把握せず」,India questions Trump's claim: 'doesn't understand' Modi's call to agree to halt purchases of Russian oil,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Modi', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EUのドローン防衛システム、2027年末までの完全導入目指すと　対ロシア防衛を強化,EU drone defense system aims to be fully introduced by end of 2027 to strengthen defense against Russia,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('2027', 'DATE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,中国のためのスパイ疑惑めぐり英政界が紛糾、MI5長官は起訴取り下げに苦言,"British politics in turmoil over suspicion of spying for China, MI5 chief complains about dropping charges",0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Buriani Raila Odinga: Mwili wa aliyekuwa Waziri Mkuu wa Kenya wazikwa","Live, Buriani Raila Odinga: The body of the former Prime Minister of Kenya was buried",0.06818181818181818,"[('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Heche ashindwa kuhudhuria mazishi ya Odinga,Heche failed to attend Odinga's funeral,-0.5,"[('Odinga', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini Urusi ina wasiwasi na muungano wa kijeshi wa nchi za Turkic?,Why is Russia worried about the military alliance of the Turkic countries?,-0.1,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Turkic', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Ida Odinga: Kwa uchungu, bila kuomboleza, nakubali mapenzi ya Mungu","Ida Odinga: With pain, without mourning, I accept God's will",0.0,"[('Ida Odinga', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Waombolezaji washindwa kujizuia jeneza la Raila lilipowasili,Mourners could not contain themselves when Raila's coffin arrived,0.0,"[('Raila', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumapili: Chelsea wako mbioni kumsajili Rogers,European football rumors Sunday: Chelsea are in the process of signing Rogers,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Chelsea', 'PERSON'), ('Rogers', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kipi kinachotokea miilini mwetu tunapokataliwa na jinsi ya kukabiliana nacho,What happens in our bodies when we are rejected and how to deal with it,0.0,[]
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mali za Iran zinazoshikiliwa katika nchi za Magharibi,Iranian assets held in Western countries,0.0,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Western', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Buriani Raila Odinga: Mwili wa 'Baba' wafikishwa Bondo kwa safari ya mwisho,Buriani Raila Odinga: The body of 'Father' is brought to Bondo for the last journey,0.0,"[('Bondo', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_19,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Sisi ni yatima': Wakenya wamuaga Raila Odinga katika ngome yake ya kisiasa,'We are orphans': Kenyans say goodbye to Raila Odinga in his political fortress,0.0,"[('Kenyans', 'NORP'), ('Raila Odinga', 'PERSON')]"
