Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué Venezuela llegó a tener uranio altamente enriquecido y cómo fue la reciente operación secreta para entregárselo a EE.UU.,Why Venezuela came to have highly enriched uranium and what was the recent secret operation to deliver it to the United States like?,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Las razones de Meliá, Iberostar y Blue Diamond, las mayores cadenas hoteleras de Cuba, para cesar operaciones en la isla ""con efecto inmediato""","The reasons for Meliá, Iberostar and Blue Diamond, the largest hotel chains in Cuba, to cease operations on the island ""with immediate effect""",0.0,neutral,"[('Meliá, Iberostar', 'ORG'), ('Blue Diamond', 'PERSON'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Solo hay una salida"": la odisea de los miles de marineros atrapados por el bloqueo del estrecho de Ormuz desde hace casi 100 días","""There is only one way out"": the odyssey of the thousands of sailors trapped by the blockade of the Strait of Hormuz for almost 100 days",0.0,neutral,"[('only one', 'CARDINAL'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('almost 100 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La joven de 18 años que huyó a cientos de kilómetros de su hogar en un taxi para escapar del matrimonio forzado,The 18-year-old girl who fled hundreds of kilometers from her home in a taxi to escape forced marriage,0.0,neutral,"[('18-year-old', 'DATE'), ('hundreds of kilometers', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué revela sobre nuestra salud el dolor de cabeza que nos da cuando comemos helado,What the headache we get when we eat ice cream reveals about our health,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué son las ""zonas muertas"" que amenazan el mar Báltico, el área de agua salobre más grande del mundo","What are the ""dead zones"" that threaten the Baltic Sea, the largest area of ​​brackish water in the world",0.0,neutral,"[('the Baltic Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La policía de Nueva York investiga videos de hombres saliendo de las alcantarillas de la ciudad,NYPD Investigates Videos of Men Coming Out of City Sewers,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Es un honor darle mi apoyo"": el polémico respaldo de Trump a Abelardo De la Espriella de cara a la segunda vuelta de las presidenciales en Colombia","""It is an honor to give him my support"": Trump's controversial support for Abelardo De la Espriella ahead of the second round of the presidential elections in Colombia",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Abelardo De la Espriella', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La ofensiva de China contra las ""cocinas fantasma"" que acaparan las aplicaciones de comida a domicilio","China's offensive against ""ghost kitchens"" that dominate food delivery applications",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La controversia por los exorbitantes precios del transporte público para llegar a los estadios del Mundial 2026 en EE.UU.,The controversy over the exorbitant prices of public transportation to reach the 2026 World Cup stadiums in the USA.,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('USA', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,तृणमूल कांग्रेस से निकाले गए ऋतब्रत बनर्जी बने पश्चिम बंगाल विधानसभा में विपक्ष के नेता,"Ritabrata Banerjee, expelled from Trinamool Congress, becomes leader of opposition in West Bengal Assembly",0.0,neutral,"[('Ritabrata Banerjee', 'PERSON'), ('Trinamool Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी के तीन प्रवक्ता कौन हैं, जानिए उनके बारे में?","Who are the three spokespersons of Cockroach Janata Party, know about them?",0.0,neutral,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,डीके शिवकुमार ने ली कर्नाटक के मुख्यमंत्री पद की शपथ, पीएम मोदी ने दी बधाई","Live, DK Shivakumar took oath as the Chief Minister of Karnataka, PM Modi congratulated",0.0,neutral,"[('DK Shivakumar', 'PERSON'), ('Karnataka', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"दिल्ली के मालवीय नगर में एक रेस्टोरेंट में लगी आग, कम से कम 21 की मौत","Fire breaks out in a restaurant in Delhi's Malviya Nagar, at least 21 dead",0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Malviya Nagar', 'PERSON'), ('at least 21', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिकी व्यापार प्रतिनिधि ने भारत समेत 60 देशों पर अतिरिक्त टैरिफ़ लगाने का प्रस्ताव क्यों दिया?,Why did the US Trade Representative propose to impose additional tariffs on 60 countries including India?,0.0,neutral,"[('the US Trade', 'ORG'), ('60', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वीडियो,दिल्ली के मालवीय नगर के होटल में लगी आग, कई लोगों की मौत, अवधि 1,10","Video, Fire breaks out in hotel in Delhi's Malviya Nagar, many dead, duration 1,10",0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Malviya Nagar', 'PERSON'), ('1,10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'पहले लगता था काश मेरा भी बच्चा होता': नसबंदी करवा चुके पूर्व नक्सली कैसे बन रहे हैं मां-बाप,'Earlier I wished I too had a child': How former Naxals who have undergone sterilization are becoming parents,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ममता बनर्जी की तृणमूल कांग्रेस क्या आने वाले समय में टूट सकती है?,Can Mamata Banerjee's Trinamool Congress disintegrate in the future?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trinamool Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पटना: ख़ान सर के कोचिंग सेंटर के बाहर फ़ायरिंग का आरोप, पुलिस ने क्या बताया","Patna: Allegation of firing outside Khan Sir's coaching centre, what did the police tell?",0.0,neutral,"[(""Khan Sir's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान ने अमेरिकी एयरबेस को बनाया निशाना तो जवाब में अमेरिका ने क़ेशम द्वीप पर किया हमला,Iran targeted American airbase and in response America attacked Qeshm Island,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Qeshm Island', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'A pátria dos Bolsonaro não é a brasileira, é a pátria estrangeira', diz Simone Tebet","'The Bolsonaro's homeland is not Brazilian, it is a foreign homeland', says Simone Tebet",0.0,neutral,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Simone Tebet', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Pecuária brasileira na 'lista suja': o que EUA dizem sobre trabalho forçado no Brasil ao propor mais tarifas,Brazilian livestock on the 'dirty list': what the US says about forced labor in Brazil when proposing more tariffs,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Anvisa manda recolher lote de água Crystal por presença de bactéria; entenda,Anvisa orders a batch of Crystal water to be recalled due to the presence of bacteria; understand,0.0,neutral,"[('Anvisa', 'PERSON'), ('Crystal', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O adolescente com superdotação que passou no vestibular aos 12 anos e sonha estudar no MIT,The gifted teenager who passed the entrance exam at age 12 and dreams of studying at MIT,0.0,neutral,"[('age 12', 'DATE'), ('MIT', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Fim da escala 6x1 sai antes da eleição? As pressões a favor e contra na reta final no Congresso,End of scale 6x1 comes out before the election? Pressures for and against in the final stretch in Congress,0.0,neutral,"[('6x1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que disse a imprensa internacional sobre ameaça de novo tarifaço de Trump: 'Instrumento para impor novas tarifas ao Brasil é alternativa mais duradoura após decisão da Suprema Corte',What the international press said about Trump's threat of new tariffs: 'Instrument to impose new tariffs on Brazil is a more lasting alternative after the Supreme Court's decision',0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), (""the Supreme Court's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Ameaças ao Pix e de novo tarifaço expõem Flávio e podem dar vitória a Lula em eleição apertada, dizem analistas","Threats to Pix and new tariffs expose Flávio and could give Lula victory in a tight election, analysts say",1.0,positive,"[('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que PIX incomoda tanto o governo Trump?,Why does PIX bother the Trump government so much?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Tarifas dos EUA podem ter efeito imediato apesar de prazo de negociação, diz ex-secretário de Comércio Exterior do Brasil","US tariffs may take immediate effect despite negotiation deadline, says former Brazilian Foreign Trade Secretary",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian Foreign Trade', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Украинские дроны атаковали Петербург в день начала экономического форума: что известно,Ukrainian drones attacked St. Petersburg on the day of the start of the economic forum: what is known,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('the day of the start of the', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Киев заявил об ударах по нефтяному терминалу и военному кораблю в Петербурге в день начала ПМЭФ","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Kyiv announced attacks on an oil terminal and a warship in St. Petersburg on the day of the start of SPIEF",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('the day of the start of', 'DATE'), ('SPIEF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Тупик и шмель вошли в число 18 животных, которые могут появиться на банкнотах в Британии",The puffin and bumblebee are among 18 animals that could appear on UK banknotes,0.0,neutral,"[('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Цветы и баклажаны под запретом. Как Россия давит на Армению перед выборами,Flowers and eggplants are prohibited. How Russia is putting pressure on Armenia before the elections,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Armenia', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Британии — скандал из-за гибели студента Генри Новака. Выяснилось, что перед смертью его арестовали, поверив словам убийцы","In Britain there is a scandal over the death of student Henry Novak. It turned out that before his death he was arrested, believing the words of the killer",-1.0,negative,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Henry Novak', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Иран запустил ракеты и дроны, США сбили их и нанесли удар по острову в Ормузском проливе","Iran launched missiles and drones, the US shot them down and struck an island in the Strait of Hormuz",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Массированная атака на Киев, Днепр и Харьков: более 20 погибших, десятки раненых","Massive attack on Kyiv, Dnieper and Kharkov: more than 20 dead, dozens wounded",-1.0,negative,"[('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Dnieper', 'PERSON'), ('Kharkov', 'PERSON'), ('more than 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Израиль и «Хезболла» приняли предложенный США план частичного прекращения огня, но в Ливане продолжаются столкновения","Israel and Hezbollah accepted US-proposed partial ceasefire plan, but clashes continue in Lebanon",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Чат‑бот Meta AI позволил хакерам получить доступ к чужим аккаунтам в Instagram,Meta AI chatbot allowed hackers to gain access to other people's Instagram accounts,0.0,neutral,"[('Meta AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Локальный дефицит бензина. Как атаки на нефтяную инфраструктуру России повлияли на рынок топлива,Local gasoline shortage. How attacks on Russian oil infrastructure affected the fuel market,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 プーチン氏、ウクライナでの戦争で妥協を拒み続ける　ロシアの世論はどうなのか,[Commentary] Mr. Putin continues to refuse to compromise on the war in Ukraine.What is the opinion of Russian public opinion?,-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英警察の反人種差別の取り組みに疑問の声　殺人事件のボディーカメラ映像公開で,British police's anti-racism efforts are questioned after body camera footage of murder case released,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,【検証】 「刺された」と訴える被害者に手錠……英警察のボディーカメラ映像から分かること, 所要時間 2,36","Video, [Verification] Victim who claims to have been stabbed is handcuffed...What we learn from British police body camera footage, Duration: 2,36",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('2,36', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米国とイラン、新たに互いを攻撃　停戦交渉が行き詰まるなか,US and Iran attack each other again as ceasefire negotiations stall,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエル、レバノン南部への攻撃を継続　ヒズボラとの部分的停戦は維持か,"Israel continues attacks on southern Lebanon, will partial ceasefire with Hezbollah be maintained?",-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英国人夫妻、イランで拘束されスパイ罪で収監　控訴棄却されハンスト中と家族,British couple detained in Iran and imprisoned on espionage charges; appeal rejected; family on hunger strike,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、米国家情報長官代行にビル・プルティ氏を指名　住宅金融局長と兼任,"Trump nominates Bill Puluti as Acting Director of National Intelligence, concurrently serving as Director of Housing Finance",0.0,neutral,"[('Bill Puluti', 'PERSON'), ('National Intelligence', 'ORG'), ('Housing Finance', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアがウクライナ首都など大規模空爆、少なくとも22人死亡,At least 22 people killed in Russia's massive airstrike on Ukrainian capital,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 22', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】イギリスの首相であり続けるのは、今やかつてないほど難しいのか,Commentary: Is it harder now than ever to remain British Prime Minister?,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 トランプ氏には終戦が必要、しかしイランは引かず……BBC国際編集長,"[Commentary] Trump needs an end to the war, but Iran won't back down...BBC International Editor-in-Chief",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('BBC International', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,CCM kuna Yuda au ni homa ya urais 2030?,CCM is there Judah or is it 2030 presidential fever?,0.0,neutral,"[('CCM', 'ORG'), ('Judah', 'PERSON'), ('2030', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani na Iran zaanzisha mashambulizi mapya, Kuwait yasema uwanja wa ndege umeshambuliwa na Iran","Immediately, the United States and Iran launch new attacks, Kuwait says the airport has been attacked by Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vita visivyoonekana ambavyo vinahatarisha usalama wa ndege,The invisible war that threatens the safety of aircraft,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini ngome hii yenye miaka 900 ni muhimu katika vita vya Israel-Hezbollah?,Why is this 900-year-old fortress important in the Israel-Hezbollah war?,-1.0,negative,"[('900-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tanzania inatafuta nini Urusi?,What is Tanzania looking for in Russia?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"AFCON U-17: Tanzania yafa kiume fainali, yaacha alama Afrika","AFCON U-17: Tanzania wins the final, leaves a mark on Africa",1.0,positive,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mapendekezo 3 ya kodi yanayozua utata miongoni mwa Wakenya,3 tax proposals causing controversy among Kenyans,0.0,neutral,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenyans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Aston Villa haina mpango wa kumuuza Rogers,European Football Rumors: Aston Villa have no plans to sell Rogers,0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Aston Villa', 'PERSON'), ('Rogers', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"WARIDI WA BBC: Akiwa na miaka 12 alitafutiwa mume wa miaka 50, leo ameokoa mabinti 300","BBC ROSIE: When she was 12 years old, she was searched for a 50-year-old husband, today she has saved 300 daughters",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('12 years old', 'DATE'), ('50-year-old', 'DATE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('300', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Visa sita vipya vya ugonjwa wa Ebola vyathibitishwa Uganda,Six new cases of Ebola have been confirmed in Uganda,0.0,neutral,"[('Six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ebola', 'GPE'), ('Uganda', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Israel is building more military posts in Gaza, satellite imagery shows","Israel is building more military posts in Gaza, satellite imagery shows",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran, Kuwait, Bahrain hit: Is the war in the Gulf escalating again?","Iran, Kuwait, Bahrain hit: Is the war in the Gulf escalating again?",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Bahrain', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup contenders: Are Morocco ready to go all the way this time?,World Cup contenders: Are Morocco ready to go all the way this time?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel’s invasion of southern Lebanon devastates centuries of history,Israel’s invasion of southern Lebanon devastates centuries of history,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('centuries', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US artist sues FIFA over destruction of Dallas whale mural for World Cup,US artist sues FIFA over destruction of Dallas whale mural for World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('Dallas', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"California showdown, Trump setback: Key primary election results","California showdown, Trump setback: Key primary election results",0.0,neutral,"[('California', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Fire at New Delhi hotel kills at least 21 people,Fire at New Delhi hotel kills at least 21 people,-1.0,negative,"[('New Delhi', 'GPE'), ('at least 21', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Hezbollah video shows attack on Israeli troops at Lebanon’s Beaufort Castle,Hezbollah video shows attack on Israeli troops at Lebanon’s Beaufort Castle,-1.0,negative,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,UK-China ‘ice age’ thaws: Why the West needs Beijing,UK-China ‘ice age’ thaws: Why the West needs Beijing,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('West', 'LOC'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Democrat and Republican go head-to-head in California governor race,Democrat and Republican go head-to-head in California governor race,0.0,neutral,"[('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('California', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Delhi hotel fire LIVE: Police files culpable homicide FIR; at least 21 people killed,Delhi hotel fire LIVE: Police files culpable homicide FIR; at least 21 people killed,-1.0,negative,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('FIR', 'ORG'), ('at least 21', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Violent protests and questions after Nowak murder case sentencing,Violent protests and questions after Nowak murder case sentencing,0.0,neutral,"[('Nowak', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Abhishek moves Calcutta HC, seeks protection against CID action in signature forgery case","Abhishek moves Calcutta HC, seeks protection against CID action in signature forgery case",0.0,neutral,"[('Abhishek', 'ORG'), ('Calcutta HC', 'PERSON'), ('CID', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,J&K CM takes his legislators to off-limit forest destination in Srinagar to dissect 19 months of NC rule,J&K CM takes his legislators to off-limit forest destination in Srinagar to dissect 19 months of NC rule,0.0,neutral,"[('J&K CM', 'ORG'), ('Srinagar', 'GPE'), ('19 months', 'DATE'), ('NC', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"After 10 years, Madras High Court declares Appavu elected from Radhapuram constituency in 2016 Assembly polls","After 10 years, Madras High Court declares Appavu elected from Radhapuram constituency in 2016 Assembly polls",0.0,neutral,"[('10 years', 'DATE'), ('Madras High Court', 'ORG'), ('Appavu', 'PERSON'), ('Radhapuram', 'ORG'), ('2016 Assembly', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The ‘harvest’ China wants is one India cannot afford,The ‘harvest’ China wants is one India cannot afford,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia war LIVE: Kuwait airport reportedly attacked by Iran drones and missiles,West Asia war LIVE: Kuwait airport reportedly attacked by Iran drones and missiles,-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Annamalai quits BJP, to start new political ‘movement’","Annamalai quits BJP, to start new political ‘movement’",0.0,neutral,"[('Annamalai', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"As screens shrink, Tamil entertainment finds new ways to tell stories","As screens shrink, Tamil entertainment finds new ways to tell stories",0.0,neutral,"[('Tamil', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Change in arrangement: On the leadership transition in Karnataka,​Change in arrangement: On the leadership transition in Karnataka,0.0,neutral,"[('Karnataka', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US and Iran launch new strikes, as Kuwait says airport hit by Iranian drones","US and Iran launch new strikes, as Kuwait says airport hit by Iranian drones",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Israel strikes southern Lebanon but partial truce with Hezbollah appears to hold,Israel strikes southern Lebanon but partial truce with Hezbollah appears to hold,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Eight killed after drone hits bus in Russia-controlled part of Ukraine,Eight killed after drone hits bus in Russia-controlled part of Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Putin remains uncompromising on Ukraine, but is public discourse on war changing in Russia?","Putin remains uncompromising on Ukraine, but is public discourse on war changing in Russia?",-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Shell pumped oil through Nigeria pipeline for years despite pollution evidence, documents show","Shell pumped oil through Nigeria pipeline for years despite pollution evidence, documents show",0.0,neutral,"[('Shell', 'ORG'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump administration drops $1.8bn 'anti-weaponisation' fund,Trump administration drops $1.8bn 'anti-weaponisation' fund,0.0,neutral,"[('1.8bn', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Foreign nationals among at least 21 killed in Delhi fire,Foreign nationals among at least 21 killed in Delhi fire,-1.0,negative,"[('at least 21', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Mayor cancels DR Congo friendly with Chile in Spain over Ebola concern,Mayor cancels DR Congo friendly with Chile in Spain over Ebola concern,0.0,neutral,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG'), ('Chile', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Ebola', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Watch: Man attacked by bear at steel works in Japan,Watch: Man attacked by bear at steel works in Japan,-1.0,negative,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"British couple lose Iran jail sentence appeal, family says","British couple lose Iran jail sentence appeal, family says",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: Kuwait Says Iranian Attack Has Damaged Its Main Airport,Iran War Live Updates: Kuwait Says Iranian Attack Has Damaged Its Main Airport,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates:', 'EVENT'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Iranian Attack Has', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine Strikes St. Petersburg on First Day of a Marquee Putin Event,Ukraine Strikes St. Petersburg on First Day of a Marquee Putin Event,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('First Day', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The New Zealand Parakeet Pair That Are Saving Their Species,The New Zealand Parakeet Pair That Are Saving Their Species,0.0,neutral,"[('The New Zealand Parakeet Pair That Are Saving Their Species', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"For Dubai’s Migrants, War Is One More Worry in Super Stressed Lives","For Dubai’s Migrants, War Is One More Worry in Super Stressed Lives",-1.0,negative,"[('Dubai', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Russia Launches Deadly Strikes on Kyiv After Threatening Ukraine for a Week,Russia Launches Deadly Strikes on Kyiv After Threatening Ukraine for a Week,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia Launches Deadly Strikes', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"U.S. Ebola Unit Plans in Kenya, Subject of Protests, Suffers New Setback From Court Ruling","U.S. Ebola Unit Plans in Kenya, Subject of Protests, Suffers New Setback From Court Ruling",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Ebola Unit Plans', 'ORG'), ('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('Protests', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Was Asked to Blacklist Colombian Cartel Gold. It Was Also Buying It.,U.S. Was Asked to Blacklist Colombian Cartel Gold. It Was Also Buying It.,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Colombian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Bombs Raining Down on Ukraine Can’t Hide Signs of Russia’s Faltering War,Bombs Raining Down on Ukraine Can’t Hide Signs of Russia’s Faltering War,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Faltering War', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Protests Grow in Albania Over Kushner-Linked Project,Protests Grow in Albania Over Kushner-Linked Project,0.0,neutral,"[('Albania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Murder of Henry Nowak, Who Was Handcuffed by Police While Dying, Fuels Outrage in UK","Murder of Henry Nowak, Who Was Handcuffed by Police While Dying, Fuels Outrage in UK",0.0,neutral,"[('Henry Nowak', 'PERSON'), ('Fuels Outrage', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
