Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo EE.UU. ha logrado reducir su epidemia de muertes por fentanilo,How the US has managed to reduce its epidemic of fentanyl deaths,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué los minerales de tierras raras se han convertido en una ventaja para China en sus negociaciones con EE.UU.,Why rare earth minerals have become an advantage for China in its negotiations with the US,0.3,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Si pudiese sostener un cuchillo, no les pediría nada"": el caso de Pablo Salgueiro, el hombre con ELA que se convirtió en símbolo de la ley de eutanasia aprobada en Uruguay","""If I could hold a knife, I wouldn't ask you for anything"": the case of Pablo Salgueiro, the man with ALS who became a symbol of the euthanasia law approved in Uruguay",0.0,"[('Pablo Salgueiro', 'PERSON'), ('ALS', 'ORG'), ('Uruguay', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,5 de los tesoros más bellos del mundo que intentaron robar del Louvre y otros museos,5 of the most beautiful treasures in the world that tried to be stolen from the Louvre and other museums,0.4083333333333334,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cuáles son las ciudades más avanzadas tecnológicamente del mundo,What are the most technologically advanced cities in the world?,0.45,[]
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप-पुतिन बातचीत 'टलते' ही रूस का यूक्रेन पर बड़ा हमला, बच्चों समेत सात लोगों की मौत","As soon as Trump-Putin talks were 'postponed', Russia attacked Ukraine, seven people including children died.",0.0,"[('Trump-Putin', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,इमरान ख़ान ने आसिम मुनीर को घेरा, सोशल मीडिया के जरिए जारी किया बयान","Live, Imran Khan surrounded Asim Munir, issued statement through social media",0.08484848484848484,"[('Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Asim Munir', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,सम्राट चौधरी ने बिहार विधानसभा चुनाव को लेकर किया ये दावा - देखिए इंटरव्यू, अवधि 2,59","Video, Samrat Chaudhary made this claim regarding Bihar assembly elections - watch interview, duration 2,59",0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('2,59', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार के इस ज़िले में 'चमत्कारी फल' ने बदली ज़िंदगियां, पर किसानों को अब भी है ये मलाल","'Miracle fruit' changed lives in this district of Bihar, but farmers still have this regret",0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सरफ़राज़ ख़ान को 'इंडिया ए' में जगह न मिलने पर क्यों उठे सवाल,Why questions were raised when Sarfaraz Khan did not get a place in 'India A',0.0,"[('Sarfaraz Khan', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,वायु प्रदूषण से आपके फेफड़ों को कितना नुक़सान? बचने के लिए क्या करें,How much damage does air pollution cause to your lungs? what to do to avoid,0.2,[]
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"आरएसएस के 'हिंदू राष्ट्र' में मुसलमान, 100 साल में बदलते सरसंघचालकों के साथ क्या कुछ बदला?","Muslims in RSS's 'Hindu Rashtra', has anything changed with changing Sarsanghchalaks in 100 years?",0.0,"[('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('RSS', 'ORG'), ('Sarsanghchalaks', 'GPE'), ('100 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'संजय दत्त पुलिस को बता देते तो मुंबई धमाके रुक सकते थे' उज्ज्वल निकम ने मुंबई धमाकों और क़साब के बारे में क्या-क्या बताया?,"'If Sanjay Dutt had informed the police, the Mumbai blasts could have been stopped' What did Ujjwal Nikam tell about the Mumbai blasts and Kasab?",0.0,"[('Sanjay Dutt', 'PERSON'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Ujjwal Nikam', 'ORG'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Kasab', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,प्रशांत किशोर ने बिहार के युवाओं के सवालों के दिए ये जवाब - देखिए इंटरव्यू, अवधि 15,24","Video, Prashant Kishore gave these answers to the questions of the youth of Bihar - watch the interview, duration 15,24",0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('15,24', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Efeito China': aproximação com o gigante asiático pode enfraquecer a indústria no Brasil?,'China effect': could rapprochement with the Asian giant weaken the industry in Brazil?,0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Asian', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Por que novo filme com Leonardo DiCaprio é sucesso de crítica, mas fracasso de bilheteria","Why new film with Leonardo DiCaprio is a critical success, but a box office failure",0.029924242424242423,"[('Leonardo DiCaprio', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Alemanha inclui alerta para guerra em guia que orienta casos de crise,Germany includes war warning in guide that guides cases of crisis,0.0,"[('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A comparação dos efeitos colaterais de diferentes antidepressivos, segundo pesquisa","Comparison of the side effects of different antidepressants, according to research",0.0,[]
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quanto podem valer as joias roubadas do Louvre?,How much could the jewels stolen from the Louvre be worth?,0.25,"[('Louvre', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O acordo que permite príncipe Andrew viver em casa com 30 cômodos,The agreement that allows Prince Andrew to live in a house with 30 rooms,0.13636363636363635,"[('Prince Andrew', 'PERSON'), ('30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O guia de espionagem dos EUA que ensina a sabotar o seu trabalho,The US spy guide that teaches you how to sabotage your work,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como roubo de Mona Lisa no Louvre fez dela a pintura mais famosa do mundo,How Mona Lisa theft from the Louvre made it the most famous painting in the world,0.5,"[('Mona Lisa', 'PERSON'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como polícia desvendou caso da 'serial killer de Guarulhos': 'Fria e manipuladora',How the police solved the case of the 'Guarulhos serial killer': 'Cold and manipulative',-0.6,"[('Guarulhos', 'PERSON'), ('Cold', 'EVENT')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ФБК потребовали признать террористической организацией в России,FBK demanded to recognize a terrorist organization in Russia,0.0,"[('FBK', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Киев может приобрести до 150 шведских истребителей Gripen","LIVELive,Война в Украине: Киев может приобрести до 150 шведских истребителей Gripen",0.0,"[('Война', 'GPE'), ('Киев', 'PERSON'), ('150', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Евросоюз готовится ужесточить санкции против России. Что попадет в 19-й пакет?,The European Union is preparing to tighten sanctions against Russia. What will be included in the 19th package?,0.0,"[('The European Union', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('19th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Премию Сахарова присудили белорусскому журналисту Анджею Почобуту и грузинской журналистке Мзие Амаглобели,The Sakharov Prize was awarded to Belarusian journalist Andrzej Poczobut and Georgian journalist Mzie Amaglobeli,0.0,"[('Belarusian', 'NORP'), ('Andrzej Poczobut', 'PERSON'), ('Georgian', 'NORP'), ('Mzie Amaglobeli', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,«Для кадыровцев не важно девушка ты, гей или критик». Что известно правозащитникам о смерти чеченки в Ереване?, Продолжительность 6,10","Video, “For Kadyrov’s men, it doesn’t matter whether you’re a girl, gay or a critic.” What do human rights activists know about the death of a Chechen woman in Yerevan?, Duration 6.10",0.20833333333333334,"[('Kadyrov', 'PERSON'), ('Chechen', 'NORP'), ('Yerevan', 'PERSON'), ('6.10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Девушка из Бердянска пропала на год в Москве. Теперь ее судят по делу о госизмене,A girl from Berdyansk disappeared for a year in Moscow. Now she is on trial for treason,0.0,"[('Berdyansk', 'ORG'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Лувр открылся после ограбления. Прокуроры заявили, что оттуда украли драгоценности на $100 млн",The Louvre reopened after the robbery. Prosecutors said $100 million worth of jewelry was stolen from there.,0.3,"[('Louvre', 'PERSON'), ('$100 million', 'MONEY')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Как любил Украину, так и буду любить, а российский паспорт взял, чтобы жить». Как устроена принудительная паспортизация","“As I loved Ukraine, I will love it, but I took a Russian passport in order to live.” How does forced passportization work?",0.20727272727272728,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Детский сад попал под удар при обстреле Харькова. Дети были в убежище,The kindergarten came under attack during shelling in Kharkov. The children were in the shelter,0.0,"[('Kharkov', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Принцип „люди — это новая нефть“ окончательно утвердился». Чего ждать россиянам от бюджета-2026?,“The principle ‘people are the new oil’ has finally been established.” What can Russians expect from the 2026 budget?,0.06818181818181818,"[('Russians', 'NORP'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 初の女性首相誕生という歴史的瞬間、ただし高市氏の理念に懸念も,"[Commentary] Historical moment with the birth of the first female prime minister, but there are concerns about Takaichi's ideals",0.08333333333333333,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Takaichi', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】日本初の女性首相、高市早苗氏はどんな人か　「鉄の女」サッチャー元英首相を私淑,"[Commentary] What kind of person is Japan's first female prime minister, Sanae Takaichi? She is a personal admirer of the ""Iron Lady"" and former British Prime Minister Thatcher.",0.14166666666666666,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the ""Iron Lady', 'LAW'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Thatcher', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ロ首脳会談、見送りに　「無駄な会談」は望んでいないとトランプ氏,"Trump says he doesn't want a ""wasteful meeting"" as US-Russia summit is postponed",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 トランプ氏、なぜウクライナでうまくいかないのか　ガザでは停戦合意まとめたが,"[Commentary] Why is Trump not doing well in Ukraine? He reached a cease-fire agreement in Gaza, but",0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ルーヴル美術館から盗難の宝飾品、総額155億円相当と検察　犯人の足取りは不明,"Jewelry stolen from Louvre Museum, worth 15.5 billion yen, prosecutors say, criminal's whereabouts unknown",-0.06666666666666668,"[('Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('15.5 billion yen', 'MONEY')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナ軍、英供与のミサイルでロシアの化学工場を攻撃,Ukrainian military attacks Russian chemical factory with British-supplied missiles,-0.05,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ホワイトハウスの一部を解体、「宴会場」を建設　トランプ氏に権限はあるのか, 所要時間 2,14","Video, Demolish part of the White House and build a ""banquet hall"" - Does Mr. Trump have the authority? Duration 2,14",0.0,"[('Demolish', 'NORP'), ('the White House', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,抹茶が世界的ブーム　古くからの宇治の茶商は需要急増にどう対応,Matcha is a global boom - how does a long-established tea merchant in Uji cope with the surge in demand?,0.0,"[('Matcha', 'GPE'), ('Uji', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「人生を変える」網膜インプラント、再び文字を読めるように, 所要時間 0,59","Video, 'Life-changing' retinal implant lets you read again, Duration 0,59",0.0,[]
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watu 46 wafariki dunia baada ya mabasi kugongana Uganda,46 people die after buses collide in Uganda,0.0,"[('46', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uganda', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mahakama Kuu ya UN: Israeli imeshindwa kutekeleza majukumu yake ya kibinadamu huko Gaza,UN High Court: Israel has failed to fulfill its humanitarian obligations in Gaza,-0.16999999999999998,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Makamu Mwenyekiti wa CHADEMA, John Heche akamatwa na kupelekwa Tarime Tanzania","The Vice Chairman of CHADEMA, John Heche was arrested and sent to Tarime Tanzania",0.0,"[('CHADEMA', 'ORG'), ('John Heche', 'PERSON'), ('Tarime Tanzania', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini Trump alifanikiwa kusuluhisha vita vya Gaza lakini anashindwa na vita vya Ukraine?,Why did Trump succeed in resolving the Gaza war but is failing in the Ukraine war?,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ni maswali gani muhimu yanayomkabili kocha wa Liverpool Arne Slot?,What are the important questions facing Liverpool coach Arne Slot?,0.4,"[('Liverpool', 'ORG'), ('Arne Slot', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Picha za wanawake wa Kisomali zinavyotumiwa kueneza taarifa ghushi mitandaoni,Photos of Somali women are being used to spread fake news on the internet,-0.5,"[('Somali', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatano: Liverpool wanafikiria kumsajili Semenyo,European Football Rumors Wednesday: Liverpool are considering signing Semenyo,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Semenyo', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, ndege ya Putin itavuka anga ya Umoja wa Ulaya kwenda Hungary?",Will Putin's plane cross EU airspace to Hungary?,0.0,"[(""Will Putin's"", 'PERSON'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Hungary', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Mshindi kutangazwa ndani ya saa 72 - INEC,Tanzania Election 2025: Winner to be announced within 72 hours - INEC,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Election 2025', 'DATE'), ('72 hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_22,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Khamenei amtaja Trump kuwa muongo kuhusu mradi wa nyuklia,Khamenei called Trump a liar about the nuclear project,0.0,"[('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
