Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Trump y Netanyahu querían reconfigurar Medio Oriente, pero el riesgo ahora es una crisis permanente","Trump and Netanyahu wanted to reconfigure the Middle East, but the risk now is a permanent crisis",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,EE.UU. lanza ataques contra Irán como represalia por el derribo de un helicóptero militar,The US launches attacks against Iran in retaliation for the downing of a military helicopter,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las predicciones de BBC Mundo para las selecciones de América Latina y España en el Mundial 2026,BBC Mundo's predictions for the Latin American and Spanish teams in the 2026 World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[(""BBC Mundo's"", 'ORG'), ('Latin American', 'NORP'), ('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Una mujer de 34 años me engañó haciéndose pasar por una adolescente de 12 con autismo,A 34-year-old woman tricked me by posing as a 12-year-old teenager with autism,0.0,neutral,"[('34-year-old', 'DATE'), ('12-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo es vivir en uno de los 5 países más seguros del mundo,What it is like to live in one of the 5 safest countries in the world,0.0,neutral,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El ""arquitecto de Dios"": así imaginó Gaudí la Sagrada Familia, la iglesia más alta del mundo y una maravilla de la ingeniería","The ""architect of God"": this is how Gaudí imagined the Sagrada Familia, the tallest church in the world and a marvel of engineering",0.0,neutral,"[('Gaudí', 'PERSON'), ('the Sagrada Familia', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué pasó en México, Colombia y Venezuela después de que sus organizaciones criminales fueran clasificadas como terroristas por EE.UU.","What happened in Mexico, Colombia and Venezuela after their criminal organizations were classified as terrorists by the US.",-1.0,negative,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El piloto de Air Canada que voló durante 17 años sin la licencia adecuada,The Air Canada pilot who flew for 17 years without the proper license,0.0,neutral,"[('Air Canada', 'ORG'), ('17 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Me interrogaron durante 11 horas"": EE.UU. niega la entrada para el Mundial al ""mejor árbitro africano del año""","""They interrogated me for 11 hours"": USA denies entry to the World Cup to the ""best African referee of the year""",0.0,neutral,"[('11 hours', 'TIME'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('the year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Mundial de fútbol 2026: consulta el calendario de partidos de tu selección (con el horario de tu país),Soccer World Cup 2026: check your team's match schedule (with your country's schedule),0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भारत ने क्या 12 परमाणु हथियारों को तैनात किया है, एक रिपोर्ट में कैसे दावे किए गए","Has India deployed 12 nuclear weapons, how claims were made in a report",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,टीएमसी और राज्यसभा से इस्तीफ़ा देने के बाद असम क्यों जाना चाहती हैं सुष्मिता देव","Live, Why does Sushmita Dev want to go to Assam after resigning from TMC and Rajya Sabha?",0.0,neutral,"[('TMC', 'ORG'), ('Rajya Sabha', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सुष्मिता देव कौन हैं, जिन्होंने ममता बनर्जी की टीएमसी से तोड़ा नाता","Who is Sushmita Dev, who broke ties with Mamata Banerjee's TMC?",0.0,neutral,"[(""Mamata Banerjee's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,उत्तर कोरिया यात्रा के दौरान किम जोंग-उन के साथ शी जिनपिंग के मतभेद कहां दिखे,Where were Xi Jinping's differences with Kim Jong-un seen during his visit to North Korea?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Xi Jinping's"", 'PERSON'), ('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"मीनाक्षी नटराजन का नामांकन रद्द होने से बीजेपी के तीनों उम्मीदवारों की जीत तय, वाक़ई कांग्रेस से चूक हुई है?","Due to cancellation of nomination of Meenakshi Natarajan, victory of all three BJP candidates is certain, has Congress really made a mistake?",1.0,positive,"[('Meenakshi Natarajan', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"एयर इंडिया विमान हादसा: 'पोती की याद आती है तो बिस्कुट याद आने लगते हैं, मौत यहाँ बेवजह आई थी'","Air India plane crash: 'When I remember my granddaughter, I start remembering biscuits, death had come here unnecessarily'",-1.0,negative,"[('Air India', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ईरान ने कुवैत को इस तरह से टारगेट क्यों किया, जानिए क्या होगा इसका असर","Why did Iran target Kuwait in this way, know what will be its effect",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बेन स्टोक्स शराब से जुड़े नए विवाद में फँसे, कप्तानी जाने और करियर थमने तक पहुँचा मामला","Ben Stokes caught in a new controversy related to alcohol, the matter reached the point of losing captaincy and stopping his career.",0.0,neutral,"[('Ben Stokes', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका ने कहा- ईरान ने उसके हेलिकॉप्टर को मार गिराया, किया जवाबी हमला","America said- Iran shot down its helicopter, retaliated",0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"राज्यसभा चुनाव: कांग्रेस नेता मीनाक्षी नटराजन का नामांकन जिस आधार पर रद्द हुआ, वो कितना सही है?",Rajya Sabha Elections: How correct is the basis on which nomination of Congress leader Meenakshi Natarajan was cancelled?,0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Meenakshi Natarajan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Tren de Aragua: como facção venezuelana na mira de Trump age no Norte do Brasil,Tren de Aragua: how Venezuelan faction in Trump's sights acts in Northern Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Northern Brazil', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A onda de protestos violentos na Irlanda do Norte após homem estrangeiro ser acusado de ataque com faca,Wave of violent protests in Northern Ireland after foreign man accused of knife attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Northern Ireland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Análise: Trump e Netanyahu queriam remodelar o Oriente Médio – agora correm o risco de uma crise permanente,Analysis: Trump and Netanyahu wanted to reshape the Middle East – now they risk a permanent crisis,-1.0,negative,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Playboy dos pobres': os quadrinhos eróticos esquecidos de dois dos maiores poetas do Brasil, Alice Ruiz e Paulo Leminski","'Poor man's Playboy': the forgotten erotic comics of two of Brazil's greatest poets, Alice Ruiz and Paulo Leminski",1.0,positive,"[('Playboy', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Alice Ruiz', 'PERSON'), ('Paulo Leminski', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Sem seleção na Copa, chineses torcem por árbitro 'campeão de cartões vermelhos'","Without a team in the World Cup, the Chinese support the referee who 'wins red cards'",1.0,positive,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Brasil, Messi, Klose e mais: as seleções e jogadores que detêm recordes nas Copas do Mundo","Brazil, Messi, Klose and more: the teams and players who hold World Cup records",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Klose', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,EUA lançam ataques contra o Irã em retaliação à derrubada de helicóptero militar,US launches strikes against Iran in retaliation for downing of military helicopter,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que a história revela sobre as  seleções que já conquistaram a Copa do Mundo,What history reveals about the teams that have won the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Copa do Mundo 2026: confira as datas e horários dos jogos de todos os grupos da 1ª fase,2026 World Cup: check the dates and times of games for all groups in the 1st phase,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('the 1st', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: украинские ракеты Flamingo поразили военный завод в Чебоксарах; российские войска атаковали Запорожье, Харьков и Одессу","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Ukrainian Flamingo missiles hit a military plant in Cheboksary; Russian troops attacked Zaporozhye, Kharkov and Odessa",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Cheboksary', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON'), ('Kharkov', 'GPE'), ('Odessa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"США нанесли удары по Ирану в ответ на сбитый в Ормузском проливе вертолет Apache, Иран в ответ атаковал американские базы в регионе",The United States launched strikes on Iran in response to the downing of an Apache helicopter in the Strait of Hormuz; Iran responded by attacking American bases in the region,-1.0,negative,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Apache', 'PRODUCT'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Дороже, чем в России и Катаре. Кто заработает на американском чемпионате мира по футболу?",More expensive than in Russia and Qatar. Who will make money from the American World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('the American World Cup', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«У меня были все необходимые документы и виза». Рефери из Сомали — о запрете на въезд в США для работы на ЧМ-2026,“I had all the necessary documents and a visa.” A referee from Somalia is banned from entering the United States to work at the 2026 World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Somalia', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,НАСА назвало имена членов экипажа миссии «Артемида-3» — очередного этапа на пути к высадке на Луне,"NASA has named the crew members of the Artemis 3 mission, the next step towards landing on the Moon.",-1.0,negative,"[('NASA', 'ORG'), ('Artemis', 'NORP'), ('Moon', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Мир на войне. Рекордное число конфликтов со времен Второй мировой,Peace at war. Record number of conflicts since World War II,-0.3333,negative,"[('World War II', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зачем лидер Китая Си Цзиньпин поехал в КНДР? Китаист Алексей Чигадаев объясняет в подкасте «Что это было?»,Why did Chinese leader Xi Jinping go to North Korea? Sinologist Alexey Chigadayev explains in the podcast “What was that?”,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Alexey Chigadayev', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,ВСУ блокируют Крым? | Военное время, Продолжительность 10,53","Video, Ukrainian Armed Forces are blocking Crimea? | Wartime, Duration 10.53",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Crimea', 'ORG'), ('10.53', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Израиль снова ударил по югу Ливана, проигнорировав угрозы Ирана","Israel strikes southern Lebanon again, ignoring Iran's threats",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Кении полиция снова разогнала акцию протеста против планов США построить карантинный центр для больных Эболой американцев,"In Kenya, police again dispersed a protest against US plans to build a quarantine center for Americans sick with Ebola.",0.0,neutral,"[('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Ebola', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米軍、イランに報復攻撃　ホルムズ海峡での米軍ヘリ撃墜受け,US military launches retaliatory attack on Iran after US military helicopter shot down in Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】米・イスラエル首脳は中東再編を目指した……が、今や終わらない紛争の危機に　BBC国際編集長,[Commentary] U.S. and Israeli leaders aimed to reorganize the Middle East...but now they are on the verge of an endless conflict BBC International Editor-in-Chief,-1.0,negative,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('BBC International', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米アンソロピック、「一般向けには強力過ぎる」AIツールを一般公開,Anthropic releases AI tool ``too powerful for general use'' to public,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゼレンスキー氏が英国王と面会、「揺るぎない」支援に感謝,"Zelensky meets British king, thanks for 'unwavering' support",0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,「新たな戦争をしない」とは約束していない、トランプ氏が選挙公約を否定, 所要時間 1,09","Video, Trump denies campaign promise, promises no new wars, Duration 1,09",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('1,09', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナが占領地への攻撃強化、ロシアの燃料危機は悪化,"Ukraine steps up attacks on occupied territories, Russia's fuel crisis worsens",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,「どうか助けて」　米ミサイルがタンカーに直撃、インド人乗組員から救助要請,“Please help me” Indian crew asks for rescue after US missile hits tanker,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,宇宙船から南半球のオーロラ撮影　うねる緑の光, 所要時間 0,45","Video, Aurora photographed in the southern hemisphere from a spacecraft, undulating green light, time required 0,45",0.0,neutral,"[('Aurora', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 イランがイスラエル攻撃……イランの政権は自分たちの粘り強さを自覚か,[Commentary] Iran attacks Israel...Is the Iranian regime aware of its own tenacity?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 大会初のソマリア人審判、アメリカ入国を拒否される,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] First Somali referee at the tournament is denied entry to the US,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('First Somali', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Mashambulizi kati ya Marekani na Iran yashika kasi baada ya helikopta ya doria ya Marekani kudunguliwa","Live, Attacks between the United States and Iran accelerate after the US patrol helicopter is shot down",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi mashambulizi ya hivi majuzi ya Iran dhidi ya Israel yanavyoashiria kuwa Tehran inazidi kujihisi kuwa na nguvu,How Iran's recent attacks against Israel indicate that Tehran is increasingly feeling powerful,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jezi hizi ndizo nzuri zaidi Kombe la Dunia 2026?,Are these the best kits for the 2026 World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Tanzania inaweza kuwa mzalishaji mkubwa wa urani duniani?",Can Tanzania become the largest producer of uranium in the world?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Waridi wa BBC: 'Kunyimwa haki ya kulea mwanangu, haikuzima shauku yangu kuwa muongoza watalii'","BBC's Rose: 'Deprived of the right to raise my son, did not extinguish my passion to be a tour guide'",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Real Madrid wanamsaka Calafiori , Man United wamfukuzia Lewis Hall wa Newcastle","European football rumours: Real Madrid are looking for Calafiori, Man United are chasing Newcastle's Lewis Hall",0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Real Madrid', 'ORG'), ('Calafiori', 'PRODUCT'), ('Newcastle', 'GPE'), ('Lewis Hall', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi uvumbuzi wa Iran ulivyoleta ustaarabu duniani,How Iran's inventions brought civilization to the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Gachagua kupinga uamuzi wa Mahakama katika Mahakama ya Rufaa,Gachagua chose to challenge the Court's decision in the Court of Appeal,0.0,neutral,"[('Court', 'ORG'), ('the Court of Appeal', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wakazi wakimbia mji wa Lebanon huku Israeli ikionya kufanya mashambulizi,Residents flee the city of Lebanon as Israel warns of attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Mwaka huu ni mashindano kwa ajili ya matajiri pekee?,World Cup 2026: Is this year a tournament only for the rich?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('this year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Why has Belfast erupted in anti-immigrant violence after a knife attack?,Why has Belfast erupted in anti-immigrant violence after a knife attack?,-1.0,negative,"[('Belfast', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Who is Graham Platner, the Democratic primary winner who slammed Gaza war?","Who is Graham Platner, the Democratic primary winner who slammed Gaza war?",0.0,neutral,"[('Graham Platner', 'PERSON'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,A four-year-old’s recovery from the trauma of war in Lebanon,A four-year-old’s recovery from the trauma of war in Lebanon,-1.0,negative,"[('four-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"‘United As One’: Why US, Mexico and Canada are cohosting World Cup 2026","‘United As One’: Why US, Mexico and Canada are cohosting World Cup 2026",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"India’s Bengal pushes Muslim Bangladeshis out, deepening religious tensions","India’s Bengal pushes Muslim Bangladeshis out, deepening religious tensions",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup 2026 contenders: Can Messi deliver again for Argentina?,World Cup 2026 contenders: Can Messi deliver again for Argentina?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Photos: Anti-immigration protests break out in Belfast after knife attack,Photos: Anti-immigration protests break out in Belfast after knife attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Belfast', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Rising from the rubble: A Gaza tech incubator defies Israel’s war,Rising from the rubble: A Gaza tech incubator defies Israel’s war,-1.0,negative,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Spidercam crashes onto pitch during Hungary match,Spidercam crashes onto pitch during Hungary match,0.0,neutral,"[('Hungary', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Twelve killed in Johannesburg mass shooting, manhunt under way","Twelve killed in Johannesburg mass shooting, manhunt under way",-1.0,negative,"[('Twelve', 'CARDINAL'), ('Johannesburg', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Bengal CM keeps Home, Swapan gets Finance in portfolio allocation","West Bengal CM keeps Home, Swapan gets Finance in portfolio allocation",0.0,neutral,"[('West Bengal CM', 'NORP'), ('Swapan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,President congratulates PM Modi on becoming longest-serving elected Prime Minister,President congratulates PM Modi on becoming longest-serving elected Prime Minister,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Kerala actor assault case: Another HC judge recuses from memory card leak hearing,Kerala actor assault case: Another HC judge recuses from memory card leak hearing,0.0,neutral,"[('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('assault', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"YouTuber Mukhtar arrested in two criminal cases, police informs Madras High Court","YouTuber Mukhtar arrested in two criminal cases, police informs Madras High Court",0.0,neutral,"[('YouTuber Mukhtar', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Madras High Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia war LIVE: Iran targets U.S. bases in Jordan, Gulf after Trump orders strikes near Hormuz","West Asia war LIVE: Iran targets U.S. bases in Jordan, Gulf after Trump orders strikes near Hormuz",-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Jordan', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The unfinished promise of transparency in CBSE’s digital evaluation system,The unfinished promise of transparency in CBSE’s digital evaluation system,0.0,neutral,"[('CBSE', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Bharathiraja passes away | Tributes pour in, T.N. Govt to accord state honours","Bharathiraja passes away | Tributes pour in, T.N. Govt to accord state honours",0.0,neutral,"[('Tributes', 'GPE'), ('T.N. Govt', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,China’s role in the international order,China’s role in the international order,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ali Fazal interview: ‘Everybody should have access to pride’,Ali Fazal interview: ‘Everybody should have access to pride’,0.0,neutral,"[('Ali Fazal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,New and raw: On Nepal-India ties,New and raw: On Nepal-India ties,0.0,neutral,"[('Nepal-India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US strikes Iran in response to downing of military helicopter,US strikes Iran in response to downing of military helicopter,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Inside Myanmar, rebels are losing ground as military forces men into army","Inside Myanmar, rebels are losing ground as military forces men into army",0.0,neutral,"[('Myanmar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,World Cup referee denied US entry arrives home to hero's welcome in Somalia,World Cup referee denied US entry arrives home to hero's welcome in Somalia,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Somalia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Manslaughter charges laid over deadly Hong Kong fire,Manslaughter charges laid over deadly Hong Kong fire,0.0,neutral,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Model who alleges Kanye West choked her tells BBC she felt 'suffocated and scared',Model who alleges Kanye West choked her tells BBC she felt 'suffocated and scared',0.0,neutral,"[('Kanye West', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Manhunt under way in South Africa after 12 killed in mass shooting in Johannesburg,Manhunt under way in South Africa after 12 killed in mass shooting in Johannesburg,-1.0,negative,"[('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Johannesburg', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Pakistan launches deadly air strikes in Afghanistan, reigniting tensions","Pakistan launches deadly air strikes in Afghanistan, reigniting tensions",0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Zelensky under pressure to end row with Poland over WW2 name of army unit,Zelensky under pressure to end row with Poland over WW2 name of army unit,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('WW2', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nasa names next astronauts for Artemis Moon programme,Nasa names next astronauts for Artemis Moon programme,0.0,neutral,"[('Nasa', 'ORG'), ('Artemis Moon', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Alleged Bondi Beach gunman charged with another 19 offences,Alleged Bondi Beach gunman charged with another 19 offences,0.0,neutral,"[('Bondi Beach', 'PERSON'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: Trump Issues New Threat Against Iran After Both Sides Exchange Strikes,Iran War Live Updates: Trump Issues New Threat Against Iran After Both Sides Exchange Strikes,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Quiet Oman Landed Itself in Trump’s Cross Hairs,How Quiet Oman Landed Itself in Trump’s Cross Hairs,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump’s Cross Hairs', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Night of Violence Grips Belfast After Stabbing Attack,Night of Violence Grips Belfast After Stabbing Attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Stabbing Attack', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Twist in Ukraine’s Drone Campaign Is ‘Really Hurting the Russians’,A Twist in Ukraine’s Drone Campaign Is ‘Really Hurting the Russians’,0.0,neutral,"[('Twist', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine’s Drone Campaign Is ‘Really Hurting', 'ORG'), ('Russians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"On the Eve of the World Cup, U.S. Immigration Policy Turns Some Away","On the Eve of the World Cup, U.S. Immigration Policy Turns Some Away",0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('U.S. Immigration Policy', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘Clumsy Diplomacy’: Inside the U.S.-Kenya Feud Over an Ebola Camp,‘Clumsy Diplomacy’: Inside the U.S.-Kenya Feud Over an Ebola Camp,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Argentina’s World Cup Sticker Albums Are a Low-Tech Craze Immune to the Digital Revolution,Argentina’s World Cup Sticker Albums Are a Low-Tech Craze Immune to the Digital Revolution,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina’s World Cup Sticker Albums Are', 'ORG'), ('the Digital Revolution', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Germany Drops Plan to Build Warplane With Allies, Hindering Push to Rearm","Germany Drops Plan to Build Warplane With Allies, Hindering Push to Rearm",-1.0,negative,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Hindering Push', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Drones Stray Into Neighboring Countries as Russia and Ukraine Battle,Drones Stray Into Neighboring Countries as Russia and Ukraine Battle,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_10,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Roar of ‘Cease-Fire’ in a Once-Thriving City,The Roar of ‘Cease-Fire’ in a Once-Thriving City,0.0,neutral,[]
