Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Se hizo rico vendiendo camellos y oro: ahora sus tropas controlan la mitad de Sudán,He became rich selling camels and gold: now his troops control half of Sudan,0.10416666666666667,"[('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Matthei, Kast y Kaiser: la batalla entre los candidatos de derecha para pasar a la segunda vuelta en las elecciones presidenciales en Chile","Matthei, Kast and Kaiser: the battle between right-wing candidates to advance to the second round in the presidential elections in Chile",-0.1,"[('Matthei', 'GPE'), ('Kaiser', 'PERSON'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La presidenta Claudia Sheinbaum denuncia a un hombre que la acosó mientras caminaba en Ciudad de México,President Claudia Sheinbaum denounces a man who harassed her while she was walking in Mexico City,0.0,"[('Claudia Sheinbaum', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico City', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Mi hijo me dio la espalda"" y elogios a Franco: qué cuenta en sus memorias el rey emérito Juan Carlos de España y por qué su publicación es tan polémica","""My son turned his back on me"" and praise for Franco: what does King Emeritus Juan Carlos of Spain say in his memoirs and why his publication is so controversial",0.275,"[('Franco', 'PERSON'), ('Juan Carlos', 'PERSON'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Varias concursantes de Miss Universo abandonan un evento después de que el director del certamen en Tailandia ""humillara"" a Miss México","Several Miss Universe contestants leave an event after the director of the pageant in Thailand ""humiliated"" Miss Mexico",0.0,"[('Thailand', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ज़ोहरान ममदानी की जीत पर अरब और इसराइल का मीडिया क्या कह रहा है?,What are Arab and Israeli media saying about Zoharan Mamdani's victory?,0.0,"[('Arab', 'NORP'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), (""Zoharan Mamdani's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,बिहार चुनाव: प्रशांत किशोर कहां हैं?","Live, Bihar Elections: Where is Prashant Kishor?",0.13636363636363635,[]
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ज़ोहरान ममदानी के मेयर बनने के बाद फिर चर्चा में न्यूयॉर्क, अमेरिका की राजधानी ना होते हुए भी इतना अहम क्यों?","After Zohran Mamdani became the mayor, New York again in discussion, why is it so important despite not being the capital of America?",0.2681818181818182,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार चुनाव: पहले चरण के लिए वोटिंग जारी, जानें कौन से बड़े चेहरे हैं मैदान में","Bihar Elections: Voting continues for the first phase, know which big faces are in the fray",0.125,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ज़ोहरान ममदानी की पत्नी रमा की इतनी चर्चा क्यों?,Why is Zohran Mamdani's wife Rama discussed so much?,0.2,"[(""Zohran Mamdani's"", 'PERSON'), ('Rama', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"राहुल गांधी ने फिर लगाया वोट चोरी का आरोप, बिहार चुनाव को लेकर ज़ाहिर की आशंका","Rahul Gandhi again accused of vote theft, expressed apprehension about Bihar elections",0.0,"[('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"न्यूयॉर्क में गूंजे नेहरू के बोल, ज़ोहरान ममदानी ने याद दिलाया मशहूर भाषण","Nehru's words echoed in New York, Zohran Mamdani reminded of his famous speech",0.3181818181818182,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ममदानी ने हासिल की ऐतिहासिक जीत, पर असली चुनौतियां अब शुरू होंगी","Mamdani achieved historic victory, but real challenges will begin now",0.1,"[('Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"हिमाचल प्रदेश: सरकारी स्कूल में दलित बच्चे के उत्पीड़न का आरोप, तीन शिक्षकों पर एफ़आईआर","Himachal Pradesh: Allegation of harassment of Dalit child in government school, FIR against three teachers",0.0,"[('Dalit', 'PERSON'), ('FIR', 'ORG'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Quem ganha e quem perde com aprovação do novo IR, que eleva isenção até R$ 5 mil e taxa super-ricos","Who wins and who loses with the approval of the new IR, which increases exemption up to R$5,000 and the super-rich tax",0.04545454545454545,"[('IR', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A foto do príncipe William aos pés do Cristo Redentor que imita cena histórica de sua mãe, Diana","The photo of Prince William at the feet of Christ the Redeemer that imitates the historical scene of his mother, Diana",0.0,"[('Prince William', 'PERSON'), ('Diana', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Agência antidrogas do governo Trump lamenta morte de policiais no Rio e oferece apoio a Castro,Trump administration's drug agency mourns the death of police officers in Rio and offers support to Castro,0.1,"[('Rio', 'GPE'), ('Castro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro na Papuda? Governo do DF pede avaliação médica do ex-presidente às vésperas de possível ordem de prisão,Bolsonaro in Papuda? DF government requests medical evaluation of the former president on the eve of a possible arrest order,-0.0125,"[('Papuda', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que é a COP30, quando começa e por que ela é importante para combater mudanças climáticas","What is COP30, when does it start and why is it important to combat climate change",0.4,[]
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Como o Comando Vermelho dominou Belém, que receberá operação das Forças Armadas para a COP30","How the Red Command dominated Belém, which will receive an Armed Forces operation for COP30",0.0,"[('the Red Command', 'ORG'), ('Armed Forces', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Rama Duwaji: quem é a mulher do prefeito eleito de Nova York, Zohran Mamdani?",Rama Duwaji: who is the wife of New York mayor-elect Zohran Mamdani?,0.13636363636363635,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Os desafios do socialista Zohran Mamdani, 1º muçulmano eleito prefeito de Nova York","The challenges of socialist Zohran Mamdani, 1st Muslim elected mayor of New York",0.13636363636363635,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('1st Muslim', 'NORP'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como Trump está remodelando a Casa Branca à sua imagem,How Trump is reshaping the White House in his image,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Чечня ее не отпускала». Кто убил Айшат Баймурадову и что это значит для тех, кто решился на побег",“Chechnya did not let her go.” Who killed Aishat Baimuradova and what does this mean for those who decided to escape,-0.25625,"[('Chechnya', 'GPE'), ('Baimuradova', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трудный выбор Виктора Орбана: российская нефть для Венгрии или расположение Трампа,Viktor Orban's difficult choice: Russian oil for Hungary or Trump's favor,-0.25,"[(""Viktor Orban's"", 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: удары по Запорожской области; Путин дал указание выяснить планы США","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: attacks on the Zaporozhye region; Putin ordered to find out US plans",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Бобровая Луна»: как ее видели жители разных стран,“Beaver Moon”: how residents of different countries saw it,0.0,"[('Beaver Moon', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Британии из тюрьмы по ошибке освободили еще двух заключенных,Two more prisoners were mistakenly released from prison in Britain,0.5,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Глава Минобороны России предложил Путину возобновить ядерные испытания. Ждать ли новую ядерную гонку?,The head of the Russian Ministry of Defense suggested that Putin resume nuclear tests. Should we expect a new nuclear race?,0.06818181818181818,"[('the Russian Ministry of Defense', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Крушение грузового самолета в США: число жертв увеличилось до 12,Cargo plane crash in US: death toll rises to 12,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Новая тактика российской армии: что вместо «мясных штурмов»?, Продолжительность 34,50","Video, New tactics of the Russian army: what instead of “meat assaults”?, Duration 34.50",0.06818181818181818,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('34.50', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Мы свергли политическую династию». Почему Зохран Мамдани победил на выборах мэра Нью-Йорка и что это означает для Демпартии США?,"""We have overthrown a political dynasty."" Why did Zohran Mamdani win the mayoral election in New York and what does this mean for the US Democratic Party?",0.1559659090909091,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('the US Democratic Party', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Год Трампа. Почему США пока не смогли убедить Россию закончить войну в Украине,Year of Trump. Why the United States has not yet been able to convince Russia to end the war in Ukraine,0.5,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 米民主党が盛り返し、重要なメッセージを手に入れた……注目の選挙から分かること,[Commentary] The US Democratic Party has made a comeback and received an important message... What we can learn from the closely watched election,0.4,"[('The US Democratic Party', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,離陸中の貨物機からエンジンが脱落し墜落、少なくとも12人死亡　米ケンタッキー州,"Engine falls off from cargo plane during takeoff and crashes, killing at least 12 people in Kentucky, US",-0.3,"[('at least 12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kentucky', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ガザ市東部、2年続く戦争で完全に荒廃　現地をBBC記者が取材, 所要時間 0,50","Video, BBC reporter covers eastern Gaza City, completely devastated by two years of war, time required: 0,50",0.1,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Gaza City', 'GPE'), ('two years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,【解説】 「民主社会主義者」とは？　次期ニューヨーク市長のマムダニ氏, 所要時間 1,58","Video, [Commentary] What is a ""democratic socialist""? Mr. Mamdani, the next mayor of New York, time required 1,58",0.06818181818181818,"[('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('1,58', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,メキシコ大統領、路上で体を触られる　加害者の男性を告訴へ,Mexican president to sue man who groped him on the street,0.0,"[('Mexican', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,フィリピンで台風の大被害、死者少なくとも114人に　大統領が「国家災害」宣言,At least 114 people killed in typhoon damage in Philippines; president declares ``national disaster'',-0.25,"[('At least 114', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ニューヨーク市長選、民主党のマムダニ氏が当選確実に,Democrat Mamdani wins New York mayoral election,0.21818181818181817,"[('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,チェイニー元米副大統領が84歳で死去　対テロ戦争主導、トランプ氏と対立,"Former US Vice President Cheney dies at age 84, leading war on terror and confronting Trump",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Cheney', 'PERSON'), ('age 84', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ベッカム氏が「サー・デイヴィッド」に、英国王誕生日の叙勲で　作家イシグロ氏にも勲章,Mr. Beckham awards ``Sir David'' and author Ishiguro a decoration on the British King's birthday.,0.0,"[('Beckham', 'PERSON'), (""David''"", 'PERSON'), ('Ishiguro', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025 ulikiuka maadili ya kidemokrasia - AU","Directly, the Tanzania 2025 election violated democratic values ​​- AU",0.1,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('democratic', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Lipa fidia ama ufe: Simulizi za 'kutisha' kutoka kwa jamaa za wafungwa wa RSF El Fasher,Pay ransom or die: 'Horrifying' stories from relatives of RSF El Fasher prisoners,-0.9,"[('El Fasher', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Sauti,'Heche anakabiliwa na mashtaka mawili ya ugaidi' – Wakili wake, Muda 3,58","Sauti, 'Heche faces two charges of terrorism' - His lawyer, Time 3,58",0.0,"[('Heche', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Mwanangu alipigwa risasi akafariki akielekea dukani',Protests in Tanzania: 'My son was shot and died on his way to the store',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Alhamisi: Real Madrid yajiondoa kwenye mbio za kumsajili Guehi,European Football Rumors Thursday: Real Madrid withdraw from the race to sign Guehi,0.1,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Real Madrid', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Shughuli zarejea Tanzania, bei za bidhaa bado kilio kwa wananchi","Activities are returning to Tanzania, the prices of products are still high for the people",0.16,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, lishe inaweza kuathiri nguvu za kiume?",Can diet affect male potency?,0.0,[]
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Tuliwaona polisi waliowapiga risasi jamaa zetu',Protests in Tanzania: 'We saw the police who shot our relatives',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Meya mpya wa New York ameandikisha historia - lakini changamoto halisi zinamsubiri - Uchambuzi,The new mayor of New York has made history - but real challenges await him - Analysis,0.15757575757575756,"[('New York', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Sijamuona mwanangu tangu Jumatano',Protests in Tanzania: 'I haven't seen my son since Wednesday',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE')]"
