Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Dimiten el director general de la BBC y la máxima responsable de noticias tras las críticas por la edición de un documental sobre Trump,The director general of the BBC and the head of news resign after criticism over the editing of a documentary about Trump,0.02500000000000001,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los centenares de mujeres africanas llevadas bajo engaños a la República de Tartaristán para fabricar drones rusos,The hundreds of African women tricked into the Republic of Tatarstan to manufacture Russian drones,0.0,"[('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('the Republic of Tatarstan', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La trabajadora guatemalteca que murió de un disparo tras llegar a limpiar la casa equivocada en EE.UU.,The Guatemalan worker who was shot dead after arriving to clean the wrong house in the US.,-0.1111111111111111,"[('Guatemalan', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La historia de los aperreadores españoles que usaron jaurías para dominar a los incas en Perú,The story of the Spanish bulldogs who used packs to dominate the Incas in Peru,0.0,"[('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Incas', 'GPE'), ('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quiénes fueron los hermanos Hunt, los ""gangsters de la plata"" que manipularon el precio del metal y provocaron el colapso del mercado","Who were the Hunt brothers, the ""silver gangsters"" who manipulated the price of the metal and caused the market to collapse?",0.0,"[('Hunt', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,डोनाल्ड ट्रंप किस तरह ज़ोहरान ममदानी की 'न्यूयॉर्क योजना' पर लगा सकते हैं ब्रेक,How Donald Trump can put brakes on Zohran Mamdani's 'New York Plan',0.13636363636363635,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), (""Zohran Mamdani's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,फ़रीदाबाद में 360 किलो विस्फोटक बरामद: गिरिराज सिंह क्या बोले","Live, 360 kg explosives recovered in Faridabad: What did Giriraj Singh say?",0.13636363636363635,"[('360 kg explosives', 'QUANTITY'), ('Faridabad', 'GPE'), ('Giriraj Singh', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"9 मिनट में हाफ़ सेंचुरी, 8 गेंदों पर 8 छक्के: कौन है ये क्रिकेटर","Half century in 9 minutes, 8 sixes in 8 balls: Who is this cricketer?",-0.16666666666666666,"[('Half century', 'DATE'), ('9 minutes', 'TIME'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('8', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बीबीसी के डायरेक्टर जनरल ने दिया इस्तीफ़ा, ट्रंप से जुड़े प्रोग्राम का क्या था मामला","Director General of BBC resigned, what was the matter with the program related to Trump?",0.02500000000000001,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,उत्तराखंड में 'पहाड़ बनाम मैदान' से अब कैसे आया सियासी भूचाल,How did 'mountains vs plains' create political turmoil in Uttarakhand?,0.0,"[('Uttarakhand', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सर्दियों में गरम या ठंडा पानी, किससे नहाना बेहतर?","Hot or cold water, which is better to take bath in winter?",0.05000000000000001,"[('winter', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,मुसलमानों को आरएसएस में आने की अनुमति है?- इस सवाल पर क्या बोले मोहन भागवत,Are Muslims allowed to join RSS? What did Mohan Bhagwat say on this question?,0.0,"[('Muslims', 'NORP'), ('RSS', 'ORG'), ('Mohan Bhagwat', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,एलन मस्क अपना पैसा इस तरह ख़र्च करते हैं,This is how Elon Musk spends his money,0.0,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,आज़ादी के बाद जूनागढ़ कैसे बना भारत का हिस्सा?- विवेचना,How did Junagadh become a part of India after independence?- Discussion,0.0,"[('Junagadh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Trump começou a dar tanta atenção à América do Sul (e o que conseguiu com isso),Why Trump started paying so much attention to South America (and what he achieved with it),0.2,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('South America', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Diretor-geral da BBC e diretora de jornalismo pedem demissão,BBC director general and director of journalism resign,0.05000000000000002,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como é viver sob a lei de ferro do Comando Vermelho (que continua exatamente como antes da megaoperação policial no Rio),What it's like to live under the iron law of the Red Command (which continues exactly as it did before the mega police operation in Rio),0.12878787878787878,"[('the Red Command', 'ORG'), ('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Tornado destrói 90% de cidade e deixa 6 mortos no Paraná; o que se sabe,Tornado destroys 90% of the city and leaves 6 dead in Paraná; what is known,-0.2,"[('Tornado', 'ORG'), ('90%', 'PERCENT'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Paraná', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Na Celac, Lula diz que América Latina quer ser 'região de paz', mas não menciona diretamente Venezuela ou ataques dos EUA a barcos","At Celac, Lula says that Latin America wants to be a 'region of peace', but does not directly mention Venezuela or US attacks on boats",0.07500000000000001,"[('Celac', 'ORG'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Latin America', 'LOC'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como é viver com prolapso genital: 'Eu sentia que meus órgãos estavam caindo',What it's like to live with genital prolapse: 'I felt like my organs were falling out',0.13636363636363635,[]
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Presos libertados por engano: a série de erros que pressiona governo britânico,Prisoners released by mistake: the series of errors that put pressure on the British government,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As jovens que são entregues aos deuses e sofrem exploração sexual,Young women who are handed over to the gods and suffer sexual exploitation,0.3,[]
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como as micro-ondas nos ajudam a conversar e ouvir o Universo,How microwaves help us talk to and listen to the Universe,0.0,"[('Universe', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сенаторы в США договорились остановить самый долгий в истории шатдаун,US senators agreed to stop the longest shutdown in history,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский заявил, что Путин «находится в тупиковой ситуации»","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Zelensky said Putin is “in a deadlock”",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Гендиректор Би-би-си Тим Дэйви уходит в отставку на фоне скандала с речью Трампа,BBC director general Tim Davey resigns amid Trump speech scandal,0.05000000000000002,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Tim Davey', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Бразилии начинается климатический саммит COP30. Что это такое и почему это важно для борьбы с изменением климата?,The COP30 climate summit begins in Brazil. What is it and why is it important to combat climate change?,0.4,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Илон Маск делает ставку на человекоподобных роботов. Нужны ли они нам?,Elon Musk is betting on humanoid robots. Do we need them?,0.0,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Скульптура, которой 12 тысяч лет. Что она может рассказать о самосознании наших предков?",A sculpture that is 12 thousand years old. What can it tell us about the self-awareness of our ancestors?,0.1,"[('12 thousand years old', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Рабыни божьи». Как индийские девушки, став девадаси, попадают в ловушку сексуальной эксплуатации","""Slaves of God."" How Indian girls become devadasi and fall into the trap of sexual exploitation",0.5,"[('Slaves of God', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Умер российский художник Эрик Булатов,Russian artist Erik Bulatov has died,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Erik Bulatov', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Лодка с мигрантами затонула у берегов Таиланда, десятки людей пропали без вести","Boat carrying migrants sank off the coast of Thailand, leaving dozens missing",-0.2,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Филиппины готовятся к «супертайфуну», почти миллион человек эвакуированы","Philippines braces for 'super typhoon', nearly a million people evacuated",0.21666666666666667,"[('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('nearly a million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,BBCの会長とニュース部門CEOが辞任　トランプ氏のドキュメンタリー番組の編集めぐり,BBC chairman and news CEO resign over editing of Trump documentary,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,台風26号、フィリピン直撃　約140万人が避難し死者2人を確認,"Typhoon No. 26 hits the Philippines, approximately 1.4 million people evacuated, 2 confirmed dead",-0.06666666666666667,"[('Typhoon No', 'EVENT'), ('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('approximately 1.4 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、兵士1人の遺体を受け取る　2014年にハマスが待ち伏せ攻撃で殺害,Israel receives body of soldier killed in 2014 ambush by Hamas,-0.2,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('2014', 'DATE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,幸運のネコ、ぼろぼろのサッカーボール……2年間の戦争でガザ住民が手放さなかったもの,"A lucky cat, a tattered soccer ball...things that Gaza residents didn't let go of during two years of war.",0.3333333333333333,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('two years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏によるポートランドへの州兵派遣は「違法」、米連邦地裁が判断,"Trump's deployment of the National Guard to Portland was ""illegal,"" a federal judge rules.",-0.5,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the National Guard', 'ORG'), ('Portland', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ各地で数千フライトに欠航や遅延　連邦政府閉鎖の影響で便数削減命令,Thousands of flights canceled or delayed across the U.S. Order to reduce flight numbers due to federal government shutdown,-0.125,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、ハマスから棺を受け取る　人質の遺体が入っているとハマス説明,Israel receives coffin from Hamas; Hamas says it contains the bodies of hostages,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,DNAの構造解明でノーベル賞、ジェイムズ・ワトソン氏死去　97歳,"James Watson, winner of Nobel Prize for elucidating the structure of DNA, dies at age 97",0.0,"[('James Watson', 'PERSON'), ('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('age 97', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タンザニア大統領選めぐる抗議デモ、少なくとも240人を反逆罪で起訴　暴力的弾圧で多数死傷,At least 240 people charged with treason during protests over Tanzanian presidential election; violent crackdown leaves many dead and injured,-0.2,"[('At least 240', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mkurugenzi Mkuu wa BBC ajiuzulu","Immediately, the Director General of the BBC resigns",0.05000000000000002,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini viongozi wawili wa BBC wamejiuzulu kwa wakati mmoja?,Why have two BBC leaders resigned at the same time?,0.0,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nini mustakabali wa Tanzania baada ya maandamano?,What is the future of Tanzania after the protests?,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Man United inawafukuzia Gallagher na Stiller,European football rumours: Man United are chasing Gallagher and Stiller,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Man United', 'PERSON'), ('Gallagher', 'PERSON'), ('Stiller', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Museveni akiri wanaharakati wa Kenya walikamatwa Uganda,President Museveni admits Kenyan activists were arrested in Uganda,0.0,"[('Museveni', 'PERSON'), ('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('Uganda', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Mtoto wangu wa miaka sita ana shida ya kuongea, je, niwe na wasiwasi?","My six-year-old has a speech impediment, should I be worried?",0.0,"[('six-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Binti wa rais wa zamani wa Afrika Kusini anayekabiliwa na mashtaka ya ugaidi,The daughter of a former South African president facing terrorism charges,0.0,"[('South African', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Zaidi ya watu 400 washtakiwa katika mikoa mbalimbali,Protests in Tanzania: More than 400 people accused in various regions,0.25,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('More than 400', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Ngozi yangu ilichubuka': Jinsi wanawake wa Kiafrika walivyolaghaiwa kutengeneza ndege za kivita za Urusi,'My skin peeled off': How African women were tricked into building Russian fighter jets,0.0,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_10,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumapili:Spurs wanamtaka winga wa Everton Ndiaye,Football rumors Sunday: Spurs want Everton winger Ndiaye,0.0,"[('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Everton', 'PERSON'), ('Ndiaye', 'ORG')]"
