Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Kim Yong-nam, el impasible jefe de Estado de Corea del Norte que sobrevivió a las brutales purgas del régimen y sirvió a tres generaciones de la dinastía Kim","Kim Yong-nam, the stolid head of state of North Korea who survived the regime's brutal purges and served three generations of the Kim dynasty",-0.875,"[('Kim Yong-nam', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Kim dynasty', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Miles de vuelos cancelados y con retraso en EE.UU. como consecuencia del prolongado cierre del gobierno,Thousands of flights canceled and delayed in the US as a result of the prolonged government shutdown,0.0,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Muere James Watson, el premio Nobel despojado de sus títulos por reiterar que los negros son menos inteligentes que los blancos por sus genes","James Watson dies, the Nobel Prize winner stripped of his titles for reiterating that black people are less intelligent than white people because of their genes",0.11666666666666668,"[('James Watson', 'PERSON'), ('the Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es Nawat Itsaragrisil, el director de Miss Universo Tailandia en el centro de la polémica por la ""humillación"" a Miss México","Who is Nawat Itsaragrisil, the director of Miss Universe Thailand at the center of the controversy over the ""humiliation"" of Miss Mexico",-0.1,"[('Nawat Itsaragrisil', 'PERSON'), ('Universe Thailand', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Una cita de 20 minutos con un depredador de Tinder destruyó mi vida durante años""","""A 20-minute date with a Tinder predator destroyed my life for years""",0.0,"[('20-minute', 'TIME'), ('Tinder', 'ORG'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"महार वतन की ज़मीनें क्या हैं, जिसे 1800 करोड़ की बजाय ₹300 करोड़ में खरीदने का आरोप अजित पवार के बेटे पर लगा","What are the lands of Mahar Watan, which Ajit Pawar's son was accused of buying for ₹ 300 crore instead of ₹ 1800 crore",0.0,"[('Mahar Watan', 'PERSON'), (""Ajit Pawar's"", 'PERSON'), ('300', 'MONEY'), ('1800', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,रूस से तेल खरीदने के बावजूद हंगरी को अमेरिकी प्रतिबंधों से एक साल की छूट","Live, Hungary gets one year exemption from US sanctions despite buying oil from Russia",0.13636363636363635,"[('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('one year', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव: पहले चरण में रिकॉर्ड मतदान की वजह कहीं एसआईआर तो नहीं?,Bihar Elections: Is SIR the reason for record voting in the first phase?,0.25,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दही से लेकर ब्रेड तक, रोज़ खाई जाने वाली वे चीज़ें जिनमें छिपा होता है बहुत ज़्यादा शुगर","From curd to bread, the things we eat daily contain a lot of sugar.",0.0,"[('daily', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'मुझे लगा कि यह एक शरारत है' - कैसे एक ब्राज़ीलियाई महिला भारत में 'वोट चोरी' विवाद का चेहरा बन गई,'I thought it was a prank' - how a Brazilian woman became the face of 'vote theft' controversy in India,0.0,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चीन का यह नया युद्धपोत अमेरिका और भारत को कितनी टक्कर देगा?,How much competition will this new warship of China give to America and India?,0.16818181818181818,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,दिल्ली के इस एयर क्वालिटी मॉनिटरिंग स्टेशन की कई दिनों से चर्चा, ये है वजह- ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट, अवधि 4,31","Video, This air quality monitoring station of Delhi has been discussed for many days, this is the reason - Ground report, duration 4,31",0.5,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('many days', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,यूरोप में नौकरी का झांसा: बेंगलुरु में फ़र्ज़ी एजेंटों पर लाखों रुपये ठगने का आरोप,Hoax of job in Europe: Fake agents in Bengaluru accused of defrauding lakhs of rupees,-0.5,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Bengaluru', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"एलन मस्क को मिलेगा एक लाख करोड़ डॉलर का सैलरी पैकेज, लेकिन एक शर्त है","Elon Musk will get a salary package of one trillion dollars, but there is a condition",0.0,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('one trillion dollars', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,STF rejeita recurso de Bolsonaro e mantém condenação a 27 anos de prisão: o que acontece agora?,STF rejects Bolsonaro's appeal and maintains 27-year prison sentence: what happens now?,0.0,"[('STF', 'ORG'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('27-year', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A foto de brasileira que virou centro de acusação de fraude eleitoral na Índia,The photo of a Brazilian woman who became the center of accusations of electoral fraud in India,-0.1,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Elon Musk quer produzir robôs humanoides,Why Elon Musk wants to produce humanoid robots,0.2,[]
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Narcossubmarinos e narcolanchas: como embarcações são usadas para tráfico de drogas para a Europa,Narco-submarines and narco-boats: how vessels are used to smuggle drugs to Europe,0.0,"[('Narco', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como descobrir se o vídeo que você está vendo é real ou gerado por IA,How to find out if the video you're watching is real or AI-generated,0.2,"[('AI', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,5 alimentos fáceis de trocar na sua dieta para melhorar a saúde intestinal,5 easy foods to swap into your diet to improve gut health,0.43333333333333335,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Soraya Thronicke: 'Bolsonaro me enganou, mas eu permiti'","Soraya Thronicke: 'Bolsonaro deceived me, but I allowed it'",0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'O senhor Trump está equivocado': críticas de latinos e moderação de Lula dão tom de cúpula em Belém,'Mr Trump is wrong': criticism from Latinos and Lula's moderation set the tone at the summit in Belém,-0.5,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Latinos', 'ORG'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Belém', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O homem que atropelou suspeito de esfaquear pessoas em trem no Reino Unido,The man who ran over a suspect who stabbed people on a train in the UK,0.0,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Просто консультировала». Подробности нового «дела о торговле детьми» в Москве,“Just consulting.” Details of the new “child trafficking case” in Moscow,0.13636363636363635,"[('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: беспилотник ударил по многоэтажному дому в Днепре","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: a drone hit a multi-storey building in the Dnieper",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,США после встречи Трампа с Орбаном согласились пока не блокировать поставки российских нефти и газа в Венгрию,"After Trump’s meeting with Orban, the United States agreed not to block Russian oil and gas supplies to Hungary for now",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Orban', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Hungary', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Лондоне поймали алжирца,  выпущенного из тюрьмы по ошибке. Его начали искать только через неделю",An Algerian man released from prison by mistake was caught in London. They started looking for him only a week later,0.0,"[('Algerian', 'NORP'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('only a week later', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,От Марты Вашингтон до Мелании Трамп: как первые леди США на протяжении истории использовали силу моды,From Martha Washington to Melania Trump: how US first ladies throughout history have harnessed the power of fashion,0.25,"[('Martha Washington', 'PERSON'), ('Melania Trump', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Это реальная опасность для Украины». Действительно ли в октябре ВСУ самовольно покинуло рекордное число солдат,“This is a real danger for Ukraine.” Did a record number of soldiers leave the Ukrainian Armed Forces without permission in October?,0.2,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('the Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('October', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Еврокомиссия ограничила выдачу россиянам многократных шенгенских виз. Что изменилось?,The European Commission has limited the issuance of multiple-entry Schengen visas to Russians. What has changed?,-0.03571428571428571,"[('The European Commission', 'ORG'), ('Schengen', 'PERSON'), ('Russians', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Умер Джеймс Уотсон. Он получил нобелевку за открытие структуры ДНК, но был лишён званий из-за слов о расовых различиях","James Watson has died. He received a Nobel Prize for discovering the structure of DNA, but was stripped of his titles because of his words about racial differences",0.0,"[('James Watson', 'PERSON'), ('a Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,У Китая появился уже третий авианосец. По приказу Си Цзиньпина на нем установили электромагнитные катапульты,"China has already acquired its third aircraft carrier. By order of Xi Jinping, electromagnetic catapults were installed on it",0.0,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,«Крестовый поход» Трампа: в США создают госрелигию?, Продолжительность 14,25","Video, Trump’s “Crusade”: is a state religion being created in the USA?, Duration 14.25",0.0,"[('Trump’s “Crusade', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('14.25', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏によるポートランドへの州兵派遣は「違法」、米連邦地裁が判断,"Trump's deployment of the National Guard to Portland was ""illegal,"" a federal judge rules.",-0.5,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the National Guard', 'ORG'), ('Portland', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、ハマスから棺を受け取る　人質の遺体が入っているとハマス説明,Israel receives coffin from Hamas; Hamas says it contains the bodies of hostages,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タンザニア大統領選めぐる抗議デモ、少なくとも240人を反逆罪で起訴　暴力的弾圧で多数死傷,At least 240 people charged with treason during protests over Tanzanian presidential election; violent crackdown leaves many dead and injured,-0.2,"[('At least 240', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,DNAの構造解明でノーベル賞、ジェイムズ・ワトソン氏死去　97歳,"James Watson, winner of Nobel Prize for elucidating the structure of DNA, dies at age 97",0.0,"[('James Watson', 'PERSON'), ('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('age 97', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ各地で数千フライトに欠航や遅延　連邦政府閉鎖の影響で便数削減命令,Thousands of flights canceled or delayed across the U.S. Order to reduce flight numbers due to federal government shutdown,-0.125,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ペロシ元米下院議長が引退を表明、20年にわたり下院で民主党を率いる,"Former U.S. House Speaker Pelosi announces retirement, leading Democrats in the House of Representatives for 20 years",0.0,"[('U.S. House', 'ORG'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('the House of Representatives', 'ORG'), ('20 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,口論し、原稿を破り、「国内の敵」と……引退表明のペロシ氏とトランプ氏の確執, 所要時間 0,48","Video, Bickering, tearing up manuscripts, calling out ``domestic enemies''... Pelosi announces retirement and Trump feud, Duration 0,48",0.0,"[('Bickering', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ミス・ユニバース、各国代表が抗議の「集団退席」　運営側がメキシコ代表を叱ったあと, 所要時間 1,31","Video, Miss Universe representatives from each country ``mass walk out'' in protest after management scolds Mexico representative, Duration 1,31",0.0,"[('Universe', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,台風25号、フィリピンとヴェトナムで死者少なくとも計193人,Typhoon Faxai kills at least 193 people in the Philippines and Vietnam,-0.3,"[('Typhoon Faxai', 'PERSON'), ('at least 193', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Maandamano Tanzania: Askofu Gwajima, makada wa Chadema wasakwa na polisi","Protests in Tanzania: Bishop Gwajima, Chadema cadres are wanted by the police",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Bishop Gwajima', 'ORG'), ('Chadema', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Uturuki yatoa vibali vya kukamatwa kwa Netanyahu, waziri wake wa ulinzi na maafisa 35 wakuu wa Israel","Directly, Turkey issues arrest warrants for Netanyahu, his defense minister and 35 senior Israeli officials",0.025,"[('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('35', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wanaharakati wa Kenya Bob Njagi na Nicholas Oyoo waachiliwa baada ya siku 38,Kenyan activists Bob Njagi and Nicholas Oyoo released after 38 days,0.0,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('Bob Njagi', 'PERSON'), ('Nicholas Oyoo', 'PERSON'), ('38 days', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Watu 240 washtakiwa kwa uhaini,Protests in Tanzania: 240 people accused of treason,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('240', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumamosi: Kiungo wa  Man United Kobbie Mainoo avivutia vilabu viwili vya Itali,European soccer rumors on Saturday: Man United midfielder Kobbie Mainoo is attracting interest from two Italian clubs,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Kobbie Mainoo', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Italian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Dk. Tulia ajiondoa rasmi kuwania Uspika wa Bunge la Tanzania,Dr. Tulia has officially withdrawn from running for the Speakership of the Tanzanian Parliament,0.0,"[('Tulia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Masuala yaliyoibuliwa na waangalizi wa uchaguzi mkuu wa Tanzania,Issues raised by Tanzanian general election observers,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ni marufuku kuyatembelea maeneo haya duniani,It is forbidden to visit these places in the world,0.0,[]
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Nilikimbia kivyangu na mume wangu kivyake',Protests in Tanzania: 'I ran separately and my husband separately',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Trump: Nilikuwa na 'udhibiti kamili' wa mashambulizi ya Israel dhidi ya Iran,Trump: I had 'full control' of Israel's attack on Iran,0.35,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
