Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué el polémico multimillonario tecnológico Peter Thiel se instaló en Argentina y cuál es su relación con el gobierno de Milei,Why the controversial technology billionaire Peter Thiel settled in Argentina and what is his relationship with the Milei government,0.0,neutral,"[('Peter Thiel', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las razones por las que Irán ve su acuerdo con EE.UU. como una victoria,The reasons why Iran sees its deal with the US as a victory,1.0,positive,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Quedé traumatizada por el intercambio de parejas y un sitio web facilitó el abuso""","""I was traumatized by partner swapping and a website facilitated the abuse""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Messi bate múltiples récords en su debut en el Mundial 2026: cómo el argentino adaptó su juego con los años para mantenerse en la cima del fútbol,Messi breaks multiple records in his debut at the 2026 World Cup: how the Argentine adapted his game over the years to stay at the top of football,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('the 2026 World Cup:', 'EVENT'), ('Argentine', 'NORP'), ('the years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,7 maneras de engañarte a ti mismo para comer mejor,7 ways to trick yourself into eating better,0.0,neutral,"[('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El FBI dice que frustró un plan para atacar la Casa Blanca con francotiradores y drones el día del cumpleaños de Trump,FBI says it foiled plot to attack White House with snipers and drones on Trump's birthday,-1.0,negative,"[('FBI', 'ORG'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué consecuencias está teniendo la caída de los precios de los diamantes en todo el mundo,What consequences is the fall in diamond prices having around the world?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué es el ""caso Plus Ultra"" por el que se imputó por blanqueo de capitales al expresidente español Zapatero (y qué vínculo tiene con Venezuela)","What is the ""Plus Ultra case"" for which former Spanish president Zapatero was charged with money laundering (and what connection does it have with Venezuela)",0.0,neutral,"[('Spanish', 'NORP'), ('Zapatero', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo la economía de EE.UU. continúa superando a las de sus rivales contra todo pronóstico,How the US economy continues to outperform its rivals against all odds,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¡Triplete de un ya histórico Messi! Argentina gana 3-0 contra Argelia en el Mundial 2026,Triplet for a now historic Messi! Argentina wins 3-0 against Algeria in the 2026 World Cup,1.0,positive,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Algeria', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ट्रंप ने कहा- ईरान के साथ समझौता अंतिम नहीं, फिर से 'बम गिराने' की दी धमकी","Trump said- agreement with Iran is not final, threatened to 'drop bombs' again",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,भारत ने अफ़ग़ानिस्तान को दिया 403 रनों का लक्ष्य, शुभमन ने बनाए 154 रन","Live, India gave target of 403 runs to Afghanistan, Shubman scored 154 runs",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('403', 'CARDINAL'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('Shubman', 'ORG'), ('154', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,50 डिग्री तापमान में ईरानी तेल की तस्करी करने वाले बाइक सवार,Bike riders smuggling Iranian oil in 50 degree temperature,0.0,neutral,"[('Bike', 'ORG'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('50 degree', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,समंदर में जहाज़ों और नाविकों की सुरक्षा के लिए कौन होता है ज़िम्मेदार?,Who is responsible for the safety of ships and sailors at sea?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान और अमेरिका के बीच डील कराकर पाकिस्तान को क्या होगा फ़ायदा?,What will Pakistan benefit by making a deal between Iran and America?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,फ़ीफ़ा वर्ल्ड कप: मेसी की दीवानगी जब सिर चढ़कर बोली,FIFA World Cup: When Messi's madness reached its peak,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Messi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"क्या टूटने वाली है उद्धव ठाकरे की शिवसेना, जानिए अब तक का घटनाक्रम","Is Uddhav Thackeray's Shiv Sena going to break, know the developments so far",0.0,neutral,"[('Shiv Sena', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,घर के अंदर जूते पहने रहना क्या सेहत के लिए हानिकारक है?,Is wearing shoes indoors harmful to health?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पीएम मोदी ने ट्रंप की मौजूदगी में भारतीय नागरिकों की मौत का किया ज़िक्र लेकिन अमेरिका का नाम ना लेने पर विपक्ष हमलावर,PM Modi mentioned the death of Indian citizens in the presence of Trump but the opposition attacked for not taking the name of America.,-1.0,negative,"[('PM Modi', 'ORG'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वर्ल्ड कप फ़ुटबॉल 2026: मेसी का कमाल, जानें ताज़ा नतीजे","World Cup Football 2026: Messi's wonder, know the latest results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Football', 'EVENT'), ('Messi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O país vizinho do Brasil onde empregados passaram a trabalhar menos e a ganhar mais (com desemprego na mínima histórica),The country neighboring Brazil where employees started to work less and earn more (with unemployment at a historic low),0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Cristiano Ronaldo: de menino que esperava por sobras de hambúrgueres no McDonald's a 1º bilionário do futebol,Cristiano Ronaldo: from a boy who waited for leftover burgers at McDonald's to football's first billionaire,0.0,neutral,"[('Cristiano Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('McDonald', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que se sabe sobre o plano de ataque à Casa Branca durante evento do UFC,What is known about the plan to attack the White House during the UFC event,-1.0,negative,"[('the White House', 'ORG'), ('UFC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,STF condena Eduardo Bolsonaro por articular ações do governo Trump contra o Brasil: o que pode acontecer com ele?,STF condemns Eduardo Bolsonaro for articulating Trump government actions against Brazil: what could happen to him?,0.0,neutral,"[('STF', 'ORG'), ('Eduardo Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Eduardo Bolsonaro condenado: como a imprensa internacional noticiou a decisão do STF,Eduardo Bolsonaro convicted: how the international press reported the STF decision,0.0,neutral,"[('Eduardo Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Do PCC e do CV ao mesmo tempo? As dúvidas que pairam sobre acusação do governo Trump contra brasileiro preso nos EUA,From PCC and CV at the same time? Doubts surrounding the Trump administration's accusation against a Brazilian arrested in the US,0.0,neutral,"[('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Messi faz 3 gols contra Argélia e vira maior artilheiro da história das Copas: por que aos 38 anos ele joga melhor do que nunca,Messi scores 3 goals against Algeria and becomes top scorer in World Cup history: why at 38 he plays better than ever,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Algeria', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('38', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Mulher traumatizada por troca de casais acusa site de 'intermediar abusos': 'Todos aqueles homens estavam abusando do meu corpo',Woman traumatized by couple exchange accuses website of 'intermediating abuse': 'All those men were abusing my body',0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o acordo entre EUA e Irã é pesadelo político para o premiê de Israel,Why the US-Iran deal is a political nightmare for Israel's prime minister,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A brasileira que teme ser expulsa do Reino Unido após anos cuidando de idosos: 'Você não pode mudar regras da imigração no meio do jogo',The Brazilian who fears being expelled from the UK after years of caring for the elderly: 'You can't change immigration rules in the middle of the game',0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Давал столько поводов, за которые сейчас убивают людей». Чем известен художник Скрепецкий, застреленный в Польше","“He gave so many reasons for which people are being killed now.” What is the artist Skrepetsky, who was shot dead in Poland, famous for?",-1.0,negative,"[('Skrepetsky', 'PERSON'), ('Poland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Три причины, по которым суда пока не идут через Ормузский пролив",Three reasons why ships are not yet sailing through the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Тегеран называет соглашение с США своей победой. Все ли иранцы считают так же?,Tehran calls the agreement with the US a victory. Do all Iranians feel the same way?,1.0,positive,"[('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: лидеры G7 пообещали Киеву увеличить поставки систем ПВО, ракет-перехватчиков и дальнобойного оружия","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: G7 leaders promised Kyiv to increase supplies of air defense systems, interceptor missiles and long-range weapons",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Гибель отца и брата, допрос в США и гол на чемпионате мира. История нападающего сборной Ирака Аймена Хуссейна","The death of his father and brother, interrogation in the USA and a goal at the World Cup. The story of Iraqi striker Aymen Hussein",-1.0,negative,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Iraqi', 'NORP'), ('Aymen Hussein', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Сделка США с Ираном может стать политическим кошмаром для Биньямина Нетаньяху,US-Iran deal could become political nightmare for Benjamin Netanyahu,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Benjamin Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"ФБР рассказало о деле радикалов, которые планировали атаковать Белый дом с помощью дронов и снайперов",The FBI spoke about the case of radicals who planned to attack the White House using drones and snipers,-1.0,negative,"[('FBI', 'ORG'), ('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Как Россия научилась глушить Starlink и готова ли к этому Украина? Интервью с советником министра обороны Украины Сергеем «Флэшем» Бескрестновым,How did Russia learn to jam Starlink and is Ukraine ready for this? Interview with Advisor to the Minister of Defense of Ukraine Sergei “Flash” Beskrestnov,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Starlink', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Flash” Beskrestnov', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Индия временно заблокировала телеграм ради борьбы со списыванием на вступительном экзамене в медицинские вузы,India temporarily blocked Telegram to combat cheating in medical school entrance exams,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Telegram', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Российские военные моряки сделали предупредительные выстрелы в сторону яхты в Ла-Манше,Russian sailors fired warning shots towards a yacht in the English Channel,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英首相、ホルムズ海峡再開に「全面的に貢献する」　G7ではウクライナでの結束も強調,British Prime Minister 'fully contributes' to reopening Strait of Hormuz; G7 also emphasizes unity in Ukraine,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('G7', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアの軍艦、イギリス人夫婦の乗ったヨットに警告射撃　英仏海峡で,Russian warship fires warning shot at yacht carrying British couple in English Channel,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【検証】 スターマー英首相を標的にした放火、背後にロシア　BBC取材で判明,"[Verification] Russia is behind the arson that targeted British Prime Minister Starmer, revealed by BBC interview",0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,食用に盗まれた猫400匹以上を救出、ヴェトナムの警察　窃盗組織を解体,"Over 400 cats stolen for food rescued, Vietnamese police dismantle theft ring",0.0,neutral,"[('Vietnamese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,トランプ氏はなぜネタニヤフ氏に激怒しているのか　イスラエルのレバノン空爆めぐり, 所要時間 1,30","Video, Why is Mr. Trump furious with Mr. Netanyahu over Israel's airstrike in Lebanon, Duration 1,30",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,プーチン氏に批判的なロシア人アーティスト、ポーランドで射殺される,Russian artist critical of Putin shot dead in Poland,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Poland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 メッシ、3ゴールで通算得点1位タイに　38歳で新たな歴史刻む,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Messi makes new history at age 38 with 3 goals to tie for first place in total points,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('age 38', 'DATE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ハンガリー国会、憲法改正でオルバン氏の首相復帰を阻止　在任期間を8年に制限,"Hungarian parliament prevents Orbán from returning as prime minister by amending the constitution, limiting his term in office to eight years",0.0,neutral,"[('Hungarian', 'NORP'), ('Orbán', 'NORP'), ('eight years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,米スタンフォード大卒業式で学生が次々と退席、グーグルCEOの祝辞で, 所要時間 1,05","Video, Students leave Stanford University Graduation Ceremony one after another as Google CEO congratulates them, Duration 1,05",0.0,neutral,"[('Stanford University Graduation Ceremony', 'ORG'), ('Google', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,アメリカとイランが暫定合意、レバノンとイスラエルにとってどんな意味があるのか, 所要時間 1,52","Video, US and Iran reach interim agreement, what it means for Lebanon and Israel, Duration 1,52",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Israel yaanzisha mashambulizi mapya dhidi ya Lebanon licha ya ukosoaji wa Trump","Directly, Israel launches new attacks against Lebanon despite Trump's criticism",-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Utata wa $300 bilioni za Iran unavyoibua vita mpya Marekani,The $300 billion Iran dispute is sparking a new war in the US,-1.0,negative,"[('$300 billion', 'MONEY'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Iran yasema imeshinda vita, wananchi wake wanauonaje ushindi huo?","Iran says it has won the war, how do its citizens see the victory?",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini uume ni kipimo muhimu cha afya ya mwanaume,Why the penis is an important measure of a man's health,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Waridi wa BBC: ""Mazishi yangu yalishaandaliwa"" simulizi ya mwanamke anayeishi na HIV kwa miaka 30","BBC News: ""My funeral has been prepared"" the story of a woman living with HIV for 30 years",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG'), ('30 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za usajili: Tonali aziingiza vitani Arsenal, Man City na Spurs","Registration rumours: Tonali will bring Arsenal, Man City and Spurs into battle",0.0,neutral,"[('Tonali', 'ORG'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Man City', 'GPE'), ('Spurs', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Senegal hoi, yachapwa 3-1 na Ufaransa",World Cup 2026: Senegal lost 3-1 to France,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ratiba, msimamo na matokeo","World Cup 2026: Schedule, standings and results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Pengo kati ya Wababe wa Soka na Afrika linazidi kupungua,World Cup 2026: The gap between the Football Powers and Africa is narrowing,1.0,positive,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('the Football Powers', 'ORG'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Trump amefanya nini tofauti na Obama kuhusu Iran?,What has Trump done differently than Obama about Iran?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Obama', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel takes control of Hebron’s Ibrahimi Mosque: What this means,Israel takes control of Hebron’s Ibrahimi Mosque: What this means,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hebron', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ex-boxing world champion Floyd Mayweather faces theft charges in Las Vegas,Ex-boxing world champion Floyd Mayweather faces theft charges in Las Vegas,0.0,neutral,"[('Floyd Mayweather', 'PERSON'), ('Las Vegas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,UK’s Starmer says Russian warship’s warning shots in Channel ‘reckless’,UK’s Starmer says Russian warship’s warning shots in Channel ‘reckless’,-1.0,negative,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Channel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup Day 7: Ronaldo chases history as England take on Croatia,World Cup Day 7: Ronaldo chases history as England take on Croatia,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day', 'EVENT'), ('Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Croatia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"G7 Summit: Modi suggests global Skilled Mobility Partnership, Economic Corridor for Global South","G7 Summit: Modi suggests global Skilled Mobility Partnership, Economic Corridor for Global South",-1.0,negative,"[('Skilled Mobility Partnership, Economic Corridor for Global South', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Iran pledges no bomb; U.S. promises sanctions relief, $300 billion financing; agreement’s leaked text shows","Iran pledges no bomb; U.S. promises sanctions relief, $300 billion financing; agreement’s leaked text shows",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('$300 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"G7 Summit Day 2 LIVE: Leaders pledge more vital help for Ukraine against Russia, Zelenskyy says","G7 Summit Day 2 LIVE: Leaders pledge more vital help for Ukraine against Russia, Zelenskyy says",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskyy', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Theatres for the masses in Madras,Theatres for the masses in Madras,0.0,neutral,"[('Madras', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"CMRL pay-off case: T. Veena, Pinarayi Vijayan's daughter, appears before ED","CMRL pay-off case: T. Veena, Pinarayi Vijayan's daughter, appears before ED",0.0,neutral,"[('T. Veena', 'ORG'), ('Vijayan', 'PERSON'), ('ED', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Maoist woman with ₹10-lakh bounty surrenders to Kolkata Police,Maoist woman with ₹10-lakh bounty surrenders to Kolkata Police,0.0,neutral,"[('Maoist', 'NORP'), ('10', 'MONEY'), ('Kolkata Police', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why was Trump’s H-1B fee struck down?,Why was Trump’s H-1B fee struck down?,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump’s H-1B', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Search for six-year-old Ebola patient after armed men storm DR Congo hospital,Search for six-year-old Ebola patient after armed men storm DR Congo hospital,0.0,neutral,"[('six-year-old', 'DATE'), ('DR Congo', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Norway's crown princess undergoes successful lung transplant, palace says","Norway's crown princess undergoes successful lung transplant, palace says",1.0,positive,"[('Norway', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Bolivia signs $20m deal with US to fight drug trafficking, foreign ministry says","Bolivia signs $20m deal with US to fight drug trafficking, foreign ministry says",0.0,neutral,"[('Bolivia', 'GPE'), ('20', 'MONEY'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Leader of South Africa's second biggest party wants his predecessor sacked as minister,Leader of South Africa's second biggest party wants his predecessor sacked as minister,0.0,neutral,"[(""South Africa's"", 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Live Updates: After G7 Leaders Praise U.S.-Iran Deal, Trump Threatens Iran Again","Live Updates: After G7 Leaders Praise U.S.-Iran Deal, Trump Threatens Iran Again",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump Threatens Iran Again', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Bahrain Revoked Their Citizenship, and Then Tried to Expel Them to Iran","Bahrain Revoked Their Citizenship, and Then Tried to Expel Them to Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('Expel Them', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Ukraine Tries to Cut Off Crimea, Choking Russian Supply Routes","Ukraine Tries to Cut Off Crimea, Choking Russian Supply Routes",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine Tries to Cut Off Crimea', 'ORG'), ('Choking Russian Supply', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"After a Bitter Split, European Leaders Play Nice With Trump","After a Bitter Split, European Leaders Play Nice With Trump",0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Congo Returns to World Cup in High Style After 52 Years Away,Congo Returns to World Cup in High Style After 52 Years Away,0.0,neutral,"[('Congo Returns', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('52 Years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Ecuador’s Andes Created a Language of Its Own,How Ecuador’s Andes Created a Language of Its Own,0.0,neutral,"[('Ecuador', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Naval Mines Could Still Stymie Gulf Shipping After War,Naval Mines Could Still Stymie Gulf Shipping After War,-1.0,negative,"[('Stymie Gulf Shipping', 'ORG'), ('War', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Russian Navy Ship Fired Warning Shots Near British Couple’s Sailboat,Russian Navy Ship Fired Warning Shots Near British Couple’s Sailboat,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian Navy Ship Fired Warning Shots Near British Couple’s Sailboat', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Australia’s Former Electricity Substations Are Being Turned Into Homes,Australia’s Former Electricity Substations Are Being Turned Into Homes,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Can a Trump-Modi Meeting Reset U.S.-India Relations?,Can a Trump-Modi Meeting Reset U.S.-India Relations?,0.0,neutral,[]
