Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Estoy vivo, veo el cielo. Llamen a mi familia"": las impactantes historias de cómo sobrevivieron algunos venezolanos la primera semana después del doble terremoto","""I'm alive, I see the sky. Call my family"": the shocking stories of how some Venezuelans survived the first week after the double earthquake",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP'), ('the first week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La destrucción que han sufrido otras localidades de Venezuela golpeadas por los terremotos y opacadas por la magnitud de la tragedia en La Guaira,The destruction suffered by other towns in Venezuela hit by earthquakes and overshadowed by the magnitude of the tragedy in La Guaira,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('La Guaira', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Viajé desde Colombia a Venezuela para buscar a mi madre y ahora solo quiero encontrar su cuerpo""","""I traveled from Colombia to Venezuela to look for my mother and now I just want to find her body""",0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quiénes son los lefebvrianos, el grupo ultraconservador que desafió al papa León XIV ordenando a 4 obispos y que hace temer un cisma en la Iglesia católica","Who are the Lefebvrians, the ultraconservative group that challenged Pope Leo XIV by ordaining 4 bishops and that raises fears of a schism in the Catholic Church",0.0,neutral,"[('Lefebvrians', 'NORP'), ('Pope Leo XIV', 'PERSON'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Catholic Church', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Cómo es Residencia, el fascinante hotel para científicos en uno de los lugares más extremos del mundo","What is Residencia like, the fascinating hotel for scientists in one of the most extreme places in the world",0.0,neutral,"[('Residencia', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Asciende a más 2.200 el número de muertos en Venezuela cuando se cumple una semana de los terremotos,"The death toll in Venezuela rises to more than 2,200 one week after the earthquakes",-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('more than 2,200', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las impactantes cifras que revelan la magnitud de los terremotos que golpearon Venezuela hace una semana,The shocking figures that reveal the magnitude of the earthquakes that hit Venezuela a week ago,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('a week ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Por qué lleva una banda en la cabeza Raúl Jiménez, el futbolista que estuvo a punto de morir y hoy lidera la esperanza de México en el Mundial","Why does Raúl Jiménez, the soccer player who almost died and today leads Mexico's hope in the World Cup, wear a band on his head?",0.0,neutral,"[('Raúl Jiménez', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,En video: el momento en el que una pareja rusa sube hasta lo más alto del Empire State de Nueva York,On video: the moment a Russian couple climbs to the top of the Empire State Building in New York,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Empire State Building', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los 4 errores más comunes al acumular cosas y cómo solucionarlos para tener tu casa organizada,The 4 most common mistakes when accumulating things and how to solve them to have your house organized,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कोलंबो में ऐसा क्या हुआ, जिसे भारत और पाकिस्तान के बीच कुछ 'पकने' की बात की जा रही","What happened in Colombo, which is being talked about as something 'ripening' between India and Pakistan?",0.0,neutral,"[('Colombo', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,टीएमसी के बाग़ी विधायकों के गुट ने चुनाव आयोग से की मुलाकात","Live, group of rebel TMC MLAs met the Election Commission",0.0,neutral,"[('TMC', 'ORG'), ('the Election Commission', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वैभव सूर्यवंशी को मौका नहीं देने पर रवि शास्त्री ख़फ़ा, गावस्कर और वॉन ने ये कहा","Ravi Shastri angry at not giving chance to Vaibhav Suryavanshi, Gavaskar and Vaughan said this",0.0,neutral,"[('Ravi Shastri', 'PERSON'), ('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Gavaskar', 'PERSON'), ('Vaughan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सरला भट्ट:  वो कश्मीरी पंडित नर्स जिनकी 36 साल पहले हुई थी हत्या, अब चार्जशीट दाख़िल होने पर क्या कह रहा परिवार","Sarla Bhatt: The Kashmiri Pandit nurse who was murdered 36 years ago, now what is the family saying after the charge sheet has been filed?",0.0,neutral,"[('Sarla Bhatt', 'PERSON'), ('The Kashmiri Pandit', 'ORG'), ('36 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"राम मंदिर चढ़ावा चोरी मामला: सबसे ज़्यादा सवाल किस पर हैं, आरएसएस, वीएचपी या मुख्यमंत्री योगी पर?","Ram Temple Offering Theft Case: On whom are the most questions raised, RSS, VHP or Chief Minister Yogi?",0.0,neutral,"[('Ram Temple Offering Theft Case', 'ORG'), ('RSS', 'ORG'), ('VHP', 'ORG'), ('Yogi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,चीन इस नए क़ानून से क्या विदेश में बैठे आलोचकों को निशाना बना सकता है?,Can China target critics sitting abroad with this new law?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,महुआ मोइत्रा पर अंडे फेंकने की घटना पर टीएमसी-बीजेपी आमने-सामने,TMC-BJP face to face over egg throwing incident on Mahua Moitra,1.0,positive,"[('TMC', 'ORG'), ('Mahua Moitra', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,व्हाट्सऐप का नया फ़ीचर: सरकार ने मेटा को क्यों भेजा नोटिस,New feature of WhatsApp: Why did the government send notice to Meta?,0.0,neutral,"[('WhatsApp', 'ORG'), ('Meta', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,डोनाल्ड ट्रंप ने राष्ट्रपति बनने के बाद क्रिप्टो से एक अरब डॉलर से अधिक रक़म बनाई,Donald Trump made more than a billion dollars from crypto after becoming President,0.0,neutral,"[('Donald Trump', 'PERSON'), ('more than a billion dollars', 'MONEY')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"तीन राज्यों के बीहड़ों में कैसे ख़ौफ़ बना चंबल का कुख्यात डकैत जगन गुर्जर, जिसकी अजमेर हाई सिक्योरिटी जेल में हुई हत्या","How Chambal's infamous dacoit Jagan Gurjar became a threat in the ravines of three states, who was murdered in Ajmer High Security Jail.",0.0,neutral,"[('Jagan Gurjar', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Briga entre Michelle e Flávio abala plano bolsonarista para eleger Senado 'anti-STF'?,Fight between Michelle and Flávio undermines Bolsonaro's plan to elect 'anti-STF' Senate?,0.0,neutral,"[('Michelle', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quanto tempo uma pessoa pode sobreviver sob os escombros após um terremoto?,How long can a person survive under the rubble after an earthquake?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,De Palio a Porsche elétrico: a 'ascensão social acentuada' de sancionado por governo Trump por suposto elo com o PCC,From Palio to electric Porsche: the 'sharp social rise' of a person sanctioned by the Trump government for alleged links with the PCC,0.0,neutral,"[('Palio', 'ORG'), ('Porsche', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('PCC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,EUA aplicam primeiras sanções contra rede acusada de ligação com PCC; especialista vê vazio jurídico entre crime e terrorismo,US applies first sanctions against network accused of links to PCC; expert sees legal gap between crime and terrorism,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('PCC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Qual a distância entre Lula e Flávio Bolsonaro nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,What is the distance between Lula and Flávio Bolsonaro in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A brasileira empresária de Haaland que se tornou a primeira mulher 'superagente' do futebol: 'Acham que a gente não entende do assunto',Haaland's Brazilian businesswoman who became football's first female 'super agent': 'They think we don't understand the subject',0.0,neutral,"[('Haaland', 'GPE'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Copa do Mundo 2026: os 'astros virais' conseguirão transformar sucesso nas redes sociais em fortuna?,World Cup 2026: will the 'viral stars' be able to turn success on social media into fortune?,1.0,positive,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como disputa por apoio no Ceará desencadeou guerra entre Michelle e Flávio Bolsonaro,How the dispute for support in Ceará triggered a war between Michelle and Flávio Bolsonaro,-1.0,negative,"[('Ceará', 'GPE'), ('Michelle', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Milhares de mortos, milhões precisando de ajuda na Venezuela: os números que mostram a dimensão da tragédia após terremotos","Thousands dead, millions needing help in Venezuela: the numbers that show the scale of the tragedy after earthquakes",0.0,neutral,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A indústria global de falsos médicos feitos por IA que usa o medo para viralizar entre idosos no Brasil: 'Achei que fosse real',The global industry of fake AI doctors that uses fear to go viral among elderly people in Brazil: 'I thought it was real',0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: при атаке на Киев погибли 17 человек, ВСУ сообщили об ударе по НПЗ в Кстово","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: 17 people were killed in the attack on Kyiv, the Ukrainian Armed Forces reported a strike on the oil refinery in Kstovo",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('the Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Kstovo', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Россия нанесла массированный удар по Украине ракетами и дронами: в Киеве более 15 погибших,Russia launched a massive attack on Ukraine with missiles and drones: more than 15 dead in Kyiv,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('more than 15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Пилот, направивший самолет в знаменитый небоскреб в Пекине, страдал психическим расстройством, заявили власти Китая","The pilot who flew the plane into a famous skyscraper in Beijing suffered from a mental disorder, Chinese authorities said.",0.0,neutral,"[('Beijing', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Временный президент Сирии назначил 70 последних депутатов в парламент, сформированный после свержения Асада. Кто в нем оказался?",Syria's interim president appointed the last 70 deputies to the parliament formed after the overthrow of Assad. Who was in it?,0.0,neutral,"[('Syria', 'GPE'), ('70', 'CARDINAL'), ('Assad', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Руферы из России забрались на шпиль Empire State Building в Нью-Йорке. Там они, по всей видимости, обручились",Roofers from Russia climbed the spire of the Empire State Building in New York. They apparently got engaged there,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('the Empire State Building', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Германии предъявили обвинения украинцу, подозреваемому в подрыве «Северного потока»",A Ukrainian suspected of blowing up the Nord Stream pipeline has been charged in Germany.,1.0,positive,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Nord Stream', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Топливный кризис в России — будет хуже? | Видеоподкаст «Что это было?», Продолжительность 32,03","Video, Fuel crisis in Russia - will it get worse? | Video podcast “What was that?”, Duration 32.03",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('32.03', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Мехико три человека погибли во время празднования победы мексиканской сборной над Эквадором на ЧМ-2026,"In Mexico City, three people died during the celebration of the Mexican team's victory over Ecuador at the 2026 World Cup.",1.0,positive,"[('Mexico City', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Верховная Рада приняла закон о создании украинского национального пантеона,The Verkhovna Rada adopted a law on the creation of the Ukrainian national pantheon,0.0,neutral,"[('The Verkhovna Rada', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Умер вокалист группы Village People Виктор Уиллис, один из авторов хита YMCA","Village People singer Victor Willis, one of the authors of the YMCA hit, has died",0.0,neutral,"[('Victor Willis', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('YMCA', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシア、キーウに大規模なミサイル・ドローン攻撃、少なくとも13人死亡,Massive missile and drone attack on Russia's Kiv kills at least 13 people,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('at least 13', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、北米貿易協定の16年延長を拒否　現在の内容では応じないと,US rejects 16-year extension of North American trade agreement,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('16-year', 'DATE'), ('North American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ドイツ検察、ノルド・ストリーム爆破でウクライナ人を起訴,German prosecutors indict Ukrainian over Nord Stream bombing,0.0,neutral,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Nord Stream', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米政府が140人以上を飛行機でヴェネズエラへ強制送還……その数時間後に地震、大勢が行方不明に,"The U.S. government deports more than 140 people to Venezuela by plane... hours later, an earthquake leaves many missing.",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('more than 140', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,北京の最高層ビルに小型機が激突、中国当局は何があったのか説明せず,"Small plane crashes into Beijing's tallest building, Chinese authorities won't explain what happened",0.0,neutral,"[('Beijing', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イングランド、コンゴ民主共和国に逆転勝ちでベスト16　ケインが2得点でチーム救う,[2026 Men's World Cup] England comes from behind to beat Democratic Republic of the Congo to reach the top 16; Kane saves team with 2 goals,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('Democratic Republic of the', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kane', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,メキシコ市で4人死亡　W杯での勝利祝い100万人以上が首都に集中,4 people killed in Mexico City; over 1 million people gather in capital to celebrate World Cup victory,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico City', 'GPE'), ('over 1 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,トランプ氏、暗号資産や「トランプ」ブランド商品などで巨額収入　ホワイトハウスは利益相反を否定, 所要時間 1,22","Video, Mr. Trump earns huge income from crypto assets and ""Trump"" brand products, White House denies conflict of interest, Required time 1,22",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('1,22', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米最高裁、「出生地主義」を維持　大幅制限を主張するトランプ氏に打撃,"U.S. Supreme Court upholds ``birthplace doctrine,'' a blow to Trump who advocates drastic restrictions",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランスジェンダー選手の女子学生スポーツへの出場禁止を支持　米最高裁,U.S. Supreme Court upholds ban on transgender athletes from participating in female collegiate sports,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Iran yasema itawazuia wakaguzi wa nyuklia kukagua vituo vyake vilivyoshambuliwa","Directly, Iran says it will prevent nuclear inspectors from inspecting its attacked facilities",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kutoka kuitwa ""chatu"" hadi kuwa sauti ya watu wenye vitiligo Tanzania","From being called a ""python"" to being the voice of people with vitiligo in Tanzania",0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwanini wanawake wa nchi hii hupenda kuvaa mavazi ya kiume?,Why do the women of this country like to wear men's clothes?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, kuna timu ya kuisimamisha Ufaransa katika kombe la Dunia?",Is there a team to stop France in the World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Siri ya wanawake wa Japan kuishi umri mrefu wa hadi miaka 100,The secret of Japanese women living a long life of up to 100 years,0.0,neutral,"[('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('up to 100 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka: Barcelona na Arsenal bado wanamwania Julián Álvarez,Football rumours: Barcelona and Arsenal are still in the running for Julián Álvarez,0.0,neutral,"[('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Julián Álvarez', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Njia 4 nadra ambazo mwanamke anaweza kupata ujauzito,4 rare ways a woman can get pregnant,0.0,neutral,"[('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: DRC yaaga, yachapwa na England 2-1","World Cup 2026: DRC bid farewell, beaten by England 2-1",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('DRC', 'ORG'), ('England 2-1', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Iran yasema inapendelea mazungumzo, lakini iko tayari kwa vita pia","Iran says it prefers talks, but is ready for war too",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Amnesty International yasema RSF ilitenda uhalifu dhidi ya ubinadamu nchini Sudan,Amnesty International says the RSF committed crimes against humanity in Sudan,0.0,neutral,"[('Amnesty International', 'ORG'), ('RSF', 'ORG'), ('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US-Iran talks in Doha: What were the outcomes and what’s next?,US-Iran talks in Doha: What were the outcomes and what’s next?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Doha', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Billions flow between EU institutions and Israel, despite Gaza genocide","Billions flow between EU institutions and Israel, despite Gaza genocide",0.0,neutral,"[('Billions', 'CARDINAL'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Alibaba to pay $600m to settle illegal drug sales allegations in US probe,Alibaba to pay $600m to settle illegal drug sales allegations in US probe,0.0,neutral,"[('600', 'MONEY'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Two reported killed, dozens hurt in hospital fire in Germany","Two reported killed, dozens hurt in hospital fire in Germany",-1.0,negative,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘The crisis is deep’: The view from Russia as fuel shortages worsen,‘The crisis is deep’: The view from Russia as fuel shortages worsen,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"In Pictures: Hunger, despair as Venezuela quake death toll rises","In Pictures: Hunger, despair as Venezuela quake death toll rises",-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Spain look to overcome ‘rough patch’ as Austria await in World Cup last 32,Spain look to overcome ‘rough patch’ as Austria await in World Cup last 32,0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Austria', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,More than 900 arrested during South Africa’s antimigrant protests,More than 900 arrested during South Africa’s antimigrant protests,0.0,neutral,"[('South Africa’s', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Maradona to Messi: Why Bangladesh loves Argentina’s footballers,Maradona to Messi: Why Bangladesh loves Argentina’s footballers,0.0,neutral,"[('Maradona', 'PERSON'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,China’s new ethnic unity law extends its legal reach overseas,China’s new ethnic unity law extends its legal reach overseas,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Rules governing creches in India | Explained,Rules governing creches in India | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Explained', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Jana Nayagan gets CBFC nod after long delay, official says","Jana Nayagan gets CBFC nod after long delay, official says",0.0,neutral,"[('Jana Nayagan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,‘Methyl Isocyanate of Law’: Supreme Court quashes verdict based on AI-generated precedents,‘Methyl Isocyanate of Law’: Supreme Court quashes verdict based on AI-generated precedents,0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Keep me away from all this, I'm an artist: Diljit on CJP protests at Delhi’s Jantar Mantar","Keep me away from all this, I'm an artist: Diljit on CJP protests at Delhi’s Jantar Mantar",0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Delhi’s Jantar Mantar', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,How does WhatsApp’s username feature compare to Telegram’s? | Explained,How does WhatsApp’s username feature compare to Telegram’s? | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('WhatsApp', 'ORG'), ('Telegram', 'ORG'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Raja Raghuvanshi murder: Meghalaya police move Supreme Court against Sonam Raghuvanshi’s bail,Raja Raghuvanshi murder: Meghalaya police move Supreme Court against Sonam Raghuvanshi’s bail,0.0,neutral,"[('Raja Raghuvanshi', 'ORG'), ('Meghalaya', 'ORG'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Sonam Raghuvanshi’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,India’s first privately developed orbital-class rocket Vikram-1 set for launch,India’s first privately developed orbital-class rocket Vikram-1 set for launch,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"The Hindu Group’s Chairman, Director call on Tamil Nadu CM Vijay","The Hindu Group’s Chairman, Director call on Tamil Nadu CM Vijay",0.0,neutral,"[('The Hindu Group’s', 'ORG'), ('Tamil Nadu CM Vijay', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The rise of Bengaluru-style darshinis in Chennai: Inside the city’s newest food obsession,The rise of Bengaluru-style darshinis in Chennai: Inside the city’s newest food obsession,0.0,neutral,"[('Bengaluru', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Fixing the rot: On the subversion of public examinations and recruitment,Fixing the rot: On the subversion of public examinations and recruitment,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,At least 18 killed in 'most massive' Russian attack on Kyiv,At least 18 killed in 'most massive' Russian attack on Kyiv,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 18', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,People smuggler convicted in France found by BBC living in UK and seeking asylum,People smuggler convicted in France found by BBC living in UK and seeking asylum,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'Two weeks after her death I got a call': Gaza patients face agonising delays for evacuation,'Two weeks after her death I got a call': Gaza patients face agonising delays for evacuation,-1.0,negative,"[('Two weeks', 'DATE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Aunt of Venezuelan boy pulled from rubble tells BBC she will give him 'mother's warmth',Aunt of Venezuelan boy pulled from rubble tells BBC she will give him 'mother's warmth',-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,From Truman's pension to Trump's billions - a White House windfall unmatched by any president,From Truman's pension to Trump's billions - a White House windfall unmatched by any president,1.0,positive,"[('Truman', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('billions -', 'MONEY'), ('White House', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Did this AI anti-drug video make drugs look appealing?,Did this AI anti-drug video make drugs look appealing?,0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Turkish police beat us with iron rods before we lost limbs to frostbite, Afghans say","Turkish police beat us with iron rods before we lost limbs to frostbite, Afghans say",0.0,neutral,"[('Turkish', 'NORP'), ('Afghans', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,The US deported them to Venezuela - hours later earthquakes struck,The US deported them to Venezuela - hours later earthquakes struck,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US blocks long-term renewal of North American trade deal,US blocks long-term renewal of North American trade deal,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('North American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nigeria to seek compensation for property abandoned by citizens fleeing South Africa,Nigeria to seek compensation for property abandoned by citizens fleeing South Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Live Updates: Russia Hammers Ukraine’s Capital in Deadly Attacks,Live Updates: Russia Hammers Ukraine’s Capital in Deadly Attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Can the World’s Largest Stadium Explain the Global Economy?,Can the World’s Largest Stadium Explain the Global Economy?,0.0,neutral,"[('the World’s Largest Stadium Explain', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Says Iran May Swap Ideology For Investment. History Shows Otherwise,U.S. Says Iran May Swap Ideology For Investment. History Shows Otherwise,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Mass Mournings,6 Days and 2 Countries: Iran Prepares to Bury Supreme Leader","Mass Mournings,6 Days and 2 Countries: Iran Prepares to Bury Supreme Leader",0.0,neutral,"[('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Drones over Europe raise concerns about Russian activities,Drones over Europe raise concerns about Russian activities,0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Can Companies Embrace A.I. Without Layoffs? This One Says It Is Trying to.,Can Companies Embrace A.I. Without Layoffs? This One Says It Is Trying to.,0.0,neutral,"[('Layoffs', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Imprisoned Chinese Journalist Seeks Medical Parole for Lung Tumor,Imprisoned Chinese Journalist Seeks Medical Parole for Lung Tumor,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Lung Tumor', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Resumes Dollar Transfers to Iraq After Monthslong Suspension,U.S. Resumes Dollar Transfers to Iraq After Monthslong Suspension,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Resumes Dollar Transfers', 'ORG'), ('Iraq', 'GPE'), ('Monthslong Suspension', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Underground Births, Under Bombardment: Childbearing in Ukraine","Underground Births, Under Bombardment: Childbearing in Ukraine",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_02,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Earthquake Death Toll Mounts, Venezuela Grapples With Recovering and Burying Bodies","As Earthquake Death Toll Mounts, Venezuela Grapples With Recovering and Burying Bodies",-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela Grapples With Recovering', 'PERSON')]"
