Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Sammi y Safi, la historia de amor entre un musulmán y una judía que se gestó mientras rescataban personas de las manos del Talibán","Sammi and Safi, the love story between a Muslim and a Jewish woman that developed while they were rescuing people from the hands of the Taliban",0.19999999999999998,"[('Sammi', 'ORG'), ('Safi', 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Jewish', 'NORP'), ('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Mi testimonio falso condenó a 3 adolescentes a cadena perpetua y la culpa me ha perseguido desde entonces""","""My false testimony sentenced 3 teenagers to life in prison and the guilt has followed me ever since""",-0.4000000000000001,"[('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,BBC Mundo en territorio de las maras en Guatemala: cómo operan y qué las diferencia de las organizaciones criminales en otros países de la región,BBC Mundo in gang territory in Guatemala: how they operate and what differentiates them from criminal organizations in other countries in the region,-0.2625,"[('BBC Mundo', 'ORG'), ('Guatemala', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La investigación del FBI sobre apuestas que reveló la nueva cara de la mafia: ""Pasaron a dedicarse a actividades mucho más lucrativas y con menos riesgos para ellos""","The FBI investigation into gambling that revealed the new face of the mafia: ""They began to dedicate themselves to much more lucrative activities and with fewer risks for them""",0.3181818181818182,"[('FBI', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"6 datos de la fascinante historia del Louvre, el antiguo palacio de la monarquía francesa convertido en el museo más grande del mundo","6 facts about the fascinating history of the Louvre, the former palace of the French monarchy converted into the largest museum in the world",0.2333333333333333,"[('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ग़ज़ा में इसराइल से लौटे शवों पर 'यातना के निशान', डॉक्टरों को इन चुनौतियों का करना पड़ रहा है सामना","'Torture marks' on dead bodies returned from Israel in Gaza, doctors are facing these challenges",-0.2,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,पेरिस में लूवर म्यूज़ियम से चोरी करने के मामले में दो संदिग्ध गिरफ़्तार","Live, two suspects arrested for theft from Louvre Museum in Paris",0.13636363636363635,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नेतन्याहू से 'नाराज़' ट्रंप आगे क्या करेंगे, अरब मीडिया में चर्चा","'Angry' Trump with Netanyahu, what will he do next, discussion in Arab media",-0.25,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Arab', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'मैंने अपने चोरी हुए फ़ोन को लंदन, दुबई और चीन जाते देखा'","'I saw my stolen phone going to London, Dubai and China'",0.0,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('Dubai', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जब औरंगज़ेब ने की मुग़ल साम्राज्य के पतन की भविष्यवाणी - विवेचना,When Aurangzeb predicted the decline of the Mughal Empire - Discussion,0.0,"[('Aurangzeb', 'PERSON'), ('the Mughal Empire - Discussion', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप और शी जिनपिंग की छह साल बाद पहली मुलाक़ात, ट्रेड वॉर रुकेगा या बढ़ेगा तनाव?","Trump and Xi Jinping's first meeting after six years, will trade war stop or will tension increase?",0.25,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), (""Xi Jinping's"", 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('six years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"महिला डॉक्टर आत्महत्या मामले में फरार पुलिस अधिकारी ने किया सरेंडर, अब तक क्या-क्या पता है?","Absconding police officer surrenders in female doctor suicide case, what is known so far?",0.05,[]
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,इमरान ख़ान की बहन अलीमा की पाकिस्तान में इतनी चर्चा क्यों है?,Why is Imran Khan's sister Alima so discussed in Pakistan?,0.0,"[(""Imran Khan's"", 'PERSON'), ('Alima', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"कुरनूल हादसा: बस से टकराने वाली बाइक पर सवार रहे शख़्स ने उस रात क्या देखा, पुलिस ने बताया","Kurnool accident: What did the person riding the bike that collided with the bus see that night, police told",0.0,"[('that night', 'TIME')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Tive uma ótima reunião com Trump', diz Lula; negociações para suspensão do tarifaço seguem neste domingo","'I had a great meeting with Trump', says Lula; negotiations to suspend tariffs continue this Sunday",0.8,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que é tão difícil que Hamas se desarme e desapareça após governar Gaza com mão de ferro por quase 20 anos,Why is it so difficult for Hamas to disarm and disappear after ruling Gaza with an iron fist for almost 20 years,-0.5,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('almost 20 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Bolsonaro é página virada para Trump, mas sanções contra ministros do STF devem ser mantidas, diz ex-embaixador americano no Brasil","Bolsonaro is a turning point for Trump, but sanctions against STF ministers must be maintained, says former American ambassador to Brazil",0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('STF', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump aumenta tarifas sobre produtos do Canadá em resposta a anúncio publicitário,Trump raises tariffs on Canadian products in response to ad,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Canadian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump diz estar aberto a reduzir tarifas do Brasil 'diante das circunstâncias certas',Trump says he is open to reducing tariffs on Brazil 'under the right circumstances',0.14285714285714285,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Vamos marcar!': como parar de fazer ghosting com os amigos,'Let's tag!': how to stop ghosting friends,0.0,[]
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O pequeno mamífero que pode guardar o segredo genético para a vida longa,The small mammal that may hold the genetic secret to long life,-0.23333333333333336,[]
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Instagram X realidade: como Bali virou vítima de seu próprio sucesso nas redes sociais,Instagram X reality: how Bali became a victim of its own success on social media,0.21458333333333332,"[('Bali', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A história inspiradora da mulher que sobreviveu por 40 anos após receber transplante de coração e pulmão,The inspiring story of the woman who survived for 40 years after receiving a heart and lung transplant,0.5,"[('40 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: при ударе дронов по Киеву погибли три человека, среди десятков пострадвших — дети","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: three people were killed in a drone strike on Kyiv, children were among dozens of victims",-0.2,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Во Франции задержали подозреваемых в ограблении Лувра. Один из них пытался покинуть страну,"In France, suspects in the robbery of the Louvre were detained. One of them tried to leave the country",0.0,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON'), ('One', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп начал турне по Азии и прибыл в Малайзию. В его присутствии Таиланд и Камбоджа подписали «договор о мире»,"Trump began a tour of Asia and arrived in Malaysia. In his presence, Thailand and Cambodia signed a “peace treaty”",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Asia', 'LOC'), ('Malaysia', 'GPE'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Герои Харькова. Как удалось спасти 48 детей из детсада, по которому ударил российский дрон",Heroes of Kharkov. How 48 children were saved from a kindergarten hit by a Russian drone,0.0,"[('Kharkov', 'GPE'), ('48', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Ученые разработали имплант, с помощью которого ослепшие пациенты снова могут читать",Scientists have developed an implant that can help blind patients read again,-0.2,[]
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Я не закончила». Камала Харрис в интервью Би-би-си не исключила, что снова попробует стать президентом","""I'm not finished."" Kamala Harris, in an interview with the BBC, did not rule out that she would try to become president again",0.0,"[('Kamala Harris', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Рекламный ролик с Рейганом сорвал торговые переговоры Канады с США. Трамп обиделся и повысил тарифы еще на 10%,The Reagan commercial derailed Canada's trade negotiations with the United States. Trump was offended and raised tariffs by another 10%,0.0,"[('Reagan', 'PERSON'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('another 10%', 'PERCENT')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В подземном хранилище безопаснее. После ограбления Лувр перевёз часть драгоценностей в Банк Франции,"It's safer in underground storage. After the robbery, the Louvre moved some of the jewelry to the Bank of France",0.0,"[('Louvre', 'PERSON'), ('the Bank of France', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Президентом Ирландии избрана Кэтрин Коннолли. Она осуждала Россию не так решительно, как другие политики",Catherine Connolly was elected President of Ireland. She did not condemn Russia as strongly as other politicians,-0.125,"[('Catherine Connolly', 'PERSON'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,На зарплаты войскам в США во время шатдауна пожертвовал донор Трампа,A Trump donor donated to pay for US troops during the shutdown,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシア産石油・ガス、世界市場から排除すると　ウクライナ支援の「有志連合」が表明,The coalition supporting Ukraine says it will exclude Russian oil and gas from the world market.,0.125,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカは「戦争をねつ造している」、ヴェネズエラ大統領が非難　近海への軍艦派遣めぐり,"Venezuelan president criticizes US for ""fabricating war"" over sending warships to nearby waters",0.0,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ホワイトハウスの東棟、完全に解体　人工衛星画像から, 所要時間 1,07","Video, East Wing of the White House completely demolished from satellite images, Required time 1,07",0.05,"[('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,チャールズ英国王とローマ教皇が並んで祈る　16世紀からの溝を修復, 所要時間 0,38","Video, King Charles and the Pope pray side by side, repairing a 16th-century ditch, Duration 0,38",0.0,"[('Charles', 'PERSON'), ('16th-century', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,上司に「できません」と言いにくい時、どう言えばいい,"What to say when it's difficult to say ""I can't"" to your boss",-0.5,[]
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、カナダとの貿易交渉「打ち切る」と発表　関税に関する広告めぐり,Trump announces ``terminus'' of trade negotiations with Canada over tariff ads,0.0,"[('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,NBAスター選手と監督やマフィアら数十人を逮捕　違法賭博の取り締まりで,"Dozens of NBA stars, managers and mafia members arrested in crackdown on illegal gambling",-0.5,"[('Dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヨルダン川西岸併合に向けた法案、イスラエル議会で1回目の可決　米副大統領ら批判,"Bill for West Bank annexation passed first time in Israeli parliament, criticized by US vice president and others",0.25,"[('Bill', 'PERSON'), ('West Bank', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,仏ルーヴル美術館から機械式リフトで降りる2人の映像　逃亡する宝石強盗団か, 所要時間 0,32","Video, Footage of two people descending from France's Louvre Museum in a mechanical lift. Could it be a gang of jewel thieves on the run? Duration: 0,32",0.0,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('jewel', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump ashuhudia utiaji saini makubaliano ya amani kati ya Cambodia na Thailand","Directly, Trump witnesses the signing of a peace agreement between Cambodia and Thailand",0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('Thailand', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tukio la Manchester lililoleta mapinduzi makubwa Afrika,The Manchester incident that brought about a great revolution in Africa,0.8,"[('Manchester', 'PERSON'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Hamas inaweza kujiimarisha upya baada ya masaibu ya Israel?",Can Hamas re-establish itself after Israel's debacle?,0.0,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Jumapili: Man Utd yamfukuzia Bellingham,Sunday Football Rumors: Man Utd sack Bellingham,0.0,"[('Bellingham', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tanzania yasikitishwa na madai ya Amnesty kuhusu ukandamizaji wa haki za binadamu,Tanzania is saddened by Amnesty's claims about the suppression of human rights,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Amnesty', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Trump anatumai China itaishawishi Urusi kuelekea mazungumzo ya amani na Ukraine,Trump hopes China will persuade Russia towards peace talks with Ukraine,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais aliyeondolewa madarakani Madagascar avuliwa uraia,Madagascar's ousted president stripped of citizenship,0.0,"[('Madagascar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watoto wa Gaza wanakufa wakisubiri Israel iwawezeshe watu kuhama,Gaza's children are dying waiting for Israel to allow people to move,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"""Alisalia na saa nne kabla ya kunyongwa"": Alitumikia miaka 40 gerezani kabla ya kubainika kuwa hana hatia","""He was four hours away from being hanged"": He served 40 years in prison before being found not guilty",0.25,"[('four hours', 'TIME'), ('40 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_26,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"'Baada ya kushambuliwa, sasa napata hofu nyakati za uchaguzi Tanzania'","'After being attacked, now I get scared during elections in Tanzania'",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
