Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Por qué Irán está arriesgando tanto por el estrecho de Ormuz?,Why is Iran risking so much for the Strait of Hormuz?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"EE.UU. advierte a Daniel Ortega que no se quedará ""de brazos cruzados"" ante el anuncio de que no volverá a haber elecciones en Nicaragua","The US warns Daniel Ortega that it will not remain ""idly"" before the announcement that there will not be elections again in Nicaragua",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Daniel Ortega', 'PERSON'), ('Nicaragua', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Zelensky destituye al comandante en jefe de Ucrania después de días de protestas en las calles por el relevo del ministro de Defensa,Zelensky dismisses Ukraine's commander-in-chief after days of street protests over replacement of defense minister,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Garabateaba"" versos entre entrega y entrega: el repartidor de comida de 56 años que ganó uno de los mayores premios literarios de China","He ""scribbled"" verses between deliveries: the 56-year-old food delivery man who won one of China's biggest literary awards",-1.0,negative,"[('56-year-old', 'DATE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""No podía aceptar que nunca encontrarían a mi amiga desaparecida y me fui al otro lado del planeta a buscarla""","""I couldn't accept that they would never find my missing friend and I went to the other side of the planet to look for her""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El debate que genera ""La Odisea"" de Nolan entre los historiadores y los amantes del cine cuando se compara con la obra original","The debate that Nolan's ""The Odyssey"" generates among historians and film lovers when it is compared to the original work",0.0,neutral,"[('Nolan', 'ORG'), ('The Odyssey', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Kaylee Hottle: muere la actriz de ""Godzilla vs. Kong"" a los 18 años","Kaylee Hottle: ""Godzilla vs. Kong"" actress dies at 18",0.0,neutral,"[('Kaylee Hottle', 'PERSON'), ('Kong', 'PERSON'), ('18', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La historia de migración y éxito de las familias de Lamine Yamal y Nico Williams, dos de las jóvenes estrellas de la España campeona del mundo","The story of migration and success of the families of Lamine Yamal and Nico Williams, two of the young stars of world champion Spain",1.0,positive,"[('Lamine Yamal', 'PERSON'), ('Nico Williams', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Video,VIDEO | ""Aquí no volverá a haber elecciones"": Daniel Ortega dice que eliminará los comicios en Nicaragua para evitar una victoria de la oposición, Duración 0,36","Video,VIDEO | ""There will be no elections again here"": Daniel Ortega says he will eliminate elections in Nicaragua to avoid a victory for the opposition, Duration 0.36",1.0,positive,"[('Daniel Ortega', 'PERSON'), ('Nicaragua', 'GPE'), ('0.36', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,De Cuba a Vietnam: los miles de extranjeros que han muerto combatiendo para Rusia en la guerra con Ucrania,From Cuba to Vietnam: the thousands of foreigners who have died fighting for Russia in the war with Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वो तस्वीरें जिनकी वजह से जंतर-मंतर पर सीजेपी प्रदर्शन की देश-विदेश में है चर्चा,Those pictures due to which CJP protest at Jantar Mantar is discussed in India and abroad,0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,टीएमसी सांसद कल्याण बनर्जी मानसून सत्र से निलंबित","Live, TMC MP Kalyan Banerjee suspended from monsoon session",0.0,neutral,"[('Kalyan Banerjee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वीडियो,जंतर-मंतर पहुंचे इस कपल ने क्या बताया?, अवधि 4,00","Video, What did this couple tell when they reached Jantar Mantar?, Duration 4,00",0.0,neutral,"[('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सीजेआई बोले- 'वक़्त बर्बाद मत कीजिए', प्रदर्शनकारियों की पिटाई के मुद्दे पर जल्द सुनवाई से इनकार","CJI said - 'Don't waste time', refused to hear soon on the issue of beating of protesters",0.0,neutral,"[('CJI', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सीजेपी आंदोलन क्या मोदी सरकार के ख़िलाफ़ कांग्रेस के लिए मौक़ा है?,Is CJP movement an opportunity for Congress against Modi government?,0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,राहुल गांधी के धरने से आम आदमी पार्टी क्यों चिढ़ गई? 'आप' के विरोध पर छिड़ी बहस,Why was Aam Aadmi Party irritated by Rahul Gandhi's strike? Debate broke out on opposition to AAP,0.0,neutral,"[('Aam Aadmi Party', 'ORG'), (""Rahul Gandhi's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'मैं गर्भवती हूं'; ये बात मेरा फ़िटनेस ट्रैकर मुझसे पहले कैसे जान गया!,'I am pregnant'; How did my fitness tracker know this before me?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"राहुल गांधी की सरकार से 5 मांगें, उद्धव और महुआ पहुंचे जंतर-मंतर, जानिए रात में क्या-क्या हुआ?","5 demands from Rahul Gandhi's government, Uddhav and Mahua reached Jantar Mantar, know what happened in the night?",0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), (""Rahul Gandhi's"", 'PERSON'), ('Uddhav', 'GPE'), ('Mahua', 'PERSON'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"राहुल गांधी, प्रियंका गांधी और अखिलेश यादव को पीएम आवास के बाहर से हिरासत में लेने के बाद रिहा किया गया","Rahul Gandhi, Priyanka Gandhi and Akhilesh Yadav released after being detained from outside PM residence",0.0,neutral,"[('Rahul Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('Priyanka Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('Akhilesh Yadav', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सीजेपी के प्रदर्शन के दौरान 21 वर्षीय छात्रा गंभीर रूप से घायल, परिवार ने क्या बताया?","21 year old student seriously injured during CJP's protest, what did the family tell?",0.0,neutral,"[('21 year old', 'DATE'), ('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que novo tarifaço de Trump não deve decidir eleição a favor de Lula,Why Trump's new tariff should not decide the election in Lula's favor,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Assédio por pelos': como campanha para incentivar homens a usar bermuda no trabalho causa polêmica no Japão,'Hair harassment': how campaign to encourage men to wear shorts at work causes controversy in Japan,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o Irã está arriscando tanto por causa do Estreito de Ormuz,Why Iran is risking so much over the Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A disparada na Copa do número de pessoas que pediram para CPF ser bloqueado nas bets: 'Hoje nem gosto mais de futebol',The increase in the number of people who asked for their CPF to be blocked in bets during the World Cup: 'Today I don't even like football anymore',0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Today', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Trabalho no feriado: o que muda para farmácias, supermercados, comércio e outros setores afetados por nova regra em vigor","Working on holidays: what changes for pharmacies, supermarkets, commerce and other sectors affected by the new rule in force",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A crise na Ucrânia que fez Zelensky demitir ministro da Defesa e comandante do Exército em plena guerra com a Rússia,The crisis in Ukraine that made Zelensky fire Defense Minister and Army Commander in the midst of war with Russia,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Army', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Estreito de Bab al-Mandab: novas ameaças dos houthis podem gerar crise de transporte no Mar Vermelho?,Bab al-Mandab Strait: could new threats from the Houthis generate a transport crisis in the Red Sea?,-1.0,negative,"[('Bab al-Mandab Strait', 'PERSON'), ('Houthis', 'PERSON'), ('the Red Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"EUA podem perder para o Brasil o papel de maior exportador agrícola do mundo, diz Financial Times","The US could lose its role as the world's largest agricultural exporter to Brazil, says Financial Times",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Financial Times', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Não conseguia aceitar que nunca encontrariam minha amiga desaparecida, então fui para o outro lado do planeta procurá-la'","'I couldn't accept that they would never find my missing friend, so I went to the other side of the planet to look for her'",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A epidemia de violência contra professores no Brasil: 'Fui ameaçada de morte pelo pai de um aluno de 6 anos',The epidemic of violence against teachers in Brazil: 'I was threatened with death by the father of a 6-year-old student',-1.0,negative,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('6-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Украина ударила по логистическим центрам Wildberries в Ставрополье и Краснодаре. Главное,Ukraine hit Wildberries logistics centers in Stavropol and Krasnodar. Main,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Stavropol', 'GPE'), ('Krasnodar', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: новые удары по Wildberries в Краснодаре и Невинномысске","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: new attacks on Wildberries in Krasnodar and Nevinnomyssk",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Krasnodar', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,США нанесли новую серию ударов по Ирану; Трамп пригрозил атакой на  подземный ядерный объект,The US launched a new series of strikes on Iran; Trump threatens attack on underground nuclear facility,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Бусификация» и нападения на сотрудников ТЦК. Как и почему мобилизация в Украине приводит к насилию,“Busification” and attacks on TCC employees. How and why mobilization in Ukraine leads to violence,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Цифровое совершеннолетие»: Франция приняла закон, запрещающий детям до 15 лет пользоваться соцсетями",“Digital coming of age”: France has passed a law prohibiting children under 15 years of age from using social networks,0.0,neutral,"[('Digital', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('under 15 years of age', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зеленский объявил об отставке главкома ВСУ Александра Сырского. Вместо него будет назначен генерал Михаил Драпатый,Zelensky announced the resignation of the commander-in-chief of the Armed Forces of Ukraine Alexander Syrsky. General Mikhail Drapaty will be appointed instead,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('the Armed Forces of Ukraine', 'ORG'), ('Alexander Syrsky', 'PERSON'), ('Mikhail Drapaty', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Министр обороны США Хегсет заявил, что война в Иране уже обошлась Вашингтону в 37,5 млрд долларов",US Defense Secretary Hegseth said that the war in Iran has already cost Washington $37.5 billion,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('$37.5 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Италии в беспорядках после смерти иммигранта из Марокко пострадали десятки полицейских,"In Italy, dozens of police were injured in riots after the death of a Moroccan immigrant.",-1.0,negative,"[('Italy', 'GPE'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Moroccan', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Инцидент в Кахети: ударивший русскоязычную туристку житель Грузии освобожден под залог,Incident in Kakheti: a Georgian resident who hit a Russian-speaking tourist is released on bail,0.0,neutral,"[('Kakheti', 'GPE'), ('Georgian', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Как выжить в войне городов и готова ли к ней Россия? | Военное время, Продолжительность 12,12","Video, How to survive in a war of cities and is Russia ready for it? | Wartime, Duration 12.12",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('12.12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、イランを11夜連続で空爆　トランプ氏は地下核施設への攻撃を示唆,US airstrikes Iran for 11 consecutive nights; Trump hints at attacking underground nuclear facilities,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('11 consecutive nights', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゼレンスキー氏、ウクライナ軍総司令官を解任　連日の抗議デモを受け,Zelenskiy dismisses commander-in-chief of Ukraine's armed forces following daily protests,1.0,positive,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('daily', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,バーナム英首相が初閣議、生活費問題への取り組みを指示,British Prime Minister Burnham instructs first cabinet meeting to address cost of living issue,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヘグセス米国防長官、対イラン戦費は375億ドルに達したと説明　多額の追加予算を要求,US Secretary of Defense Hegseth explains that war costs against Iran have reached $37.5 billion and requests a large additional budget,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Defense Hegseth', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('$37.5 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアの軍艦が英プリマス沖で実弾演習、英仏軍が監視するなか,"Russian warships conduct live-fire drills off the coast of Plymouth, England as British and French forces monitor",-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Plymouth', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエル軍がガザ地区を攻撃、家族6人を含む12人殺害と医療関係者,"Israeli army attacks Gaza Strip, killing 12 people, including 6 family members, and medical personnel",-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza Strip', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('6', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,東京都、猛暑で男性のハーフパンツ勤務を推奨　女性からは「スネハラ」との声も,"Tokyo recommends men to work in shorts due to intense heat; some women say it's ""snehara""",0.0,neutral,"[('Tokyo', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,警察の拘束中に男性が死亡、抗議デモで数十人が負傷　伊ボローニャ,"Man dies in police custody, dozens injured during protests in Bologna, Italy",0.0,neutral,"[('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bologna', 'GPE'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】バーナム新英政権の最初の24時間……解任、サプライズ人事、政策,"[Commentary] The first 24 hours of the new British Burnham administration...dismissals, surprise personnel changes, and policies",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('British Burnham', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ガイアナ沖でフェリーが転覆、少なくとも41人死亡,At least 41 people killed as ferry capsizes off the coast of Guyana,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 41', 'CARDINAL'), ('Guyana', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yashambulia kwa siku 11 mfululizo; mifumo ya ulinzi wa anga yawashwa katika maeneo kadhaa ya Iran","Directly, the United States attacks for 11 consecutive days; Air defense systems have been activated in several areas of Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('11 consecutive days', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Beckham akawa sura ya Kombe la Dunia nchini Marekani?,Why did Beckham become the face of the World Cup in the United States?,0.0,neutral,"[('Beckham', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Baada ya kuthibitishwa kuwa nina ugonjwa huu nilitamani kufa','After it was confirmed that I have this disease I wished to die',0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nchi sita zinazowavutia watalii zaidi  barani Afrika,The six countries that attract the most tourists in Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mlima Kallang uko wapi na kwa nini Trump anautolea vitisho vya kuushambulia?,Where is Mount Kallang and why is Trump threatening to attack it?,-1.0,negative,"[('Mount Kallang', 'LOC'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za soka Jumatano: Chelsea, Arsenal, Tottenham zamuwania Rashford","Football rumors Wednesday: Chelsea, Arsenal, Tottenham for Rashford",0.0,neutral,"[('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Chelsea, Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Tottenham', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Trump atishia kushambulia kituo cha Nyuklia cha Iran chini ya Mlima Kalang,Trump threatens to attack Iran's Nuclear facility under Mount Kalang,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Mount Kalang', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Khalil al-Hayya: Mfahamu kiongozi mpya wa Hamas, mrithi wa Yahya Sinwar","Khalil al-Hayya: Meet the new leader of Hamas, Yahya Sinwar's successor",0.0,neutral,"[('Khalil al-Hayya', 'PERSON'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), (""Yahya Sinwar's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Namna umri unavyoathiri hamu ya kushiriki tendo la ndoa,How age affects the desire to participate in marriage,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kambi ambayo wanajeshi wa Marekani wameuawa na mashambulizi ya Iran,The camp where American soldiers have been killed by Iranian attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Morgan Rogers ‘so happy’ after joining Chelsea in record British deal,Morgan Rogers ‘so happy’ after joining Chelsea in record British deal,0.0,neutral,"[('Morgan Rogers', 'ORG'), ('Chelsea', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Rabat demands answers after Moroccan man dies during arrest in Italy,Rabat demands answers after Moroccan man dies during arrest in Italy,0.0,neutral,"[('Rabat', 'PERSON'), ('Moroccan', 'NORP'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,FIFA World Cup final draws record viewership in United States,FIFA World Cup final draws record viewership in United States,0.0,neutral,"[('FIFA World Cup', 'ORG'), ('United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"US ‘open’ to negotiations with Iran but Tehran not ‘serious’, Rubio says","US ‘open’ to negotiations with Iran but Tehran not ‘serious’, Rubio says",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Rubio', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,India opposition leader Gandhi freed after detention at student-led protest,India opposition leader Gandhi freed after detention at student-led protest,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Gandhi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran toll in Hormuz would set ‘dangerous precedent’ says Rubio,Iran toll in Hormuz would set ‘dangerous precedent’ says Rubio,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('Rubio', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Goats of football: Indian village holds tournament with an indigenous twist,Goats of football: Indian village holds tournament with an indigenous twist,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Palestine weekly: Ahead of elections, Israel doubles down on attacks","Palestine weekly: Ahead of elections, Israel doubles down on attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Palestine', 'GPE'), ('weekly', 'DATE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"More than 140 dead, missing on refugee boat stranded off Mauritania","More than 140 dead, missing on refugee boat stranded off Mauritania",0.0,neutral,"[('More than 140', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mauritania', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,How armed group alliances are reshaping Mali’s conflict and the wider Sahel,How armed group alliances are reshaping Mali’s conflict and the wider Sahel,-1.0,negative,"[('Mali', 'PERSON'), ('Sahel', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Policeman killed in terror attack in Anantnag, Jammu and Kashmir","Policeman killed in terror attack in Anantnag, Jammu and Kashmir",-1.0,negative,"[('Anantnag', 'GPE'), ('Jammu', 'GPE'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,‘Don’t waste our time’: CJI Kant declines to take cognisance of police violence during CJP’s Parliament march,‘Don’t waste our time’: CJI Kant declines to take cognisance of police violence during CJP’s Parliament march,0.0,neutral,"[('CJI Kant', 'ORG'), ('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Pellet guns, shock batons used against protesters in Delhi; police deny","Pellet guns, shock batons used against protesters in Delhi; police deny",0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,INDIA bloc parties marching separately but striking together,INDIA bloc parties marching separately but striking together,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"For the first time, undergraduate enrolments decline in India | Data","For the first time, undergraduate enrolments decline in India | Data",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Nothing can shame people unfazed by Ram temple donation theft: Allahabad High Court,Nothing can shame people unfazed by Ram temple donation theft: Allahabad High Court,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Difference between ‘chest’ and ‘breast’ immaterial in POCSO offences: Kerala HC,Difference between ‘chest’ and ‘breast’ immaterial in POCSO offences: Kerala HC,0.0,neutral,"[('Kerala', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Before ‘Jana Nayagan’: When an 18-year-old Vijay walked the halls of Loyola,Before ‘Jana Nayagan’: When an 18-year-old Vijay walked the halls of Loyola,0.0,neutral,"[('18-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Vijay', 'PERSON'), ('Loyola', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Lists of folly: On the Supreme Court, the SIR and benefits","Lists of folly: On the Supreme Court, the SIR and benefits",0.0,neutral,"[('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('SIR', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Political minefields: On the new Prime Minister of the United Kingdom,Political minefields: On the new Prime Minister of the United Kingdom,0.0,neutral,"[('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Zelensky sacks Ukraine's top army commander after days of protests,Zelensky sacks Ukraine's top army commander after days of protests,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ukrainian drones hit more sites of Russian online retailer Wildberries,Ukrainian drones hit more sites of Russian online retailer Wildberries,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Iran war has cost US $37.5bn so far, Hegseth says, as Pentagon seeks billions more","Iran war has cost US $37.5bn so far, Hegseth says, as Pentagon seeks billions more",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('37.5bn', 'MONEY'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('Pentagon', 'ORG'), ('billions', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,India's Modi government under growing pressure as 'cockroach' protests intensify,India's Modi government under growing pressure as 'cockroach' protests intensify,1.0,positive,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Modi', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,France passes law banning under-15s from social media,France passes law banning under-15s from social media,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Tokyo urges men to wear shorts to work, but some women say it's 'leg hair harassment'","Tokyo urges men to wear shorts to work, but some women say it's 'leg hair harassment'",0.0,neutral,"[('Tokyo', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Police station opens at Hitler's birthplace in bid to rid site of Nazi link,Police station opens at Hitler's birthplace in bid to rid site of Nazi link,0.0,neutral,"[('Hitler', 'PERSON'), ('Nazi', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US renews strikes on Iran as Trump threatens to attack underground nuclear site,US renews strikes on Iran as Trump threatens to attack underground nuclear site,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Michelin-starred restaurateur faces jail for using ants as dessert garnish,Michelin-starred restaurateur faces jail for using ants as dessert garnish,0.0,neutral,"[('Michelin', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Rebel Wilson cleared in defamation case brought by actress in her own film,Rebel Wilson cleared in defamation case brought by actress in her own film,0.0,neutral,"[('Rebel Wilson', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Lettuce-Growing Region in Mexico Stomachs the Fallout From the Cyclospora Outbreak,A Lettuce-Growing Region in Mexico Stomachs the Fallout From the Cyclospora Outbreak,1.0,positive,"[('Lettuce-Growing Region', 'ORG'), ('Mexico Stomachs', 'FAC'), ('the Cyclospora Outbreak', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Germany’s Military Buyers Look to Reduce Caution and Embrace Drones,Germany’s Military Buyers Look to Reduce Caution and Embrace Drones,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Embrace Drones', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Zelensky Dismisses Ukraine’s Top General After Protests,Zelensky Dismisses Ukraine’s Top General After Protests,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Protests', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Japan Is Startled by Prime Minister’s Grueling Sleep Schedule,Japan Is Startled by Prime Minister’s Grueling Sleep Schedule,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('’s Grueling', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Inside the Fight to Rid South Africa of Black Immigrants,Inside the Fight to Rid South Africa of Black Immigrants,0.0,neutral,"[('Black Immigrants', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,3 Myths Fueling Anti-Immigrant Sentiment in South Africa,3 Myths Fueling Anti-Immigrant Sentiment in South Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,K-pop’s NewJeans Hints at Comeback After Monthslong Feud With Its Label,K-pop’s NewJeans Hints at Comeback After Monthslong Feud With Its Label,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,India’s Young Protesters Are Bloodied but Unbowed,India’s Young Protesters Are Bloodied but Unbowed,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Young Protesters Are Bloodied', 'ORG'), ('Unbowed', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Netanyahu Ad Uses a Questionable Tactic Against Bereaved Rival,Netanyahu Ad Uses a Questionable Tactic Against Bereaved Rival,0.0,neutral,"[('Netanyahu Ad Uses a Questionable Tactic Against Bereaved Rival', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_22,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iran’s Neighbors Long for a Deal, Any Deal, to End the War","Iran’s Neighbors Long for a Deal, Any Deal, to End the War",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
