Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,3 ejemplos que evidencian cómo Delcy Rodríguez está desmantelando en Venezuela el modelo económico chavista,3 examples that show how Delcy Rodríguez is dismantling the Chavista economic model in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delcy Rodríguez', 'PERSON'), ('Chavista', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El nuevo monumento en Pyongyang que revela cuántos soldados de Corea del Norte han muerto en la guerra entre Rusia y Ucrania,The new monument in Pyongyang that reveals how many North Korean soldiers have died in the war between Russia and Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Pyongyang', 'GPE'), ('North Korean', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El ""cazador de dictadores"": ""Siempre me agrada ver a un dictador esposado, pero no a cualquier costo""","The ""dictator hunter"": ""I always like to see a dictator in handcuffs, but not at any cost""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Shakira gana su batalla de 8 años contra la Hacienda española, que deberá devolverle 60 millones de euros","Shakira wins her 8-year battle against the Spanish Treasury, which must return 60 million euros",1.0,positive,"[('8-year', 'DATE'), ('the Spanish', 'ORG'), ('Treasury', 'ORG'), ('60 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Vehículos espías: la enorme cantidad de datos que tu auto recopila de ti (y qué puedes hacer para limitarla),Spy vehicles: the enormous amount of data your car collects from you (and what you can do to limit it),0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Mundial de fútbol 2026: consulta el calendario y los resultados de los partidos (con el horario de tu país),Soccer World Cup 2026: check the schedule and match results (with your country's schedule),0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Apareció un mundo de ensueño"": la historia del químico suizo que experimentó el primer viaje con LSD montado en una bicicleta","""A dream world appeared"": the story of the Swiss chemist who experienced the first LSD trip riding a bicycle",0.0,neutral,"[('Swiss', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué se puede decir que las plantas ven,Why can we say that plants see?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es el empresario colombiano Alex Saab, aliado y supuesto testaferro de Nicolás Maduro al que Venezuela extraditó a EE.UU.","Who is the Colombian businessman Alex Saab, ally and alleged figurehead of Nicolás Maduro whom Venezuela extradited to the US.",0.0,neutral,"[('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('Alex Saab', 'PERSON'), ('Nicolás Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué fue la Revolución Cultural de Mao Zedong y cómo marcó la historia de China hace 60 años,What was Mao Zedong's Cultural Revolution and how it marked the history of China 60 years ago,0.0,neutral,"[(""Mao Zedong's"", 'PERSON'), ('Cultural Revolution', 'EVENT'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('60 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,उमर ख़ालिद को ज़मानत न देने वाले अपने ही फ़ैसले पर सुप्रीम कोर्ट ने क्यों उठाए सवाल,Why did the Supreme Court raise questions on its own decision not to grant bail to Omar Khalid?,0.0,neutral,"[('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Omar Khalid', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"रायपुर में दीमक चाट गई म्यूज़ियम के रिकॉर्ड, हज़ारों साल पुरानी चीज़ों की सुरक्षा ख़तरे में","Termites lick museum records in Raipur, safety of thousands of years old things in danger",0.0,neutral,"[('Termites lick museum', 'PERSON'), ('Raipur', 'PERSON'), ('thousands of years old', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,मुख्यमंत्री शुभेंदु अधिकारी ने कोलकाता में पुलिस पर पत्थरबाज़ी की घटना के बाद दी चेतावनी","Live, Chief Minister Shubhendu Adhikari warned after the incident of stone pelting on police in Kolkata",-1.0,negative,"[('Shubhendu Adhikari', 'PERSON'), ('Kolkata', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत में मीडिया और अल्पसंख्यकों पर डच पीएम की 'चिंता' का मोदी सरकार ने दिया ये जवाब,Modi government gave this answer to Dutch PM's 'concern' on media and minorities in India,0.0,neutral,"[(""Dutch PM's '"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रंप के रवाना होने के फ़ौरन बाद पुतिन भी जा रहे हैं शी जिनपिंग से मिलने, क्या चीन नए वर्ल्ड ऑर्डर की धुरी बन रहा है?","Immediately after Trump's departure, Putin is also going to meet Xi Jinping, is China becoming the pivot of the new world order?",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,लखनऊ रेज़ीडेंसी की लड़ाई: भारतीयों की जीत के बावजूद हार की कहानी,Battle of Lucknow Residency: Story of defeat despite Indian victory,1.0,positive,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,एयर शो के दौरान जब आपस में टकराए फ़ाइटर जेट, अवधि 0,40","Video: When fighter jets collided during an air show, duration 0,40",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,कर्नाटक: हिजाब और जनेऊ जैसे धार्मिक प्रतीकों पर छूट के बाद अब क्या हैं चुनौतियाँ,Karnataka: What are the challenges now after relaxation on religious symbols like Hijab and sacred thread?,0.0,neutral,"[('Karnataka', 'PERSON'), ('Hijab', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"यूएई के बराकाह न्यूक्लियर प्लांट पर हमले की भारत ने की निंदा, कितना अहम है ये प्लांट","India condemned the attack on UAE's Barakah Nuclear Plant, how important is this plant",-1.0,negative,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'ORG'), ('Barakah Nuclear Plant', 'FAC')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नीट पेपर लीक: गिरफ़्तार महिला प्रोफ़ेसर कौन हैं, एनटीए ने दी थी क्या ज़िम्मेदारी?","NEET Paper Leak: Who is the arrested female professor, what responsibility was given by NTA?",0.0,neutral,"[('NEET Paper Leak', 'PRODUCT'), ('NTA', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os bastidores da operação de resgate que levou a BYD à lista suja do trabalho escravo (e à demissão de um secretário em Brasília),Behind the scenes of the rescue operation that led BYD to the slave labor dirty list (and the dismissal of a secretary in Brasília),0.0,neutral,"[('BYD', 'ORG'), ('Brasília', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Corpos de mergulhadores são resgatados nas Maldivas; como foi a morte trágica,Bodies of divers are recovered in the Maldives; How was the tragic death?,-1.0,negative,"[('Maldives', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que um veterano das Guerras Napoleônicas tem sido invocado para compreender a Guerra do Irã,Why a Napoleonic Wars veteran has been called upon to understand the Iran War,-1.0,negative,"[('the Iran War', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Tempo está se esgotando': a nova ameaça de Trump ao Irã em meio às negociações paralisadas,'Time is running out': Trump's new threat to Iran amid stalled negotiations,-1.0,negative,"[('Time', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Carros inteligentes: como você pode estar sendo espionado sem saber (e o que fazer para evitar),Smart cars: how you could be being spied on without knowing it (and what to do to avoid it),1.0,positive,"[('Smart', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Convocação da Seleção Brasileira será anunciada nesta segunda; tudo sobre a primeira Copa do Mundo com 48 seleções,The call-up of the Brazilian team will be announced this Monday; everything about the first World Cup with 48 teams,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('this Monday', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('48', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Ebola: o que saber sobre surto na República Democrática do Congo,Ebola: what to know about the outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('the Democratic Republic of Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O quanto da nossa personalidade é definida no momento em que nascemos?,How much of our personality is defined the moment we are born?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Há cobrança para que a gente faça arte política': Adriana Varejão critica rótulo imposto a artistas latinos,'There is a demand for us to make political art': Adriana Varejão criticizes the label imposed on Latin artists,0.0,neutral,"[('Adriana Varejão', 'PERSON'), ('Latin', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Мы молились, чтобы вернуться живыми». Репортаж корреспондента Би-би-си из «килл-зоны» возле Константиновки","""We prayed to come back alive."" Report from a BBC correspondent from the “kill zone” near Konstantinovka",-1.0,negative,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Konstantinovka', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Вспышка Эболы в ДР Конго: почему с ней особенно трудно бороться и стоит ли волноваться всему миру?,Ebola outbreak in DR Congo: why is it especially difficult to combat and should the whole world worry?,0.0,neutral,"[('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Возможно, вы слышите мой голос в последний раз». С началом войны в Иране резко возросло число политических казней","“This may be the last time you hear my voice.” Since the start of the war in Iran, the number of political executions has increased sharply",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: российские беспилотники атаковали гражданские сухогрузы в Черном море","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Russian drones attacked civilian cargo ships in the Black Sea",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трое погибших, 17 раненых: что известно о самой крупной атаке дронов на Москву и область за год","Three dead, 17 wounded: what is known about the largest drone attack on Moscow and the region in a year",-1.0,negative,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('a year', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Часы тикают». Нетаньяху и Трамп обсудили возможность нового этапа войны против Ирана, сообщают израильские СМИ","""The clock is ticking."" Netanyahu and Trump discussed the possibility of a new stage of the war against Iran, Israeli media report",-1.0,negative,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ВОЗ объявила вспышку Эболы в Африке ЧС международного значения,WHO declares Ebola outbreak in Africa a national emergency,0.0,neutral,"[('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Болгария победила в финале 70-го «Евровидения» в Вене, Израиль занял второе место","Bulgaria won the final of the 70th Eurovision in Vienna, Israel took second place",0.0,neutral,"[('Bulgaria', 'GPE'), ('Vienna', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Новая гигантская карта Вселенной поможет понять природу темной энергии,New giant map of the Universe will help understand the nature of dark energy,0.0,neutral,"[('Universe', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Выиграть время до родов. Ученые разрабатывают новый метод лечения тяжелого осложнения беременности,Gain time before giving birth. Scientists are developing a new method for treating a severe pregnancy complication,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、「一刻を争う」とイランに警告　交渉行き詰まるなか,Trump warns Iran that 'every minute counts' as negotiations stall,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英労働党﻿党首選、実施なら「出馬する」とストリーティング氏　バーナム氏は党を「救う」,Streeting says he will run if UK Labor Party leadership election takes place; Burnham says he will 'save' the party,0.0,neutral,"[('UK Labor Party', 'ORG'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,台湾総統、台湾は紛争を挑発しないが主権は手放さないと　トランプ氏の警告受け,Taiwanese president warns Taiwan not to provoke conflict but not give up sovereignty,-1.0,negative,"[('Taiwanese', 'NORP'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エボラ出血熱、コンゴ民主共和国で流行　WHOが「国際的な緊急事態」宣言,Ebola hemorrhagic fever outbreak in Democratic Republic of Congo; WHO declares 'international emergency',0.0,neutral,"[('Democratic Republic of Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏の「宴会場」警備費に連邦予算おりず、米上院が規則違反と判断,"No federal funding for security at Trump's banquet hall, ruled by U.S. Senate a violation of rules",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('U.S. Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロンドンで対立する2グループの大規模デモが同時に　43人逮捕と警察発表,"Large-scale demonstration by two opposing groups in London simultaneously, 43 people arrested, police announced",0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('43', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏の支持する上院議員候補、弾劾に賛成した現職を下す　ルイジアナ州共和党予備選,Trump-backed Senate candidate defeats incumbent who supported impeachment in Louisiana Republican primary,0.0,neutral,"[('Senate', 'ORG'), ('Louisiana', 'GPE'), ('Republican', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、イランの核開発停止「20年間で十分」　履行の保証があればと,"Trump says ``20 years is enough'' to halt Iran's nuclear program, as long as there is a guarantee that it will be implemented.",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,習氏との会談終えたトランプ氏、台湾の独立望んでいないと発言　合意の詳細は明かされず,"After meeting with Xi, Trump says he does not want independence for Taiwan, details of agreement not disclosed",1.0,positive,"[('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,レバノン、南部でイスラエルが救急隊員など6人殺害と発表　米はイスラエルとレバノンの停戦延長を発表,Israel announces killing of 6 people including emergency workers in southern Lebanon; US announces extension of ceasefire between Israel and Lebanon,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Maandamano ya kupinga ongezeko la bei ya mafuta yashika kasi Kenya, mgomo wa usafiri ukiendelea","Directly, Protests against the increase in fuel prices are gaining momentum in Kenya, as the transport strike continues",0.0,neutral,"[('Protests', 'NORP'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Video za droni zilizorushwa na Hezbollah zaonesha jinsi kundi hilo lilivyobadili mfumo wa kuishambulia Israel,Videos of drones launched by Hezbollah show how the group changed the system of attacking Israel,-1.0,negative,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kombe la Dunia 2026 linaanza lini, na maswali mengine kuhusu Kombe la Dunia la kwanza lenye timu 48","When does the 2026 World Cup start, and other questions about the first 48-team World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('48', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"CHADEMA vs Msajili, vita vya panzi au mgogoro wa mfumo?","CHADEMA vs Registrar, grasshopper war or system crisis?",-1.0,negative,"[('Registrar', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,J-10C Fighters: Nini kinazifanya ndege hizi za kivita kuwa hatari zaidi?,J-10C Fighters: What makes these fighter jets so dangerous?,0.0,neutral,"[('J-10C Fighters', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Korea Kusini yaitaka Iran kuonesha msimamo wake kuhusu shambulio dhidi ya meli ya mafuta katika Mlango bahari wa Hormuz,South Korea wants Iran to show its position regarding the attack on the oil tanker in the Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mkenya apinga ongezeko la bei ya mafuta mahakamani,A Kenyan opposes the increase in fuel prices in court,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Vinywaji vya kuongeza nguvu vina madhara gani kwa vijana?,What are the effects of energy drinks on young people?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu mambo Matano muhimu kumhusu mtuhumiwa mkuu wa mauaji ya kimbari ya Rwanda,Know five important things about the main suspect of the Rwandan genocide,0.0,neutral,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rwandan', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kwa nini nyoka waliokuwa na miguu sasa hawana tena, wanawezaje kutambaa haraka hivyo?","Why do snakes that had legs now no longer have them, how can they crawl so fast?",0.0,neutral,[]
