Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Harry Potter y el prisionero de guerra: el soldado ucraniano que recitó la saga de memoria para ayudar a sus compañeros a sobrevivir,Harry Potter and the Prisoner of War: the Ukrainian soldier who recited the saga by heart to help his companions survive,-1.0,negative,"[('Harry Potter', 'PERSON'), ('the Prisoner of War', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quién era el ""Niño Guerrero"", líder del Tren de Aragua, y qué se sabe del operativo anunciado por Trump que llevó a su muerte","Who was ""Niño Guerrero"", leader of the Aragua Train, and what is known about the operation announced by Trump that led to his death",-1.0,negative,"[('the Aragua Train', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""No a los 10 millones de habitantes"": Suiza, el primer país del mundo que se plantea poner un límite a su población","""No to 10 million inhabitants"": Switzerland, the first country in the world to consider putting a limit on its population",0.0,neutral,"[('10 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Bette Graham, la secretaria que hizo una fortuna porque cometía demasiados errores","Bette Graham, the secretary who made a fortune because she made too many mistakes",0.0,neutral,"[('Bette Graham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Puma vs Adidas: cómo la pelea entre dos hermanos partió en dos una ciudad alemana durante décadas,Puma vs Adidas: how the fight between two brothers split a German city in two for decades,0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('two for decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo una higuera me ayudó a descubrir la prisión secreta donde fui torturada,How a fig tree helped me discover the secret prison where I was tortured,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Elecciones en Perú: Keiko Fujimori adelanta a Roberto Sánchez con una ventaja de unos 18.000 votos en las disputadas presidenciales,"Elections in Peru: Keiko Fujimori overtakes Roberto Sánchez with an advantage of about 18,000 votes in the presidential dispute",0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('about 18,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué algunos lugares quieren ser retirados de la Lista del Patrimonio Mundial de la Unesco,Why some places want to be removed from the UNESCO World Heritage List,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Por qué en EE.UU. le dicen al fútbol soccer y cuál es el origen de esa palabra (no, no la crearon los estadounidenses)","Why in the US do they call football soccer and what is the origin of that word (no, the Americans did not create it)",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Conoces las camisetas del Mundial? ¡Ponte a prueba con este quiz!,Do you know the World Cup t-shirts? Test yourself with this quiz!,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पटना में रेलवे स्टेशन पर पत्थरबाज़ी और ट्रेनों को रोका गया, परीक्षार्थी किस बात से थे ग़ुस्से में","Stone pelting and trains were stopped at the railway station in Patna, what were the candidates angry about?",0.0,neutral,"[('Patna', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,दिल्ली में यमुना नदी की सफ़ाई में हिस्सा ले रही टेरिटोरियल आर्मी ने क्या बताया?","Live, what did the Territorial Army taking part in the cleaning of Yamuna river in Delhi tell?",0.0,neutral,"[('the Territorial Army', 'ORG'), ('Yamuna', 'NORP'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिका और ईरान के बीच संभावित समझौते में किन बिंदुओं का ज़िक्र है,Which points are mentioned in the possible agreement between America and Iran?,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बांदा में दलित युवक से शादी करने वाली युवती की थाने में हत्या पर क्यों उठ रहे सवाल,Why are questions being raised on the murder of a girl who married a Dalit youth in Banda in the police station?,0.0,neutral,"[('Dalit', 'PERSON'), ('Banda', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारतीय नाविकों की मौत के मामले में रुबियो का बयान क्या भारत के लिए 'चेतावनी' है?,Is Rubio's statement a 'warning' for India regarding the death of Indian sailors?,-1.0,negative,"[('Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अश्लील जोक्स पर क्यों हंसते हैं लोग,Why do people laugh at obscene jokes?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,भारत में कमज़ोर होते क्षेत्रीय दल किस राजनीतिक बदलाव की ओर इशारा कर रहे हैं?,What political change are the weakening regional parties in India indicating?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'पुश इन से पहले बत्तियां बंद कर दी जाती हैं': बीएसएफ़ को लेकर बांग्लादेश का दावा,'Lights are switched off before push in': Bangladesh's claim regarding BSF,0.0,neutral,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('BSF', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अहमदाबाद विमान हादसे का वीडियो बनाने वाले आर्यन को क्यों छोड़ना पड़ा शहर,"Why did Aryan, who made the video of Ahmedabad plane crash, have to leave the city?",0.0,neutral,"[('Aryan', 'PERSON'), ('Ahmedabad', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'परसों ही बेटे से बात हुई थी..., ओमान में मिसाइल हमले में मारे गए शिवानंद के पिता ने और क्या बताया","'I spoke to my son the day before yesterday..., what else did the father of Shivanand, who was killed in the missile attack in Oman, tell?",-1.0,negative,"[('the day before yesterday', 'DATE'), ('Shivanand', 'GPE'), ('Oman', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As desculpas de joelho que o Vaticano fez a povoado no Peru: 'Fizeram o que queriam conosco porque somos pobres',The kneeling apology that the Vatican made to people in Peru: 'They did what they wanted with us because we are poor',0.0,neutral,"[('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump afirma que assinatura de acordo entre EUA e Irã está prevista para domingo; Teerã expressa dúvida,Trump says the signing of an agreement between the US and Iran is scheduled for Sunday; Tehran expresses doubt,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Vini Jr. salva Brasil de derrota contra o Marrocos na estreia da Copa 2026,Vini Jr. saves Brazil from defeat against Morocco in the 2026 World Cup debut,0.0,neutral,"[('Vini Jr.', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A aposta do Brasil nos 'coletes inteligentes' para voltar a brilhar na Copa do Mundo,Brazil's bet on 'smart vests' to shine again in the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Da semifinal histórica ao sonho do título: Marrocos, o adversário do Brasil na estreia","From the historic semi-final to the dream of the title: Morocco, Brazil's opponent in the debut",0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Aura ou carma: de onde vêm a veneração e o temor inspirados pelo número da camiseta na Seleção,Aura or karma: where the veneration and fear inspired by the shirt number in the National Team come from,0.0,neutral,"[('National Team', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Superestrela na Espanha, questionado no Brasil: será que Vini Jr. conseguirá convencer o país na Copa?","Superstar in Spain, asked in Brazil: will Vini Jr. be able to convince the country in the World Cup?",0.0,neutral,"[('Superstar', 'ORG'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Vini Jr.', 'PERSON'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Aqui não temos medo': a família brasileira que achou segurança no Marrocos,'We are not afraid here': the Brazilian family who found safety in Morocco,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump anuncia morte do líder do grupo venezuelano Tren de Aragua: quem era Niño Guerrero?,Trump announces death of the leader of the Venezuelan group Tren de Aragua: who was Niño Guerrero?,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('Tren de Aragua', 'PERSON'), ('Niño Guerrero', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Torcer para o Brasil está mais caro? A alta do preço da carne, da cerveja e de outros itens para assistir aos jogos da Copa","Is supporting Brazil more expensive? The rise in the price of meat, beer and other items to watch the World Cup games",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Британия перехватила судно российского «теневого флота» в Ла-Манше,Britain intercepts a Russian “shadow fleet” vessel in the English Channel,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трамп заявил, что соглашение с Ираном будет подписано в воскресенье, после чего откроется Ормузский пролив","Trump said an agreement with Iran will be signed on Sunday, after which the Strait of Hormuz will open.",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Нью-Йорк Никс» впервые за более чем 50 лет выиграли чемпионат НБА,The New York Knicks won the NBA Championship for the first time in more than 50 years.,0.0,neutral,"[('The New York Knicks', 'ORG'), ('the NBA Championship', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('more than 50 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: удары по Сумской и Запорожской областям, есть жертвы","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: attacks on Sumy and Zaporozhye regions, there are casualties",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Sumy', 'PERSON'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Шотландия вернулась на ЧМ спустя 28 лет и обыграла Гаити; Бразилия сыграла вничью с Марокко,Scotland returned to the World Cup after 28 years and beat Haiti; Brazil drew with Morocco,0.0,neutral,"[('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('28 years', 'DATE'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зеленский подписал закон об отмене защиты русского языка. Что это означает,Zelensky signed a law abolishing protection of the Russian language. What does this mean,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Белфасте тысячи людей вышли на митинг против расизма после беспорядков из-за нападения с ножом,Thousands rally against racism in Belfast following riots over stabbing attack,0.0,neutral,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Belfast', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Швейцарии пройдет референдум о том, не следует ли ограничить численность населения 10 миллионами",Switzerland to hold referendum on whether population should be capped at 10 million,0.0,neutral,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('10 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"День рождения Карла III: парад в центре Лондона, пролет «Красных стрел» и королевская семья на балконе Букингемского дворца","Birthday of Charles III: parade in central London, flypast of the Red Arrows and the royal family on the balcony of Buckingham Palace",0.0,neutral,"[('Charles III:', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('the Red Arrows', 'ORG'), ('Buckingham Palace', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Трамп заявил, что американские военные убили лидера группировки Tren de Aragua",Trump said that the US military killed the leader of the Tren de Aragua group,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the Tren de Aragua', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イラン、戦闘終結で合意ならホルムズ海峡は再開と,Iran will reopen Strait of Hormuz if agreement ends fighting,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,マスク氏が世界初の「トリリオネア」に　スペースXの株式公開で資産1兆ドル超え,"Musk becomes world's first 'trillionaire', with wealth exceeding $1 trillion after SpaceX goes public",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('$1 trillion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英現代画家ホックニー氏が死去、国王も追悼,"British contemporary painter Hockney dies, King pays tribute",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Hockney', 'GPE'), ('King', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,韓国・尹前大統領、さらに懲役30年の判決　北朝鮮にドローン飛ばすよう指示,"Former South Korean President Yoon sentenced to 30 years in prison, ordered to send drones to North Korea",0.0,neutral,"[('South Korean', 'NORP'), ('Yoon', 'PERSON'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本はどんなチームなのか　BBCスポーツ記者が分析,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] What kind of team is Japan? BBC sports reporter analyzes,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英国防相が辞任、防衛費めぐり政府内で対立　スターマー氏の指導力に新たな打撃,UK Defense Minister resigns as government conflict over defense spending deals another blow to Starmer's leadership,-1.0,negative,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Starmer', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 英国防相の辞任、スターマー政権と防衛計画にどんな影響があるのか,[Commentary] What impact does the resignation of the UK Defense Secretary have on the Starmer government and defense plans?,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 メキシコで開幕、いきなり3人退場の波乱　色鮮やかな開会式も,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Opening in Mexico, turbulent with 3 people suddenly sent off, colorful opening ceremony too",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup] Opening', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、戦争終結の合意に近づいていると表明　対イラン攻撃の中止を発表後,"Trump says he is close to a deal to end the war, after announcing a halt to attacks on Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,アメリカとの国境線上にある図書館、カナダ側にも入り口を新設　トランプ政権の規制強化で, 所要時間 2,26","Video, A library on the border with the United States has a new entrance on the Canadian side. Due to the Trump administration's tightened regulations, the time required is 2.26",0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('2.26', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Hatua za mwisho kuelekea makubaliano, Marekani na Iran wasubiri kutia saini hati ya maelewano","One by one, the last steps towards an agreement, the United States and Iran are waiting to sign a memorandum of understanding",-1.0,negative,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tunachojua kuhusu makubaliano yatakayotiwa saini na Marekani na Iran,What we know about the agreement that will be signed by the United States and Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Mauaji, mateso na ukatili: Tawala tano zilizoacha historia ya umwagaji damu Afrika","Murder, torture and brutality: Five regimes that left a bloody history in Africa",0.0,neutral,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ni wimbo gani wa kombe la Dunia uliokuwa maarufu zaidi?,What was the most popular World Cup song?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Morocco yajiondoa kuwania uenyeji wa mashindano yoyote ya Afrika,Morocco withdrew from competing for the hosting of any African tournament,0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco', 'ORG'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ratiba, msimamo na matokeo","World Cup 2026: Schedule, standings and results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini baadhi ya watu wanashauriwa kujiepusha kula maembe,Why are some people advised to refrain from eating mangoes?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, wanadamu wanaweza kupata watoto katika anga za juu?",Can humans have children in outer space?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi mpya za soka: Man City, Man Utd na Bayern zamtaka Branthwaite, Arsenal macho kwa Tzolis","New football rumours: Man City, Man Utd and Bayern want Branthwaite, Arsenal eyeing Tzolis",0.0,neutral,"[('Man City', 'GPE'), ('Branthwaite', 'PERSON'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Tzolis', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwanini Tanzania inaweza kufuzu Kombe la Dunia 2030?,Why can Tanzania qualify for the 2030 World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('the 2030 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Romanian president picks Liberal former mayor as PM to form new government,Romanian president picks Liberal former mayor as PM to form new government,0.0,neutral,"[('Romanian', 'NORP'), ('Liberal', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Will the US-Iran deal be signed on Sunday? What we know so far,Will the US-Iran deal be signed on Sunday? What we know so far,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup Day 4: Netherlands take on Japan, Curacao set to make history","World Cup Day 4: Netherlands take on Japan, Curacao set to make history",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day 4', 'EVENT'), ('Netherlands', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Curacao', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,UK court to rule on Palestine Action ‘terrorist’ label: What we know,UK court to rule on Palestine Action ‘terrorist’ label: What we know,-1.0,negative,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Palestine Action', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Signing of US-Iran deal not on Trump’s public schedule,Signing of US-Iran deal not on Trump’s public schedule,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,UK forces seize suspected Russian shadow fleet tanker in English Channel,UK forces seize suspected Russian shadow fleet tanker in English Channel,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Switzerland votes on right-wing bid to cap country’s population,Switzerland votes on right-wing bid to cap country’s population,1.0,positive,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran war day 107: Washington, Tehran close to signing first stage of deal","Iran war day 107: Washington, Tehran close to signing first stage of deal",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran war day', 'EVENT'), ('107', 'CARDINAL'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Australia spoil Turkiye’s return to the World Cup with shock 2-0 victory,Australia spoil Turkiye’s return to the World Cup with shock 2-0 victory,1.0,positive,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Turkiye', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_14,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Smiles all around as Morocco, Brazil share spoils and Knicks make history","Smiles all around as Morocco, Brazil share spoils and Knicks make history",0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Knicks', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Column | Why didn’t you let me read?,Column | Why didn’t you let me read?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The human cost of H1-B dream | Tanul Thakur’s Wild Wild East,The human cost of H1-B dream | Tanul Thakur’s Wild Wild East,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanul Thakur’s', 'NORP'), ('Wild Wild East', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,What Granta’s Commonwealth Prize AI scandal tells us about the future of literary writing,What Granta’s Commonwealth Prize AI scandal tells us about the future of literary writing,0.0,neutral,"[('Granta’s Commonwealth Prize AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Interview | Manil Suri on his new book A Room in Bombay: A Memoir,Interview | Manil Suri on his new book A Room in Bombay: A Memoir,0.0,neutral,"[('Manil Suri', 'PERSON'), ('A Room in Bombay:', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Memoir', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"As heatwaves intensify, India’s ASHA workers are paying the price","As heatwaves intensify, India’s ASHA workers are paying the price",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"India is innovating for a sustainable future; India is innovating for the world, says PM Modi","India is innovating for a sustainable future; India is innovating for the world, says PM Modi",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia war LIVE: Iran media says Tehran 'not yet' taken final decision on U.S. peace deal,West Asia war LIVE: Iran media says Tehran 'not yet' taken final decision on U.S. peace deal,0.0,neutral,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Indian Army unveils new uniform policy, phases out colonial-era practices","Indian Army unveils new uniform policy, phases out colonial-era practices",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian Army', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"CJP protest in Bengaluru LIVE: Prakash Raj, Sonam Wangchuk, among others to participate","CJP protest in Bengaluru LIVE: Prakash Raj, Sonam Wangchuk, among others to participate",0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Bengaluru', 'GPE'), ('Sonam Wangchuk', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Abhishek Banerjee reaches CID headquarters for questioning in forgery case,Abhishek Banerjee reaches CID headquarters for questioning in forgery case,0.0,neutral,"[('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump says US-Iran deal to be signed on Sunday as Tehran casts doubt on timing,Trump says US-Iran deal to be signed on Sunday as Tehran casts doubt on timing,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Switzerland votes on plan to cap population at 10 million,Switzerland votes on plan to cap population at 10 million,0.0,neutral,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('10 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Russian families use AI to 'resurrect' loved ones killed in Ukraine,Russian families use AI to 'resurrect' loved ones killed in Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('AI', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,New York Knicks win NBA championship for first time in over 50 years,New York Knicks win NBA championship for first time in over 50 years,1.0,positive,"[('New York Knicks', 'ORG'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('over 50 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Author Chimamanda Adichie accuses hospital of stalling review into son's death,Author Chimamanda Adichie accuses hospital of stalling review into son's death,-1.0,negative,"[('Chimamanda Adichie', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Vincent's parents 'never say he's good enough' - so he turned to a middle-aged couple online,Vincent's parents 'never say he's good enough' - so he turned to a middle-aged couple online,1.0,positive,"[('Vincent', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Norway braces for verdict in rape trial of crown princess's son Høiby,Norway braces for verdict in rape trial of crown princess's son Høiby,0.0,neutral,"[('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Høiby', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Armed men kidnap high-ranking security official in Haiti,Armed men kidnap high-ranking security official in Haiti,0.0,neutral,"[('Haiti', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump's name removed from Kennedy Center after court order,Trump's name removed from Kennedy Center after court order,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Kennedy Center', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_14,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Kidnapped Nigerian retired general dies in captivity,Kidnapped Nigerian retired general dies in captivity,0.0,neutral,"[('Nigerian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: U.S. and Tehran Send Mixed Signals on Emerging Peace Agreement,Iran War Live Updates: U.S. and Tehran Send Mixed Signals on Emerging Peace Agreement,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran War Live Updates', 'EVENT'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The G7 Summit Is Dogged by Chaos and Divided by Trump,The G7 Summit Is Dogged by Chaos and Divided by Trump,0.0,neutral,"[('The G7 Summit Is Dogged by Chaos', 'ORG'), ('Divided', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Deadlocked Wars: How Major Powers Misread the Regions They Attacked,Deadlocked Wars: How Major Powers Misread the Regions They Attacked,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Meet the Smallest Country Ever to Reach the World Cup,Meet the Smallest Country Ever to Reach the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Japan Is Running Out of Royals. Are More Men the Answer?,Japan Is Running Out of Royals. Are More Men the Answer?,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Germany and Japan Are Rearming Again, 80 Years After World War II","Germany and Japan Are Rearming Again, 80 Years After World War II",-1.0,negative,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('80 Years', 'DATE'), ('World War II', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"With a Deal Seemingly Close, the U.S. Faces an Iran More Willing to Withstand Pressure","With a Deal Seemingly Close, the U.S. Faces an Iran More Willing to Withstand Pressure",0.0,neutral,"[('the U.S. Faces', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Withstand Pressure', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Russia Is Rich in Ballistic Missiles. Ukraine Is Short of Ways to Stop Them.,Russia Is Rich in Ballistic Missiles. Ukraine Is Short of Ways to Stop Them.,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ballistic Missiles', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"At the Canadian Screen Awards, the Industry Steps Outside Hollywood’s Shadow","At the Canadian Screen Awards, the Industry Steps Outside Hollywood’s Shadow",-1.0,negative,"[('the Canadian Screen Awards', 'ORG'), ('the Industry Steps Outside Hollywood’s Shadow', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_14,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A Tren de Aragua Leader Is Killed in a Joint Strike, U.S. and Venezuela Say","A Tren de Aragua Leader Is Killed in a Joint Strike, U.S. and Venezuela Say",-1.0,negative,"[('Joint Strike', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela Say', 'ORG')]"
