Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Tu avión se desvía 1.000 millas"": la preocupante guerra invisible del GPS que está alterando el transporte aéreo","""Your plane deviates 1,000 miles"": the worrying invisible GPS war that is disrupting air travel",-1.0,negative,"[('1,000 miles', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Quiénes son los principales candidatos para presidir Colombia y suceder a Petro,Who are the main candidates to preside over Colombia and succeed Petro?,0.0,neutral,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Petro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Brooklyn Rivera, el líder indígena nicaragüense que fue detenido en 2023 y ahora está en un hospital con ""ventilación mecánica""","Brooklyn Rivera, the Nicaraguan indigenous leader who was arrested in 2023 and is now in a hospital with ""mechanical ventilation""",0.0,neutral,"[('Brooklyn Rivera', 'ORG'), ('Nicaraguan', 'NORP'), ('2023', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Tengo miedo de verlos de nuevo"": la indignación en Reino Unido por el caso de tres adolescentes que evitaron la cárcel tras ser condenados por violar a dos menores","""I'm afraid to see them again"": the outrage in the United Kingdom over the case of three teenagers who avoided prison after being convicted of raping two minors",0.0,neutral,"[('the United Kingdom', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Mi hermano se transformó en otra persona"": cómo el mexicano Temach se convirtió en la mayor estrella de la machosfera en América Latina","""My brother transformed into another person"": how the Mexican Temach became the biggest star of the machosphere in Latin America",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,5 gráficos que muestran la Colombia que heredará el próximo presidente,5 graphics that show the Colombia that the next president will inherit,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La restauración del monumento milenario más ""obsceno"" de Reino Unido","The restoration of the most ""obscene"" ancient monument in the United Kingdom",0.0,neutral,"[('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,100 años de Marilyn Monroe: su estrecha relación con México y otros 3 hechos de la vida de la icónica actriz que quizás no conocías,100 years of Marilyn Monroe: her close relationship with Mexico and 3 other facts from the life of the iconic actress that you may not have known,0.0,neutral,"[('100 years', 'DATE'), ('Marilyn Monroe', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"EE.UU. e Irán están cerca de alcanzar un acuerdo para extender el alto el fuego, según el vicepresidente JD Vance","US and Iran are close to reaching an agreement to extend the ceasefire, according to Vice President JD Vance",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('JD Vance', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El sufrimiento silencioso de los niños en Gaza que han perdido la capacidad de hablar,The silent suffering of children in Gaza who have lost the ability to speak,0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,आईपीएल 2026: अगर गुजरात टाइटंस और राजस्थान रॉयल्स का मैच धुल गया तो कौन पहुंचेगा फ़ाइनल में?,"IPL 2026: If the match between Gujarat Titans and Rajasthan Royals is washed out, then who will reach the final?",0.0,neutral,"[('Gujarat Titans', 'ORG'), ('Rajasthan Royals', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,क्वाड गुट पर चीन की टिप्पणी के बाद भारतीय विदेश मंत्रालय का आया बयान","Live, Indian Foreign Ministry's statement after China's comment on Quad group",0.0,neutral,"[(""Indian Foreign Ministry's"", 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Quad', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"इंदिरा गांधी ने रुपए को जानबूझकर कमज़ोर क्यों किया था, सोवियत संघ हुआ था नाराज़","Why did Indira Gandhi deliberately weaken the rupee, the Soviet Union was angry",0.0,neutral,"[('Indira Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('the Soviet Union', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बरेलीः स्कूलों को बेसहारा गायों को भूसा दान करने के आदेश पर क्यों हुआ विवाद,Bareilly: Why was there controversy over the order to donate straw to destitute cows in schools?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सबरीमाला केस में बड़ा सवाल, क्या अदालतें धार्मिक प्रथाओं की जाँच कर सकती हैं?","Big question in Sabarimala case, can courts investigate religious practices?",0.0,neutral,"[('Sabarimala', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"दो सौ साल पहले आज ही के दिन अनजाने में ईजाद हुई थी माचिस, जानिए ग़ुमनाम आविष्कारक की कहानी","Two hundred years ago, on this day, the matchbox was invented unknowingly, know the story of the unknown inventor.",1.0,positive,"[('Two hundred years ago', 'DATE'), ('this day', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वैभव सूर्यवंशी पर प्यार और प्रशंसा की बारिश पाकिस्तान में भी, प्यार से नाम भी बदला","Love and praise showered on Vaibhav Suryavanshi in Pakistan too, even changed his name with love",0.0,neutral,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ज़किया अहमद: एवरेस्ट फ़तह करने वाली पहली अफ़ग़ान महिला, तालिबान से ऐसे बचाई थी जान","Zakia Ahmed: The first Afghan woman to conquer Everest, this is how she saved her life from Taliban",0.0,neutral,"[('Zakia Ahmed', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Afghan', 'NORP'), ('Everest', 'LOC'), ('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"""उजाले अपनी यादों के…"", उर्दू शायरी को महफ़िलों से निकालकर अवाम तक पहुँचाने वाले बशीर बद्र नहीं रहे","""Ujale apni yaadon ke..."", Bashir Badr, who brought Urdu poetry from the gatherings to the common people, is no more.",0.0,neutral,"[('Bashir Badr', 'PERSON'), ('Urdu', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'सत्ता छीननी पड़ती है':  'कांग्रेस के संकटमोचक' डीके शिवकुमार कैसे पहुँचे सीएम की कुर्सी तक,'Power has to be snatched': How 'Congress' troubleshooter' DK Shivkumar reached CM's chair,0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('DK Shivkumar', 'PERSON'), ('CM', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como o governo Lula perdeu a batalha que fez EUA declararem CV e PCC como terroristas,How the Lula government lost the battle that made the US declare CV and PCC terrorists,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('CV', 'GPE'), ('PCC', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Classificação de PCC e CV como terroristas pelos EUA abre espaço para ação da CIA no Brasil, diz promotor que há 20 anos combate facção paulista","Classification of PCC and CV as terrorists by the USA opens space for CIA action in Brazil, says prosecutor who has been fighting São Paulo faction for 20 years",-1.0,negative,"[('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('São Paulo', 'PERSON'), ('20 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Vitória para Flávio, derrota para Lula? Como as eleições podem ser impactadas por decisão de Trump de classificar PCC e Comando Vermelho como terroristas","Victory for Flávio, defeat for Lula? How the elections could be impacted by Trump's decision to classify PCC and Red Command as terrorists",0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('PCC', 'ORG'), ('Red Command', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"EUA classificaram PCC e CV como terroristas 'após pressão dos Bolsonaros', diz NY Times; como a imprensa internacional noticiou decisão","USA classified PCC and CV as terrorists 'after pressure from Bolsonaros', says NY Times; how the international press reported the decision",-1.0,negative,"[('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaros', 'PERSON'), ('NY Times', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que pode acontecer após Trump declarar PCC e CV como organizações terroristas,What could happen after Trump declares PCC and CV as terrorist organizations,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Governo Trump classifica CV e PCC como terroristas e Flávio Bolsonaro comemora: 'Grande dia',Trump government classifies CV and PCC as terrorists and Flávio Bolsonaro celebrates: 'Great day',0.0,neutral,"[('CV', 'ORG'), ('PCC', 'ORG'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Rússia cruzou mais uma linha': a reação da UE e da Otan após drone russo atingir prédio na Romênia,'Russia has crossed another line': the EU and NATO's reaction after Russian drone hits building in Romania,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Romania', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Fim da escala 6x1 com transição curta 'é inviável', diz dono de pizzaria: 'Como eu faço para ter um novo chef em 60 dias?'","End of the 6x1 scale with a short transition 'is unfeasible', says pizzeria owner: 'How do I get a new chef in 60 days?'",0.0,neutral,"[('6x1', 'CARDINAL'), ('60 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o dono da Ford criou a escala de trabalho 5x2 há 100 anos — e como isso impactou o mundo,Why the owner of Ford created the 5x2 work schedule 100 years ago — and how it impacted the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Ford', 'ORG'), ('5x2', 'ORG'), ('100 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Камера на двоих, нары, унитаз, кран с холодной водой». Митрополит Иларион рассказал Би-би-си об обстоятельствах своего задержания в Чехии","“A cell for two, bunks, a toilet, a tap with cold water.” Metropolitan Hilarion told the BBC about the circumstances of his detention in the Czech Republic",0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Metropolitan Hilarion', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('the Czech Republic', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Потери России в Украине: что известно из поименного подсчета и оценок разведок,Russia's losses in Ukraine: what is known from roll calls and intelligence assessments,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Удар по Старобельску: что известно неделю спустя,Strike on Starobelsk: what is known a week later,0.0,neutral,"[('Starobelsk', 'PERSON'), ('a week later', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: российский беспилотник упал на дом в Румынии; два человека погибли в Волгограде при атаке на химзавод","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Russian drone falls on a house in Romania; two people died in Volgograd during an attack on a chemical plant",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Romania', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Volgograd', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Нетаньяху заявил, что поручил ЦАХАЛ расширить контроль над сектором Газа до 70% территории",Netanyahu said he instructed the IDF to expand control over the Gaza Strip to 70% of the territory.,0.0,neutral,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('IDF', 'ORG'), ('the Gaza Strip', 'GPE'), ('70%', 'PERCENT')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Венгрии при новой власти полиция не увидела оснований для запрета ЛГБТ-прайда,"In Hungary, under the new government, the police saw no reason to ban LGBT pride",0.0,neutral,"[('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('LGBT', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В многоэтажку в Румынии попал российский дрон, Бухарест заявил о серьезной эскалации. Что известно","A Russian drone hit a high-rise building in Romania, Bucharest announced a serious escalation. What is known",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Romania', 'GPE'), ('Bucharest', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Милане реставрируют мозаику с изображением туринского быка, пострадавшего от ритуала «на удачу»","In Milan, a mosaic depicting the bull of Turin, damaged by a ritual “for good luck”, is being restored",1.0,positive,"[('Milan', 'GPE'), ('mosaic', 'PRODUCT'), ('Turin', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Искра удачи. 200 лет назад малоизвестный аптекарь из Англии случайно изобрел спички,"A spark of luck. 200 years ago, a little-known pharmacist from England accidentally invented matches.",0.0,neutral,"[('200 years ago', 'DATE'), ('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Тихановская встретилась с Зеленским в Киеве, на войне в Украине погиб разгонявший протесты омоновец. Главное в Беларуси за неделю",Tikhanovskaya met with Zelensky in Kyiv; a riot policeman who was dispersing protests died in the war in Ukraine. The main things in Belarus in a week,-1.0,negative,"[('Tikhanovskaya', 'ORG'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアのドローンが東欧ルーマニアの集合住宅を直撃、2人負傷　EUやNATOが厳しく批判,"Russian drone hits apartment complex in Romania, Eastern Europe, injuring 2 people, harshly criticized by EU and NATO",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Romania', 'GPE'), ('Eastern Europe', 'LOC'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカとイラン、合意に「まだ達していない」が「非常に近づいている」と米副大統領,"US and Iran 'not yet' in agreement, but 'very close', says US vice president",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエルがレバノン首都を攻撃、停戦発効後で2回目,Israel attacks Lebanese capital for second time since ceasefire takes effect,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanese', 'NORP'), ('second', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,欧州で熱波、ポルトガルは40.3度で5月の最高を更新　フランスでは休校も,"Heatwave in Europe, Portugal hits record high of 40.3 degrees in May; schools closed in France",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Portugal', 'GPE'), ('40.3 degrees', 'QUANTITY'), ('May', 'DATE'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 米国とイランは和平に近づいているのか、再び戦争へ向かっているのか,[Commentary] Are the US and Iran getting closer to peace or heading towards war again?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,EU、中国「Temu」に370億円の罰金　違法製品の販売めぐり,EU fines China's Temu 37 billion yen for selling illegal products,0.0,neutral,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Temu 37 billion yen', 'LAW')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,輸送コンテナをキッチン・バス完備の住居に　住宅価格が高騰するキューバ, 所要時間 1,07","Video, Turning a shipping container into a home with a kitchen and bath as housing prices soar in Cuba, Required time 1,07",0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,【分析】 トランプ氏とSNS、数千件の投稿から分かること, 所要時間 2,36","Video, [Analysis] What we can learn from thousands of posts about Mr. Trump and SNS, Required time 2,36",0.0,neutral,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('SNS', 'ORG'), ('2,36', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ブルー・オリジンのロケット、燃焼試験中に爆発　米フロリダ州,"Blue Origin rocket explodes during combustion test in Florida, US",0.0,neutral,"[('Blue Origin', 'ORG'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【写真で見る】イギリス南部の空で劇的な雷と稲妻　記録的な高気温の後,[See in photos] Dramatic thunder and lightning in the skies over southern England after record high temperatures,0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mahakama yasitisha kwa muda kufunguliwa kwa hospitali ya ebola ya Marekani nchini Kenya,The court temporarily halts the opening of an American Ebola hospital in Kenya,0.0,neutral,"[('American Ebola', 'ORG'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Iran na Marekani zafikia makubaliano ya kuongeza muda wa usitishaji mapigano","Immediately, Iran and the United States reached an agreement to extend the ceasefire",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,AFCON U-17: Tanzania yatinga fainali na kufuzu kombe la dunia kwa mara ya kwanza,AFCON U-17: Tanzania reaches the final and qualify for the world cup for the first time,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kauli tata za wanasiasa wanaohama vyama Tanzania,Controversial statements of politicians who change parties in Tanzania,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, ni wachezaji gani matajiri zaidi wa soka duniani?",Who are the richest soccer players in the world?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mfamasia wa Uingereza alivyovumbua jinsi moto unavyowashwa,A British pharmacist discovered how fire is lit,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Einstein hakutaka kuwa Rais wa Israel?,Why did Einstein not want to be the President of Israel?,0.0,neutral,"[('Einstein', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Barcelona inamfukuzia Hincapie Arsenal,European Football Rumors Friday: Barcelona chase Arsenal's Hincapie,0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Hincapie', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Marekani na Iran zinakaribia kuweka amani au kurudi kwenye vita?",Are the US and Iran about to make peace or return to war?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"""Tulikuwa tunatafuta watoto wetu gizani"" - Simanzi baada ya wanafunzi 16 kufa kwenye moto Kenya","""We were looking for our children in the dark"" - Simanzi after 16 students died in a fire in Kenya",0.0,neutral,"[('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Australian court sets August date for ‘mushroom murderer’ appeal hearing,Australian court sets August date for ‘mushroom murderer’ appeal hearing,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP'), ('August', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Dangerous colonial occupation’: Israel’s digital West Bank land register,‘Dangerous colonial occupation’: Israel’s digital West Bank land register,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US-Iran 60-day proposal: What we know,US-Iran 60-day proposal: What we know,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('60-day', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Kenyan court suspends US Ebola quarantine facility plan,Kenyan court suspends US Ebola quarantine facility plan,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('US Ebola', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,A visual guide to Ethiopia’s ethnic groups and conflict areas,A visual guide to Ethiopia’s ethnic groups and conflict areas,-1.0,negative,"[('Ethiopia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Gaza parents brave dental dilemma: Costly treatment or food on the table?,Gaza parents brave dental dilemma: Costly treatment or food on the table?,0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,NATO states slam Russia after drone crashes in Romania,NATO states slam Russia after drone crashes in Romania,0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Romania', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup dark horses: Unheralded Netherlands should not be written off,World Cup dark horses: Unheralded Netherlands should not be written off,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Unheralded Netherlands', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel football dispute to ‘heat up’ after protest in Ireland-Qatar match,Israel football dispute to ‘heat up’ after protest in Ireland-Qatar match,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,How Indian PM Modi’s efforts to isolate Pakistan ‘backfired’,How Indian PM Modi’s efforts to isolate Pakistan ‘backfired’,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"How caste, history and science shape traditional Bengali sweets","How caste, history and science shape traditional Bengali sweets",0.0,neutral,"[('Bengali', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Everest Day 2026: Living goddesses, TikTok and a new Prime Minister; explore Nepal beyond the mountains","Everest Day 2026: Living goddesses, TikTok and a new Prime Minister; explore Nepal beyond the mountains",0.0,neutral,"[('Everest Day 2026', 'DATE'), ('TikTok', 'ORG'), ('Nepal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Art in conflict zones: Nicky Chandam’s visual documentation of Manipur and the politics of performance,Art in conflict zones: Nicky Chandam’s visual documentation of Manipur and the politics of performance,-1.0,negative,"[('Nicky Chandam’s', 'PERSON'), ('Manipur', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Beyond the Baradari: Mohammad Ali Baig traces the legend of Taramati in his period-drama ‘Chand Tara’,Beyond the Baradari: Mohammad Ali Baig traces the legend of Taramati in his period-drama ‘Chand Tara’,0.0,neutral,"[('Baradari', 'PERSON'), ('Mohammad Ali Baig', 'PERSON'), ('Taramati', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The ice apple is more than just a seasonal delicacy,The ice apple is more than just a seasonal delicacy,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"NEET paper leaks traumatic for students and families, institutions must learn, says SC","NEET paper leaks traumatic for students and families, institutions must learn, says SC",0.0,neutral,"[('NEET', 'ORG'), ('SC', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Contradictions within India’s cow protection regime,Contradictions within India’s cow protection regime,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Twisha Sharma death case: Bhopal Court sends Samarth Singh, Giribala Singh to CBI custody for five days","Twisha Sharma death case: Bhopal Court sends Samarth Singh, Giribala Singh to CBI custody for five days",-1.0,negative,"[('Twisha Sharma', 'PERSON'), ('Bhopal Court', 'ORG'), ('Samarth Singh', 'PERSON'), ('Giribala Singh', 'PERSON'), ('CBI', 'ORG'), ('five days', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"AAP celebrates as it wins over 690 wards, counting of votes for civic polls underway","AAP celebrates as it wins over 690 wards, counting of votes for civic polls underway",0.0,neutral,"[('690', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Shivakumar’s elevation as Karnataka CM poses existential challenge for JD(S),Shivakumar’s elevation as Karnataka CM poses existential challenge for JD(S),0.0,neutral,"[('Shivakumar', 'ORG'), ('Karnataka CM', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Eight students arrested in Kenya after suspected deadly school arson attack,Eight students arrested in Kenya after suspected deadly school arson attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Exploding rocket casts doubts over Nasa's Moon plans,Exploding rocket casts doubts over Nasa's Moon plans,0.0,neutral,"[('Nasa', 'ORG'), ('Moon', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US and Iran 'very close' to deal but 'not there yet', Vance says","US and Iran 'very close' to deal but 'not there yet', Vance says",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Vance', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Netanyahu says he has directed IDF to increase control of Gaza to 70%,Netanyahu says he has directed IDF to increase control of Gaza to 70%,0.0,neutral,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('70%', 'PERCENT')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Survival before safety for Delhi's poor as temperatures hit 45C,Survival before safety for Delhi's poor as temperatures hit 45C,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('45C', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Italy restores lucky testicles on bull mosaic worn down by tourists,Italy restores lucky testicles on bull mosaic worn down by tourists,0.0,neutral,"[('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Mother-in-law of Indian bride whose death set off media frenzy arrested,Mother-in-law of Indian bride whose death set off media frenzy arrested,-1.0,negative,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Gaza City hospitals say several killed in strike, as Israel targets Hamas leaders","Gaza City hospitals say several killed in strike, as Israel targets Hamas leaders",-1.0,negative,"[('Gaza City', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Man jailed for 15 years over plot to attack Taylor Swift concert in Vienna,Man jailed for 15 years over plot to attack Taylor Swift concert in Vienna,-1.0,negative,"[('15 years', 'DATE'), ('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Vienna', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Villas, cars and cash: Italy seizes dead Mafia mobster's millions","Villas, cars and cash: Italy seizes dead Mafia mobster's millions",0.0,neutral,"[('Villas', 'PERSON'), ('Italy', 'GPE'), ('Mafia', 'ORG'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: Uncertainty Hangs Over Talks as U.S. Says It Is Close to Agreement,Iran War Live Updates: Uncertainty Hangs Over Talks as U.S. Says It Is Close to Agreement,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates: Uncertainty', 'EVENT'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Russian Drone Hits Romanian Apartment Building, Officials Say","Russian Drone Hits Romanian Apartment Building, Officials Say",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian Drone Hits Romanian Apartment Building', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,France’s Far Right Has 2 Leaders. They Don’t Always Have One Voice.,France’s Far Right Has 2 Leaders. They Don’t Always Have One Voice.,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('One', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"No, Not That Georgia. A.I. Compounds a Nation’s Identity Woes.","No, Not That Georgia. A.I. Compounds a Nation’s Identity Woes.",0.0,neutral,"[('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('A.I. Compounds a Nation’s Identity Woes', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Trump’s Boat Strikes Have Failed to Curb Cocaine Flow to U.S., Experts Say","Trump’s Boat Strikes Have Failed to Curb Cocaine Flow to U.S., Experts Say",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump’s Boat Strikes Have Failed', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Europe Is Edging Closer to a Trade War With China. Here’s Why.,Europe Is Edging Closer to a Trade War With China. Here’s Why.,-1.0,negative,"[('Europe Is Edging Closer', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Argentina, U.S. Tech Billionaire Peter Thiel Finds An Escape","In Argentina, U.S. Tech Billionaire Peter Thiel Finds An Escape",0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Peter Thiel Finds', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Guatemala Agrees to Joint Drug Gang Strikes With U.S., Expanding Trump’s Campaign","Guatemala Agrees to Joint Drug Gang Strikes With U.S., Expanding Trump’s Campaign",0.0,neutral,"[('Guatemala Agrees', 'PERSON'), ('Joint Drug Gang Strikes', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Expanding Trump’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Ukraine’s Street Style Is Shaped by the War,How Ukraine’s Street Style Is Shaped by the War,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Mideast Is Baffled by Trump’s Call to Expand Abraham Accords,The Mideast Is Baffled by Trump’s Call to Expand Abraham Accords,0.0,neutral,"[('Mideast', 'LOC'), ('Trump’s Call', 'PERSON')]"
