Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo el nuevo régimen de Irán es totalmente diferente del anterior,How Iran's new regime is totally different from the previous one,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué sentí al volver a La Guaira y ver que el lugar en el que nací está ahora devastado y con cadáveres apilados,What did it feel like to return to La Guaira and see that the place where I was born is now devastated and with corpses piled up?,0.0,neutral,"[('La Guaira', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Cruza una línea roja"": por qué es tan escandalosa la decisión de la FIFA de suspender la sanción al goleador de EE.UU., Folarin Balogun, tras una llamada de Trump","""Crosses a red line"": why FIFA's decision to suspend the sanction of US goalscorer Folarin Balogun after a call from Trump is so scandalous",0.0,neutral,"[('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Folarin', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Jugamos como nunca y perdimos como siempre"": el sueño mundialista de México se acaba tras la derrota con Inglaterra","""We played like never before and lost like always"": Mexico's World Cup dream ends after the defeat against England",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Una comida durante unas vacaciones me dejó con 38 parásitos en el cerebro""","""A meal during a vacation left me with 38 parasites in my brain""",0.0,neutral,"[('38', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo un país europeo consiguió derrotar un ciberataque contra sus hospitales gracias al lápiz y al papel,How a European country managed to defeat a cyber attack against its hospitals thanks to pencil and paper,-1.0,negative,"[('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Lágrimas de un lado, remo vikingo del otro: Brasil queda eliminado del Mundial 2026 tras perder 1-2 contra Noruega","Tears on one side, Viking oars on the other: Brazil is eliminated from the 2026 World Cup after losing 1-2 against Norway",0.0,neutral,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Norway', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Resuelven el misterio de las ""bolas del espacio"" que aparecieron en una playa australiana","They solve the mystery of the ""space balls"" that appeared on an Australian beach",0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Nueva Suecia, la desconocida y diminuta colonia que ayudó al nacimiento de EE.UU. hace 250 años","New Sweden, the unknown and tiny colony that helped the birth of the United States 250 years ago",0.0,neutral,"[('New Sweden', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('250 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,“Cuando me giré ya no quedaba nada”: el fulminante colapso del Ritasol Palace por los terremotos que sacudieron Venezuela,“When I turned around there was nothing left”: the sudden collapse of the Ritasol Palace due to the earthquakes that shook Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('the Ritasol Palace', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बारुईपुर में नाबालिग लड़की से रेप के बाद हत्या, ममता को 'हाउस अरेस्ट' किए जाने का दावा","Minor girl murdered after rape in Baruipur, claims Mamta has been put under 'house arrest'",0.0,neutral,"[('Baruipur', 'GPE'), ('Mamta', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,पीएम मोदी इंडोनेशिया पहुंचे, किन देशों की और करेंगे यात्रा","Live, PM Modi reached Indonesia, which countries will he visit?",0.0,neutral,"[('Indonesia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"चेहरे पर झुर्रियां, याददाश्त या आंखों की रोशनी: मोबाइल के इस्तेमाल से शरीर पर क्या असर पड़ता है?","Wrinkles on face, memory or eyesight: What effect does mobile use have on the body?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'सतलुज' के ओटीटी से हटने पर दिलजीत बोले- 'हद ही हो गई', कौन हैं जसवंत सिंह खालड़ा जिन पर बनी फ़िल्म","On 'Sutlej' being removed from OTT, Diljit said - 'This is too much', who is Jaswant Singh Khalda on whom the film was made?",0.0,neutral,"[('OTT', 'ORG'), ('Diljit', 'PERSON'), ('Jaswant Singh Khalda', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बांकीपुर उप चुनाव: प्रशांत किशोर की बीजेपी को उसके गढ़ में चुनौती देने के पीछे क्या रणनीति है,Bankipur by-election: What is Prashant Kishor's strategy behind challenging BJP in its stronghold?,0.0,neutral,"[('Bankipur', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,नेतन्याहू ने जेडी वेंस की किस बात का जवाब देते हुए भारत से दोस्ती का किया ज़िक्र,Netanyahu mentioned friendship with India while replying to JD Vance.,0.0,neutral,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('JD Vance', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अली ख़ामेनेई के जनाज़े में नहीं दिखे उनके बेटे मोजतबा, इसराइल को क्यों माना जा रहा वजह","Ali Khamenei's son Mojtaba was not seen at his funeral, why is Israel being considered the reason?",0.0,neutral,"[(""Ali Khamenei's"", 'PERSON'), ('Mojtaba', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,महिलाओं से जुड़ी बीमारियों के डायग्नोसिस में क्यों होती है देरी?,Why is there delay in diagnosis of diseases related to women?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'तीजन बाई, इंडिया' के पते पर जब पेरिस से भेजी गई एक चिट्ठी उन तक सीधे पहुंच गई","When a letter sent from Paris to the address of 'Tejan Bai, India' reached him directly",0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE'), ('Tejan Bai', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पाकिस्तान की क्रिकेट टीम में कप्तानी का कैसा 'खेल' चल रहा है?,What kind of 'game' of captaincy is going on in Pakistan cricket team?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A economista que tenta entender a insatisfação dos brasileiros sob Lula: 'Redes sociais criam desejos de consumo para além do crescimento da renda',The economist who tries to understand Brazilians' dissatisfaction under Lula: 'Social networks create consumer desires beyond income growth',1.0,positive,"[('Brazilians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Seleção brasileira virou uma marca em vez de um time?', questiona jornal britânico","'Has the Brazilian team become a brand instead of a team?', asks British newspaper",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Com ketchup e queijo': menina conta como sobreviveu por 32h à espera de resgate após terremotos na Venezuela,'With ketchup and cheese': girl tells how she survived 32 hours waiting for rescue after earthquakes in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('32 hours', 'TIME'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil eliminado: o que o maior jejum em Copas desde 1958 diz sobre nosso futebol — e o futuro da amarelinha,Brazil eliminated: what the longest World Cup drought since 1958 says about our football — and the future of hopscotch,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('1958', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Eliminado pela Noruega de Haaland, Brasil vê futuro de Ancelotti como incerto","Eliminated by Haaland's Norway, Brazil sees Ancelotti's future as uncertain",0.0,neutral,"[('Haaland', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Ancelotti', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Entre as grandes decadentes': como imprensa internacional reagiu à eliminação do Brasil na Copa 2026,'Among the great decadents': how the international press reacted to Brazil's elimination from the 2026 World Cup,1.0,positive,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quartas de final da Copa do Mundo 2026: os confrontos definidos e os horários dos próximos jogos,Quarterfinals of the 2026 World Cup: the defined clashes and the times of the next games,0.0,neutral,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Vídeo,'Dia mais incrível da minha vida': a festa da Noruega em um bar de Nova York, Duration 0,59","Video, 'Most amazing day of my life': Norway's party in a New York bar, Duration 0.59",0.0,neutral,"[('Norway', 'GPE'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('0.59', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Qual a distância entre Lula e Flávio Bolsonaro nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,What is the distance between Lula and Flávio Bolsonaro in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Análise: Brasil agora pode pensar futuro sem Neymar, diz Tim Vickery","Analysis: Brazil can now think about the future without Neymar, says Tim Vickery",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Neymar', 'GPE'), ('Tim Vickery', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Россия нанесла второй за неделю массированный удар по Киеву. Что известно,Russia launched its second massive attack on Kyiv in a week. What is known,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: более 10 человек погибли в результате новой российской атаки на Киев, беспилотники впервые сбиты над Омском","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: more than 10 people killed in new Russian attack on Kyiv, drones shot down over Omsk for the first time",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('more than 10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Omsk', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Решающий в истории альянса». Чего ждать от саммита НАТО на фоне разлада США и Европы?,"""Decisive in the history of the alliance."" What to expect from the NATO summit against the backdrop of discord between the US and Europe?",0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Британия заявила, что российский Ту-142 совершал опасные маневры около ее авианосца в Норвежском море",Britain said a Russian Tu-142 carried out dangerous maneuvers near its aircraft carrier in the Norwegian Sea.,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Norwegian Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,ЧМ-2026: драматическая победа Англии над Мексикой; Норвегия вынесла Бразилию; ФИФА вернула нападающего США после звонка Трампа,World Cup 2026: England's dramatic victory over Mexico; Norway knocked out Brazil; FIFA returns US striker after Trump's call,1.0,positive,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Австралийскому премьеру задали неприличный вопрос о Кайли Миноуг. За ответ пришлось извиняться,The Australian Prime Minister was asked an indecent question about Kylie Minogue. I had to apologize for the answer,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Kylie Minogue', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Австралии вынесло на берег загадочные шары. Власти считают, что это объекты из космоса",Mysterious balls washed ashore in Australia. Authorities believe these are objects from outer space,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Судьбоносный момент: решение суда по делу Марин Ле Пен определит ход президентской кампании во Франции,Fateful moment: the court's decision in the Marine Le Pen case will determine the course of the presidential campaign in France,0.0,neutral,"[('the Marine Le Pen', 'ORG'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Прощание с аятоллой Хаменеи в Тегеране собирает огромные толпы. Но его сын и преемник Моджтаба пока не появился,Farewell to Ayatollah Khamenei in Tehran attracts huge crowds. But his son and successor Mojtaba has not yet appeared,1.0,positive,"[('Ayatollah Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Mojtaba', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Восемь из десяти самых густонаселенных стран не участвуют в чемпионате мира. Почему?,Eight of the ten most populous countries are not participating in the World Cup. Why?,0.0,neutral,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('ten', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,中国、太平洋でミサイル発射実験　豪州とフィジーが同盟条約に署名した直後,"China tests missile in the Pacific Ocean, immediately after Australia and Fiji sign alliance treaty",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('the Pacific Ocean', 'LOC'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Fiji', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 FIFA、アメリカFWバログンの出場停止処分を猶予　トランプ氏が処分の再考求めたか,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] FIFA suspends suspension of American forward Balogun; Trump asked for reconsideration of suspension?,-1.0,negative,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イラン前最高指導者の葬儀に息子モジタバ師は不在　高官らは参列,Son Mojtaba was absent at the funeral of Iran's former supreme leader; dignitaries attended,0.0,neutral,"[('Mojtaba', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年ウィンブルドン】 大坂、世界1位のサバレンカ破る　初の準々決勝進出,"[2026 Wimbledon] Osaka defeats world No. 1 Sabalenka, advances to quarterfinals for the first time",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('Wimbledon', 'GPE'), ('Osaka', 'GPE'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イングランドがメキシコに勝ちベスト8、べリンガムが2ゴール　ブラジルはノルウェーに敗退,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] England beats Mexico in top 8, Bellingham scores 2 goals, Brazil loses to Norway",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bellingham', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,テヘランで前最高指導者の葬儀、感情と政治が交錯　BBCが現地取材, 所要時間 1,09","Video, Emotions and politics intertwine at former supreme leader's funeral in Tehran; BBC reports on site, Duration 1,09",1.0,positive,"[(""supreme leader's"", 'ORG'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('1,09', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ建国250年、花火や記念飛行でお祝い　異常気象で行事に影響も,America's 250th anniversary celebrated with fireworks and commemorative flight; event affected by abnormal weather,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('250th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ポーランド首相、ロシアの脅威を念頭に警告　「今後数カ月が極めて重要」になり得ると,Polish Prime Minister warns of Russian threat: 'coming months could be crucial',-1.0,negative,"[('Polish', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), (""'coming months"", 'DATE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英で少女2人をレイプした少年2人に控訴審で拘禁刑　第一審の量刑が軽すぎると首相も批判,Two boys who raped two girls in the UK are sentenced to imprisonment by appeal court; the prime minister also criticizes the first trial's sentence as too lenient,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イラン前最高指導者ハメネイ師の葬儀始まる,Funeral begins for former Iranian supreme leader Ayatollah Khamenei,0.0,neutral,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Ayatollah Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Polisi, jeshi watanda kuzuia maandamano 7/7 Tanzania","The police, the army will stop the 7/7 protest in Tanzania",0.0,neutral,"[('7/7', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Idadi ya vifo kutokana na Ebola yafikia 506 DR Congo","Directly, the number of deaths due to Ebola reaches 506 DR Congo",-1.0,negative,"[('506', 'CARDINAL'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Timu ya Brazil inayozeeka inahitaji mabadiliko makubwa – lakini je, Ancelotti ndiye mtu sahihi wa kuyafanya?",Brazil's aging squad needs major changes - but is Ancelotti the right man to make them?,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi taarifa za milipuko ya magonjwa zinavyoathiri afya ya akili na namna tunavyofikiri,How information about disease outbreaks affects mental health and the way we think,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mambo matano yanayoifanya Iran ya sasa kuwa tofauti kabisa na ilivyokuwa awali,Five things that make today's Iran completely different from what it was before,0.0,neutral,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatatu: Real  Madrid yamfukuzia Olise wa Bayern Munich,European Football Rumors Monday: Real Madrid sack Bayern Munich's Olise,0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Monday', 'DATE'), ('Madrid', 'GPE'), (""Bayern Munich's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini udi unaochomwa majumbani ni hatari?,Why is udi burned at home dangerous?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi vifaa vya kielektroniki vinavyoathiri miili yetu,How electronic devices affect our bodies,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini kuna hofu kwamba Kanisa Katoliki linaweza kugawanyika?,Why is there a fear that the Catholic Church could be divided?,0.0,neutral,"[('the Catholic Church', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jeshi la Tanzania latoa onyo dhidi ya wavunjifu wa amani,The Tanzanian army issues a warning against peace breakers,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Huge crowd joins funeral procession for Iran’s Supreme Leader Khamenei,Huge crowd joins funeral procession for Iran’s Supreme Leader Khamenei,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Supreme', 'ORG'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Impeachment trial of Philippine Vice President Sara Duterte begins,Impeachment trial of Philippine Vice President Sara Duterte begins,0.0,neutral,"[('Philippine', 'NORP'), ('Sara Duterte', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,UK’s Farage’s gold deal tests his populist brand as Restore Britain rises,UK’s Farage’s gold deal tests his populist brand as Restore Britain rises,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Restore Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Philippine Vice President Duterte’s impeachment trial begins: What we know,Philippine Vice President Duterte’s impeachment trial begins: What we know,0.0,neutral,"[('Philippine', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Haaland matches Messi, Mbappe in race for World Cup’s Golden Boot award","Haaland matches Messi, Mbappe in race for World Cup’s Golden Boot award",-1.0,negative,"[('Haaland', 'GPE'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Mbappe', 'ORG'), ('World Cup’s', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup day 26: Who will advance to the FIFA World Cup round of 16?,World Cup day 26: Who will advance to the FIFA World Cup round of 16?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Mexican fans proud despite World Cup exit,Mexican fans proud despite World Cup exit,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,At least 20 people killed in Sri Lanka prison clashes,At least 20 people killed in Sri Lanka prison clashes,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sri Lanka', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Moment Israeli soldier hurls stun grenade into Palestinians’ car,Moment Israeli soldier hurls stun grenade into Palestinians’ car,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('hurls stun grenade', 'PERSON'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Super Typhoon Bavi makes landfall on US Pacific islands,Super Typhoon Bavi makes landfall on US Pacific islands,0.0,neutral,"[('Super Typhoon Bavi', 'ORG'), ('US Pacific', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Supreme Court refuses to ‘short-circuit’ procedure, declines PIL on Prophet Muhammad remarks","Supreme Court refuses to ‘short-circuit’ procedure, declines PIL on Prophet Muhammad remarks",0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Prophet Muhammad', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Heavy rain to continue till July 8: Maharashtra on high alert, says CM Fadnavis | LIVE","Heavy rain to continue till July 8: Maharashtra on high alert, says CM Fadnavis | LIVE",0.0,neutral,"[('July 8', 'DATE'), ('CM Fadnavis', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,West Asia War LIVE: Mourners throng funeral procession in Tehran for Iran's Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei,West Asia War LIVE: Mourners throng funeral procession in Tehran for Iran's Supreme Leader Ayatollah Ali Khamenei,-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia War', 'LOC'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Supreme', 'ORG'), ('Ayatollah Ali Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Karur stampede case: SC to hear DMK’s plea to bar TVK leaders from ‘influencing’ material witnesses,Karur stampede case: SC to hear DMK’s plea to bar TVK leaders from ‘influencing’ material witnesses,0.0,neutral,"[('SC', 'ORG'), ('DMK', 'ORG'), ('TVK', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Questioning the hype around Uttar Pradesh’s ‘revenue surplus’ in 10 charts,Questioning the hype around Uttar Pradesh’s ‘revenue surplus’ in 10 charts,0.0,neutral,"[('Uttar Pradesh’s', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Delhi HC gives two weeks to Wrestling Federation to decide on show-cause notice to Vinesh Phogat,Delhi HC gives two weeks to Wrestling Federation to decide on show-cause notice to Vinesh Phogat,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi HC', 'PERSON'), ('two weeks', 'DATE'), ('Wrestling Federation', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,How are terrorists designated under the UAPA? | Explained,How are terrorists designated under the UAPA? | Explained,-1.0,negative,"[('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Diljit Dosanjh unsurprised by ‘Satluj’ removal from Zee5, says was ‘bound to happen’","Diljit Dosanjh unsurprised by ‘Satluj’ removal from Zee5, says was ‘bound to happen’",0.0,neutral,"[('Diljit Dosanjh', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"The tarnished game: Trump, FIFA, and a suspended red card","The tarnished game: Trump, FIFA, and a suspended red card",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('FIFA', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Two together: on the Japanese Prime Minister’s visit to India,​Two together: on the Japanese Prime Minister’s visit to India,0.0,neutral,"[('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ukraine warns of interceptor missile shortage as 18 killed in Kyiv region,Ukraine warns of interceptor missile shortage as 18 killed in Kyiv region,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('18', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"'I ate ketchup and cheese,' says Venezuelan girl trapped under quake rubble for 32 hours","'I ate ketchup and cheese,' says Venezuelan girl trapped under quake rubble for 32 hours",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('32 hours', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Australian PM apologises for 'inappropriate' comments about Kylie Minogue,Australian PM apologises for 'inappropriate' comments about Kylie Minogue,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Kylie Minogue', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Marine Le Pen appeal verdict: Why this moment matters for France,Marine Le Pen appeal verdict: Why this moment matters for France,0.0,neutral,"[('Marine Le Pen', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"A global hub for fake luxury goods, Vietnam cracks down on its black market","A global hub for fake luxury goods, Vietnam cracks down on its black market",1.0,positive,"[('Vietnam', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Super Typhoon Bavi makes landfall on US Pacific islands with huge wind gusts,Super Typhoon Bavi makes landfall on US Pacific islands with huge wind gusts,1.0,positive,"[('Super Typhoon Bavi', 'ORG'), ('US Pacific', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Australia space agency has found 'likely source' of mystery space balls,Australia space agency has found 'likely source' of mystery space balls,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'Definitely felt a big bang': Delta plane hit by firework while landing in Chicago,'Definitely felt a big bang': Delta plane hit by firework while landing in Chicago,0.0,neutral,"[('Delta', 'LOC'), ('Chicago', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,The African fishermen who blame Chinese trawlers for their woes,The African fishermen who blame Chinese trawlers for their woes,0.0,neutral,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Bangladesh courts China even as ties with India improve,Bangladesh courts China even as ties with India improve,1.0,positive,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Deadly Russian Strikes Rock Kyiv on Eve of NATO Summit,Deadly Russian Strikes Rock Kyiv on Eve of NATO Summit,0.0,neutral,"[('Deadly Russian Strikes Rock Kyiv', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Ukraine Rewrote Air Defense Tactics. Against Russia, It’s Still Not Enough.","Ukraine Rewrote Air Defense Tactics. Against Russia, It’s Still Not Enough.",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine Rewrote Air Defense Tactics', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Erdogan-Trump Friendship Can Help NATO, Turkey’s Foreign Minister Says","Erdogan-Trump Friendship Can Help NATO, Turkey’s Foreign Minister Says",0.0,neutral,"[('Erdogan-Trump Friendship Can Help NATO', 'ORG'), ('Turkey', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"From Haiti to Venezuela, Earthquakes Reveal Shift in U.S. Relief Efforts","From Haiti to Venezuela, Earthquakes Reveal Shift in U.S. Relief Efforts",0.0,neutral,"[('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,China Test Fires Long-Range Ballistic Missile in the Pacific,China Test Fires Long-Range Ballistic Missile in the Pacific,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Trump Cools on NATO, Turkey Hosts Summit Meeting","As Trump Cools on NATO, Turkey Hosts Summit Meeting",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump Cools', 'PERSON'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Turkey Hosts Summit Meeting', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,NATO Leaders Are Meeting This Week. Here’s What to Know.,NATO Leaders Are Meeting This Week. Here’s What to Know.,0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('This Week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The World Cup Gave Mexicans a Fantasy They Won’t Soon Forget,The World Cup Gave Mexicans a Fantasy They Won’t Soon Forget,0.0,neutral,"[('The World Cup Gave Mexicans a Fantasy They Won’t', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Andy Burnham, the UK’s Likely Next Prime Minister, Made His Name in Manchester. Here’s How.","Andy Burnham, the UK’s Likely Next Prime Minister, Made His Name in Manchester. Here’s How.",0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Manchester', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Manchester’s Bee Buses and Trams Helped Fuel Andy Burnham’s Rise,How Manchester’s Bee Buses and Trams Helped Fuel Andy Burnham’s Rise,0.0,neutral,"[('Manchester’s Bee Buses', 'PERSON'), ('Trams Helped Fuel Andy Burnham’s Rise', 'PERSON')]"
