Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Venezuela: por qué hay tantas réplicas después de los terremotos y cuánto tiempo pueden durar,Venezuela: why there are so many aftershocks after earthquakes and how long they can last,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Perros, drones y detectores de sonido: cómo encuentran sobrevivientes los rescatistas en Venezuela","Dogs, drones and sound detectors: how rescuers find survivors in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""¡Que nadie se mueva!"": los tensos 10 minutos de silencio en los que todo se detiene para tratar de oír voces bajo los escombros","""Nobody move!"": the tense 10 minutes of silence in which everything stops to try to hear voices under the rubble",0.0,neutral,"[('10 minutes', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La madre rescatada de entre los escombros en Venezuela junto a su bebé le cuenta a la BBC cómo el recién nacido la ayudó a sobrevivir,The mother rescued from the rubble in Venezuela with her baby tells the BBC how the newborn helped her survive,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cuánto tiempo se puede sobrevivir bajo los escombros tras un terremoto y qué factores dan esperanza a los rescatistas,How long can you survive under the rubble after an earthquake and what factors give rescuers hope,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Así te lo contamos: Más de 1.700 muertos en Venezuela mientras las familias excavan entre los escombros para encontrar sobrevivientes 5 días después de los terremotos,"This is how we tell you: More than 1,700 dead in Venezuela as families dig through the rubble to find survivors 5 days after the earthquakes",0.0,neutral,"[('More than 1,700', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('5 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué millones de teléfonos Android recibieron una alerta sobre el doble terremoto en Venezuela antes de que se sintiera,Why millions of Android phones received an alert about the double earthquake in Venezuela before it was felt,0.0,neutral,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Android', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Aarón, el joven de 21 años rescatado tras pasar 106 horas bajo los escombros por el doble terremoto de Venezuela","Aarón, the 21-year-old rescued after spending 106 hours under the rubble of the double earthquake in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('21-year-old', 'DATE'), ('106 hours', 'TIME'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Las autoridades confirman que Daveigh Chase, actriz de ""The Ring"" y una de las voces de ""Lilo & Stitch"", murió de SIDA","Authorities confirm that Daveigh Chase, actress of ""The Ring"" and one of the voices of ""Lilo & Stitch"", died of AIDS",0.0,neutral,"[('Daveigh Chase', 'PERSON'), ('The Ring', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lilo & Stitch', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¡Proeza de Paraguay!: elimina a Alemania del Mundial 2026 en la tanda de penales y se clasifica para octavos de final,Paraguay's feat!: eliminates Germany from the 2026 World Cup in the penalty shootout and qualifies for the round of 16,0.0,neutral,"[('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,आयुर्वेद और होम्योपैथी पर सवाल उठाने वाले  'लिवर डॉक्टर' कौन हैं?,Who is the 'Liver Doctor' raising questions on Ayurveda and Homeopathy?,0.0,neutral,"[('Ayurveda', 'ORG'), ('Homeopathy', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,सीजेपी फ़ाउंडर अभिजीत दीपके का दावा- पुलिस लोगों को धरना स्थल पर आने से रोक रही है","Live, CJP Founder Abhijeet Deepke's claim - Police is stopping people from coming to the protest site.",0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Abhijeet Deepke', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'एटीएम में एसी लगाए पर चुरा लिया ग़रीबों का पानी' मोहम्मद हनीफ़ का ब्लॉग,'Installed AC in ATM but stole water from the poor' Mohammad Hanif's blog,0.0,neutral,"[('ATM', 'ORG'), (""Mohammad Hanif's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,मलबे में दबने के कितने दिनों बाद तक ज़िंदा रह सकते हैं लोग?,How long can people survive after being buried under debris?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,व्हाट्सऐप का नया फ़ीचर: बिना फ़ोन नंबर शेयर किए यूज़र एक-दूसरे से जुड़ सकते हैं,New feature of WhatsApp: Users can connect with each other without sharing phone numbers,0.0,neutral,"[('WhatsApp', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,महाराष्ट्र: तीन साल की बच्ची के रेप और हत्या के अभियुक्त को कोर्ट ने 50 दिन में सुनवाई पूरी करके सुनाई फांसी की सज़ा,Maharashtra: The court completed the hearing in 50 days and awarded death sentence to the accused of rape and murder of a three-year-old girl.,-1.0,negative,"[('50 days', 'DATE'), ('three-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,मुहर्रम जुलूस में ज़हरीले कैप्सूल बांटने की साज़िश को दो महिलाओं ने कैसे रोका?,How did two women stop a conspiracy to distribute poisonous capsules in the Muharram procession?,0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Muharram', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"टेलीग्राफ़ के पूर्व संपादक बोले, 'ये बेहद अपमानजनक', वोटर लिस्ट से नाम हटने के बाद उनका पासपोर्ट वेरिफ़िकेशन भी लटका","Former editor of Telegraph said, 'This is extremely insulting', after his name was removed from the voter list, his passport verification also stopped.",0.0,neutral,"[('Telegraph', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वर्ल्ड कप फ़ुटबॉल 2026: चार बार की चैंपियन जर्मनी बाहर, पराग्वे ने हराकर आख़िरी 16 में बनाई जगह","World Cup Football 2026: Four-time champion Germany out, defeated Paraguay and made place in last 16",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Football', 'EVENT'), ('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('last 16', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"आयुष मलिक का कथित वीडियो आया सामने, हिंदू धर्म में वापसी की कह रहे बात","Alleged video of Ayush Malik surfaced, talking about returning to Hinduism",0.0,neutral,"[('Ayush Malik', 'PERSON'), ('Hinduism', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Governo Trump vai 'tensionar' eleições no Brasil por medo da China, diz especialista que mapeou direita na América Latina","Trump government will 'tension' elections in Brazil due to fear of China, says expert who mapped the right in Latin America",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Latin America', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Celulares Android podem ajudar a prever terremoto?,Can Android phones help predict earthquakes?,0.0,neutral,"[('Android', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Causa da morte de atriz de 'O Chamado' e 'Lilo & Stitch' foi Aids, aponta laudo","'The Ring' and 'Lilo & Stitch' actress' cause of death was AIDS, report shows",-1.0,negative,"[(""Lilo & Stitch'"", 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Pesadelo da Alemanha' e Holanda dominada por sensação africana: a noite da queda de dois grandes na Copa,'Germany's nightmare' and the Netherlands dominated by an African sensation: the night of the fall of two greats in the World Cup,1.0,positive,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Netherlands', 'GPE'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('the night', 'TIME'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil mostra poder de reação com apostas de Ancelotti e ganha fôlego para seguir sonhando com hexa,Brazil shows power to react with Ancelotti's bets and gains momentum to continue dreaming of hexa,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Ancelotti', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Ancelotti é antídoto do Brasil contra o caos': imprensa internacional enaltece técnico, mas vê Seleção longe de convencer","'Ancelotti is Brazil's antidote against chaos': international press praises coach, but sees Seleção far from convincing",0.0,neutral,"[('Ancelotti', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Seleção', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil 2 x 1 Japão: veja como foi e as análises do jogo pela BBC,Brazil 2 x 1 Japan: see how it went and the analysis of the game by the BBC,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quando é o próximo jogo do Brasil na Copa e quem será o adversário?,When is Brazil's next World Cup game and who will be the opponent?,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Pesquisas para presidente: quem está à frente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Polls for president: who is ahead? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Qual o caminho até o hexa? Quem o Brasil precisa vencer para chegar à final,What is the way to the hexa? Who Brazil needs to beat to reach the final,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Буддист и Мефисто: куда война и репрессии завели режиссеров Кирилла Серебренникова и Константина Богомолова,Buddhist and Mephisto: where war and repression took directors Kirill Serebrennikov and Konstantin Bogomolov,-1.0,negative,"[('Buddhist', 'NORP'), ('Mephisto', 'PERSON'), ('Kirill Serebrennikov', 'PERSON'), ('Konstantin Bogomolov', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: В Подмосковье при атаке дронов погиб ребенок, Польша отказалась передавать Украине истребители МиГ-29","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: A child died in a drone attack in the Moscow region, Poland refused to transfer MiG-29 fighters to Ukraine",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Мы ждем ответов». Венесуэльцы своими руками раскапывают завалы и критикуют власти,"""We are waiting for answers."" Venezuelans dig up rubble with their own hands and criticize the authorities",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Великобритании беженцев обяжут возвращать около £10 000 за господдержку,"In the UK, refugees will be required to repay about £10,000 for government support",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('about £10,000', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"27 перелетов, 24 матча: какой углеродный след оставил президент ФИФА своими поездками на ЧМ-2026","27 flights, 24 matches: what carbon footprint did the FIFA president leave with his trips to the 2026 World Cup?",0.0,neutral,"[('27', 'CARDINAL'), ('24', 'CARDINAL'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Шесть человек погибли в результате стрельбы в городе Штаде на севере Германии. Нападавший задержан,Six people were killed in a shooting in the northern German city of Stade. The attacker was detained,-1.0,negative,"[('Six', 'CARDINAL'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Stade', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"На газовозе «Газпрома» установили пулеметы, узнали журналисты. Зачем?","Machine guns were installed on the Gazprom gas carrier, journalists learned. For what?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Исторический пик» отношений и сигнал Путину. Зачем Лукашенко встречался с Си Цзиньпином в Пекине,“Historic peak” of relations and a signal to Putin. Why did Lukashenko meet with Xi Jinping in Beijing?,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Lukashenko', 'PERSON'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"США и Иран договорились прекратить удары и вернуться к переговорам во вторник, заявляют в Вашингтоне. Тегеран встречу в Дохе не подтверждает","The United States and Iran have agreed to stop strikes and return to negotiations on Tuesday, Washington says. Tehran does not confirm meeting in Doha",0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Doha', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Почему арестовали Лунина, грозившего Путину мятежом? | Видеоподкаст «Что это было?», Продолжительность 30,01","Video, Why was Lunin arrested, who threatened Putin with rebellion? | Video podcast “What was that?”, Duration 30.01",0.0,neutral,"[('Lunin', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('30.01', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本、ブラジルに逆転負けしベスト32で敗退　後半終了間際に決勝点奪われる,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Japan loses to Brazil and is eliminated in the best 32, losing the winning goal just before the end of the second half",1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('32', 'DATE'), ('the end of the second half', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,バーナム氏が政策構想を発表、英首相官邸の支部設置で地方分権を加速と,"Burnham announces policy concept, accelerating decentralization by establishing a branch of the British Prime Minister's Office",0.0,neutral,"[('Burnham', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴェネズエラ地震、政府の支援届かず救助難航　強い余震も,"Venezuela earthquake: rescue efforts difficult due to lack of government aid, strong aftershocks",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米最高裁、トランプ氏の性的暴行認めた下級審判断を支持　8億円の賠償支払い確定,"U.S. Supreme Court upholds lower court ruling admitting sexual assault by Trump, confirming payment of 800 million yen in compensation",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S. Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('800 million yen', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,プーチン氏、ロシア国内の燃料不足を初めて公に認める　ウクライナによる空爆で,Putin publicly admits fuel shortage in Russia for the first time due to Ukrainian airstrikes,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 トランプ氏にとっての一つの大勝利と三つの敗北、米最高裁の劇的な1日,"[Commentary] One big victory and three defeats for Trump, a dramatic day at the US Supreme Court",1.0,positive,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the US Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ドイツの母子向け施設で銃撃、6人死亡　容疑者は娘の親権争いの最中,Six people killed in shooting at mother-child facility in Germany; suspect in custody battle for daughter,-1.0,negative,"[('Six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本とブラジル、どう戦ったのか　BBC記者分析,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] How Japan and Brazil fared: BBC reporter analysis,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】スターマー英首相の失脚を解剖する……BBC政治編集長,[Commentary] Anatomizing the downfall of British Prime Minister Starmer...BBC Political Editor,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,パキスタンがアフガニスタンを攻撃、自爆攻撃への報復と　民間人少なくとも28人死亡と国連機関,"Pakistan attacks Afghanistan in retaliation for suicide bombing, killing at least 28 civilians, UN agency says",-1.0,negative,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('at least 28', 'CARDINAL'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Trump asema mazungumzo ya Doha ni muhimu huku Iran ikisema hakuna mkutano uliopangwa","Directly, Trump says the Doha talks are important while Iran says no meeting is planned",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Doha', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vyuo 10 bora zaidi barani Afrika  2026,Top 10 Universities in Africa 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nini huzuia wanawake wengi kutofika kileleni?,What prevents many women from reaching the top?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Jinsi Brazil mpya inavyoimarika na umuhimu wa Cunha,World Cup 2026: How the new Brazil is shaping up and the importance of Cunha,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Cunha', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nani analinda fedha zako serikalini?,Who protects your money in the government?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za Soka: Kane kusalia Bayern, Man City kutema watano","Football Rumors: Kane to stay at Bayern, Man City to spit five",0.0,neutral,"[('Kane', 'PERSON'), ('Bayern', 'ORG'), ('Man City', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Morocco yatinga 16 bora kwa penati,Morocco will advance to the top 16 on penalties,0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini China inaongeza silaha za nyuklia?,Why is China increasing nuclear weapons?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Marufuku ya mikusanyiko iliyotolewa na serikali DRC ni uamuzi “wa kisiasa,”-Upinzani","The ban on gatherings issued by the DRC government is a ""political"" decision - the Opposition",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_30,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Soko la mitumba linavyoathiri sekta ya mavazi Afrika Mashariki,The second-hand market affects the clothing industry in East Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('East Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Paraguay shock Germany in shootout win for one of all-time World Cup upsets,Paraguay shock Germany in shootout win for one of all-time World Cup upsets,1.0,positive,"[('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran denies Trump’s claim of Doha meeting, slams France’s Hormuz plans","Iran denies Trump’s claim of Doha meeting, slams France’s Hormuz plans",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Doha', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Keiko Fujimori leads in Peruvian presidential race as vote count concludes,Keiko Fujimori leads in Peruvian presidential race as vote count concludes,0.0,neutral,"[('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Peruvian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Australian football legend Sam Kerr signs with Gotham FC after Chelsea exit,Australian football legend Sam Kerr signs with Gotham FC after Chelsea exit,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP'), ('Sam Kerr', 'PERSON'), ('Gotham FC', 'PERSON'), ('Chelsea', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Netherlands vs Morocco LIVE: FIFA World Cup 2026,Netherlands vs Morocco LIVE: FIFA World Cup 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('Netherlands', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Marco Rubio meets Libyan commander as US pushes to resolve Libya crisis,Marco Rubio meets Libyan commander as US pushes to resolve Libya crisis,-1.0,negative,"[('Marco Rubio', 'PERSON'), ('Libyan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Libya', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,What’s behind the anti-corruption crackdown in Iraq?,What’s behind the anti-corruption crackdown in Iraq?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iraq', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Brazil beat Japan with injury-time winner to reach World Cup last 16,Brazil beat Japan with injury-time winner to reach World Cup last 16,1.0,positive,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Sixty-six years on: The promise of DRC independence remains unfulfilled,Sixty-six years on: The promise of DRC independence remains unfulfilled,0.0,neutral,"[('Sixty-six years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_30,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Ex-NBA players Malik Beasley, Ed Davis indicted in betting investigation","Ex-NBA players Malik Beasley, Ed Davis indicted in betting investigation",0.0,neutral,"[('Ex-NBA', 'ORG'), ('Malik Beasley', 'PERSON'), ('Ed Davis', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"TET paper-leak scam: What it’s all about, how Maharashtra Police busted it? | Explained","TET paper-leak scam: What it’s all about, how Maharashtra Police busted it? | Explained",0.0,neutral,"[('TET', 'ORG'), ('Maharashtra Police', 'ORG'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,General Dhiraj Seth takes charge as new Army Chief,General Dhiraj Seth takes charge as new Army Chief,0.0,neutral,"[('Dhiraj Seth', 'PERSON'), ('Army', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why Punjab’s anti-sacrilege law has triggered a row with Akal Takht | Explained,Why Punjab’s anti-sacrilege law has triggered a row with Akal Takht | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Akal Takht', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,AIADMK leader S.P. Velumani likely to resign as MLA: Party sources,AIADMK leader S.P. Velumani likely to resign as MLA: Party sources,0.0,neutral,"[('AIADMK', 'ORG'), ('S.P. Velumani', 'PERSON'), ('MLA', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"How similar are Uttarakhand, Gujarat and Assam’s Uniform Civil Codes?","How similar are Uttarakhand, Gujarat and Assam’s Uniform Civil Codes?",0.0,neutral,"[('Uttarakhand', 'GPE'), ('Gujarat', 'GPE'), ('Assam’s Uniform Civil Codes', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,U.S.-India relationship at its lowest in 30 years: Indian-American Democrat leader,U.S.-India relationship at its lowest in 30 years: Indian-American Democrat leader,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.-India', 'ORG'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('Indian-American', 'NORP'), ('Democrat', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Sudha Kongara moves Madras HC to prevent release of ‘Idhayam Murali’ over ‘Parasakthi’ movie payment dispute,Sudha Kongara moves Madras HC to prevent release of ‘Idhayam Murali’ over ‘Parasakthi’ movie payment dispute,0.0,neutral,"[('Sudha Kongara', 'PERSON'), ('Idhayam Murali', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Supreme Court refuses to entertain plea seeking CBI probe into ‘extra-judicial’ killing of Bharat Tiwari,Supreme Court refuses to entertain plea seeking CBI probe into ‘extra-judicial’ killing of Bharat Tiwari,-1.0,negative,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('CBI', 'ORG'), ('Bharat', 'NORP'), ('Tiwari', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"What is WhatsApp’s new username feature, and how to reserve one for yourself?","What is WhatsApp’s new username feature, and how to reserve one for yourself?",0.0,neutral,"[('WhatsApp', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Delayed honour: On Operation Sindoor, gains and losses","Delayed honour: On Operation Sindoor, gains and losses",0.0,neutral,"[('Operation Sindoor', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Angry Venezuelans accuse government of negligence over earthquake response,Angry Venezuelans accuse government of negligence over earthquake response,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Aftershock frays nerves as many Venezuelans left to fend for themselves,Aftershock frays nerves as many Venezuelans left to fend for themselves,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Founder of Asian super-app Gojek sentenced to years in jail for corruption,Founder of Asian super-app Gojek sentenced to years in jail for corruption,0.0,neutral,"[('Asian', 'NORP'), ('Gojek', 'PERSON'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Heavy security in South Africa as anti-migrant protesters take to the streets,Heavy security in South Africa as anti-migrant protesters take to the streets,0.0,neutral,"[('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Manhunt under way after bomb injures Ukrainian oligarch and family in Monaco,Manhunt under way after bomb injures Ukrainian oligarch and family in Monaco,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Monaco', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,One big win and three defeats for Trump in dramatic day at Supreme Court,One big win and three defeats for Trump in dramatic day at Supreme Court,1.0,positive,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Chinese tycoon sentenced to 30 years in US jail,Chinese tycoon sentenced to 30 years in US jail,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Osaka pays 'love and respect to Japan' in Wimbledon kimono,Osaka pays 'love and respect to Japan' in Wimbledon kimono,0.0,neutral,"[('Osaka', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Wimbledon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US says it has agreed to 'stand down' after exchange of strikes with Iran,US says it has agreed to 'stand down' after exchange of strikes with Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Pakistani strikes kill at least 28 civilians in Afghanistan, UN says","Pakistani strikes kill at least 28 civilians in Afghanistan, UN says",-1.0,negative,"[('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('at least 28', 'CARDINAL'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Why the True Death Toll of Venezuela’s Quakes Is So Hard to Know,Why the True Death Toll of Venezuela’s Quakes Is So Hard to Know,-1.0,negative,"[('the True Death Toll', 'LAW'), ('Venezuela’s Quakes', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mideast Live Updates: U.S. and Iran Gear Up for Meetings in Qatar,Mideast Live Updates: U.S. and Iran Gear Up for Meetings in Qatar,0.0,neutral,"[('Mideast Live', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Meetings', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"The Prom Went On in Kyiv, but Masha’s Date Danced Alone","The Prom Went On in Kyiv, but Masha’s Date Danced Alone",0.0,neutral,"[('The Prom Went On in', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Masha’s Date Danced Alone', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,China Increases Military and Economic Pressure on Japan,China Increases Military and Economic Pressure on Japan,0.0,neutral,"[('China Increases Military and Economic Pressure', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Australian Man Charged With Homicide After Thai Teen’s Body Found in Suitcase,Australian Man Charged With Homicide After Thai Teen’s Body Found in Suitcase,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Norway’s ‘Viking Row’ Is a Fan Phenomenon at the World Cup,Norway’s ‘Viking Row’ Is a Fan Phenomenon at the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Norway', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Trump Cut a Billion-Dollar Mining Deal. His Sons Stand to Profit.,Trump Cut a Billion-Dollar Mining Deal. His Sons Stand to Profit.,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump Cut a', 'ORG'), ('Profit', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Pakistan Attacks Afghanistan, Killing More Than 30","Pakistan Attacks Afghanistan, Killing More Than 30",-1.0,negative,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('More Than 30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Efforts to Rescue Venezuela Quake Victims Grow More Desperate,Efforts to Rescue Venezuela Quake Victims Grow More Desperate,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_30,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"At Funerals, Venezuela’s Wounded Families and Friends Unite in Grief","At Funerals, Venezuela’s Wounded Families and Friends Unite in Grief",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
