Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""El bebé fue mi motor para estar despierta y alerta"": la BBC habla con la madre rescatada junto a su hijo de 18 días en Venezuela","""The baby was my driving force to be awake and alert"": the BBC speaks with the mother rescued with her 18-day-old son in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('18-day-old', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El padre que espera en un hospital de La Guaira a que aparezca su hijo de 10 años desaparecido: ""Estoy seguro de que debe estar buscándome""","The father waiting in a hospital in La Guaira for his missing 10-year-old son to appear: ""I'm sure he must be looking for me""",0.0,neutral,"[('La Guaira', 'FAC'), ('10-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cuánto tiempo se puede sobrevivir bajo los escombros tras un terremoto y qué factores dan esperanza a los rescatistas,How long can you survive under the rubble after an earthquake and what factors give rescuers hope,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las emotivas imágenes de las labores de rescate en la búsqueda de sobrevivientes tras los terremotos de Venezuela,The emotional images of the rescue efforts in the search for survivors after the earthquakes in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El campo de golf en La Guaira que era un símbolo de opulencia y ahora es el refugio ante la devastación por los terremotos en Venezuela,The golf course in La Guaira that was a symbol of opulence and is now a refuge from the devastation caused by the earthquakes in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('La Guaira', 'FAC'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Hay edificios donde no se ha removido ni una sola piedra"": crece la frustración en Venezuela mientras se desvanece la esperanza de hallar más sobrevivientes","""There are buildings where not a single stone has been removed"": frustration grows in Venezuela while hope of finding more survivors fades",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Rescatan a dos niños atrapados durante días entre los escombros con la ayuda de equipos de Colombia y México,Two children trapped for days in the rubble are rescued with the help of teams from Colombia and Mexico,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('days', 'DATE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La conmovedora historia del bebé de 18 días y su madre que fueron rescatados de entre los escombros tras el terremoto doble en Venezuela,The moving story of the 18-day-old baby and his mother who were rescued from the rubble after the double earthquake in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('18-day-old', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""No hay soberanía con el plato vacío"": las reformas inspiradas en China y Vietnam con las que Cuba intenta rescatar a su economía","""There is no sovereignty with an empty plate"": the reforms inspired by China and Vietnam with which Cuba tries to rescue its economy",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""El culto a San Sebastián"": cómo un santo del siglo III brutalmente torturado se convirtió en un icono gay","""The Cult of Saint Sebastian"": How a Brutally Tortured 3rd Century Saint Became a Gay Icon",0.0,neutral,"[('The Cult of Saint Sebastian', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('3rd', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान-अमेरिका समझौते का आर्टिकल 5 क्या है और इसे क्यों बताया जा रहा है तनाव की वजह?,What is Article 5 of the Iran-US agreement and why is it being said to be the cause of tension?,0.0,neutral,"[('Article 5 of the', 'LAW'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,राम मंदिर चढ़ावा मामलाः सभी आठ अभियुक्तों को 14 दिन की न्यायिक हिरासत में भेजा गया","Live, Ram temple offering case: All eight accused sent to 14 days judicial custody",0.0,neutral,"[('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('14 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"प्रेम कहानी में सरहद बनी दीवार, माँ हिरासत में और घर पर बच्चे कर रहे हैं इंतज़ार","In a love story, the border becomes a wall, the mother is in custody and the children are waiting at home.",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"यॉर्कर किंग से परे, वकार यूनुस की अनकही दास्तान","Beyond the Yorker King, the untold story of Waqar Younis",0.0,neutral,"[('the Yorker King', 'PERSON'), ('Waqar Younis', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,मुंबई: मुहर्रम जुलूस में लोगों को चूहे मारने की दवा मिले कैप्सूल बांटने के आरोप में शख़्स गिरफ़्तार,Mumbai: Man arrested for distributing capsules containing rat poison to people during Muharram procession,0.0,neutral,"[('Mumbai', 'GPE'), ('Muharram', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"शराब पिलाकर आठ लोगों के मर्डर का आरोप, वजह अंधविश्वास या कुछ और?","Allegation of murder of eight people by drinking alcohol, reason for superstition or something else?",0.0,neutral,"[('eight', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिका और रूस के मुक़ाबले चीन के पास कितने परमाणु हथियार हैं?,How many nuclear weapons does China have compared to America and Russia?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बांग्लादेश‑पाकिस्तान की बढ़ती दोस्ती क्या भारत के लिए चिंता की बात है?,Is the growing friendship between Bangladesh and Pakistan a matter of concern for India?,1.0,positive,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भारत की आयरलैंड के हाथों हार पर एक्सपर्ट बोले- 'विदेशी पिच पर फ़ेल', सूर्यवंशी को ना खिलाने पर नाराज़गी","On India's defeat to Ireland, experts said - 'Failed on foreign pitch', angry at not playing Suryavanshi",-1.0,negative,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('Suryavanshi', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,महिला टी-20 विश्व कप: हरमनप्रीत की तूफ़ानी बैटिंग के बावजूद ऑस्ट्रेलिया से कैसे हारी भारतीय टीम,Women's T20 World Cup: How Indian team lost to Australia despite Harmanpreet's stormy batting,0.0,neutral,"[(""Women's T20 World Cup:"", 'ORG'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Harmanpreet', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump e tensão entre Brasil e EUA viram 'motor de engajamento' para Lula e Flávio Bolsonaro nas redes sociais,Trump and tension between Brazil and the USA become an 'engagement engine' for Lula and Flávio Bolsonaro on social media,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como Vini Jr. virou protagonista do Brasil na Copa e pode fazer a diferença contra o Japão,How Vini Jr. became Brazil's protagonist in the World Cup and could make the difference against Japan,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Vini Jr. chegou' para ser 'herói dos brasileiros': artilheiro do Brasil é destaque na imprensa internacional,'Vini Jr. has arrived' to be a 'hero of Brazilians': Brazil's top scorer is highlighted in the international press,0.0,neutral,"[('Vini Jr.', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilians', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Chaveamento da Copa do Mundo: quem está no mata-mata? Veja a tabela definitiva e horários dos próximos jogos,World Cup bracket: who is in the knockout stage? See the definitive table and schedules of upcoming games,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Equipes de resgate na Venezuela enfrentam 'horas críticas' após terremotos, enquanto número de mortos chega a 1.450","Rescue teams in Venezuela face 'critical hours' after earthquakes as death toll reaches 1,450",-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('1,450', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Os resgates de dois meninos de 11 anos presos após dias nos escombros dos terremotos na Venezuela,The rescues of two 11-year-old boys trapped after days in the rubble of the earthquakes in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('two 11-year-old', 'DATE'), ('days', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,De 'aluno' a rival na Copa: como Brasil ajudou Japão a dar um salto no futebol,From 'student' to World Cup rival: how Brazil helped Japan take a leap forward in football,-1.0,negative,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Como era o pequeno Vinicius Jr., segundo seu primeiro técnico: velocidade de 'moto', tímido, mas já 'bailador'","What little Vinicius Jr. was like, according to his first coach: 'motorcycle' speed, shy, but already a 'dancer'",0.0,neutral,"[('Vinicius Jr.', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como a infertilidade masculina ainda não recebe a atenção necessária,How male infertility still doesn't get the attention it needs,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_29,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que está por trás da onda de calor na Europa associada a 1.300 mortes,"What's behind Europe's heatwave linked to 1,300 deaths",-1.0,negative,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('1,300', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Штурма в кредит». Чем отличается фронт в отчетах российского Генштаба от реальности,"""Sturma on credit."" How does the front in the reports of the Russian General Staff differ from reality?",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: при ударах по Днепру и Запорожью погибли восемь человек, пострадали более 30","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: attacks on the Dnieper and Zaporozhye killed eight people, injured more than 30",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Dnieper', 'PERSON'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Обвиняемые по первому в России делу об «ЛГБТ‑экстремизме» получили сроки до семи лет,The defendants in Russia's first case of “LGBT extremism” received sentences of up to seven years,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('up to seven years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зебры против шершней: как Россия пытается защититься от украинских «умных дронов»,Zebras versus hornets: how Russia is trying to protect itself from Ukrainian “smart drones”,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Британия заменит старые эсминцы кораблями с воздушными, надводными и подводными дронами","Britain will replace old destroyers with ships equipped with air, surface and underwater drones",0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Ущерб есть». Путин об атаках Украины, дефиците бензина, договоренностях Анкориджа и заявлениях Лукашенко — главное из интервью Зарубину","“There is damage.” Putin about Ukrainian attacks, gasoline shortages, Anchorage agreements and Lukashenko’s statements - the main thing from an interview with Zarubin",-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Lukashenko', 'PERSON'), ('Zarubin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В результате ударов пакистанской армии в Афганистане погибли десятки людей,Dozens of people have been killed in Pakistani army strikes in Afghanistan.,-1.0,negative,"[('Dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"США и Иран договорились прекратить удары и вернуться к переговорам, но не в Швейцарии, а в Катаре, узнали СМИ","The United States and Iran agreed to stop strikes and return to negotiations, but not in Switzerland, but in Qatar, media learned",0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,11 человек погибли в результате крушения самолета с парашютистами на борту на востоке Франции,11 people were killed when a plane with paratroopers on board crashed in eastern France,-1.0,negative,"[('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Выжившая после землетрясения в Венесуэле: «Я слышу, как мой сын плачет под обломками»",Venezuela earthquake survivor: 'I can hear my son crying under the rubble',0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴェネズエラ地震、死者1400人超す　週末に33人救出,"Venezuela earthquake kills over 1,400; 33 rescued over weekend",-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('over 1,400', 'CARDINAL'), ('33', 'CARDINAL'), ('weekend', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米国とイランが攻撃停止で合意と米報道　互いに停戦合意違反を非難の後,"US and Iran agree to cease attacks, US reports, after accusing each other of violating ceasefire agreement",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,欧州の熱波で約1300人が超過死亡の可能性、WHOトップが警告　ドイツでは3日連続で最高気温を更新,"Approximately 1,300 people may die from heat wave in Europe, WHO chief warns; Germany hits record high for third day in a row",-1.0,negative,"[('Approximately 1,300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('third day in a row', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ヴェネズエラ地震、被災地の住民が当局に怒り　がれきを素手で, 所要時間 1,19","Video, Residents of Venezuela earthquake disaster area angry at authorities, clearing debris with bare hands, Required time 1,19",-1.0,negative,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本がブラジルに勝利と予想、BBC解説者　決勝T初戦,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Japan will beat Brazil, BBC commentator predicts the first match of the final T",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 韓国、1次リーグ敗退で大統領が監督ら非難　スコットランドとイランも姿消す,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] President criticizes coach after South Korea loses in first round; Scotland and Iran also disappear,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ハンガリー首都でプライド・パレード、オルバン氏失脚後で初　昨年は禁止措置, 所要時間 1,00","Video, Pride parade in Hungarian capital, first since Orbán's ouster, banned last year, Duration 1,00",0.0,neutral,"[('Hungarian', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Orbán', 'ORG'), ('last year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,パキスタンの攻撃で数十人死亡とタリバン政権　前日の自爆攻撃への報復と,"Dozens killed in Pakistani attack, Taliban regime says in retaliation for the previous day's suicide bombing",-1.0,negative,"[('Dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('Taliban', 'ORG'), (""the previous day's"", 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ヴェネズエラ地震、がれきの下から男性が救出された瞬間, 所要時間 0,28","Video, The moment a man was rescued from the rubble of the Venezuela earthquake, Duration 0,28",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ヴェネズエラ地震、11歳の男の子をがれきの下から救出, 所要時間 0,37","Video, Venezuela earthquake: 11-year-old boy rescued from rubble, Duration 0,37",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('11-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Iran na Marekani zakubaliana kusitisha mashambulizi na kufanya mazungumzo Doha - Axios","Directly, Iran and the United States agree to stop attacks and hold talks Doha - Axios",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Doha', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini China inaongeza silaha za nyuklia?,Why is China increasing nuclear weapons?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Soko la mitumba linavyoathiri sekta ya mavazi Afrika Mashariki,The second-hand market affects the clothing industry in East Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('East Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Afrika yaweka rekodi Kombe la Dunia, je, safari ya kutwaa taji imekaribia?","Africa sets a record in the World Cup, is the journey to win the title close?",1.0,positive,"[('Africa', 'LOC'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kama serikali inaweza kuchapisha fedha, kwa nini ikope?","If the government can print money, why should it borrow?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Zijue nchi 10 wauzaji wakubwa wa silaha duniani,Know the 10 biggest arms exporters in the world,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za Soka: Arsenal yataka watano, Liverpool yatoswa na Diomande","Football Rumors: Arsenal want five, Liverpool are interested in Diomande",0.0,neutral,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Diomande', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, unaamka saa nane au tisa usiku na kushindwa kulala tena?",Do you wake up at eight or nine at night and can't go back to sleep?,0.0,neutral,"[('eight or nine at night', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Tanzania inajenga makazi bora kwa nani?",Is Tanzania building better housing for whom?,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Iran yaitaka Marekani kuizuia Israel kuendelea na operesheni za kijeshi Lebanon,Iran wants the United States to prevent Israel from continuing military operations in Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Nigerians return home after fleeing xenophobic attacks in South Africa,Nigerians return home after fleeing xenophobic attacks in South Africa,-1.0,negative,"[('Nigerians', 'NORP'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Saudi Arabia’s early World Cup exit prompts federation chief to resign,Saudi Arabia’s early World Cup exit prompts federation chief to resign,0.0,neutral,"[('Saudi Arabia’s', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Tit-for-tat US-Iran attacks appear to be over’,‘Tit-for-tat US-Iran attacks appear to be over’,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Israeli attack in Gaza kills three, including a child","Israeli attack in Gaza kills three, including a child",-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Drone relayers off: Ukraine’s diplomatic triumph over Russia ally Belarus,Drone relayers off: Ukraine’s diplomatic triumph over Russia ally Belarus,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Venezuela rescuers race against the clock to find more survivors,Venezuela rescuers race against the clock to find more survivors,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel triggers huge explosion in southern Lebanon,Israel triggers huge explosion in southern Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"South Korea announces more than $1 trillion AI, chip investment drive","South Korea announces more than $1 trillion AI, chip investment drive",0.0,neutral,"[('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('more than $1 trillion', 'MONEY'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Australia and Vanuatu sign deal to block foreign military bases,Australia and Vanuatu sign deal to block foreign military bases,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('Vanuatu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_29,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Incompetent people’: South Korea’s World Cup 2026 exit prompts fury at home,‘Incompetent people’: South Korea’s World Cup 2026 exit prompts fury at home,0.0,neutral,"[('South Korea’s', 'GPE'), ('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,CJP protest: Dipke slams Centre's 'apathy' towards student suicides; Wangchuk's fast enters second day,CJP protest: Dipke slams Centre's 'apathy' towards student suicides; Wangchuk's fast enters second day,-1.0,negative,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Centre', 'GPE'), ('Wangchuk', 'ORG'), ('second day', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Violence erupts at Thiruvananthapuram Corporation meeting as BJP councillor attacks Congress leader Sabarinadhan,Violence erupts at Thiruvananthapuram Corporation meeting as BJP councillor attacks Congress leader Sabarinadhan,-1.0,negative,"[('Thiruvananthapuram Corporation', 'ORG'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Sabarinadhan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ayodhya lawyers refuse to represent Ram Temple embezzlement accused,Ayodhya lawyers refuse to represent Ram Temple embezzlement accused,0.0,neutral,"[('Ram Temple', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Eight newly-elected MPs take oath as Rajya Sabha members,Eight newly-elected MPs take oath as Rajya Sabha members,0.0,neutral,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rajya Sabha', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why are States opposing VB-G RAM G | Explained,Why are States opposing VB-G RAM G | Explained,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Iran says no technical meeting expected with U.S. in coming days | LIVE,Iran says no technical meeting expected with U.S. in coming days | LIVE,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('coming days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Haryana, Rajasthan sign MoU to implement 1994 Yamuna water agreement","Haryana, Rajasthan sign MoU to implement 1994 Yamuna water agreement",0.0,neutral,"[('Haryana', 'PERSON'), ('Rajasthan', 'PERSON'), ('1994', 'DATE'), ('Yamuna', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,‘Bhagyaraj’s mourning turned into a circus’: Radikaa Sarathkumar criticises media,‘Bhagyaraj’s mourning turned into a circus’: Radikaa Sarathkumar criticises media,0.0,neutral,"[('Radikaa Sarathkumar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Lydian Nadhaswaram’s unveils his Symphony No. 1 – New Beginnings,Lydian Nadhaswaram’s unveils his Symphony No. 1 – New Beginnings,-1.0,negative,"[('Lydian Nadhaswaram’s', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('New Beginnings', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_29,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Buyer beware: On the QR code-based drug traceability framework,Buyer beware: On the QR code-based drug traceability framework,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Mum rescued from Venezuela rubble with newborn baby tells BBC how he helped her survive,Mum rescued from Venezuela rubble with newborn baby tells BBC how he helped her survive,0.0,neutral,"[('Mum', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Five dead following shooting in Stade, northern Germany","Five dead following shooting in Stade, northern Germany",1.0,positive,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Stade', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US says it has agreed to 'stand down' after exchange of strikes with Iran,US says it has agreed to 'stand down' after exchange of strikes with Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Pakistani strikes kill dozens in Afghanistan,Pakistani strikes kill dozens in Afghanistan,-1.0,negative,"[('Pakistani', 'NORP'), ('dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,South Korea football coach quits as president calls for probe into World Cup loss,South Korea football coach quits as president calls for probe into World Cup loss,0.0,neutral,"[('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'You are Canadian heroes' - the forgotten hosts making World Cup history,'You are Canadian heroes' - the forgotten hosts making World Cup history,0.0,neutral,"[('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Teyana Taylor's tears and Lauryn Hill tribute steal show at BET Awards,Teyana Taylor's tears and Lauryn Hill tribute steal show at BET Awards,-1.0,negative,"[(""Teyana Taylor's"", 'PERSON'), ('Lauryn Hill', 'PERSON'), ('BET Awards', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Fitness brand founder and Olympian Les Mills dies aged 91,Fitness brand founder and Olympian Les Mills dies aged 91,0.0,neutral,"[('Olympian Les Mills', 'PERSON'), ('91', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Indian journalists condemn 'denial' of voting and passport rights of prominent editor,Indian journalists condemn 'denial' of voting and passport rights of prominent editor,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_29,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Biden blasts Trump 'vanity projects', calling him a 'loser' at fundraising event","Biden blasts Trump 'vanity projects', calling him a 'loser' at fundraising event",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Trump Cut a Billion-Dollar Mining Deal. His Sons Stand to Profit.,Trump Cut a Billion-Dollar Mining Deal. His Sons Stand to Profit.,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump Cut a', 'ORG'), ('Profit', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Mideast Live Updates: U.S. and Iran Set for New Talks in Qatar, Trump Says","Mideast Live Updates: U.S. and Iran Set for New Talks in Qatar, Trump Says",0.0,neutral,"[('Mideast Live', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran Risks Peace Talks With U.S. to Maintain Leverage Over Strait,Iran Risks Peace Talks With U.S. to Maintain Leverage Over Strait,1.0,positive,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Maintain Leverage Over Strait', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Pakistan Attacks Afghanistan, Killing More Than 30","Pakistan Attacks Afghanistan, Killing More Than 30",-1.0,negative,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE'), ('More Than 30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Whatever You Do in Russia, Don’t Talk About the War","Whatever You Do in Russia, Don’t Talk About the War",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Andy Burnham, the UK’s Likely Next Prime Minister, Promises Shift of Power Out of London","Andy Burnham, the UK’s Likely Next Prime Minister, Promises Shift of Power Out of London",0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Venezuela, a Community Comes Together to Search for Earthquake Survivors","In Venezuela, a Community Comes Together to Search for Earthquake Survivors",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Delcy Rodriguez, Venezuela’s President, Is Accused of Politicizing Earthquake Relief","Delcy Rodriguez, Venezuela’s President, Is Accused of Politicizing Earthquake Relief",0.0,neutral,"[('Delcy Rodriguez', 'PERSON'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"France Recorded 1,000 Excess Deaths During Heat Wave, Officials Say","France Recorded 1,000 Excess Deaths During Heat Wave, Officials Say",-1.0,negative,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('1,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_29,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"For These Teens in Mexico, Soccer Is Life. Now, the Cartels Want In.","For These Teens in Mexico, Soccer Is Life. Now, the Cartels Want In.",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('the Cartels Want In', 'LAW')]"
