Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El Patronato: los reformatorios donde la dictadura de Franco internaba a mujeres solteras, lesbianas o rebeldes para inculcarles valores católicos ultraconservadores","The Board of Trustees: the reformatories where Franco's dictatorship interned single, lesbian or rebellious women to instill ultra-conservative Catholic values ​​in them",-0.03571428571428571,"[('The Board of Trustees', 'ORG'), ('Franco', 'PERSON'), ('Catholic', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Después de haber sido tan exitosa, ahora dependo de comida gratis"": la ""pobreza"" repentina que hace que millones de personas en EE.UU. necesiten ayuda para alimentarse","""After being so successful, I now depend on free food"": the sudden ""poverty"" that leaves millions of people in the US needing help to feed themselves",0.3833333333333333,"[('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Me llamó traidora"": cómo el caso Epstein divide al movimiento MAGA y enfrenta a Trump con una de sus más fieles aliadas","""He called me a traitor"": how the Epstein case divides the MAGA movement and pits Trump against one of his most faithful allies",0.5,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('MAGA', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Asclepios, la escuela escondida en una montaña suiza donde realizan entrenamientos extremos para astronautas","Asclepios, the school hidden in a Swiss mountain where they carry out extreme training for astronauts",-0.14583333333333331,"[('Asclepios', 'PRODUCT'), ('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Dos jueces de Miss Universo renuncian en medio de acusaciones de que el concurso está amañado y tras el escándalo con Miss México,Two Miss Universe judges resign amid accusations that the contest is rigged and after the scandal with Miss Mexico,0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"नीतीश की नई सरकार में जानिए किस पार्टी से कौन-कौन और कितने लोग बने मंत्री, एक मुस्लिम चेहरा","Know who and how many people from which party became ministers in Nitish's new government, one Muslim face",0.3181818181818182,"[('Nitish', 'ORG'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,नीतीश कुमार के शपथ ग्रहण वाले दिन प्रशांत किशोर का उपवास","Live, Prashant Kishor's fast on the day of Nitish Kumar's swearing-in",0.16818181818181818,"[('Kishor', 'GPE'), ('the day', 'DATE'), ('Nitish', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुतिन के भारत दौरे से पहले तेल आयात में आई गिरावट का क्या असर होगा?,What will be the impact of the decline in oil imports before Putin's visit to India?,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नीतीश कुमार के लिए मुख्यमंत्री की कुर्सी इस बार कई चुनौतियों से भरी क्यों,Why is the post of Chief Minister full of many challenges for Nitish Kumar this time?,0.425,"[('Nitish Kumar', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुरुषों के लिए पेशाब बैठकर करना ज़्यादा सही है या खड़े होकर,Is it better for men to urinate while sitting or standing?,0.5,[]
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अख़लाक़ लिंचिंग: अभियुक्तों पर केस वापस लेने की यूपी सरकार की अपील के बाद अब उनके परिवार के पास क्या विकल्प हैं?,"Akhlaq Lynching: After the UP government's appeal to withdraw the case against the accused, what options do the family have now?",0.0,[]
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जेम्स बॉन्ड का चरित्र इस जासूस की असली ज़िंदगी के आधार पर गढ़ा गया,The character of James Bond was based on the real life of this spy,0.2,"[('James Bond', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ट्रंप के सऊदी अरब को एफ़-35 फ़ाइटर जेट देने से कितनी बढ़ जाएगी उसकी ताक़त?,How much will Trump's power increase by giving F-35 fighter jets to Saudi Arabia?,0.2,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('F-35', 'PRODUCT'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीआईपी का चार में से तीन चुनावों में स्कोर रहा ज़ीरो, अब क्या होगा मुकेश सहनी का भविष्य?","VIP's score was zero in three out of four elections, now what will be the future of Mukesh Sahni?",0.0,"[('zero', 'CARDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mukesh Sahni', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Tony Tornado, 95 anos: as 1001 vidas do homem que fez o Brasil assumir seu black power","Tony Tornado, 95 years old: the 1001 lives of the man who made Brazil assume its black power",-0.033333333333333326,"[('Tony Tornado', 'PERSON'), ('95 years old', 'DATE'), ('1001', 'DATE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"É ingenuidade achar que transformar o Supremo em convento traria credibilidade, diz Gilmar Mendes","It is naive to think that transforming the Supreme Court into a convent would bring credibility, says Gilmar Mendes",-0.3,"[('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Gilmar Mendes', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Alemanha vai investir 1 bi de euros em fundo lançado por Lula na COP30 que usa mercado financeiro para proteger florestas,Germany will invest 1 billion euros in a fund launched by Lula at COP30 that uses financial markets to protect forests,0.0,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('1 billion', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A descoberta arqueológica que revela violência escravocrata em bairro japonês de SP,The archaeological discovery that reveals slave violence in a Japanese neighborhood in SP,0.0,"[('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('SP', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O psiquiatra que determinou que nazistas 'não eram loucos' e podiam ser julgados,The psychiatrist who ruled that Nazis were 'not crazy' and could be tried,0.3,"[('Nazis', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Odiava ter traços asiáticos, não ter olhos azuis ou cabelo loiro': estrela de 'Guerreiras do K-Pop' fala sobre sua infância difícil nos EUA","'I hated having Asian features, not having blue eyes or blonde hair': 'K-Pop Warriors' star talks about her difficult childhood in the US",-0.27999999999999997,"[('Asian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A surpreendente ligação entre os cabelos grisalhos e o câncer,The Surprising Link Between Gray Hair and Cancer,0.7,[]
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Primeiro beijo surgiu há 21 milhões de anos, dizem cientistas","First kiss appeared 21 million years ago, scientists say",0.25,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('21 million years ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Trump mudou de ideia sobre os arquivos de Epstein,Why Trump Changed His Mind About Epstein Files,0.0,[]
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Трамп одобрил мирный план, втайне разработанный в Белом доме, сообщает NBC","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Trump approves peace plan secretly developed in White House, NBC reports",0.05,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('NBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп подписал закон о публикации «файлов Эпштейна»,Trump signs law to release Epstein files,0.0,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Это равносильно капитуляции Украины». Что известно о мирном плане Трампа,“This is tantamount to the surrender of Ukraine.” What we know about Trump's peace plan,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Российский разведывательный корабль направил лазеры на британских военных пилотов, которые его отслеживали",A Russian spy ship aimed lasers at British military pilots who were tracking it.,-0.03333333333333333,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Акуленок ту-ру-ру-ру». Как из 90-секундного детского ролика вырос 400-миллионный бизнес,“Baby shark tu-ru-ru-ru.” How a 90-second children's video grew into a $400 million business,0.0,"[('90-second', 'TIME'), ('$400 million', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Верховная рада отправила в отставку двух министров на фоне коррупционного скандала. Завершен  ли на этом политический кризис?,The Verkhovna Rada dismissed two ministers amid a corruption scandal. Is this the end of the political crisis?,0.0,"[('The Verkhovna Rada', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Шон Пенн за 1 доллар снялся в украинском фильме о войне. Что это за фильм?,Sean Penn starred in a Ukrainian film about the war for $1. What kind of movie is this?,0.6,"[('Sean Penn', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('1', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Целоваться на Земле начали еще 21 миллион лет назад, утверждают ученые","Kissing on Earth began 21 million years ago, scientists say",0.0,"[('Earth', 'LOC'), ('21 million years ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Ситуация в Гуляйполе. Удастся ли там остановить российское наступление?,The situation in Gulyai-Polye. Will it be possible to stop the Russian offensive there?,0.0,"[('Gulyai', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Тернополе более 20 человек погибли в результате попадания в девятиэтажки,"In Ternopil, more than 20 people died as a result of being hit by a nine-story building",0.5,"[('Ternopil', 'GPE'), ('more than 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、「エプスティーン・ファイル」公開を司法省に命じる法案に署名,Trump signs bill ordering Justice Department to release Epstein file,0.0,"[('Justice Department', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍高官がウクライナ入り、戦争終結に向け協議　米ロが新たな和平案用意と報じられるなか,"High-ranking US military officials enter Ukraine to hold talks towards ending the war, amid reports that the US and Russia are preparing a new peace plan",0.018181818181818174,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアのスパイ船が英軍機にレーザー照射、英国防相は「軍事的選択肢」も準備と,"Russian spy ship beams laser at British military plane, UK defense minister prepares for ``military option''",-0.05,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル軍がガザ各地を攻撃、25人死亡と現地保健当局,"Israeli military attacks across Gaza, killing 25 people, local health authorities say",-0.05,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('25', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアがウクライナ空爆、子ども含む26人死亡　西部への攻撃では最悪規模,"Russia's airstrike on Ukraine kills 26 people, including children, worst attack on western country",-0.5,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('26', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インスタやフェイスブック、16歳未満の豪ユーザーにアカウント閉鎖を通知　SNS禁止措置の施行を前に,"Instagram, Facebook notify Australian users under 16 of account closure ahead of enforcement of SNS ban",0.0,"[('Australian', 'NORP'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('SNS', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ミス・ユニバースの審査員2人、開幕直前に辞任　1人は「不正操作」と主張,"Two Miss Universe judges resign just before the competition begins, one alleging ``rigging''",0.0,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ大統領がサウジ皇太子と会談、カショジ記者殺害事件で擁護　「物事は起こる」,President Trump meets Saudi crown prince and defends him over Khashoggi murder case: ``Things happen'',0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('Khashoggi', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スコットランド、サッカー男子W杯の28年ぶり出場を決める　デンマーク破り,Scotland defeats Denmark to qualify for Men's World Cup for the first time in 28 years,0.25,"[('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Denmark', 'GPE'), (""Men's World Cup"", 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('28 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump asaini muswada unaoamuru wizara ya sheria kutoa nyaraka za Epstein","Immediately, Trump signs a bill ordering the Justice Department to release Epstein's documents",0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the Justice Department', 'ORG'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marais wa Afrika Mashariki wapongezwa na CAF kwa mchango wao kwenye michezo,East African presidents are congratulated by CAF for their contribution to sports,0.0,"[('East African', 'NORP'), ('CAF', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maridhiano Tanzania: Jumuiya ya Madola na mustakabali wa ghasia za uchaguzi,Reconciliation Tanzania: The Commonwealth and the future of electoral violence,0.0,"[('Commonwealth', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hakimi na Chebbak watuzwa wachezaji bora wa soka barani Afrika,Hakimi and Chebbak were awarded the best soccer players in Africa,1.0,"[('Chebbak', 'ORG'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, chama cha Raila Odinga kitamudu hadi uchaguzi ujao?",Will Raila Odinga's party survive until the next election?,0.0,"[(""Will Raila Odinga's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Alhamisi: Ni Liverpool pekee inaweza kumsajili Guehi - Crystal Palce,European Football Rumors Thursday: Only Liverpool can sign Guehi - Crystal Palce,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Guehi - Crystal Palce', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"CHADEMA, ACT waikataa Tume ya Oktoba 29, CCM yaunga mkono","CHADEMA, ACT reject the October 29 Commission, CCM supports it",0.0,"[('October 29 Commission', 'DATE'), ('CCM', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Hitler alikuwa na uhusiano wowote na Wayahudi?",Did Hitler have anything to do with the Jews?,0.0,"[('Hitler', 'PERSON'), ('Jews', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mke wa Besyige amshutumu Rais Museveni kumuandaa mtoto wake kumrithi,Besyige's wife accuses President Museveni of preparing her son to succeed him,0.0,"[('Besyige', 'PERSON'), ('Museveni', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini Trump ameshindwa kumshawishi Putin kumaliza mzozo wa Ukraine?,Why has Trump failed to convince Putin to end the conflict in Ukraine?,-0.5,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
