Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo los recientes ataques de Irán contra Israel indican que Teherán se siente cada vez más fuerte,How Iran's recent attacks on Israel indicate that Tehran is feeling increasingly stronger,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué la creciente popularidad de los banquetes masivos en Francia despierta recelos en la izquierda del país,Why the growing popularity of mass banquets in France raises suspicions on the country's left,1.0,positive,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Elecciones en Perú: Roberto Sánchez supera a Keiko Fujimori en el reñido recuento de votos para la presidencia,Elections in Peru: Roberto Sánchez surpasses Keiko Fujimori in the close vote count for the presidency,0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Muchos espectadores no aceptarían un James Bond negro"": el actor Idris Elba pide que el agente secreto no sea ""woke""","""Many viewers would not accept a black James Bond"": actor Idris Elba asks that the secret agent not be ""woke""",0.0,neutral,"[('James Bond', 'PERSON'), ('Idris Elba', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cosmeticorexia: cómo las niñas están cayendo en la peligrosa obsesión de tener una piel perfecta,Cosmeticorexia: how girls are falling into the dangerous obsession with having perfect skin,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Contra ""las pérdidas de tiempo"" y otras nuevas normas que buscan revolucionar el juego en el Mundial 2026","Against ""time wasting"" and other new rules that seek to revolutionize the game in the 2026 World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""El Mundial no es para nosotros, es para ellos"": el enfado de los fans a los que no conceden visas para ir a EE.UU. a ver el torneo","""The World Cup is not for us, it is for them"": the anger of fans who are not granted visas to go to the US to watch the tournament",0.0,neutral,"[('The World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo se activó el dispositivo cardíaco del futbolista danés Eriksen al volver a colapsar durante un partido,How Danish footballer Eriksen's heart device was activated when he collapsed again during a match,0.0,neutral,"[('Danish', 'NORP'), ('Eriksen', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Irán e Israel anuncian que detendrán sus ataques tras intercambiar fuego por primera vez desde el cese el fuego en abril,Iran and Israel announce they will stop their attacks after exchanging fire for the first time since the ceasefire in April,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('April', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Xi Jinping visita a Kim Jong-un: cuál es el origen de la relación amor-odio entre China y Corea del Norte,Xi Jinping visits Kim Jong-un: what is the origin of the love-hate relationship between China and North Korea,0.0,neutral,"[('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,शामली के आयुष मलिक के मोहम्मद अली बनने का क्या है पूरा मामला,What is the whole matter of Shamli's Ayush Malik becoming Mohammed Ali?,0.0,neutral,"[('Ayush Malik', 'PERSON'), ('Mohammed Ali', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"डॉन 3: बदक़िस्मती, कामयाबी और इस फ़िल्म सिरीज़ से जुड़ा 48 साल का अभिशाप","Don 3: Bad luck, success and the 48-year curse associated with this film series",1.0,positive,"[('Don', 'PERSON'), ('48-year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,असम: ग्वालपाड़ा ज़िले के स्कूलों में टिफ़िन में मांसाहारी भोजन लाने पर लगाई गई रोक","Live, Assam: Ban on bringing non-vegetarian food in tiffin in schools of Goalpara district",0.0,neutral,"[('Goalpara', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"फ़ीफ़ा वर्ल्ड कप: अमेरिका ने रेफरी उमर अब्दुल क़ादिर को नहीं दी एंट्री, भारी विवाद","FIFA World Cup: America did not give entry to referee Omar Abdul Qadir, huge controversy",0.0,neutral,"[('FIFA World Cup: America', 'ORG'), ('Omar Abdul Qadir', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,उपेंद्र कुशवाहा के बेटे दीपक प्रकाश एमएलसी का नामांकन क्यों नहीं भर पाए,Why Upendra Kushwaha's son Deepak Prakash could not file MLC nomination?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Upendra Kushwaha's"", 'PERSON'), ('Deepak Prakash', 'PERSON'), ('MLC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,दिल्ली आग: मालवीय नगर में इतने विदेशी नागरिकों की जान क्यों गई?,Delhi fire: Why did so many foreign nationals lose their lives in Malviya Nagar?,0.0,neutral,"[('Malviya Nagar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इंडिया गठबंधन में कांग्रेस की पकड़ मज़बूत हुई लेकिन विजय के न आने से बढ़ी चिंता,Congress's hold on India alliance strengthened but Vijay's absence raised concerns,0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Vijay', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,आलू खाने से क्या गैस की समस्या बढ़ती है या खाने का तरीक़ा सुधारने की ज़रूरत,Does eating potatoes increase the problem of gas or is there a need to improve the way of eating?,1.0,positive,[]
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,टीएमसी नेता काकोली घोष के दावों के बाद 20 पार्टी सांसदों को लेकर कैसी है चर्चा,How is the discussion regarding 20 party MPs after the claims of TMC leader Kakoli Ghosh?,0.0,neutral,"[('20', 'CARDINAL'), ('TMC', 'ORG'), ('Kakoli Ghosh', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इंडिया गठबंधन की बैठक में कौन-कौन हुआ शामिल और किन मुद्दों पर बनी सहमति,Who attended the India Alliance meeting and on which issues was consensus reached?,0.0,neutral,"[('India Alliance', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A tentativa 'invisível' de manipular a Justiça com IA que preocupa tribunais pelo Brasil: 'É só a ponta do iceberg',The 'invisible' attempt to manipulate justice with AI that worries courts across Brazil: 'It's just the tip of the iceberg',0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Vacina do Butantan contra a dengue é suspensa; entenda o que levou à decisão e o que fazer se você já foi vacinado,Butantan vaccine against dengue is suspended; understand what led to the decision and what to do if you have already been vaccinated,0.0,neutral,"[('Butantan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Árbitro somali da Fifa é barrado nos EUA e fica fora da Copa do Mundo,Somali FIFA referee is banned from the USA and is left out of the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como Trump tenta influenciar eleições em outros países — e por que seu apoio nem sempre tem o resultado esperado,How Trump tries to influence elections in other countries — and why his support doesn't always have the expected results,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Eleições no Peru: Roberto Sánchez ultrapassa Keiko Fujimori em disputa voto a voto para presidente,Elections in Peru: Roberto Sánchez overtakes Keiko Fujimori in vote-by-vote dispute for president,0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como age a pílula que dá esperança contra um dos cânceres mais letais que existem,How the pill that gives hope against one of the most lethal cancers in existence works,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como medicina veterinária e ciência do comportamento animal ajudam consultora a decifrar 'enigmas felinos',How veterinary medicine and the science of animal behavior help consultants decipher 'feline enigmas',0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que Xi Jinping visita a Coreia do Norte — e o que está em jogo na disputa com a Rússia,Why Xi Jinping visits North Korea — and what's at stake in the dispute with Russia,0.0,neutral,"[('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,PEC da Liberdade ou Escravidão? O que pode mudar no regime de trabalho por hora proposto por Flávio Bolsonaro para barrar fim da 6x1,PEC of Freedom or Slavery? What could change in the hourly work regime proposed by Flávio Bolsonaro to stop the end of 6x1,0.0,neutral,"[('PEC', 'ORG'), ('Slavery', 'ORG'), ('hourly', 'TIME'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('6x1', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Китай и КНДР напомнили миру о своей дружбе. Разногласия оставили за закрытыми дверями,China and North Korea reminded the world of their friendship. Disagreements were left behind closed doors,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Удар беспилотника по поезду в аннексированном Крыму. Как ВСУ усиливают блокаду полуострова,Drone strike on a train in annexed Crimea. How the Ukrainian Armed Forces are strengthening the blockade of the peninsula,0.0,neutral,"[('Crimea', 'ORG'), ('the Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Дело о Белом орле. Почему снова поссорились Украина и Польша, и есть ли перспективы мира?","The Case of the White Eagle. Why did Ukraine and Poland quarrel again, and are there prospects for peace?",1.0,positive,"[('The Case of the White Eagle', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Poland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Харьковской области трое погибших и более 20 раненых после массированной атаки","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: in the Kharkov region three dead and more than 20 wounded after a massive attack",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kharkov', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('more than 20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Футбольного судью из Сомали не пустили в США. Теперь он не сможет обслуживать матчи ЧМ-2026,A soccer referee from Somalia was not allowed into the United States. Now he will not be able to officiate at the 2026 World Cup matches,0.0,neutral,"[('Somalia', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Это были самые скандальные выборы». Как российские телеканалы освещали день голосования в Армении,“This was the most scandalous election ever.” How Russian TV channels covered voting day in Armenia,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Armenia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Во Франции взят под стражу певец Патрик Брюэль. 13 женщин обвиняют его в сексуализированном насилии,Singer Patrick Bruel was taken into custody in France. 13 women accuse him of sexualized violence,0.0,neutral,"[('Patrick Bruel', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('13', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,После ракетных ударов войну вокруг Ирана снова поставили на паузу,"After missile attacks, the war over Iran was paused again",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Выборы президента в Перу грозят тупиком в подсчетах. И не впервые,The presidential election in Peru is threatening a deadlock in the counting. And not for the first time,0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Британский ультиматум Apple и Google: от техногигантов требуют поставить заслон «обнаженке» в телефонах подростков,British ultimatum from Apple and Google: tech giants are required to block nudity in teenagers' phones,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Apple', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イランとイスラエル、攻撃停止を表明　停戦違反あれば報復するとも警告,"Iran and Israel announce halt to attacks, warn of retaliation if ceasefire is violated",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 イランがイスラエル攻撃……イランの政権は自分たちの粘り強さを自覚か,[Commentary] Iran attacks Israel...Is the Iranian regime aware of its own tenacity?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,習氏が7年ぶりに北朝鮮を訪問、その背景をBBC特派員が説明, 所要時間 0,58","Video, Mr. Xi visits North Korea for the first time in seven years, a BBC correspondent explains the background, Duration 0,58",0.0,neutral,"[('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('seven years', 'DATE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 大会初のソマリア人審判、アメリカ入国を拒否される,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] First Somali referee at the tournament is denied entry to the US,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('First Somali', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米アップル、SiriのAI機能刷新を発表　クックCEOの退任を前に,Apple announces updates to Siri's AI functions ahead of CEO Cook's retirement,0.0,neutral,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Siri', 'GPE'), ('Cook', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,トランプ氏、ネタニヤフ氏は「自分の意向に逆らっていない」　BBC編集長との電話で語る, 所要時間 1,12","Video, Mr. Trump says Mr. Netanyahu is ""not going against his wishes"" in telephone call with BBC editor-in-chief, duration 1,12",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('1,12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,トランプ氏はイラン戦争を制御できなくなりつつあるのか, 所要時間 0,59","Video, Is Trump losing control of the Iran war? Duration 0,59",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,フィリピン南部沖で地震、死者少なくとも37人に,Earthquake off southern Philippines kills at least 37 people,-1.0,negative,"[('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('at least 37', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イラン代表チーム、メキシコに到着　米国とビザ問題で揺れるなか,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Iran national team arrives in Mexico amidst turmoil over visa issues with the US,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、米NBCインタビューをいきなり打ち切る　「仕組まれた選挙」めぐるやりとりの後,Trump abruptly ends NBC interview after exchange over ``rigged election'',0.0,neutral,"[('NBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Wakazi wakimbia mji wa Lebanon huku Israeli ikionya kufanya mashambulizi","Directly, Residents flee the city of Lebanon as Israel warns to attack",-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ufumbuzi mpya wa kukabiliana na upara unamaanisha nini kwa wanawake?,What does the new solution to combat baldness mean for women?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, huu ndio mwisho wa Rigathi Gachagua katika siasa za Kenya?",Is this the end of Rigathi Gachagua in Kenyan politics?,0.0,neutral,"[('Rigathi Gachagua', 'ORG'), ('Kenyan', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Jumanne: Tottenham wanaendelea na mazungumzo ili kumnasa Savinho,Football rumors Tuesday: Tottenham are in talks to sign Savinho,0.0,neutral,"[('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Tottenham', 'GPE'), ('Savinho', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mwamuzi wa Fifa wa Somalia azuiwa kuingia Marekani,Somalia's Fifa referee barred from entering US,0.0,neutral,"[('Somalia', 'GPE'), ('Fifa', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Gachagua apata pigo huku Mahakama Kuu ikitupilia mbali ombi la kupinga kuondolewa madarakani,Gachagua receives a blow as the High Court rejects the petition against his removal from power,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mythos ni nini na kwa nini inaonekana kuwa tishio kubwa kuliko Mlango bahari wa Hormuz?,What is Mythos and why does it seem to be a bigger threat than the Strait of Hormuz?,0.0,neutral,"[('Mythos', 'PERSON'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ratiba, msimamo na matokeo","World Cup 2026: Schedule, standings and results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ni nini hasa kinachoiunganisha China na Urusi?,What exactly connects China and Russia?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Netanyahu asema Israel inasitisha mashambulizi dhidi ya Iran 'kwa sasa',Netanyahu says Israel is halting attacks on Iran 'for now',-1.0,negative,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Historic’ wave of Palestinian solidarity grows at universities in Germany,‘Historic’ wave of Palestinian solidarity grows at universities in Germany,0.0,neutral,"[('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Russian attacks kill 5 in Ukraine as Zelenskyy hails talks with US envoys,Russian attacks kill 5 in Ukraine as Zelenskyy hails talks with US envoys,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskyy', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup star power: Do Ronaldo & Messi still rule, or is Mbappe the guy?","World Cup star power: Do Ronaldo & Messi still rule, or is Mbappe the guy?",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Ronaldo & Messi', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Photos: Trump courts boos at historic New York NBA Finals appearance,Photos: Trump courts boos at historic New York NBA Finals appearance,0.0,neutral,"[('New York NBA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran says US has revoked World Cup ticket allocation for their supporters,Iran says US has revoked World Cup ticket allocation for their supporters,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup form guide: Ranking the eight MENA teams in the tournament,World Cup form guide: Ranking the eight MENA teams in the tournament,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Indian crew rescued after attack on oil tanker off Oman,Indian crew rescued after attack on oil tanker off Oman,-1.0,negative,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Oman', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Deschamps backs hat-trick hero Olise to shine for France at World Cup,Deschamps backs hat-trick hero Olise to shine for France at World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Deschamps', 'ORG'), ('Olise', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Protests erupt in Kenya over US Ebola quarantine centre in Nanyuki,Protests erupt in Kenya over US Ebola quarantine centre in Nanyuki,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenya', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup 2026: What time can fans in Europe, Middle East and Africa watch?","World Cup 2026: What time can fans in Europe, Middle East and Africa watch?",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Middle East', 'LOC'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Lottery baron Santiago Martin, MLA wife Leema Rose and daughter Daisy move Madras High Court against ED action","Lottery baron Santiago Martin, MLA wife Leema Rose and daughter Daisy move Madras High Court against ED action",0.0,neutral,"[('Santiago Martin', 'PERSON'), ('MLA', 'PERSON'), ('Leema Rose', 'PERSON'), ('Daisy', 'PERSON'), ('Madras High Court', 'ORG'), ('ED', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Supreme Court flags 40-year delay by Allahabad HC in murder case, seeks solutions to judicial backlog","Supreme Court flags 40-year delay by Allahabad HC in murder case, seeks solutions to judicial backlog",0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('40-year', 'DATE'), ('Allahabad HC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Patna court stays arrest of ‘Khan Sir’,Patna court stays arrest of ‘Khan Sir’,0.0,neutral,"[('Khan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,MSC Elsa 3 sinking: Kerala HC permits three crew members to return to home countries,MSC Elsa 3 sinking: Kerala HC permits three crew members to return to home countries,0.0,neutral,"[('MSC Elsa 3', 'PERSON'), ('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Power cuts leave Chennai residents fuming; protests erupt across city,Power cuts leave Chennai residents fuming; protests erupt across city,0.0,neutral,"[('Chennai', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"ED raids in Punjab: BJP misusing Central agencies to harass traders, says CM Bhagwant Mann","ED raids in Punjab: BJP misusing Central agencies to harass traders, says CM Bhagwant Mann",0.0,neutral,"[('Punjab', 'NORP'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Central', 'ORG'), ('Bhagwant Mann', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The trust deficit in India-Bangladesh ties,The trust deficit in India-Bangladesh ties,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Venkateshwara Granite owner, four others booked for illegally storing and using explosives at quarry near Bengaluru","Venkateshwara Granite owner, four others booked for illegally storing and using explosives at quarry near Bengaluru",-1.0,negative,"[('Venkateshwara Granite', 'ORG'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bengaluru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Manoj Bajpayee interview: On ‘Governor’, OTT fatigue and why box office obsession must end","Manoj Bajpayee interview: On ‘Governor’, OTT fatigue and why box office obsession must end",0.0,neutral,"[('Manoj Bajpayee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Unity in diversity: On the INDIA bloc meeting,Unity in diversity: On the INDIA bloc meeting,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump tells BBC Netanyahu did not defy him,Trump tells BBC Netanyahu did not defy him,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC Netanyahu', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Israel and Iran flare-up could strengthen Tehran's negotiating hand,Israel and Iran flare-up could strengthen Tehran's negotiating hand,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Hundreds of aftershocks jolt Philippines as officials say death toll could rise,Hundreds of aftershocks jolt Philippines as officials say death toll could rise,-1.0,negative,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump booed in New York as he becomes first US president to attend NBA Finals,Trump booed in New York as he becomes first US president to attend NBA Finals,0.0,neutral,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,ICC suspends top prosecutor after investigating misconduct allegations,ICC suspends top prosecutor after investigating misconduct allegations,0.0,neutral,"[('ICC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Man accused of killing mother-in-law with poison-laced satay,Man accused of killing mother-in-law with poison-laced satay,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Xi Jinping and Kim Jong Un vow stronger ties as North Korea visit wraps up,Xi Jinping and Kim Jong Un vow stronger ties as North Korea visit wraps up,0.0,neutral,"[('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('Kim Jong Un', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Tickets for Iran fans revoked, says federation","Tickets for Iran fans revoked, says federation",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Kenyan police fire tear gas at protest against US Ebola quarantine centre plan,Kenyan police fire tear gas at protest against US Ebola quarantine centre plan,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('US Ebola', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_09,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Black bear caught in Japan after days of sightings,Black bear caught in Japan after days of sightings,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: Israel Launches New Strikes in Southern Lebanon,Iran War Live Updates: Israel Launches New Strikes in Southern Lebanon,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates', 'EVENT'), ('Israel Launches New Strikes', 'ORG'), ('Southern Lebanon', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Challenge in the U.S.-Iran Talks: Both Sides Demand Victory,A Challenge in the U.S.-Iran Talks: Both Sides Demand Victory,1.0,positive,[]
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Roar of ‘Cease-Fire’ in a Once-Thriving City,The Roar of ‘Cease-Fire’ in a Once-Thriving City,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine’s Neighbors Seek Shelter as More and More Drones Fly Overhead,Ukraine’s Neighbors Seek Shelter as More and More Drones Fly Overhead,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Infantino’s Yearslong Effort to Woo Trump for the World Cup,Infantino’s Yearslong Effort to Woo Trump for the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Infantino', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,One of Pope Leo’s Best Friends Works in Spain. They Talk About Cars.,One of Pope Leo’s Best Friends Works in Spain. They Talk About Cars.,0.0,neutral,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Why a U.K. By-Election in Makerfield Could Topple Prime Minister Keir Starmer,Why a U.K. By-Election in Makerfield Could Topple Prime Minister Keir Starmer,0.0,neutral,"[('U.K.', 'GPE'), ('Keir Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A ‘Miraculous Transformation’: How Kim Jong-un Fortified North Korea,A ‘Miraculous Transformation’: How Kim Jong-un Fortified North Korea,0.0,neutral,"[('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Artisanal or Exploitative? Unraveling the Story of Mexico’s World Cup Jerseys,Artisanal or Exploitative? Unraveling the Story of Mexico’s World Cup Jerseys,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Jerseys', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_09,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,At Least 32 Dead After Earthquake and Landslide in the Philippines,At Least 32 Dead After Earthquake and Landslide in the Philippines,0.0,neutral,"[('At Least 32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
