Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué papel juega EE.UU. en Somalia, el país del que Trump no quiere inmigrantes y el Pentágono lleva años bombardeando","What role does the US play in Somalia, the country from which Trump does not want immigrants and the Pentagon has been bombing for years?",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Somalia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Pentagon', 'ORG'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Así quedan los 12 grupos del Mundial de fútbol 2026: ¿contra quién juega tu equipo?,This is how the 12 groups of the 2026 Soccer World Cup remain: who does your team play against?,0.0,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El análisis de BBC Mundo del sorteo del Mundial de 2026 para las selecciones de América Latina y España,BBC Mundo's analysis of the 2026 World Cup draw for the teams from Latin America and Spain,0.0,"[(""BBC Mundo's"", 'ORG'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Latin America', 'LOC'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Arquitectura de las remesas: cómo el dinero que llega de EE.UU. está transformando los pueblos y ciudades de Guatemala,Architecture of remittances: how money arriving from the US is transforming the towns and cities of Guatemala,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Guatemala', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"10 de los edificios más emblemáticos de Frank Gehry, el titán de la arquitectura que murió a los 96 años","10 of the most emblematic buildings of Frank Gehry, the titan of architecture who died at the age of 96",0.5,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Frank Gehry', 'PERSON'), ('the age of 96', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,डॉक्टर आंबेडकरः जिन्होंने जाति को महिलाओं के नज़रिए से देखा और समझा था,Dr. Ambedkar: Who saw and understood caste from women's perspective,0.0,"[('Ambedkar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत और रूस का अब आगे का रास्ता क्या होगा और इसमें कौन-सी चुनौतियां हैं?,What will be the way forward for India and Russia and what are the challenges in it?,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,पुतिन के लिए आयोजित दावत में विपक्षी नेताओं को आमंत्रित नहीं किए जाने पर मनोज झा ने ये कहा","Live, Manoj Jha said this on opposition leaders not being invited to the banquet organized for Putin",0.13636363636363635,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'पुतिन-मोदी मुलाक़ात से यूरोपीय देश और ट्रंप परेशान', पुतिन के भारत दौरे पर बोला रूसी मीडिया","'European countries and Trump are troubled by Putin-Modi meeting', Russian media said on Putin's visit to India",-0.16666666666666666,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Putin-Modi', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुतिन के लिए आयोजित डिनर में शशि थरूर को बुलाने पर क्यों हुआ विवाद?,Why was there controversy over inviting Shashi Tharoor to the dinner organized for Putin?,0.0,"[('Shashi Tharoor', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'मस्जिद ज़रूर बनेगी', पश्चिम बंगाल विधायक हुमायूं कबीर के दावे की परीक्षा का दिन","'Mosque will definitely be built', test day for West Bengal MLA Humayun Kabir's claim",0.0,"[('Mosque', 'NORP'), (""Humayun Kabir's"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,साल 2030 तक पाकिस्तानी सेना की कमान मिलने के बाद बोले आसिम मुनीर-अब आगे बढ़ेगा पाकिस्तान,"After getting the command of Pakistani Army till the year 2030, Asim Munir said - Now Pakistan will move forward",0.0,"[('Pakistani Army', 'ORG'), ('the year 2030', 'DATE'), ('Asim Munir', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"गाना गाने से क्यों मिलता है सुकून, क्या कहता है विज्ञान?","Why does singing provide solace, what does science say?",0.0,[]
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुतिन-मोदी मुलाक़ात: इन अहम समझौतों पर बनी सहमति,Putin-Modi meeting: Agreement reached on these important agreements,0.4,"[('Putin-Modi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Jair Bolsonaro escolhe o filho Flávio para disputar a Presidência - a quem decisão agrada e desagrada?,Jair Bolsonaro chooses his son Flávio to run for President - whose decision pleases and displeases?,0.0,"[('Jair Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Como e quantos são os navios de guerra, aviões e soldados que os EUA enviaram para a região da Venezuela","How and how many warships, planes and soldiers the US sent to the Venezuela region",0.5,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como ficam os grupos da Copa do Mundo 2026 — e quem Brasil vai enfrentar na 1ª fase,What the 2026 World Cup groups look like — and who Brazil will face in the 1st phase,0.0,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the 1st', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O prêmio da paz criado pela Fifa e concedido a Trump em sorteio da Copa do Mundo,The peace prize created by FIFA and awarded to Trump in a World Cup draw,0.0,"[('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As 'cores do ano' que podem transformar sua casa em 2026,The 'colors of the year' that can transform your home in 2026,0.0,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Joesley Batista: as investidas do dono da JBS na diplomacia,Joesley Batista: JBS owner's forays into diplomacy,0.0,"[('Joesley Batista', 'PERSON'), ('JBS', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Alexandre de Moraes é 'herói' em lista dos 25 mais influentes do ano do Financial Times,Alexandre de Moraes is a 'hero' on the Financial Times' list of the 25 most influential people of the year,0.25,"[('Alexandre de Moraes', 'PERSON'), (""the Financial Times'"", 'ORG'), ('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('the year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como vulcão pode ter provocado pandemia que dizimou metade da população da Europa no século 14,How a volcano may have caused a pandemic that wiped out half of Europe's population in the 14th century,-0.16666666666666666,"[('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('the 14th century', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A surpreendente compra da Warner Bros pela Netflix que pode revolucionar indústria do cinema nos EUA,The surprising purchase of Warner Bros by Netflix that could revolutionize the film industry in the US,0.7,"[('Warner Bros', 'ORG'), ('Netflix', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Серьезная потеря для детей? Что такое Roblox и почему российские власти его заблокировали,A serious loss for children? What is Roblox and why did Russian authorities block it?,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Roblox', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Вашингтон и Киев на переговорах во Флориде «согласовали рамки договоренностей в сфере безопасности»","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Washington and Kyiv at negotiations in Florida “agreed on the framework of security agreements”",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Florida', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Умер архитектор Фрэнк Гери. Среди его работ — музей Гуггенхайма в Бильбао,Architect Frank Gehry has died. Among his works is the Guggenheim Museum in Bilbao,0.0,"[('Frank Gehry', 'PERSON'), ('the Guggenheim Museum', 'ORG'), ('Bilbao', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«У нас было два врага — украинцы и наше командование». Как «герой Z» стал дезертиром,"“We had two enemies - the Ukrainians and our command.” How ""Hero Z"" became a deserter",0.0,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukrainians', 'NORP'), ('Hero Z', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Конец эры массовой миграции, непобедимая армия и доктрина Монро. США обнародовали новую стратегию национальной безопасности","The end of the era of mass migration, the invincible army and the Monroe Doctrine. US unveils new national security strategy",0.13636363636363635,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,США помогут Южной Корее построить атомные подводные лодки. Что это может значить для региона?,The US will help South Korea build nuclear submarines. What could this mean for the region?,-0.3125,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Драма для людей, которые создают драмы». Netflix покупает бизнес Warner Bros., в том числе HBO","""Drama is for people who create drama."" Netflix buys Warner Bros. business, including HBO",0.0,"[('Drama', 'PERSON'), ('Netflix', 'ORG'), ('Warner Bros.', 'ORG'), ('HBO', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Энергетика, торговля, бизнес. О чем договорились Путин и Моди","Energy, trade, business. What did Putin and Modi agree on?",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Modi', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Вязки». Как принудительная фиксация в российской психиатрии калечит и убивает,"""Matings."" How forced fixation in Russian psychiatry maims and kills",-0.15000000000000002,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сергей Тихановский недоволен офисом своей жены. Белорусы не верят в демократическое будущее. Главное в Беларуси за неделю,Sergei Tikhanovsky is dissatisfied with his wife’s office. Belarusians do not believe in a democratic future. The main things in Belarus in a week,0.08333333333333333,"[('Sergei Tikhanovsky', 'PERSON'), ('Belarusians', 'NORP'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 プーチン氏とモディ氏、デリー会談で何を得たのか,[Commentary] What did Mr. Putin and Mr. Modi gain from the Delhi meeting?,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Modi', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ米政権、ヨーロッパは「文明消滅」の危機と警告　新たな戦略文書で,Trump administration warns that Europe is at risk of ``annihilation of civilization'' in new strategic document,0.13636363636363635,"[('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米連邦最高裁、市民権の「出生地主義」めぐる訴訟を受理　トランプ政権は廃止目指す,U.S. Supreme Court accepts lawsuit over citizenship citizenship; Trump administration aims to abolish it,0.0,"[('U.S. Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 抽選会で組み合わせ決定　FIFAがトランプ氏に「平和賞」を授与,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Pairings determined by lottery; FIFA awards Trump the Peace Prize,0.0,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('Trump the Peace Prize', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 米ネットフリックスがワーナーの主要事業を買収へ　何が起こっているのか,[Commentary] US Netflix to acquire Warner's main business - what's going on?,0.16666666666666666,"[('Warner', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン氏、ウクライナ軍撤退なければドンバスを「武力で掌握」と警告,"Putin warns that if Ukrainian troops do not withdraw, he will seize Donbas by force",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Donbas', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヘグセス米長官は「全員殺せ」と命令していないと海軍提督　連邦議員たちに証言,Navy admiral tells federal lawmakers that US Secretary of State Hegseth did not give order to kill everyone,0.0,"[('Navy', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,欧州歌合戦「ユーロヴィジョン」、来年のイスラエルの出場認める　アイルランドなど4カ国がボイコット表明,"Four countries, including Ireland, announce boycott of European singing competition ``Eurovision'' to allow Israel to participate next year",0.0,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Eurovision', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('next year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,オットセイの赤ちゃんがバーに侵入、ニュージーランド, 所要時間 1,12","Video, Baby fur seal breaks into bar, New Zealand, Duration 1,12",0.13636363636363635,"[('New Zealand', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Tanzania kutengwa kidiplomasia?",Is Tanzania diplomatically isolated?,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump asifu makubaliano ya amani ya kihistoria kati ya DR Congo na Rwanda","Directly, Trump praised the historic peace agreement between DR Congo and Rwanda",0.05,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('DR Congo', 'ORG'), ('Rwanda', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Droo yazipanga makundi magumu timu za Afrika,World Cup 2026: The draw organizes difficult groups for African teams,-0.25,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Klabu 12 zinamtaka Mainoo,European football rumours: 12 clubs want Mainoo,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Serikali  yaijibu jamii ya kimataifa,Protests in Tanzania: The government responds to the international community,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Jeshi la polisi Tanzania lapiga marufuku maandamano ya Desemba 9, 2025","The Tanzanian police force bans the protest of December 9, 2025",0.0,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('December 9, 2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mapigano yapamba moto DRC saa chache baada ya kufikiwa kwa makubaliano ya amani,Fighting flares up in DRC a few hours after a peace agreement was reached,-0.2,"[('DRC', 'ORG'), ('a few hours', 'TIME')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Balozi 16 za nchi za magharibi zataka uchunguzi huru wa matukio ya Octoba 29,Protests in Tanzania: 16 embassies of western countries want an independent investigation of the events of October 29,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('October 29', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Meta yajibu sababu za kufungia akaunti za wanaharakati wawili wa Tanzania,Meta answers the reasons for freezing the accounts of two Tanzanian activists,0.0,"[('Meta', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_06,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, miamba ya ajabu inayopatikana kwenye sayari ni ishara ya uhai?",Are the strange rocks found on the planet a sign of life?,-0.05,[]
