Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los países de Europa que decidieron (o debaten) el ingreso de mujeres al servicio militar ante la amenaza de una agresión de Rusia,The European countries that decided (or are debating) the entry of women into military service in the face of the threat of aggression from Russia,-0.05,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Varias aerolíneas internacionales cancelan sus vuelos a Venezuela tras alerta de la FAA sobre ""incremento de la actividad militar"" en ese país","Several international airlines cancel their flights to Venezuela after the FAA alert about ""increased military activity"" in that country",-0.03333333333333333,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('FAA', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El temor de los iraníes conversos al cristianismo en EE.UU. que están siendo deportados a su país,The fear of Iranian converts to Christianity in the US who are being deported to their country,0.0,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Christianity', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,La extraordinaria  historia del egipcio que espió a Israel durante 17 años (y que Tel Aviv asegura que fue agente doble),The extraordinary story of the Egyptian who spied on Israel for 17 years (and who Tel Aviv claims was a double agent),0.16666666666666666,"[('Egyptian', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('17 years', 'DATE'), ('Tel Aviv', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cuán cierto es que los átomos son inmortales (y si lo son, por qué todo lo vivo muere)","How true it is that atoms are immortal (and if they are, why does everything alive die)",0.22499999999999998,[]
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान इंटरनेशनल एयरलाइन्स के कर्मचारी कनाडा जाकर क्यों हो रहे हैं 'ग़ायब',Why are Pakistan International Airlines employees going to Canada and disappearing?,0.0,"[('Pakistan International Airlines', 'ORG'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,मौलाना अरशद मदनी के बयान पर जेडीयू ने 'गिनाए मुसलमान वाइस चांसलरों के नाम'","Live, on the statement of Maulana Arshad Madani, JDU 'listed the names of Muslim Vice Chancellors'",0.13636363636363635,"[('Maulana Arshad Madani', 'PERSON'), ('JDU', 'ORG'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सम्राट हर्षवर्धन जो तलवार और कलम दोनों चलाने में थे माहिर - विवेचना,Emperor Harshvardhan who was expert in using both sword and pen - Discussion,0.0,"[('Harshvardhan', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"आधार कार्ड में होने जा रहे हैं बड़े बदलाव, जानिए क्या-कुछ होगा नया?","Big changes are going to happen in Aadhar Card, know what will be new?",0.06818181818181818,"[('Aadhar Card', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,शेख़ हसीना को सज़ा-ए-मौत: भारत को अब क्या रुख़ अपनाना चाहिए?,Death sentence to Sheikh Hasina: What stance should India take now?,0.0,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"रिलायंस ने रूस से तेल आयात किया बंद, अमेरिकी टैरिफ़ क्या अब कम होंगे?","Reliance stops importing oil from Russia, will American tariffs be reduced now?",0.0,"[('Reliance', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इस्लाम में तलाक़-ए-हसन क्या है, जिस पर सुप्रीम कोर्ट में हो रही है बहस","What is Talaq-e-Hassan in Islam, which is being debated in the Supreme Court.",0.0,"[('Talaq', 'GPE'), ('Islam', 'GPE'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,'नतीजे 15-20 मिनट ही देखे, समझ गया था फ़र्श पर आने वाले थे'- प्रशांत किशोर इंटरव्यू, अवधि 29,51","Video, 'After watching the results only for 15-20 minutes, I understood that they were going to be on the floor'- Prashant Kishor Interview, Duration 29,51",0.0,"[('15-20 minutes', 'TIME')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"अब एक साल की नौकरी पर ग्रेच्युटी के हक़दार, नया लेबर कोड क्या है जिसका कई मज़दूर संगठन कर रहे हैं विरोध","Now entitled to gratuity after one year's service, what is the new labor code which many labor organizations are opposing?",0.3181818181818182,"[(""one year's"", 'DATE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro é preso por risco de fuga após violar tornozeleira e Flávio convocar vigília: o que acontece agora?,Bolsonaro is arrested for being a flight risk after violating an ankle bracelet and Flávio calls for a vigil: what happens now?,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro diz que usou ferro de solda em tornozeleira: 'Curiosidade',Bolsonaro says he used a soldering iron on an ankle bracelet: 'Curiosity',0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como bolsonaristas reagiram à prisão de Bolsonaro: 'Preso por uma oração',How Bolsonaro supporters reacted to Bolsonaro's arrest: 'Arrested for a prayer',-0.05,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Flávio Bolsonaro mantém vigília em Brasília e acusa Moraes: 'Se meu pai morrer, a culpa é sua'","Flávio Bolsonaro keeps vigil in Brasília and accuses Moraes: 'If my father dies, it's your fault'",0.0,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Brasília', 'GPE'), ('Moraes', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,VÍDEO: Veja como é a 'sala de Estado' onde Bolsonaro ficará preso, Duration 0,17","Video,VIDEO: See what the 'state room' looks like where Bolsonaro will be imprisoned, Duration 0.17",0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como imprensa internacional noticia prisão preventiva de Bolsonaro,How international press reports Bolsonaro's preventive arrest,-0.025,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Moraes rejeita pedido de prisão domiciliar humanitária para Bolsonaro: quais são os problemas de saúde do ex-presidente,Moraes rejects request for humanitarian house arrest for Bolsonaro: what are the former president's health problems,-0.025,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Moraes decreta prisão de Ramagem após fuga para o exterior; o que se sabe,Moraes orders Ramagem's arrest after fleeing abroad; what is known,-0.05,"[('Ramagem', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"O que levou à prisão quatro ex-presidentes do Brasil, de Collor a Bolsonaro","What led to the arrest of four former presidents of Brazil, from Collor to Bolsonaro",-0.025,"[('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: переговоры Украины, США и Европы пройдут в воскресенье в Женеве","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: negotiations between Ukraine, the US and Europe will be held on Sunday in Geneva",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Geneva', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Европейские лидеры на саммите G20: мирный план США требует доработки,European leaders at G20 summit: US peace plan needs improvement,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('G20', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,COP30 в тупике: на саммите ООН по климату не удалось договориться об отказе от ископаемого топлива,COP30 deadlock: UN climate summit fails to agree on fossil fuel divestment,-0.5,"[('UN', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Из приюта для бездомных — к мировому признанию. Как профессор Иджеома Учегбу стала известной ученой,From a homeless shelter to global recognition. How Professor Ijeoma Uchegbu Became a Famous Scientist,0.25,"[('Ijeoma Uchegbu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Экс-президента Бразилии Жаира Болсонару снова задержали, признав склонным к побегу","Former Brazilian President Jair Bolsonaro was detained again, found prone to escape",0.0,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Jair Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,По делу о громком убийстве мэра в Мексике арестованы семь его телохранителей,Seven of his bodyguards have been arrested in connection with the high-profile murder of a mayor in Mexico.,0.0,"[('Seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Англию хотят вернуть диких кошек. Но некоторые боятся, что они будут спариваться с домашними",They want to return wild cats to England. But some are afraid that they will mate with domestic ones,-0.16666666666666666,"[('England', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Боевики похитили более 300 детей из католической школы в Нигерии,Gunmen kidnap more than 300 children from Catholic school in Nigeria,0.25,"[('more than 300', 'CARDINAL'), ('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как украинских подростков вербуют через Telegram для диверсий против своей страны,How Ukrainian teenagers are recruited via Telegram for sabotage against their country,0.0,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Telegram', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Либо потеря достоинства, либо потеря ключевого партнера». Зеленский в обращении к нации ответил на «мирный план» США",“Either loss of dignity or loss of a key partner.” Zelensky responded to the US “peace plan” in his address to the nation,0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ウクライナ和平案は「最終提案」ではないと発言,Trump says Ukraine peace plan is not 'final proposal',0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、アメリカの支援失う危険あるとウクライナ国民に演説　ホワイトハウスの和平案めぐり,Zelenskiy speaks to Ukrainians about risk of losing US support over White House peace plan,0.0,"[('Ukrainians', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「彼を応援する」と友好的に……トランプ氏がマムダニ次期NY市長と会談, 所要時間 1,28","Video, ``Support him'' and friendly...Trump talks with New York Mayor Mamdani, Duration 1,28",0.13636363636363635,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ミス・ユニバース世界大会、運営に対抗したメキシコ代表が優勝,"Miss Universe world pageant, Mexican representative wins against management",0.15,"[('Universe', 'PERSON'), ('Mexican', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,生物の「初めてのキス」は約2100万年前、最新研究が起源を解明,Latest research reveals the origin of the first kiss of living things about 21 million years ago,0.375,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏と対立した米保守派グリーン氏、来年1月に下院議員を辞職へ,"US conservative Greene, who has opposed Trump, plans to resign from the House of Representatives in January next year",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Greene', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the House of Representatives', 'ORG'), ('January next year', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏とマムダニ次期NY市長の会談、意外なほど友好的に,Meeting between Trump and New York Mayor Mamdani turns surprisingly friendly,0.2556818181818182,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英のコロナ対策、「不十分で遅すぎた」と独立調査委　政府対応で第1波の死者増えたと,"Britain's coronavirus response was 'insufficient and too slow', independent commission says, with government response leading to more deaths in first wave",0.11249999999999999,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 デフリンピック、東京で100周年記念大会　パラとの違いや選手の思い,"[Commentary] Deaflympics, 100th anniversary event held in Tokyo - Differences from Para and athletes' thoughts",0.0,"[('Commentary] Deaflympics', 'ORG'), ('100th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('Para', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mashirika ya ndege yasitisha safari za kuelekea Venezuela baada ya mamlaka ya usafiri wa anga ya Marekani kuonya","Directly, Airlines suspend flights to Venezuela after the US aviation authority warned",0.1,"[('Airlines', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nigeria yashuhudia utekaji nyara mbaya zaidi huku 315 wakithibitishwa kutekwa kutoka shuleni,Nigeria is witnessing the worst kidnapping with 315 confirmed abductions from schools,-0.3,"[('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('315', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumapili: Mshambuliaji wa Borussia Dortmund achagua Arsenal badala ya Man United,European soccer rumors Sunday: Borussia Dortmund striker chooses Arsenal over Man United,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Borussia Dortmund', 'ORG'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Sababu za 'bingwa kibonde' Liverpool kuchapwa kila siku,The reasons for the 'basket champion' Liverpool to be beaten every day,0.0,"[('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('every day', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini watu mashuhuri wanakumbatia kudungwa manii ya samaki usoni?,Why are celebrities embracing facial injections of fish sperm?,0.0,[]
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Ukraine iko njia panda ""ama kupoteze utu, au mshirika mkuu""","Ukraine is at a crossroads ""either lose humanity, or a major partner""",0.0625,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mjumbe wa bodi ya BBC ajiuzulu,BBC board member to resign,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Vita vya Iraq: Wanajeshi wa Marekani wahusishwa na mauaji ya familia,Iraq war: US soldiers linked to family murders,0.0,"[('Iraq', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini wanasayansi wanaunda aina hii ya damu adimu zaidi duniani?,Why do scientists create this rarest blood type in the world?,0.0,[]
2025_11_23,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, kupata watoto wengi kunaweza kufupisha maisha yako?",Can having more children shorten your life?,0.5,[]
