Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué tanto transformó Petro a Colombia, ""el presidente del cambio"" que se juega su legado aunque no pueda ser reelegido","How much Petro transformed Colombia, ""the president of change"" who risks his legacy even if he cannot be re-elected",0.0,neutral,"[('Petro', 'GPE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El acuerdo entre EE.UU. e Irán es un bienvenido regalo de cumpleaños para Trump, pero está envuelto en incertidumbre: análisis de la BBC",US-Iran deal a welcome birthday present for Trump but shrouded in uncertainty: BBC analysis,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Mueren 6 personas en un choque de helicópteros donde viajaba el youtuber argentino Gaspi, de 23 años","6 people die in a helicopter crash where the Argentine youtuber Gaspi, 23, was traveling",0.0,neutral,"[('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Argentine', 'NORP'), ('23', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Condenan al hijo de la princesa heredera de Noruega, Mette-Marit, a 4 años de prisión por cargos de violación",Norwegian Crown Princess Mette-Marit's son sentenced to 4 years in prison on rape charges,0.0,neutral,"[('Norwegian', 'NORP'), ('Crown', 'PRODUCT'), (""Mette-Marit's"", 'PERSON'), ('4 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"¿Messi, Maradona o Pelé? El ranking de la BBC de las 10 leyendas de los Mundiales","Messi, Maradona or Pelé? The BBC ranking of the 10 legends of the World Cups",0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Maradona', 'PERSON'), ('Pelé', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cups', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,EE.UU. e Irán anuncian un acuerdo para alcanzar la paz y  reabrir el estrecho de Ormuz,US and Iran announce agreement to reach peace and reopen Strait of Hormuz,1.0,positive,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Iremos más allá que cualquier otro país"": Reino Unido anuncia la prohibición de redes sociales para menores de 16 años","""We will go further than any other country"": United Kingdom announces ban on social networks for those under 16 years of age",0.0,neutral,"[('United Kingdom', 'GPE'), ('under 16 years of age', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El agotamiento que producen las apps de citas y 4 consejos para evitarlo,The exhaustion caused by dating apps and 4 tips to avoid it,0.0,neutral,"[('dating apps', 'PERSON'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Por qué dominar la ""sentadilla asiática"" es clave para nuestra salud","Why mastering the ""Asian squat"" is key to our health",0.0,neutral,"[('Asian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Puma vs Adidas: cómo la pelea entre dos hermanos partió en dos una ciudad alemana durante décadas,Puma vs Adidas: how the fight between two brothers split a German city in two for decades,0.0,neutral,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('two for decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ममता के साथ सियासी सफ़र शुरू करने वालीं काकोली घोष कैसे बनीं बग़ावत का चेहरा,"How Kakoli Ghosh, who started her political journey with Mamata, became the face of rebellion",0.0,neutral,"[('Kakoli Ghosh', 'PERSON'), ('Mamata', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,अकाल तख़्त ने पंजाब के सीएम भगवंत मान को 'खालसा पंथ विरोधी' करार दिया","Live, Akal Takht termed Punjab CM Bhagwant Mann as 'anti-Khalsa Panth'",0.0,neutral,"[('Akal Takht', 'PERSON'), ('Mann', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"रंगा-बिल्ला केस क्या था, जिस पर बनी वेब सिरीज़ 'राख़' की हो रही है चर्चा","What was the Ranga-Billa case, on which the web series 'Rakh' is being discussed?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पाकिस्तान की नई हैंगोर पनडुब्बी कितनी ताक़तवर?,How powerful is Pakistan's new Hangor submarine?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Hangor', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,हवाई यात्रियों की सुरक्षा के लिए क्या पर्याप्त कदम उठाए जा रहे हैं? - बीबीसी पड़ताल,Are adequate steps being taken for the safety of air passengers? - BBC Investigation,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"नेशनलिस्ट सिटिज़ंस पार्टी क्या है, जिसमें टीएमसी के 20 बाग़ी सांसद कर रहे हैं विलय","What is Nationalist Citizens Party, in which 20 rebel TMC MPs are merging?",0.0,neutral,"[('Nationalist Citizens Party', 'ORG'), ('20', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ईरान और अमेरिका में डील तो हो गई लेकिन ये ख़तरे अब भी बाक़ी,Deal reached between Iran and America but these dangers still remain,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका और ईरान में शांति समझौते का एलान, होर्मुज़ स्ट्रेट समेत किन बातों पर बनी सहमति","Peace agreement announced between America and Iran, what things were agreed upon including the Strait of Hormuz",1.0,positive,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पाकिस्तान ने अपने रक्षा बजट में किया भारी इज़ाफ़ा, भारत को लेकर क्या कहा गया","Pakistan made a huge increase in its defense budget, what was said about India?",0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,दीप्ति शर्मा और स्मृति मंधाना के कमाल ने कैसे पाकिस्तान की उम्मीदों पर पानी फेरा,How the magic of Deepti Sharma and Smriti Mandhana dashed Pakistan's hopes,0.0,neutral,"[('Deepti Sharma', 'ORG'), ('Smriti Mandhana', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,EUA e Irã chegam a acordo de paz e Trump diz que estreito de Ormuz vai reabrir; o que se sabe,US and Iran reach peace agreement and Trump says Strait of Hormuz will reopen; what is known,1.0,positive,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Trump elogia acordo com o Irã, mas dúvidas — e riscos — continuam","Trump praises deal with Iran, but doubts — and risks — remain",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Filho de princesa da Noruega é condenado à prisão por dois estupros,Son of Norwegian princess sentenced to prison for two rapes,0.0,neutral,"[('Norwegian', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O soldado ucraniano que recontou os livros de Harry Potter que sabia de cor para ajudar companheiros de cela,The Ukrainian soldier who retold the Harry Potter books he knew by heart to help cellmates,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Harry Potter', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Reino Unido vai banir menores de 16 anos das redes sociais e avalia restringir chats de inteligência artificial,UK will ban children under 16 from social media and consider restricting artificial intelligence chats,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('under 16', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Queda de helicópteros no Rio deixa 6 mortos; cantor americano e YouTuber argentino estavam na lista de passageiros,Helicopter crash in Rio leaves 6 dead; American singer and Argentine YouTuber were on the passenger list,0.0,neutral,"[('Rio', 'GPE'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Argentine', 'NORP'), ('YouTuber', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quiz Copa do Mundo 2026: você consegue identificar estas camisas de seleções?,2026 World Cup Quiz: can you identify these national team shirts?,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup Quiz', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que 'sobrevivência milagrosa' de guia no Everest levanta questões sobre a indústria do turismo,Why Everest guide's 'miraculous survival' raises questions about tourism industry,0.0,neutral,"[('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que café de R$ 34 no Reino Unido revela sobre a turbulenta economia global,What £34 coffee in the UK reveals about the turbulent global economy,0.0,neutral,"[('34', 'MONEY'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Neymar, 10 e Vini Jr., 7: o que o número na camiseta da seleção revela sobre a história do Brasil na Copas","Neymar, 10 and Vini Jr., 7: what the number on the team's shirt reveals about Brazil's history in the World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('Neymar', 'ORG'), ('10', 'DATE'), ('Vini Jr.', 'PERSON'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Россия ночью нанесла удар по Киеву. Пострадала Киево-Печерская лавра,Russia attacked Kyiv at night. Kiev Pechersk Lavra was damaged,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Kiev Pechersk Lavra', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Что происходит вокруг Ормузского пролива после объявленной сделки США и Ирана,What's happening around the Strait of Hormuz after the announced US-Iran deal,0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Лондоне двух мужчин украинского происхождения признали виновными в поджогах имущества, связанного со Стармером","In London, two men of Ukrainian origin were found guilty of setting fire to property linked to Starmer.",0.0,neutral,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Киев и Харьков подверглись массированной атаке, погибли 10 человек","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Kyiv and Kharkov were subjected to a massive attack, 10 people were killed",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kharkov', 'PERSON'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Видео,Сделка США и Ирана: война окончена? | Видеоподкаст «Что это было?», Продолжительность 32,02","Video, US-Iran deal: is the war over? | Video podcast “What was that?”, Duration 32.02",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('32.02', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Футбол во время войны. Каково иранской сборной играть на чемпионате мира в США,Football during the war. What is it like for the Iranian team to play at the World Cup in the USA?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('USA', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Сын кронпринцессы Норвегии приговорен к четырем годам тюрьмы за изнасилование двух женщин,The son of the Crown Princess of Norway sentenced to four years in prison for raping two women,0.0,neutral,"[('the Crown Princess of', 'ORG'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('four years', 'DATE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Член экипажа задержанного в Британии танкера теневого флота России арестован за нарушение санкций,Crew member of Russian shadow fleet tanker seized in Britain arrested for violating sanctions,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Последняя схватка Месси и Роналду. Кто войдет в историю величайшим футболистом 21 века?,The last fight between Messi and Ronaldo. Who will go down in history as the greatest football player of the 21st century?,1.0,positive,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('the 21st century', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Швейцарцы на референдуме отклонили предложение антимигрантских партий ограничить рост населения,The Swiss rejected the proposal of anti-migrant parties to limit population growth in a referendum,1.0,positive,"[('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米・イラン、戦闘終結へ合意と発表　船は「エンジン始動」をとトランプ氏,US and Iran announce agreement to end hostilities; Trump urges ships to “start their engines”,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 米・イラン合意で不透明性は緩和、しかし課題山積,"[Commentary] U.S.-Iran deal eases uncertainty, but challenges remain",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本、強豪オランダとの初戦を引き分ける　勝ち点獲得,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Japan draws first match against powerhouse Netherlands, earns points",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Netherlands', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアがキーウ攻撃、世界遺産の大聖堂で火災　ウクライナとロシアで死傷者,"Russia attacks Kyiv, fire at world heritage cathedral, casualties in Ukraine and Russia",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本は今大会のダークホースになるか,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Will Japan be a dark horse for this tournament?,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英海兵隊がロシア「影の艦隊」の石油タンカーを拿捕　英仏海峡で,Royal Marines seize Russian 'Shadow Fleet' oil tanker in the English Channel,0.0,neutral,"[('Royal Marines', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,英海兵隊が作戦映像を公開、ロシア「影の艦隊」の石油タンカーを拿捕, 所要時間 0,44","Video, Royal Marines release footage of operation to seize oil tanker from Russia's 'Shadow Fleet', Duration 0,44",0.0,neutral,"[('Royal Marines', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), (""Shadow Fleet', Duration"", 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリスと日本、180億ポンド規模の投資計画で合意　両首脳がロンドンで会談,UK and Japan agree on £18 billion investment plan; two leaders meet in London,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('£18 billion', 'MONEY'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,スイスで「人口1000万人上限」を右派政党が提案、国民投票で否決,"Right-wing party proposes a ``10 million population cap'' in Switzerland, rejected in referendum",1.0,positive,"[('10 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 FIFA、ソマリアのアルタン審判に報酬全額支払いへ　アメリカが入国拒否,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] FIFA to pay full compensation to Somali referee Altan; US refuses entry,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Somali', 'NORP'), ('Altan', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani na Iran zafikia makubaliano ya kumaliza vita, Trump asema Mlango wa Bahari wa Hormuz utafunguliwa tena","Immediately, the United States and Iran reach an agreement to end the war, Trump says the Strait of Hormuz will be reopened",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini tarehe ya mazishi ya Ali Khamenei imetangazwa sasa?,Why is Ali Khamenei's funeral date announced now?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Ali Khamenei's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi FIFA inavyovuna mabilioni ya dola katika kila Kombe la Dunia,How FIFA reaps billions of dollars in every World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('billions of dollars', 'MONEY'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Vita ya  Marekani na Iran yaipa thamani gesi asilia Tanzania,The war between the United States and Iran puts the value of natural gas in Tanzania,-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Dirisha la usajili limefunguliwa rasmi EPL, klabu yako inahitaji nini kuongeza nguvu?","The registration window is officially open in the EPL, what does your club need to strengthen?",1.0,positive,"[('EPL', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Moshi unaoua kimya kimya,Smoke that kills silently,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Yote unayohitaji kufahamu kuhusu makubaliano ya Iran na Marekani,Everything you need to know about the Iran-US deal,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Arsenal na Liverpool vitani kwa Bouaddi,European Football Rumors: Arsenal and Liverpool in battle for Bouaddi,0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors: Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Bouaddi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Video,Tazama: Jinsi makomando wa Uingereza walivyoikamata meli ya mafuta ya Urusi, Muda 0,44","Video, Watch: How British commandos captured a Russian oil tanker, Time 0,44",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_15,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ratiba, msimamo na matokeo","World Cup 2026: Schedule, standings and results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,How Pakistan mediated a US-Iran agreement after more than 100 days of war,How Pakistan mediated a US-Iran agreement after more than 100 days of war,-1.0,negative,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('more than 100 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Record daily jump in DRC Ebola outbreak takes death toll to 178,Record daily jump in DRC Ebola outbreak takes death toll to 178,-1.0,negative,"[('daily', 'DATE'), ('DRC Ebola', 'ORG'), ('178', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Spain vs Cape Verde live: World Cup 2026,Spain vs Cape Verde live: World Cup 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Cape Verde', 'LOC'), ('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Ebola risk for World Cup is ‘extremely low’, but US is ready, experts say","Ebola risk for World Cup is ‘extremely low’, but US is ready, experts say",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Island surrounded by war’: Crimeans panic amid Ukrainian attacks,‘Island surrounded by war’: Crimeans panic amid Ukrainian attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Crimeans', 'NORP'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran, US agree tentative deal to ‘end war’: Your questions answered","Iran, US agree tentative deal to ‘end war’: Your questions answered",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Video shows man shot by Israeli drone while sitting with others in Gaza,Video shows man shot by Israeli drone while sitting with others in Gaza,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup racism monitor urges FIFA to remove VAR official over gesture,World Cup racism monitor urges FIFA to remove VAR official over gesture,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('VAR', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup day five: Spain face Cape Verde as Iran’s opener draws attention,World Cup day five: Spain face Cape Verde as Iran’s opener draws attention,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Cape Verde', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,UK Court of Appeal upholds ban on Palestine Action as ‘terrorist’ group,UK Court of Appeal upholds ban on Palestine Action as ‘terrorist’ group,-1.0,negative,"[('UK Court of Appeal', 'ORG'), ('Palestine Action', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Indian seafarers not to be deployed to conflict zones: Directorate General of Shipping,Indian seafarers not to be deployed to conflict zones: Directorate General of Shipping,-1.0,negative,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Indian LNG carrier Disha safely transits Strait of Hormuz,Indian LNG carrier Disha safely transits Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('LNG', 'ORG'), ('Disha', 'GPE'), ('Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia LIVE: 'Deep mistrust' in U.S. remains despite deal, says Iran's foreign ministry","West Asia LIVE: 'Deep mistrust' in U.S. remains despite deal, says Iran's foreign ministry",0.0,neutral,"[('West Asia LIVE', 'LOC'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Cockroach Janta Party founder Abhijeet Dipke slapped during protest in Jaipur,Cockroach Janta Party founder Abhijeet Dipke slapped during protest in Jaipur,0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janta Party', 'ORG'), ('Abhijeet Dipke', 'PERSON'), ('Jaipur', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Khan Sir got my brother murdered: Rival tutor Raushan Anand after bail from court in vandalism case,Khan Sir got my brother murdered: Rival tutor Raushan Anand after bail from court in vandalism case,0.0,neutral,"[('Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Raushan Anand', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,In Focus podcast | Can the new U.S.-Iran deal hold?,In Focus podcast | Can the new U.S.-Iran deal hold?,0.0,neutral,"[('Focus', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"India, Slovakia elevate ties to status of Comprehensive Partnership, says PM Modi","India, Slovakia elevate ties to status of Comprehensive Partnership, says PM Modi",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Slovakia', 'ORG'), ('Comprehensive Partnership', 'ORG'), ('PM Modi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,CID team visits Bengal Assembly in signature forgery probe,CID team visits Bengal Assembly in signature forgery probe,0.0,neutral,"[('Bengal Assembly', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Supreme Court stays High Court proceedings on challenges to new transgender law,Supreme Court stays High Court proceedings on challenges to new transgender law,0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,NCERT shades image of Indus Valley ‘dancing girl’ in new class 9 art textbook,NCERT shades image of Indus Valley ‘dancing girl’ in new class 9 art textbook,0.0,neutral,"[('NCERT', 'ORG'), ('Indus Valley', 'LOC'), ('9', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Oil prices fall and shares jump after US-Iran deal announced,Oil prices fall and shares jump after US-Iran deal announced,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Norwegian crown princess's son found guilty of two counts of rape,Norwegian crown princess's son found guilty of two counts of rape,0.0,neutral,"[('Norwegian', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Russian strikes kill 11 and set historic cathedral in Kyiv ablaze,Russian strikes kill 11 and set historic cathedral in Kyiv ablaze,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('11', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Brazil woman dies after rope-jumping instructors fail to attach cord,Brazil woman dies after rope-jumping instructors fail to attach cord,-1.0,negative,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US musician Oliver Tree dies in helicopter collision in Brazil,US musician Oliver Tree dies in helicopter collision in Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Oliver Tree', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,South Korea's Starbucks to shut for staff history lesson after backlash,South Korea's Starbucks to shut for staff history lesson after backlash,0.0,neutral,"[(""South Korea's"", 'GPE'), ('Starbucks', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'Spider-Man of Yemen' dies falling into volcanic crater,'Spider-Man of Yemen' dies falling into volcanic crater,0.0,neutral,"[('Spider-Man of', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Yemen', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Man apologises for making racist gesture at Korean in World Cup match,Man apologises for making racist gesture at Korean in World Cup match,0.0,neutral,"[('Korean', 'NORP'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,China detains two leaders of influential underground church,China detains two leaders of influential underground church,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_15,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,South African TV star arrested after allegedly kidnapping man in girlfriend dispute,South African TV star arrested after allegedly kidnapping man in girlfriend dispute,0.0,neutral,"[('South African', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iran War Live Updates: U.S.-Iran Framework Brings Relief, but Challenges Loom","Iran War Live Updates: U.S.-Iran Framework Brings Relief, but Challenges Loom",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates', 'EVENT'), ('Challenges Loom', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine Is About to Take a Big Step on a Long Road Toward the European Union,Ukraine Is About to Take a Big Step on a Long Road Toward the European Union,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('a Long Road Toward', 'ORG'), ('the European Union', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"After Russia Attacks Kyiv With Missiles and Drones, Historic Orthodox Cathedral Burns","After Russia Attacks Kyiv With Missiles and Drones, Historic Orthodox Cathedral Burns",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Drones', 'PERSON'), ('Historic Orthodox Cathedral Burns', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Quebec Left the Church and Became the World Leader in Assisted Dying,How Quebec Left the Church and Became the World Leader in Assisted Dying,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Britain Announces Social Media Ban for Children,Britain Announces Social Media Ban for Children,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain Announces', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Ukraine Uses A.I. to Knock Deadly Russian Drones Out of the Skies,How Ukraine Uses A.I. to Knock Deadly Russian Drones Out of the Skies,0.0,neutral,"[('A.I.', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Inside Colombia’s Never-Ending Drug War,Inside Colombia’s Never-Ending Drug War,-1.0,negative,"[('Never-Ending Drug War', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Son of Norway’s Crown Princess Is Convicted of Rape,Son of Norway’s Crown Princess Is Convicted of Rape,0.0,neutral,"[('Norway’s Crown Princess Is Convicted of Rape', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Many Iranians Express Relief Over Agreement to End the War,Many Iranians Express Relief Over Agreement to End the War,-1.0,negative,"[('Iranians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_15,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Switzerland Rejects Measure to Cap Its Population at 10 Million,Switzerland Rejects Measure to Cap Its Population at 10 Million,0.0,neutral,"[('Switzerland Rejects Measure', 'ORG'), ('10 Million', 'CARDINAL')]"
