Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué miles de personas salieron a protestar en Ucrania tras la destitución del ministro de Defensa,Why thousands of people came out to protest in Ukraine after the dismissal of the Defense Minister,0.0,neutral,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La FIFA confirma que evalúa posibles sanciones a Argentina por mostrar una pancarta de las Malvinas/Falklands tras el triunfo sobre Inglaterra,FIFA confirms that it is evaluating possible sanctions against Argentina for displaying a Falklands/Malvinas banner after the victory over England,1.0,positive,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Falklands/Malvinas', 'ORG'), ('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Crecer en un mundo de gigantes"": las personas que viven con síndrome de Laron en Ecuador (y por qué pueden ser clave para combatir la diabetes y el cáncer)","""Growing up in a world of giants"": people living with Laron syndrome in Ecuador (and why they can be key to fighting diabetes and cancer)",1.0,positive,"[('Laron', 'ORG'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Video,El padre que encontró el cuerpo de su hija entre los escombros 20 días después de los terremotos en Venezuela, Duración 1,40","Video,The father who found his daughter's body in the rubble 20 days after the earthquakes in Venezuela, Duration 1.40",0.0,neutral,"[('the rubble', 'DATE'), ('20 days', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('1.40', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"9 cosas que debes saber para entender ""La Odisea""","9 things you need to know to understand ""The Odyssey""",0.0,neutral,"[('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('The Odyssey', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Reino Unido pide a la FIFA investigar a Argentina después de que jugadores mostraran una pancarta de las Malvinas/Falklands tras la victoria sobre Inglaterra,UK asks FIFA to investigate Argentina after players display Malvinas/Falklands banner after victory over England,1.0,positive,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Malvinas/Falklands', 'ORG'), ('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Pasamos 17 años buscando la verdad"": la lucha de 3 hermanos por descubrir quién asesinó a su madre","""We spent 17 years looking for the truth"": the fight of 3 brothers to discover who murdered their mother",0.0,neutral,"[('17 years', 'DATE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cientos de incendios forestales ponen en alerta por mala calidad del aire a Canadá y EE.UU.,Hundreds of forest fires put Canada and the US on alert due to poor air quality.,0.0,neutral,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¡Tenemos una nueva app en BBC News Mundo! Descárgala,We have a new app on BBC News Mundo! Download it,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News Mundo', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La nueva especie de mono con labios naranjas que fue descubierta en el corazón de África,The new species of monkey with orange lips that was discovered in the heart of Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सोनम वांगचुक: इनोवेशन से बदलाव लाने वाले इंजीनियर, सिर्फ़ शिक्षा ही नहीं अपने इन कामों से भी कमाई शोहरत","Sonam Wangchuk: Engineer who brought change through innovation, earned fame not only through education but also through his work.",0.0,neutral,"[('Sonam', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,बुलेट ट्रेन प्रोजेक्ट में देरी पर जापान के पूर्व मंत्री ने भारत को ठहराया ज़िम्मेदार, कांग्रेस ने क्या कहा?","Live, Former Japanese minister held India responsible for the delay in Bullet Train project, what did Congress say?",0.0,neutral,"[('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Bullet Train', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इसरो से इतनी बड़ी संख्या में वैज्ञानिक इस्तीफ़ा क्यों दे रहे हैं? बदले गए इस्तीफ़ा स्वीकार करने के नियम,Why are such a large number of scientists resigning from ISRO? Changed rules for accepting resignations,0.0,neutral,"[('ISRO', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"आमिर ख़ान ने कहा, 'सोनम वांगचुक पर नहीं बनी थी थ्री इडियट्स',  भूख हड़ताल पर की ये टिप्पणी","Aamir Khan said, 'Three Idiots' was not made on Sonam Wangchuk, made this comment on hunger strike",0.0,neutral,"[('Aamir Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sonam Wangchuk', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,चलते हुए या सीढ़ियां चढ़ते समय सांस फूलना किन बीमारियों का लक्षण हो सकता है?,Which diseases can cause shortness of breath while walking or climbing stairs?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,रोहित शर्मा क्या लॉर्ड्स में खेलेंगे अपने करियर का आख़िरी मैच?,Will Rohit Sharma play the last match of his career at Lord's?,0.0,neutral,"[('Will Rohit Sharma', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,सोनम वांगचुक की भूख हड़ताल पर अंतरराष्ट्रीय मीडिया में ऐसी चर्चा,Such discussion in international media on Sonam Wangchuk's hunger strike,0.0,neutral,"[(""Sonam Wangchuk's"", 'LOC')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,होर्मुज़ स्ट्रेट पूरी तरह से बंद हो जाए तो क्या इन रास्तों से दुनिया का काम चल सकता है?,"If the Strait of Hormuz is completely closed, can the world survive through these routes?",0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,गुजरात के इस इलाके में शेर अचानक इंसानों पर इतने हमलावर क्यों हो गए हैं?,Why have lions suddenly become so aggressive on humans in this area of ​​Gujarat?,0.0,neutral,"[('​​Gujarat', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"छत्तीसगढ़: ई20 पेट्रोल से कार ख़राब होने का दावा, मारुति ने नई गाड़ी देने के आदेश को चुनौती देने की बात कही","Chhattisgarh: Claim of car being damaged due to E20 petrol, Maruti said to challenge the order of giving a new car.",0.0,neutral,"[('Maruti', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Com novo tarifaço de Trump e déficit fiscal crescente, Brasil chega à eleição mais importante do mundo em 2026 sem margem para erro, diz analista","With Trump's new tariff and growing fiscal deficit, Brazil reaches the most important election in the world in 2026 with no margin for error, says analyst",1.0,positive,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A reação do governo Lula ao novo tarifaço de Trump: 'Seguiremos sem viralatice',The Lula government's reaction to Trump's new tariff: 'We will continue without going viral',0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump fala em 'vulnerabilidades chocantes' do sistem eleitoral às vésperas das eleições de meio de mandato dos EUA,Trump talks about 'shocking vulnerabilities' in the electoral system on the eve of the US midterm elections,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que necropsias revelam sobre o risco de morte cardíaca entre fisiculturistas,What autopsies reveal about the risk of cardiac death among bodybuilders,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Lula 'priorizou próprio ego' e não 'negociou de boa fé': o ataque de ministro de Trump,Lula 'prioritized his own ego' and did not 'negotiate in good faith': Trump's minister's attack,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Minha mãe me deixou doente de propósito durante anos, até que um médico a desmascarou'",'My mother made me sick on purpose for years until a doctor exposed her',0.0,neutral,"[('years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Qual o impacto do tarifaço de Trump no Brasil? 'Deve ser restrito' e mostra 'limites do protecionismo americano', diz economista","What is the impact of Trump's tariffs on Brazil? 'It must be restricted' and shows 'limits of American protectionism', says economist",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'As Malvinas são argentinas': Reino Unido pede investigação e Argentina pode ser punida por faixa após a semifinal,'The Falklands are Argentine': United Kingdom calls for investigation and Argentina could be punished for banner after semi-final,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentine', 'NORP'), ('United Kingdom', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil é país que mais viu tarifas aumentarem desde que Trump voltou ao poder,Brazil is the country that has seen tariffs increase the most since Trump returned to power,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Sexo, estratégia e poder': como as mulheres moldam 'A Odisseia', o clássico de Homero dirigido por Christopher Nolan nos cinemas","'Sex, strategy and power': how women shape 'The Odyssey', Homer's classic directed by Christopher Nolan in theaters",0.0,neutral,"[('Homer', 'PERSON'), ('Christopher Nolan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Зеленский поручил исполнять обязанности министра обороны Украины Евгению Хмаре. Кто он такой?,Zelensky instructed Yevgeny Khmara to act as Minister of Defense of Ukraine. Who is he?,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Yevgeny Khmara', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Беларусь экспортировала в Россию рекордный объем бензина в июне. Грозит ли это дефицитом и ростом цен внутри страны?,Belarus exported a record volume of gasoline to Russia in June. Does this threaten a shortage and rising prices within the country?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('June', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Он придумал, как расколоть страну». В Украине разгорелся открытый конфликт между экс-министром обороны Федоровым и главкомом Сырским",“He figured out how to split the country.” An open conflict broke out in Ukraine between ex-Minister of Defense Fedorov and Commander-in-Chief Syrsky,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: при ракетном ударе по Одессе погибли два человека, среди пострадавших есть дети","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: two people were killed in a missile attack on Odessa, children were among the victims",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Odessa', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Мэр Лондона Садик Хан станет лордом,London Mayor Sadiq Khan to become Lord,0.0,neutral,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('Khan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Джей Ди Вэнс обвинил Израиль в «манипулировании» общественным мнением в США, чтобы продлить войну с Ираном","JD Vance accused Israel of ""manipulating"" public opinion in the US to prolong the war with Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('JD Vance', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Оператор телесуфлера обвинен в выигрыше около $100 тыс. на ставках на содержание речей Трампа,"Teleprompter operator accused of winning nearly $100,000 betting on the content of Trump's speeches",1.0,positive,"[('nearly $100,000', 'MONEY'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,США и Иран снова воюют? Текстовая версия подкаста «Что это было?» с иранистом Никитой Смагиным,Are the US and Iran at war again? Text version of the podcast “What was that?” with Iranist Nikita Smagin,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iranist', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Вечные страдания старой доброй Англии. Как страна переживает очередную футбольную трагедию,Eternal suffering of good old England. How the country is coping with another football tragedy,1.0,positive,"[('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Экс-глава компании-оператора платных автодорог Италии признан виновным в обрушении моста в Генуе,Former head of Italian toll road operator found guilty of Genoa bridge collapse,0.0,neutral,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('Genoa', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,バーナム氏、英労働党の新党首に就任へ　演説で新たな道筋を約束する見通し,"Burnham to become new leader of the UK Labor Party, expected to promise new path in speech",0.0,neutral,"[('the UK Labor Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 バーナム氏の政策について分かっていること　週明けに新たな英首相に,[Commentary] What we know about Mr. Burnham's policies: The new British Prime Minister will be appointed at the beginning of this week,0.0,neutral,"[('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('the beginning of this week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、米選挙システムに「衝撃的な脆弱性」あると主張　中間選挙を控え,Trump claims 'shocking vulnerabilities' in US election system ahead of midterm elections,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 FIFA、アルゼンチン代表の横断幕について「報告書を精査中」　フォークランド諸島領有権を主張,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] FIFA is ``examining the report'' regarding Argentina national team's banner, claiming sovereignty over the Falkland Islands",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the Falkland Islands', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゼレンスキー氏、ウクライナで高い支持のフェドロフ国防相を更迭　各地で抗議広がる,"Zelenskiy dismisses Defense Minister Fedorov, who has high support in Ukraine, sparking protests across the country",0.0,neutral,"[('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Fedorov', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,フランス議会、「支援を受けた死」法案を可決　一部条項は合憲性を判断へ,French parliament passes ``assisted dying'' bill; constitutionality of some provisions to be determined,0.0,neutral,"[('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,「私の政治の旅は終わり」スターマー英首相が下院で最後の質疑、野党からも称賛や冗談,"``My political journey is over'' British Prime Minister Starmer takes final question in the House of Commons, receives praise and jokes from opposition parties",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('the House of Commons', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシア軍がウクライナ各地攻撃、14人殺害　ウクライナ軍は黒海で石油タンカーを攻撃,"Russian troops attack various parts of Ukraine, killing 14 people; Ukrainian army attacks oil tanker in Black Sea",-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Black Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヘグセス氏、米軍でテストステロン欠乏症の検査を開始すると発言,Hegseth says he will begin testing for testosterone deficiency in the U.S. military,0.0,neutral,"[('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,世界25カ国・地域、アメリカより中国に好意的　米機関調査で初めて多数派に,25 countries and regions around the world are more favorable toward China than the United States; majority for the first time in a U.S. agency survey,-1.0,negative,"[('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yaendelea na mashambulizi dhidi ya Iran huku miundombinu ya Bandar Abbas ikilengwa","Directly, the United States continues its attacks against Iran while the infrastructure of Bandar Abbas is targeted",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Bandar Abbas', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini dunia inazidi kupendelea China kuliko Marekani?,Why is the world increasingly favoring China over the United States?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini wanawake wengi huficha dalili za ukomo wa hedhi?,Why do many women hide the symptoms of menopause?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wanasayansi wagundua sukari katika anga za mbali,Scientists discover sugar in deep space,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Inter Milan wanasuka mipango kumsajili Spence,European football rumors Friday: Inter Milan are making plans to sign Spence,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Inter Milan', 'ORG'), ('Spence', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kutoka vita hadi mazungumzo: Safari ngumu ya amani kati ya Wahouthi na Saudi Arabia,From war to dialogue: The difficult journey to peace between the Houthis and Saudi Arabia,0.0,neutral,"[('Houthis', 'NORP'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Hii ndiyo sababu yeye ni mfalme' – Messi alivyoiwezesha Argentina kufuzu fainali ya tatu ya Kombe la Dunia,'This is why he is king' - how Messi enabled Argentina to qualify for the third World Cup final,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, vitisho vya Trump vitaishinikiza Iran kurejea kwenye mazungumzo?",Will Trump's threats pressure Iran to return to negotiations?,0.0,neutral,"[('Will Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Kwa nini kipigo cha England kimezidisha maumivu ya kusubiri kwa miaka 60?,World Cup 2026: Why England's defeat has increased the pain of waiting for 60 years?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('England', 'PERSON'), ('60 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Kenya inapaswa kuwa na wasiwasi kuhusu kuongezeka kwa magenge ya wahuni?,Why should Kenya be concerned about the rise of gangs?,0.0,neutral,"[('Kenya', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Germany repeats call for EU force to replace UN peacekeepers in Lebanon,Germany repeats call for EU force to replace UN peacekeepers in Lebanon,1.0,positive,"[('Germany', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"US strikes destroy key bridges, tower in southern Iran","US strikes destroy key bridges, tower in southern Iran",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Gulf states come under Iranian fire as US strikes intensify,Gulf states come under Iranian fire as US strikes intensify,0.0,neutral,"[('Gulf', 'LOC'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"US attacks southern Iran, as Tehran hits Gulf countries: What’s the latest?","US attacks southern Iran, as Tehran hits Gulf countries: What’s the latest?",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Why is Pakistan’s Sindh province facing a major child HIV outbreak?,Why is Pakistan’s Sindh province facing a major child HIV outbreak?,0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Sindh', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,China’s Xi says AI ‘should not be a solo performance by a single country’,China’s Xi says AI ‘should not be a solo performance by a single country’,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Key takeaways from Donald Trump’s controversial speech on election security,Key takeaways from Donald Trump’s controversial speech on election security,0.0,neutral,"[('Donald Trump’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israeli settlers attack Sinjil town in occupied West Bank,Israeli settlers attack Sinjil town in occupied West Bank,-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Sinjil', 'PRODUCT'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,China rebukes UK over nationalisation of British Steel,China rebukes UK over nationalisation of British Steel,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('British Steel', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,IEA chief warns Strait of Hormuz crisis threatens global energy security,IEA chief warns Strait of Hormuz crisis threatens global energy security,-1.0,negative,"[('IEA', 'ORG'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The composer in mridangist Arun Prakash takes centre stage,The composer in mridangist Arun Prakash takes centre stage,0.0,neutral,"[('Arun Prakash', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Dates with devotion: The division in Puri’s Rath Yatra celebrations,Dates with devotion: The division in Puri’s Rath Yatra celebrations,0.0,neutral,"[('Puri', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Cricket World Cup - Will expansion lead to elevation?,Cricket World Cup - Will expansion lead to elevation?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cricket World Cup - Will', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Rot in recruitment runs deep,Rot in recruitment runs deep,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,‘The Odyssey’ review: Nolan’s epic palimpsest of destiny and design finds its way home,‘The Odyssey’ review: Nolan’s epic palimpsest of destiny and design finds its way home,0.0,neutral,"[('Nolan', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,SC to examine whether persons deleted from voter list in SIR can be denied welfare schemes,SC to examine whether persons deleted from voter list in SIR can be denied welfare schemes,0.0,neutral,"[('SC', 'ORG'), ('SIR', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Jantar Mantar protest LIVE: 'Will stay alive till July 20 at any cost', says Wangchuk","Jantar Mantar protest LIVE: 'Will stay alive till July 20 at any cost', says Wangchuk",0.0,neutral,"[('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON'), ('July 20', 'DATE'), ('Wangchuk', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Parliamentary panel on bill to remove PM, CMs defers adoption of report","Parliamentary panel on bill to remove PM, CMs defers adoption of report",0.0,neutral,"[('CMs', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,PM Modi flags off India’s first hydrogen-powered train,PM Modi flags off India’s first hydrogen-powered train,0.0,neutral,"[('PM Modi', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_17,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Beyond political reshuffles, renew education in India","Beyond political reshuffles, renew education in India",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US launches new strikes as Iran says civilian infrastructure hit,US launches new strikes as Iran says civilian infrastructure hit,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump alleges China meddled in 2020 election and questions voting security ahead of midterms,Trump alleges China meddled in 2020 election and questions voting security ahead of midterms,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('2020', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,More than 500 Rohingya vanished at sea - what happened?,More than 500 Rohingya vanished at sea - what happened?,0.0,neutral,"[('More than 500', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rohingya', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Japan relaxes royal succession rules - but ban on female emperors remains,Japan relaxes royal succession rules - but ban on female emperors remains,1.0,positive,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Philippines condemns monkey video on Chinese media as racist,Philippines condemns monkey video on Chinese media as racist,0.0,neutral,"[('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump Media to sell instant access to 'market-moving' social posts,Trump Media to sell instant access to 'market-moving' social posts,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,School bus crash kills at least 20 pupils in Uganda,School bus crash kills at least 20 pupils in Uganda,-1.0,negative,"[('at least 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uganda', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Canada fires prompt US air quality alerts as smoke blankets major cities,Canada fires prompt US air quality alerts as smoke blankets major cities,0.0,neutral,"[('Canada', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,China hits out at British Steel nationalisation,China hits out at British Steel nationalisation,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('British Steel', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Olympic cyclist admits to driving despite ban after crash that killed wife,Olympic cyclist admits to driving despite ban after crash that killed wife,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"‘Suddenly, I Was Free’: A Chinese Pastor’s Journey From Jail to the U.S.","‘Suddenly, I Was Free’: A Chinese Pastor’s Journey From Jail to the U.S.",0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Blazes Spread Near Paris, Extreme Heat Is Changing How France Fights Fires","As Blazes Spread Near Paris, Extreme Heat Is Changing How France Fights Fires",0.0,neutral,"[('Blazes Spread', 'ORG'), ('Paris', 'GPE'), ('Extreme Heat Is Changing', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"How Andy Burnham, ‘King of the North,’ Conquered U.K. Politics","How Andy Burnham, ‘King of the North,’ Conquered U.K. Politics",0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Dubai Migrant Worker Layoffs Reveal Costs of Middle East War,Dubai Migrant Worker Layoffs Reveal Costs of Middle East War,-1.0,negative,"[('Dubai', 'GPE'), ('Middle East War', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"He Was a Russian Political Survivor, Until the Masked Men Appeared","He Was a Russian Political Survivor, Until the Masked Men Appeared",0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the Masked Men Appeared', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Venezuela Earthquakes Force a Grim Homecoming for Migrants,Venezuela Earthquakes Force a Grim Homecoming for Migrants,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela Earthquakes Force', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Japan Passes New Law Banning Flag Desecration in Nationalist Push,Japan Passes New Law Banning Flag Desecration in Nationalist Push,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan Passes New Law Banning Flag Desecration', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Philippines Condemns AI Video Posted by Chinese State Media Depicting It as a Monkey,Philippines Condemns AI Video Posted by Chinese State Media Depicting It as a Monkey,0.0,neutral,"[('Philippines Condemns AI Video Posted', 'ORG'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Andy Burnham Becomes Britain’s New Prime Minister,How Andy Burnham Becomes Britain’s New Prime Minister,0.0,neutral,"[('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_17,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine’s Ousted Defense Minister Attacks the Military’s Old Guard,Ukraine’s Ousted Defense Minister Attacks the Military’s Old Guard,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
