Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué ha cambiado en la política de Trump hacia Venezuela desde su primer mandato (y cómo eso explica las actuales tensiones en el Caribe),What has changed in Trump's policy towards Venezuela since his first term (and how that explains the current tensions in the Caribbean),0.125,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Caribbean', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Nos golpearon y humillaron, nos impedían comer, beber e ir al baño"": las torturas que denuncian los prisioneros palestinos liberados por Israel","""They beat us and humiliated us, they prevented us from eating, drinking and going to the bathroom"": the torture denounced by Palestinian prisoners released by Israel",0.0,"[('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Philippe Aghion, premio Nobel de Economía, explica a BBC Mundo qué es la destrucción creativa y por qué cree que es indispensable para crecer","Philippe Aghion, Nobel Prize winner in Economics, explains to BBC Mundo what creative destruction is and why he believes it is essential for growth",0.25,"[('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Economics', 'ORG'), ('BBC Mundo', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Por favor, vengan. Los necesitamos, los extrañamos"": lo que la caída de visitantes a Las Vegas dice sobre el turismo en EE.UU. en la era Trump","'Please come. We need you, we miss you': What the drop in visitors to Las Vegas says about US tourism in the Trump era",0.0,"[('Las Vegas', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo nuestra nariz nos delata cuando estamos estresados (¡y no solo a los humanos!),How our nose gives us away when we're stressed (and not just to humans!),0.0,[]
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मेडागास्कर: सैन्य तख़्तापलट में 'जेन ज़ी' का ज़िक्र, कहां है यह देश और क्या है इसका इतिहास","Madagascar: 'Gen Z' mentioned in military coup, where is this country and what is its history",-0.1,[]
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,युद्धविराम समझौते के एक दिन बाद ही इसराइल की गोलीबारी में सात फ़लस्तीनियों की मौत","Live, seven Palestinians killed in Israeli firing a day after the ceasefire agreement",-0.03181818181818183,"[('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,उत्तर प्रदेश में जेल से कैसे क़ैदी और कर्मचारियों ने मिलकर निकाल लिए 52 लाख रुपये,How prisoners and staff together took out Rs 52 lakh from jail in Uttar Pradesh,-0.1,"[('52', 'CARDINAL'), ('Uttar Pradesh', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,रेयर अर्थ खनिजों और अफ़ग़ानिस्तान से हुई झड़पों पर चीन ने पाकिस्तान को दी यह सलाह,China gave this advice to Pakistan on rare earth minerals and clashes with Afghanistan,0.3,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मैथिली ठाकुर बीजेपी में हुईं शामिल, बिहार चुनाव लड़ने के सवाल पर यह बोलीं","Maithili Thakur joined BJP, said this on the question of contesting Bihar elections",0.0,"[('Thakur', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार में चुनाव आयोग के इस दावे पर उठ रहे हैं सवाल,Questions are being raised on this claim of Election Commission in Bihar,0.0,"[('Election Commission', 'ORG'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"एक कीड़ा जिससे हो रही है ख़तरनाक बीमारी, वैज्ञानिक भी परेशान","An insect is causing dangerous disease, even scientists are worried",-0.6,[]
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"अब पीएफ़ खाते से निकाल सकेंगे 'पूरा पैसा', ईपीएफ़ओ ने नियमों में ये बदलाव किए","Now you can withdraw 'full money' from PF account, EPFO ​​made these changes in the rules",0.35,"[('EPFO', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"सोना सवा लाख के पार, गोल्ड की डिमांड बढ़ने की ये है असल कहानी","Gold crosses Rs. 1.25 lakh, this is the real story of increase in demand for gold",0.2,"[('1.25', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que cada vez mais analistas falam em 'bolha' da inteligência artificial prestes a estourar,Why more and more analysts are talking about an artificial intelligence 'bubble' about to burst,0.13333333333333333,[]
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que são fintechs e por que governo Lula diz que elas devem pagar mais impostos,What are fintechs and why does the Lula government say they should pay more taxes,0.5,[]
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O aplicativo indiano que quer desafiar a supremacia do WhastApp,The Indian app that wants to challenge WhastApp's supremacy,0.2,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('WhastApp', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Militares anunciam tomada de poder em Madagascar após impeachment de presidente e onda de protestos,Military announces seizure of power in Madagascar after impeachment of president and wave of protests,-0.1,"[('Madagascar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,STF começa a julgar 'núcleo de desinformação' da tentativa de golpe: entenda quem são os réus e as acusações,STF begins to judge 'disinformation nucleus' of the coup attempt: understand who the defendants and the accusations are,0.0,"[('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como corpo de jovem encontrado após 8 anos enrolado em carpete foi identificado,How the body of a young man found after 8 years rolled up in carpet was identified,0.1,"[('8 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como nariz gelado 'denuncia' estresse em imagens com câmeras especiais,How a cold nose 'tells' stress in images with special cameras,-0.12142857142857141,[]
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como um professor de escola pública e uma parlamentar negra criaram o Dia do Professor há quase 80 anos,How a public school teacher and a black congresswoman created Teachers' Day almost 80 years ago,-0.08333333333333333,"[(""Teachers' Day"", 'EVENT')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como funciona a nova ferramenta do WhatsApp para resumir conversas com IA,How WhatsApp's new tool works to summarize conversations with AI,0.13636363636363635,"[('WhatsApp', 'ORG'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Зеленский лишил мэра Одессы украинского гражданства, сообщают источники Би-би-си. Труханова обвинили в том, что у него есть российский паспорт","Zelensky deprived the mayor of Odessa of Ukrainian citizenship, BBC sources report. Trukhanov was accused of having a Russian passport",0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Odessa of Ukrainian', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trukhanov', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: ООН обвинила Россию в ударе по гуманитарной колонне, в Харькове бомба попала в больницу","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: The UN accused Russia of attacking a humanitarian convoy; a bomb hit a hospital in Kharkov",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('UN', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Kharkov', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Военные заявили о захвате власти на Мадагаскаре. В администрации президента утверждают, что он остается на посту",The military announced the seizure of power in Madagascar. The presidential administration says he remains in office,-0.1,"[('Madagascar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,По России ударят американские «Томагавки»? | Подкаст «Что это было?», Продолжительность 27,54","Video, Will American Tomahawks hit Russia? | Podcast “What was that?”, Duration 27.54",0.0,"[('Will American Tomahawks', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Podcast', 'PERSON'), ('27.54', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп грозит дать Киеву Tomahawk, если Путин не закончит войну. Что могут изменить эти ракеты?",Trump threatens to give Kyiv a Tomahawk if Putin does not end the war. What can these missiles change?,0.0,"[('Kyiv a Tomahawk if', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Перемирие в Газе: боевики ХАМАС вернулись на улицы анклава; семьи погибших израильских заложников требуют возвращения тел родных,Truce in Gaza: Hamas militants return to the streets of the enclave; Families of dead Israeli hostages demand return of bodies of relatives,-0.2,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ФСБ завела дело о террористическом сообществе на Ходорковского и «Антивоенный комитет России»,The FSB opened a case of a terrorist community against Khodorkovsky and the Anti-War Committee of Russia,0.0,"[('FSB', 'ORG'), ('Khodorkovsky', 'ORG'), ('the Anti-War Committee', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Почему первое казино в Азербайджане строят рядом с мусульманскими святынями?,Why is the first casino in Azerbaijan being built next to Muslim shrines?,0.125,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Azerbaijan', 'GPE'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Охота за ближайшим механиком». Глава НАТО пошутил о российской подводной лодке, которая всплыла в Ла-Манше","""Hunt for the nearest mechanic."" The head of NATO joked about a Russian submarine that surfaced in the English Channel",0.0,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Microsoft прекратила бесплатную поддержку Windows 10. Что должны знать пользователи,Microsoft has ended free support for Windows 10. What users should know,0.4,"[('Microsoft', 'ORG'), ('Windows 10', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,イスラエルとパレスチナで緊張緩和と喜び……未来への期待は　BBC国際編集長, 所要時間 8,10","Video, Detente and joy in Israel and Palestine... Hope for the future, BBC International Editor-in-Chief, Duration 8,10",0.26666666666666666,"[('Detente', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Palestine', 'GPE'), ('BBC International', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ガザ停戦第1段階、中東に「歴史的夜明け」とトランプ氏　イスラエル人人質とパレスチナ人収監者の交換実現で,"First phase of ceasefire in Gaza marks a ``historic dawn'' in the Middle East, Trump says, as Israeli hostages and Palestinian prisoners are exchanged",0.08333333333333333,"[('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「中東和平を実現」　トランプ氏ら仲介国首脳、ガザ和平文書に署名, 所要時間 1,03","Video, ""Achieving peace in the Middle East"" Trump and other leaders of mediating countries sign Gaza peace document, time required 1,03",-0.0625,"[('the Middle East', 'LOC'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「中東に黄金時代が訪れる」　トランプ米大統領がイスラエル国会で演説, 所要時間 0,50","Video, ""A Golden Age Comes to the Middle East"" US President Trump Speech at the Israeli Parliament, Duration 0,50",0.15,"[('A Golden Age Comes to the Middle East"" US', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Trump Speech', 'PERSON'), ('the Israeli Parliament', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ハマスから解放された人質が家族と再会、抱き合い涙, 所要時間 1,11","Video, Hostages released from Hamas reunite with family, hug each other in tears, Duration 1,11",-0.125,"[('Hostages', 'PERSON'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「言葉に表せないほどうれしい」パレスチナ人収監者の釈放を祝うヨルダン川西岸地区, 所要時間 1,30","Video, 'Indescribably happy' West Bank celebrates release of Palestinian prisoner, Duration 1,30",0.8,"[('West Bank', 'GPE'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米中が追加の港湾使用料発効、貿易摩擦が再燃,"Additional port fees take effect between US and China, rekindling trade tensions",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、ウクライナへの長距離ミサイル供与を示唆　ゼレンスキー氏が近く訪米へ,Trump hints at providing long-range missiles to Ukraine; Zelenskyy to visit US soon,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskyy', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スポーツブランドは靴を片方でも売ってほしい、元陸上世界チャンピオンの夢と活動,"I want sports brands to sell at least one pair of shoes, the dreams and activities of a former track and field world champion",-0.15,"[('at least one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jeshi la Madagascar lasema limenyakua mamlaka - ripoti,Madagascar's army says it has seized authority - report,0.0,"[('Madagascar', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mkufu wa Nile ni nini? Na kwanini Sisi anampa Trump,What is the Nile necklace? And why is we giving Trump,0.0,"[('Nile', 'LOC'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais wa Madagascar asema 'nimejificha mahali salama' huku akionya kuhusu jaribio la mapinduzi,The president of Madagascar says 'I'm hiding in a safe place' while warning of a revolutionary attempt,0.5,"[('Madagascar', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Mashariki ya Kati 'itaangamia' bila taifa la Palestina, Mfalme wa Jordan aiambia BBC","The Middle East will 'perish' without the Palestinian nation, the king of Jordan tells the BBC",0.0,"[('The Middle East', 'LOC'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Jordan', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kipi kifuatacho Gaza baada ya kuachiliwa mateka?,What follows Gaza after the release of the captives?,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumanne: Man Utd na Crystal Palace wamtaka Bellingham,European football rumors Tuesday: Man utd and Crystal Palace want Bellingham,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Crystal Palace', 'FAC'), ('Bellingham', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Urusi: Tutaipatia Iran silaha za kijeshi inazohitaji,Russia: We will give Iran the military weapons it needs,-0.1,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, mateka wanaoachiliwa ni akina nani?",Who are the captives released?,0.0,[]
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, mabilionea wa teknolojia wanajiandaa na maangamizi ya akili mnemba (AI)?",Are technology billionaires preparing for the destruction of Mnemba (AI)?,0.0,"[('Mnemba', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_14,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi waganga Afrika Kusini wavyotumia waziwazi dawa haramu kutibu maradhi ya akili,How South African Physicians clearly use illegal drugs to treat mental illness,-0.125,"[('South African', 'NORP')]"
