Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El socialista demócrata Zohran Mamdani gana las elecciones en Nueva York y se convertirá en el alcalde más joven de la ciudad en un siglo,Democratic socialist Zohran Mamdani wins New York election and will become the city's youngest mayor in a century,0.21818181818181817,"[('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('a century', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Quién es el socialista Zohran Mamdani y cómo logró una improbable victoria que lo convertirá en el primer alcalde musulmán de Nueva York,Who is socialist Zohran Mamdani and how he achieved an improbable victory that will make him the first Muslim mayor of New York,0.19318181818181818,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los miles de adoptados por padres estadounidenses que ahora temen ser deportados a pesar de llevar décadas en EE.UU.,The thousands of adopted by American parents who now fear being deported despite having been in the United States for decades.,0.0,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Interceptan en el Atlántico un narcosubmarino que transportaba 1,7 toneladas de cocaína",A narco-submarine carrying 1.7 tons of cocaine is intercepted in the Atlantic,0.0,"[('1.7 tons', 'QUANTITY'), ('Atlantic', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,El momento en el que un león salva a una hiena preñada de una jauría de perros salvajes,The moment a lion saves a pregnant hyena from a pack of wild dogs,0.21666666666666667,[]
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ज़ोहरान ममदानी न्यूयॉर्क मेयर चुनाव जीते, ये पद पाने वाले पहले मुस्लिम होंगे","Zohran Mamdani wins New York mayor election, will be the first Muslim to get this post",0.22878787878787876,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Muslim', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,हारिस रऊफ़ पर दो मैचों का बैन और सूर्यकुमार यादव पर जुर्माना क्यों लगा?,Why was Haris Rauf banned for two matches and Suryakumar Yadav fined?,0.0,"[('Haris Rauf', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Suryakumar Yadav', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,मणिपुर में सुरक्षाबलों के साथ मुठभेड़ में चार उग्रवादियों की मौत, चुराचांदपुर में बंद","Live, four militants killed in encounter with security forces in Manipur, bandh in Churachandpur",-0.03181818181818183,"[('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Manipur', 'GPE'), ('Churachandpur', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,केवाईवी नहीं किया तो टोल पर फंस सकती है गाड़ी, समझिए केवाईवी की प्रक्रिया, अवधि 3,51","Video, If KYV is not done, the vehicle may get stuck at toll, understand the process of KYV, duration 3,51",0.0,"[('KYV', 'ORG'), ('KYV', 'ORG'), ('3,51', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सर क्रीक से कराची तक: पाकिस्तान और भारत अचानक युद्धाभ्यास क्यों कर रहे हैं?,From Sir Creek to Karachi: Why are Pakistan and India suddenly conducting maneuvers?,0.0,"[('Creek', 'PERSON'), ('Karachi', 'ORG'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,मालदीव: जब सेफ़ हाउस में छिपे राष्ट्रपति को बचाने गई थी भारतीय सेना,Maldives: When Indian Army went to save the President hiding in the safe house,0.5,"[('Indian Army', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"स्वदेशी यात्री विमान की उड़ान कितनी दूर, रूस से क्यों है उम्मीद?",How far will the indigenous passenger plane fly? Why is there hope from Russia?,0.45,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तेहरान का 'डे ज़ीरो': शहर के एक करोड़ लोगों के पास बचा है सिर्फ़ दो हफ़्ते का पानी,Tehran's 'Day Zero': 10 million people of the city have only two weeks of water left,0.0,"[('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('10 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('only two weeks', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तेज प्रताप से क्या आरजेडी को कुछ सीटों पर नुक़सान हो सकता है?,Can RJD suffer loss on some seats due to Tej Pratap?,-0.125,"[('RJD', 'PERSON'), ('Tej Pratap', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula diz que governo quer investigar operação 'desastrosa' no Rio: 'Houve matança',Lula says the government wants to investigate 'disastrous' operation in Rio: 'There was killing',-0.24999999999999997,"[('Lula', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Relatora vota por cassação de Cláudio Castro no TSE; o que acontece a partir de agora,Rapporteur votes to impeach Cláudio Castro from the TSE; what happens from now on,0.0,"[('Rapporteur', 'ORG'), ('Cláudio Castro', 'PERSON'), ('TSE', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Câmara aprova aumento da licença-paternidade; quais os benefícios da ampliação, segundo estudos","Chamber approves increase in paternity leave; what are the benefits of expansion, according to studies",0.0,"[('Chamber', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A história por trás de Silva, o sobrenome mais popular do Brasil","The story behind Silva, the most popular surname in Brazil",0.2333333333333333,"[('Silva', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quais os riscos econômicos se Brasil declarar facções criminosas como terroristas?,What are the economic risks if Brazil declares criminal factions as terrorists?,-0.1,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que 10 milhões de pessoas só têm água para mais duas semanas na capital do Irã,Why 10 million people only have water for two more weeks in Iran's capital,0.25,"[('10 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('two more weeks', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Shein proíbe venda de bonecas sexuais após indignação com aparência infantil dos produtos,Shein bans sale of sex dolls after outrage over childish appearance of products,-0.2,[]
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Tentei esticar ao máximo a pouca comida que tenho': os 40 milhões de americanos em risco de perder a ajuda que garante sua sobrevivência,'I tried to make the most of the little food I have': the 40 million Americans at risk of losing the aid that guarantees their survival,0.15625,"[('40 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que seguros residenciais contra desastres climáticos ainda são tão incomuns no Brasil?,Why is home insurance against weather disasters still so uncommon in Brazil?,0.8,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Год Трампа. Почему США пока не смогли убедить Россию закончить войну в Украине,Year of Trump. Why the United States has not yet been able to convince Russia to end the war in Ukraine,0.5,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как африканских женщин заманивают на российский завод по производству ударных дронов,How African women are lured to a Russian factory for the production of attack drones,0.0,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: власти сообщили об атаках дронов на Орел и Владимир","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: authorities reported drone attacks on Oryol and Vladimir",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Oryol', 'PERSON'), ('Vladimir', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Демократ-социалист Зохран Мамдани побеждает на выборах мэра Нью-Йорка — прогнозы,Democratic Socialist Zohran Mamdani Wins New York Mayoral Election - Predictions,0.21818181818181817,"[('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York Mayoral Election - Predictions', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Грузовой самолет разбился в США, число жертв растет","Cargo plane crashes in US, death toll rises",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как Трамп переделывает Белый дом по своему образу и подобию,How Trump is remaking the White House in his image,0.0,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Что происходит в Покровске? Украина говорит об успешных контрдействиях, Россия настаивает, что город в окружении","What's happening in Pokrovsk? Ukraine talks about successful counter-actions, Russia insists the city is surrounded",0.75,"[('Pokrovsk', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Лидер британской оппозиции призвала к увольнениям на Би-би-си из-за отредактированной речи Трампа,British opposition leader calls for BBC sackings over Trump's edited speech,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Дэвида Бекхэма посвятили в рыцари,David Beckham knighted,0.0,"[('David Beckham', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Атака с ножом в британском поезде: пресса недоумевает, почему подозреваемого не остановили раньше",Knife attack on British train: press wonders why suspect wasn't stopped sooner,0.0,"[('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米ニューヨーク市長選、民主党のマムダニ氏が当選確実に,Democrat Mamdani wins New York mayoral election,0.21818181818181817,"[('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,チェイニー元米副大統領が84歳で死去　対テロ戦争主導、トランプ氏と対立,"Former US Vice President Cheney dies at age 84, leading war on terror and confronting Trump",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Cheney', 'PERSON'), ('age 84', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,フィリピンで台風の大被害、少なくとも60人以上が死亡,"Typhoon devastates the Philippines, killing at least 60 people",-0.3,"[('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('at least 60', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー大統領、激戦地ポクロフスク近郊の前線部隊を視察,President Zelenskiy inspects front-line troops near fierce battleground Pokrovsk,0.1,"[('Zelenskiy', 'PERSON'), ('Pokrovsk', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ベッカム氏が「サー・デイヴィッド」に、英国王誕生日の叙勲で　作家イシグロ氏にも勲章,Mr. Beckham awards ``Sir David'' and author Ishiguro a decoration on the British King's birthday.,0.0,"[('Beckham', 'PERSON'), (""David''"", 'PERSON'), ('Ishiguro', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,仏当局、シーインなど米中オンライン小売大手を捜査　未成年がポルノにアクセスできる疑い,French authorities investigate major U.S.-China online retailers including Seein on suspicion of allowing minors to access pornography,0.03125,"[('French', 'NORP'), ('U.S.-China', 'PERSON'), ('Seein', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ハマスがイスラエルに1遺体を返還、人質と主張,"Hamas returns body to Israel, claims to be hostage",0.0,"[('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル軍の元法務トップ逮捕、パレスチナ人拘束者への「虐待映像」流出めぐり,Former Israeli military legal chief arrested over leaked footage of abuse of Palestinian detainees,0.03333333333333333,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英列車内での刺傷事件、32歳男性を殺人未遂などで起訴　直前の別件でも起訴,32-year-old man charged with attempted murder in stabbing incident on British train; also charged in separate case,-0.3,"[('32-year-old', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Maandamano Tanzania: Chadema 'yatangaza siku saba za maombolezo'","Live, Protests in Tanzania: Chadema 'announces seven days of mourning'",0.13636363636363635,"[('Protests', 'NORP'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('seven days', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Tuliwaona polisi waliowapiga risasi jamaa zetu',Protests in Tanzania: 'We saw the police who shot our relatives',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Meya mpya wa New York ameandikisha historia - lakini changamoto halisi zinamsubiri - Uchambuzi,The new mayor of New York has made history - but real challenges await him - Analysis,0.15757575757575756,"[('New York', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Uhusiano wa Marekani na Tanzania unapaswa kutazamwa upya' - Kamati ya Seneti Marekani,'The US-Tanzania relationship should be re-examined' - US Senate Committee,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Sijamuona mwanangu tangu Jumatano',Protests in Tanzania: 'I haven't seen my son since Wednesday',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatano: Real Madrid tayari kumuuza Vinicius,European Football Rumors Wednesday: Real Madrid ready to sell Vinicius,0.13333333333333333,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Madrid', 'GPE'), ('Vinicius', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Khamenei aweka masharti matatu kwa ushirikiano wa Iran na Marekani kuafikiwa,Khamenei sets three conditions for the cooperation between Iran and the United States to be achieved,0.0,"[('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Alipata pesa zake kwa kuuza ngamia na dhahabu. Sasa mbabe huyu wa kivita anadhibiti nusu ya Sudan,He earned his money by selling camels and gold. Now this warlord controls half of Sudan,-0.16666666666666666,"[('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,SADC yasema Uchaguzi wa Tanzania uligubikwa na dosari,SADC says Tanzania's election was marred by flaws,0.0,"[('SADC', 'PERSON'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_05,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Yesu pekee ndiye aliyeokoa ulimwengu, sio bikira Maria - Vatican","Only Jesus saved the world, not the virgin Mary - Vatican",0.0,"[('Jesus', 'PERSON'), ('Mary - Vatican', 'PERSON')]"
