Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Nuestra única misión es matar"": cómo la brutal milicia de Sudán perpetró una masacre en la ciudad de El Fasher",'Our only mission is to kill': how Sudan's brutal militia carried out a massacre in the city of El Fasher,-0.4375,"[('Sudan', 'GPE'), ('El Fasher', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""El caos ha desaparecido"": la nueva realidad en Texas tras la ofensiva de Trump contra los migrantes","""The chaos has disappeared"": the new reality in Texas after Trump's offensive against migrants",0.13636363636363635,"[('Texas', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los centenares de mujeres africanas llevadas bajo engaños a la República de Tartaristán para fabricar drones rusos,The hundreds of African women tricked into the Republic of Tatarstan to manufacture Russian drones,0.0,"[('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('the Republic of Tatarstan', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué se sabe de la nueva crisis carcelaria en Ecuador que dejó 27 presos ahorcados el fin de semana,What is known about the new prison crisis in Ecuador that left 27 prisoners hanged over the weekend,0.06818181818181818,"[('Ecuador', 'GPE'), ('27', 'CARDINAL'), ('the weekend', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,5 sencillos cambios en tu dieta que pueden mejorar tu salud intestinal,5 simple changes to your diet that can improve your intestinal health,0.0,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'जो हो रहा है उसे माफ़ नहीं किया जा सकता',  धर्मेंद्र को लेकर चल रही ख़बरों पर हेमा मालिनी ने जताई नाराज़गी","'What is happening cannot be forgiven', Hema Malini expressed displeasure over the news regarding Dharmendra",0.0,"[('Hema Malini', 'PERSON'), ('Dharmendra', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,धर्मेंद्र ने जब बीबीसी से कहा था, ""मैं मिट्टी का बेटा हूँ, अपनी जड़ों से दूर नहीं हो सकता"", अवधि 6,02","Video, When Dharmendra told BBC, ""I am a son of the soil, I cannot move away from my roots"", duration 6,02",0.0,"[('Dharmendra', 'PERSON'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('6,02', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,दिल्ली धमाके पर पीएम मोदी ने कहा- षड्यंत्रकारियों को बख़्शा नहीं जाएगा","Live, on Delhi blast, PM Modi said - conspirators will not be spared",0.13636363636363635,"[('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दिल्ली धमाका: एलएनजेपी अस्पताल में रात में कैसा था माहौल?,Delhi blast: How was the atmosphere in LNJP hospital at night?,0.0,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('LNJP', 'ORG'), ('night', 'TIME')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"दिल्ली: लाल क़िला मेट्रो स्टेशन के पास कार धमाके में 8 लोगों की मौत, अब तक क्या पता है","Delhi: 8 people killed in car blast near Lal Qila metro station, what is known so far",0.0,"[('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Lal Qila', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार में दूसरे चरण का मतदान, ये वोटर साबित होंगे निर्णायक","Second phase of voting in Bihar, these voters will prove to be decisive",0.0,"[('Second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'मैं तीन बार गिरा और संभला': लाल क़िला मेट्रो स्टेशन के पास कार धमाके के चश्मदीदों ने क्या देखा,'I fell three times and recovered': What eyewitnesses saw of the car blast near Red Fort metro station,0.05,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Red Fort', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"अमेज़न के जंगल धीरे-धीरे मर रहे हैं, क्यों है  दुनिया के लिए ख़तरे की घंटी","Amazon forests are slowly dying, why is this an alarm bell for the world",-0.30000000000000004,"[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,एक महिला की पलकों में मिली 250 जूँ,250 lice found in a woman's eyelashes,0.0,"[('250', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump, metas e legado: o discurso de Lula na COP30 em 3 pontos","Trump, goals and legacy: Lula's speech at COP30 in 3 points",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O erro do IBGE que 'mudou o signo' da maioria dos brasileiros — e foi tirado do ar após alerta da BBC,The IBGE error that 'changed the sign' of most Brazilians — and was taken off the air after a warning from the BBC,0.5,"[('IBGE', 'ORG'), ('Brazilians', 'NORP'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A destruição da Amazônia continua: ainda há tempo para salvá-la?,The destruction of the Amazon continues: is there still time to save it?,0.0,"[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"COP30, geradores e diesel: como reunião sobre o clima em Belém será movida a petróleo","COP30, generators and diesel: how the climate meeting in Belém will be powered by oil",0.0,"[('Belém', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O 'roubo' transatlântico que mudou a história de Belém e da Amazônia,The transatlantic 'robbery' that changed the history of Belém and the Amazon,0.0,"[('Amazon', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O antes e o depois do tornado que destruiu 90% de cidade no Paraná,The before and after of the tornado that destroyed 90% of the city in Paraná,0.0,"[('90%', 'PERCENT'), ('Paraná', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As revelações do chefão da quadrilha cibernética que deixou um rastro de destruição,The revelations of the leader of the cyber gang that left a trail of destruction,0.0,[]
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que dois diretores da BBC renunciaram ao mesmo tempo e o que isso tem a ver com Trump?,Why did two BBC directors resign at the same time and what does this have to do with Trump?,0.0,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O adolescente fã de Sherlock Holmes que viralizou em foto 'misteriosa' na cena do roubo do Louvre,The teenage Sherlock Holmes fan who went viral in a 'mysterious' photo at the scene of the Louvre robbery,0.0,"[('Holmes', 'PERSON'), ('Louvre', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: ФСБ заявила о попытке угона МиГ-31 с «Кинжалом»","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: FSB announced an attempt to hijack a MiG-31 with a Kinzhal",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kinzhal', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Букеровскую премию 2025 года получил Дэвид Солой за роман «Плоть»,David Soloy wins the 2025 Man Booker Prize for his novel Flesh,0.3,"[('David Soloy', 'PERSON'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('Flesh', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Убиты за то, что они алавиты». Религиозные меньшинства в Сирии рассказывают о расправах после падения режима Асада",“Killed because they are Alawites.” Religious minorities in Syria speak of massacres since the fall of Assad's regime,-0.1,"[('Alawites', 'GPE'), ('Syria', 'GPE'), ('Assad', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В туристическом районе Нью-Дели при взрыве автомобиля погибли восемь человек,Eight people killed in car bombing in New Delhi tourist area,-0.03181818181818183,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('New Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Подозреваемый в подрыве «Северного потока» экс-офицер ВСУ говорит, что в Италии на него давят, пытаясь добиться признания","The ex-AFU officer suspected of blowing up the Nord Stream says that in Italy they are putting pressure on him, trying to get a confession.",0.0,"[('the Nord Stream', 'FAC'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Глава Совета Би-би-си извинился перед парламентом, Трамп угрожает корпорации судебным иском","The head of the BBC Council apologized to Parliament, Trump threatens the corporation with legal action",0.15000000000000002,"[('the BBC Council', 'ORG'), ('Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Видео,Видео: гендиректор Би-би-си уходит в отставку на фоне скандала с речью Трампа, Продолжительность 6,16","Video,Video: BBC director general resigns amid Trump speech scandal, Duration 6.16",0.05000000000000002,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('6.16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В тюрьме в Эквадоре обнаружили десятки повешенных заключенных,Dozens of hanged prisoners found in Ecuador prison,0.0,"[('Dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп встретился в Вашингтоне с лидером Сирии аш-Шараа. Тот вошел в Белый дом через боковую дверь,Trump met in Washington with Syrian leader al-Sharaa. He entered the White House through a side door.,0.0,"[('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('al-Sharaa', 'PERSON'), ('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Иране беспрецедентная засуха, Тегерану грозит эвакуация","Iran faces unprecedented drought, Tehran faces evacuation",0.6,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,シリア暫定大統領がホワイトハウス訪問、対IS国際有志連合にも参加へ,Syria's interim president visits the White House and joins the international coalition against IS,0.0,"[('Syria', 'GPE'), ('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米上院、つなぎ予算案を可決　政府閉鎖が数日以内に終わる可能性,U.S. Senate passes bridge budget bill; government shutdown could end within days,0.0,"[('U.S. Senate', 'ORG'), ('days', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,インド・デリーの世界遺産近くで車両が爆発、少なくとも8人死亡,"At least 8 people killed in car explosion near world heritage site in Delhi, India",-0.13333333333333333,"[('At least 8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、BBCを訴えると警告　演説映像の編集めぐり,Trump threatens to sue BBC over editing of speech video,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ルーヴル美術館の盗難事件、謎の「ソフト帽の男」が話題に　探偵ファンの10代と判明,"The mysterious ``man in a fedora'' becomes a hot topic after the Louvre Museum theft incident, revealed to be a teenager who is a detective fan",0.125,"[('the Louvre Museum', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,BBCの会長とニュース部門CEOが辞任　トランプ氏のドキュメンタリー番組の編集めぐり,BBC chairman and news CEO resign over editing of Trump documentary,0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,台風26号、フィリピン直撃　約140万人が避難し死者2人を確認,"Typhoon No. 26 hits the Philippines, approximately 1.4 million people evacuated, 2 confirmed dead",-0.06666666666666667,"[('Typhoon No', 'EVENT'), ('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('approximately 1.4 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 BBCの「地殻変動」　会長ら辞任で上層部の亀裂あらわに,"[Commentary] BBC's ""tectonic shift""; chairman and others resign, exposing cracks in upper management",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,BBC会長とニュース責任者が辞任　問題はどこに, 所要時間 4,04","Video, BBC chairman and news chief resign; what's the problem? Duration 4,04",0.0,"[('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Trump atishia kuishtaki BBC","Directly, Trump threatens to sue the BBC",0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Rais Samia anatupiwa lawama?,Why is President Samia being blamed?,0.0,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Elon Musk: Tajiri anayeishi kimasikini,Elon Musk: Rich living in poverty,0.375,[]
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Israel haitaki vikosi vya Uturuki Gaza?,Why Israel does not want Turkish forces in Gaza?,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Turkish', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wajue marais wa Afrika walioshinda kwa zaidi ya asilimia 90,Know the African presidents who won by more than 90 percent,0.25,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('more than 90 percent', 'PERCENT')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: City, Madrid zamgombania Szoboszlai","European Football Rumors: City, Madrid vying for Szoboszlai",0.0,"[('European Football Rumors:', 'ORG'), ('Madrid', 'GPE'), ('Szoboszlai', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Heche na viongozi wengine wa CHADEMA waachiwa kwa dhamana Tanzania,Heche and other leaders of CHADEMA were released on bail in Tanzania,-0.125,"[('Heche', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini viongozi wawili wa BBC wamejiuzulu kwa wakati mmoja?,Why have two BBC leaders resigned at the same time?,0.0,"[('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mdukuzi wa mitandao aliyesakwa sana na FBI afichua siri za kundi lililoacha uharibifu,A hacker wanted by the FBI reveals the secrets of a group that left destruction,0.0,"[('FBI', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_11,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nini mustakabali wa Tanzania baada ya maandamano?,What is the future of Tanzania after the protests?,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
