Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Me da miedo lo que voy a ver allá dentro"": BBC Mundo visita la morgue improvisada de Los Silos, donde los cadáveres se acumulan al aire libre tras los terremotos en Venezuela","""I'm afraid of what I'm going to see in there"": BBC Mundo visits the improvised morgue of Los Silos, where corpses accumulate in the open air after the earthquakes in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC Mundo', 'ORG'), ('Los Silos', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El mapa satelital que muestra la magnitud de la destrucción en La Guaira, la zona más afectada por los terremotos de Venezuela","The satellite map showing the magnitude of the destruction in La Guaira, the area most affected by the earthquakes in Venezuela",1.0,positive,"[('La Guaira', 'FAC'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,3 factores que explican por qué se derrumbaron tantos edificios en La Guaira por el terremoto en Venezuela,3 factors that explain why so many buildings in La Guaira collapsed due to the earthquake in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('La Guaira', 'FAC'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""¡Un milagro!"": el extraordinario rescate de Hernán, el hombre que estuvo 8 días bajo los escombros tras los terremotos en Venezuela","""A miracle!"": the extraordinary rescue of Hernán, the man who spent 8 days under the rubble after the earthquakes in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('Hernán', 'ORG'), ('8 days', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Gasté US$6.000 en un viaje para ver el Mundial y me dejaron tirado en la puerta del estadio""","""I spent US$6,000 on a trip to see the World Cup and they left me stranded at the stadium door""",0.0,neutral,"[('6,000', 'MONEY'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El Vaticano excomulga a los obispos rebeldes del grupo de los lefebvrianos y advierte a sus miles de seguidores,The Vatican excommunicates the rebellious bishops of the Lefebvrian group and warns their thousands of followers,-1.0,negative,"[('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('Lefebvrian', 'NORP'), ('thousands', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El vuelo de la tragedia: los 146 deportados por EE.UU. el mismo día de los terremotos que acabaron bajo los escombros en Venezuela,The flight of tragedy: the 146 deported by the US on the same day as the earthquakes that ended up under the rubble in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('146', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('the same day', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Lo cuidaré como una madre hasta que aparezca mi hermana"": habla con la BBC la tía del niño de 2 años que fue rescatado seis días después de los terremotos en Venezuela","""I will take care of him like a mother until my sister appears"": the aunt of the 2-year-old boy who was rescued six days after the earthquakes in Venezuela speaks to the BBC",0.0,neutral,"[('2-year-old', 'DATE'), ('six days', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Cómo es Residencia, el fascinante hotel para científicos en uno de los lugares más extremos del mundo","What is Residencia like, the fascinating hotel for scientists in one of the most extreme places in the world",0.0,neutral,"[('Residencia', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quiénes son los lefebvrianos, el grupo ultraconservador excomulgado por el Vaticano luego de desafiar al papa León XIV ordenando a 4 obispos","Who are the Lefebvrians, the ultraconservative group excommunicated by the Vatican after challenging Pope Leo XIV by ordaining 4 bishops",0.0,neutral,"[('Lefebvrians', 'NORP'), ('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('Pope', 'PERSON'), ('Leo XIV', 'PERSON'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"तुर्की ने कहा- इसराइल नए दुश्मन की तलाश में है, लेकिन हम डरेंगे नहीं","Turkey said- Israel is looking for a new enemy, but we will not be afraid",0.0,neutral,"[('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,प्रधानमंत्री नरेंद्र मोदी अब न्यूज़ीलैंड के दौरे पर जाएंगे","Live, Prime Minister Narendra Modi will now visit New Zealand",0.0,neutral,"[('Narendra Modi', 'PERSON'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इंस्टाग्राम में छिपी एक भयानक दुनिया का पर्दाफ़ाश- बीबीसी पड़ताल,A terrifying world hidden in Instagram exposed - BBC investigation,0.0,neutral,"[('Instagram', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'ओडिया किताब में 'निंबूड़ा-निंबूड़ा', हम्पी को बताया कोणार्क मंदिर', स्कूली किताबों की ग़लतियों पर घिरी ओडिशा सरकार","'Nimbooda-Nimbooda' in Odia book, Hampi described as Konark Temple, Odisha government surrounded by mistakes in school books",0.0,neutral,"[(""Nimbooda-Nimbooda'"", 'ORG'), ('Hampi', 'PERSON'), ('Konark Temple', 'PERSON'), ('Odisha', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ब्रिटेन की महिला का दावा: भारत यात्रा के बाद उनके दिमाग़ में पाए गए 38 परजीवी,British woman claims: 38 parasites found in her brain after trip to India,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('38', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ईरान: मोजतबा ख़ामेनेई क्या अपने पिता के अंतिम संस्कार में शामिल होंगे, जानिए क्या है करबला से तेहरान तक तैयारी","Iran: Will Mojtaba Khamenei attend his father's funeral, know what are the preparations from Karbala to Tehran",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Will Mojtaba Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Karbala', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पेड़ गिरने से 11 साल के बच्चे की मौत का मामला, क्या चेतावनियों को किया गया नज़रअंदाज़?","Case of 11 year old child's death due to falling of a tree, were warnings ignored?",-1.0,negative,"[('11 year old', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बॉम्बे हाई कोर्ट ने कहा, 'लोगों को भारत सरकार का ग़ुलाम बनाया जा रहा है, विरोध करने पर केस दर्ज किए जा रहे हैं'","Bombay High Court said, 'People are being made slaves of the Government of India, cases are being registered for protesting'",0.0,neutral,"[('Bombay High Court', 'ORG'), ('the Government of India', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"रूस तेल बेचता था लेकिन ख़ुद ही तेल संकट में कैसे घिरा, पंपों पर लंबी क़तारें, भारत का भी ज़िक्र","Russia used to sell oil but how did it itself get into oil crisis, long queues at the pumps, India also mentioned.",-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सैयद अता हसनैन कौन हैं, जो ख़ामेनेई के अंतिम संस्कार में करेंगे भारत का प्रतिनिधित्व","Who is Syed Ata Hasnain, who will represent India at Khamenei's funeral?",0.0,neutral,"[('Syed Ata Hasnain', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"O que Flávio prometeu a Trump caso seja eleito sobre Pix, Mercosul e redes sociais","What Flávio promised Trump if he is elected about Pix, Mercosul and social media",0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Mercosul', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como é o necrotério improvisado onde cadáveres se acumulam a céu aberto após terremotos na Venezuela: 'estou com medo do que vou encontrar lá',What the improvised morgue looks like where corpses pile up in the open after earthquakes in Venezuela: 'I'm scared of what I'll find there',0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que Nordeste é a região do Brasil com mais risco de terremoto,Why the Northeast is the region of Brazil with the highest risk of earthquakes,0.0,neutral,"[('Northeast', 'LOC'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,8 dos 10 países mais populosos do mundo não estão na Copa. Por quê?,8 of the 10 most populous countries in the world are not in the World Cup. Why?,0.0,neutral,"[('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Venezuelano é resgatado vivo após 8 dias sob escombros de terremoto: 'Resgate tecnicamente mais difícil',Venezuelan is rescued alive after 8 days under earthquake rubble: 'Technically more difficult rescue',0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('8 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Casamento de Taylor Swift: tudo sobre a provável cerimônia em NY,Taylor Swift's wedding: everything about the likely ceremony in NY,0.0,neutral,"[(""Taylor Swift's"", 'PERSON'), ('NY', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Briga entre Michelle e Flávio abala plano bolsonarista para eleger Senado 'anti-STF'?,Fight between Michelle and Flávio undermines Bolsonaro's plan to elect 'anti-STF' Senate?,0.0,neutral,"[('Michelle', 'PERSON'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Papa excomunga bispos de grupo católico ultraconservador que reza missa em latim e com padre de costas: como é o movimento no Brasil,Pope excommunicates bishops from ultraconservative Catholic group that says Mass in Latin with the priest turned away: what the movement is like in Brazil,0.0,neutral,"[('Pope', 'PERSON'), ('Catholic', 'NORP'), ('Latin', 'LANGUAGE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Qual a distância entre Lula e Flávio Bolsonaro nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,What is the distance between Lula and Flávio Bolsonaro in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O voo da tragédia: os 146 deportados pelos EUA no dia dos terremotos que ficaram sob os escombros na Venezuela,The flight of tragedy: the 146 deported by the USA on the day of the earthquakes who were left under the rubble in Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('146', 'CARDINAL'), ('the day', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: число жертв удара по Киеву, нанесенного в четверг, увеличилось до 30","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: the number of victims of the attack on Kyiv on Thursday increased to 30",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Лукашенко помиловал 32 человека, его сын Николай получил диплом Пекинского университета. Главное в Беларуси за неделю","Lukashenko pardoned 32 people, his son Nikolai received a diploma from Peking University. The main things in Belarus in a week",0.0,neutral,"[('Lukashenko', 'PERSON'), ('32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nikolai', 'PERSON'), ('Peking University', 'ORG'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Семь дней и миллионы скорбящих: как проходят похороны убитого верховного лидера Ирана Али Хаменеи?,Seven days and millions of mourners: how is the funeral of the assassinated Supreme Leader of Iran Ali Khamenei going?,0.0,neutral,"[('Seven days', 'DATE'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Supreme', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ali Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Свадьба Тейлор Свифт и Трэвиса Келси: как развивались их отношения,The wedding of Taylor Swift and Travis Kelsey: how their relationship developed,0.0,neutral,"[('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Travis Kelsey', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Ватикан: последователей ультраконсервативного движения SSPX будут отлучать от церкви,Vatican: Followers of the ultra-conservative SSPX movement will be excommunicated,0.0,neutral,"[('SSPX', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Нормализует советскую военную эстетику»: британские политики призывают убрать «Машу и Медведя» со стриминговых сервисов,“Normalizes Soviet military aesthetics”: British politicians call for Masha and the Bear to be removed from streaming services,0.0,neutral,"[('Soviet', 'NORP'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Masha', 'PERSON'), ('Bear', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Прокуратура Германии заявила, что за взрывами «Северного потока» стояло украинское государство",German prosecutors said that the Ukrainian state was behind the Nord Stream explosions,0.0,neutral,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Nord Stream', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Украина наносит удары по российским центрам космической связи. Зачем?,Ukraine attacks Russian space communications centers. For what?,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Я в Европу не поеду». Новая система учета приезжающих в ЕС приводит к хаосу, утверждают авиакомпании и туристы","“I won’t go to Europe.” New EU travel registration system is causing chaos, say airlines and tourists",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('EU', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Бывший глава спецслужб Кыргызстана Камчыбек Ташиев осужден за попытку переворота, но избежал тюрьмы","Former head of Kyrgyzstan's special services Kamchybek Tashiev was convicted of attempting a coup, but avoided prison",0.0,neutral,"[('Kyrgyzstan', 'GPE'), ('Kamchybek Tashiev', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴェネズエラ地震発生から8日、生存者を倒壊した建物から救出,"8 days after Venezuela earthquake, survivors rescued from collapsed building",0.0,neutral,"[('8 days', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアのキーウ空爆、死者少なくとも30人に　「最大規模の攻撃」と市長,At least 30 killed in Russia's airstrike on KiV; mayor calls it 'largest attack',-1.0,negative,"[('At least 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('KiV', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ロシアの攻撃、キーウの集合住宅を破壊　BBCが現地報告, 所要時間 1,27","Video, Russian attack destroys apartment complex in Kiv, BBC reports on the ground, Duration 1,27",-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kiv', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴァチカン、世界的なカトリック教会分派の信者らを破門　異例の厳しい対応,Vatican excommunicates members of a worldwide sect of the Catholic Church in an unusually harsh response,0.0,neutral,"[('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('the Catholic Church', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イングランドとウェールズのパブ、午前5時まで営業可能に　イングランド対メキシコ戦に合わせ,[2026 Men's World Cup] Pubs in England and Wales to be open until 5am for England vs. Mexico match,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Wales', 'GPE'), ('5am', 'TIME'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,北京・最高層ビルの小型機衝突、操縦者の「個人的理由」が原因と　中国当局が発表,Chinese authorities say pilot's ``personal reasons'' were the cause of small plane crash into Beijing's tallest building,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,コウモリに顔に乗られ、狂犬病で死亡　カナダの11歳少年,11-year-old boy in Canada dies of rabies after getting hit in the face by a bat,0.0,neutral,"[('11-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、北米貿易協定の16年延長を拒否　現在の内容では応じないと,US rejects 16-year extension of North American trade agreement,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('16-year', 'DATE'), ('North American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米政府が140人以上を飛行機でヴェネズエラへ強制送還……その数時間後に地震、大勢が行方不明に,"The U.S. government deports more than 140 people to Venezuela by plane... hours later, an earthquake leaves many missing.",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('more than 140', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシア、キーウに大規模なミサイル・ドローン攻撃、少なくとも13人死亡,Massive missile and drone attack on Russia's Kiv kills at least 13 people,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('at least 13', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Lissu aiomba mahakama, DPP amlipe fidia kwa kuchelewesha shauri siku 139","Directly, Lissu asked the court, the DPP to pay him compensation for delaying the case for 139 days",0.0,neutral,"[('Lissu', 'ORG'), ('DPP', 'ORG'), ('139 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Binadamu wa siku zijazo watakuwa na muonekano na sura gani?,What will the human of the future look like?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Marekani bado inaitumia ndege hii ya kivita ya B-52 miaka 70 baadaye?,Why is the US still using this B-52 fighter jet 70 years later?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('B-52', 'PRODUCT'), ('70 years later', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Lissu afika Mahakama ya Rufani, marejeo ya kesi ya uhaini yasikilizwa leo","Lissu arrives at the Court of Appeal, references to the treason case will be heard today",0.0,neutral,"[('Lissu', 'ORG'), ('the Court of Appeal', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ifahamu teknolojia mpya inatoa matumaini kwa wanaume walioambiwa hawana uwezo wa kuzalisha,Know that new technology gives hope to men who were told they were unable to produce,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi makubaliano ya sekta ya afya kati ya Marekani na nchi za Afrika yalivyozua maoni yanayokinzana,How the health sector agreement between the United States and African countries created conflicting opinions,-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kuanzia Tehran hadi Najaf: Tunachojua kuhusu mazishi ya Ali Khamenei,From Tehran to Najaf: What we know about Ali Khamenei's funeral,0.0,neutral,"[('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Najaf', 'GPE'), (""Ali Khamenei's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Tetesi za soka: Man United yamtaka Baleba, Arsenal yaongeza nguvu kwa Guimaraes","Football rumours: Man United want Baleba, Arsenal add strength to Guimaraes",0.0,neutral,"[('Baleba', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Afrika Kusini na Ghana zakumbwa na mvutano wa kidiplomasia kuhusu mauaji ya raia wa Ghana,South Africa and Ghana experienced diplomatic tension over the killing of Ghanaian citizens,-1.0,negative,"[('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Ghana', 'GPE'), ('Ghanaian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_03,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"UFO ni nini na je, sayansi iko karibu kujibu kitendawili chake?",What is a UFO and is science close to answering its riddle?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Four killed in Ukraine a day after deadliest Russian attacks this year,Four killed in Ukraine a day after deadliest Russian attacks this year,-1.0,negative,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('this year', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,UN warns likelihood of ‘extreme weather events’ as El Nino set to intensify,UN warns likelihood of ‘extreme weather events’ as El Nino set to intensify,-1.0,negative,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('El Nino', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"$500m for Trump, access for Pakistan: How a crypto-diplomatic bet paid off","$500m for Trump, access for Pakistan: How a crypto-diplomatic bet paid off",0.0,neutral,"[('500', 'MONEY'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"EU lawmaker investigating surveillance hacked by Israeli spyware, report says","EU lawmaker investigating surveillance hacked by Israeli spyware, report says",-1.0,negative,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran’s Khamenei funeral: Which world leaders are attending?,Iran’s Khamenei funeral: Which world leaders are attending?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Seven pro-Palestine protesters convicted of misdemeanour charges in US,Seven pro-Palestine protesters convicted of misdemeanour charges in US,0.0,neutral,"[('Seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Ukraine strike hits Belgorod, causing fire and power outages","Ukraine strike hits Belgorod, causing fire and power outages",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Belgorod', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,David vs Goliath: Cape Verde face Argentina in World Cup last-32 clash,David vs Goliath: Cape Verde face Argentina in World Cup last-32 clash,0.0,neutral,"[('David vs Goliath', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('World Cup last-32', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Man holding Tibetan flag dies after setting himself on fire outside UN,Man holding Tibetan flag dies after setting himself on fire outside UN,0.0,neutral,"[('Tibetan', 'NORP'), ('UN', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,At least 40 killed in passenger bus crash in southwest Pakistan,At least 40 killed in passenger bus crash in southwest Pakistan,-1.0,negative,"[('At least 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"How Benoy Behl, master of low-light photography, captured Ajanta’s murals","How Benoy Behl, master of low-light photography, captured Ajanta’s murals",0.0,neutral,"[('Benoy Behl', 'PERSON'), ('Ajanta’s', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ellyse Perry and Ashleigh Gardner — linchpins of an imperious Aussie machine,Ellyse Perry and Ashleigh Gardner — linchpins of an imperious Aussie machine,0.0,neutral,"[('Perry', 'PERSON'), ('Ashleigh Gardner', 'PERSON'), ('Aussie', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The Himalayas as a battleground of belief,The Himalayas as a battleground of belief,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,How the Blues found a home in Meghalaya,How the Blues found a home in Meghalaya,0.0,neutral,"[('Blues', 'LOC'), ('Meghalaya', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Bijayini Satpathy’s Trikāyā questions the gendered body,Bijayini Satpathy’s Trikāyā questions the gendered body,0.0,neutral,"[('Bijayini Satpathy’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"‘When all else fails, people still repose their trust in the judiciary’: INDIA bloc leaders in letter to CJI","‘When all else fails, people still repose their trust in the judiciary’: INDIA bloc leaders in letter to CJI",-1.0,negative,"[('CJI', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Ram temple donation theft: RSS calls incident ‘unfortunate’, urges patience and strict action","Ram temple donation theft: RSS calls incident ‘unfortunate’, urges patience and strict action",0.0,neutral,"[('RSS', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Places of Worship Act does not bar acquisition of religious sites for public purpose, says Allahabad HC","Places of Worship Act does not bar acquisition of religious sites for public purpose, says Allahabad HC",0.0,neutral,"[('Allahabad HC', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,DMK MLA Anitha Radhakrishnan arrested over objectionable remarks against Tamil Nadu CM Vijay,DMK MLA Anitha Radhakrishnan arrested over objectionable remarks against Tamil Nadu CM Vijay,0.0,neutral,"[('DMK', 'ORG'), ('Anitha Radhakrishnan', 'PERSON'), ('Tamil Nadu CM Vijay', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Supreme Court refuses to stay bail granted to Sonam Raghuvanshi in honeymoon murder case,Supreme Court refuses to stay bail granted to Sonam Raghuvanshi in honeymoon murder case,0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Sonam Raghuvanshi', 'PERSON'), ('honeymoon murder', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"France records 2,025 excess deaths at peak of heatwave as Europe braces for more extreme weather","France records 2,025 excess deaths at peak of heatwave as Europe braces for more extreme weather",-1.0,negative,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('2,025', 'CARDINAL'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"On the Strait of Hormuz, BBC finds seized ships and shark fishermen as uneasy calm returns","On the Strait of Hormuz, BBC finds seized ships and shark fishermen as uneasy calm returns",0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Venezuela quake survivor pulled out alive after eight days,Venezuela quake survivor pulled out alive after eight days,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('eight days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,At least 32 dead after overcrowded bus plunges into ravine in Pakistan,At least 32 dead after overcrowded bus plunges into ravine in Pakistan,0.0,neutral,"[('At least 32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Instagram running ads promoting child sexual abuse material in India, BBC finds","Instagram running ads promoting child sexual abuse material in India, BBC finds",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Taylor Swift's rumoured wedding celebrations begin with star-studded New York event,Taylor Swift's rumoured wedding celebrations begin with star-studded New York event,0.0,neutral,"[(""Taylor Swift's"", 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Iran begins public mourning for Ayatollah killed in February,Iran begins public mourning for Ayatollah killed in February,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ayatollah', 'PERSON'), ('February', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,A mayor in Japan announced her maternity leave - and got the whole country talking,A mayor in Japan announced her maternity leave - and got the whole country talking,0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'Most massive' Russian attack on Kyiv kills at least 30,'Most massive' Russian attack on Kyiv kills at least 30,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kyiv', 'PERSON'), ('at least 30', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_03,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Bomb blast at Damascus cafe kills nine, Syrian state media say","Bomb blast at Damascus cafe kills nine, Syrian state media say",-1.0,negative,"[('Damascus', 'GPE'), ('nine', 'CARDINAL'), ('Syrian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Russia Hammers Ukraine’s Capital in Deadly Attacks,Russia Hammers Ukraine’s Capital in Deadly Attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Can the World’s Largest Stadium Explain the Global Economy?,Can the World’s Largest Stadium Explain the Global Economy?,0.0,neutral,"[('the World’s Largest Stadium Explain', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Hopes for Investment in Iran Would Break With Decades of History,U.S. Hopes for Investment in Iran Would Break With Decades of History,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Iran Prepares to Bury Supreme Leader, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, Killed at Iran War’s Outset","Iran Prepares to Bury Supreme Leader, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, Killed at Iran War’s Outset",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Ayatollah Ali Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Iran War’s', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Court Investigates Spanish Police Chief, Heaping Pressure on Prime Minister","Court Investigates Spanish Police Chief, Heaping Pressure on Prime Minister",0.0,neutral,"[('Spanish', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Bomb Explodes at Damascus Cafe, Killing at Least 6","Bomb Explodes at Damascus Cafe, Killing at Least 6",-1.0,negative,"[('Bomb Explodes', 'PERSON'), ('Damascus Cafe, Killing at Least 6', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Dutch and U.K. Governments Apologize for Their Roles in Forced Adoptions,Dutch and U.K. Governments Apologize for Their Roles in Forced Adoptions,0.0,neutral,"[('Dutch', 'NORP'), ('U.K.', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,India and Japan Expand Defense and Economic Ties,India and Japan Expand Defense and Economic Ties,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Japan Expand Defense and Economic Ties', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,An Aerial View of Disaster at a Venezuela Housing Project,An Aerial View of Disaster at a Venezuela Housing Project,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_07_03,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,9 Buddhist Monks Killed After Boy Crashes Truck Into Procession,9 Buddhist Monks Killed After Boy Crashes Truck Into Procession,-1.0,negative,"[('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('Buddhist', 'NORP')]"
