Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Elecciones en Perú: Keiko Fujimori y Roberto Sánchez se disputan voto a voto el conteo de boletas en busca de la presidencia,Elections in Peru: Keiko Fujimori and Roberto Sánchez dispute vote by vote the counting of ballots in search of the presidency,0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Xi Jinping visita a Kim Jong-un: cuál es el origen de la relación de amor y odio entre China y Corea del Norte,Xi Jinping visits Kim Jong-un: what is the origin of the love-hate relationship between China and North Korea,0.0,neutral,"[('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Trump les pide a Israel e Irán que dejen de ""dispararse"" luego de que ambos países se atacaran mutuamente por primera vez desde el alto el fuego de abril",Trump tells Israel and Iran to stop 'shooting' after both countries attack each other for the first time since April ceasefire,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('April', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Guía visual: así son los 16 estadios del Mundial de México, EE.UU. y Canadá","Visual guide: these are the 16 World Cup stadiums in Mexico, the USA and Canada",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""El Mundial no es para nosotros, es para ellos"": el enfado de los fans a los que no conceden visas para ir a EE.UU. a ver el torneo","""The World Cup is not for us, it is for them"": the anger of fans who are not granted visas to go to the US to watch the tournament",0.0,neutral,"[('The World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Decenas de muertos y heridos por un fuerte terremoto de magnitud 7,8 en el sur de Filipinas que obligó a emitir alertas de tsunami",Dozens killed and injured by a strong 7.8 magnitude earthquake in the southern Philippines that forced tsunami warnings to be issued,-1.0,negative,"[('Dozens', 'CARDINAL'), ('7.8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Bishkek, la moderna capital de Kirguistán que está demoliendo su imponente arquitectura soviética","Bishkek, the modern capital of Kyrgyzstan that is demolishing its imposing Soviet architecture",0.0,neutral,"[('Bishkek', 'ORG'), ('Kyrgyzstan', 'GPE'), ('Soviet', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Las señoritas de Avignon"", la obra más polémica de Picasso que sigue generando debate un siglo después","""The Young Ladies of Avignon"", Picasso's most controversial work that continues to generate debate a century later",0.0,neutral,"[('The Young Ladies of Avignon', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Picasso', 'PERSON'), ('a century later', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Si tuviera dinero, me iría del país"": cómo la inseguridad y la inestabilidad política son los factores que más motivan a los votantes en las elecciones en Perú","""If I had money, I would leave the country"": how insecurity and political instability are the factors that most motivate voters in the elections in Peru",0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Quiénes son Roberto Sánchez y Keiko Fujimori y qué puede decidir la carrera por presidir el inestable Perú,Who are Roberto Sánchez and Keiko Fujimori and what can decide the race to preside over unstable Peru,0.0,neutral,"[('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,जनरल नरवणे चीन पर बोले- पीएम मोदी ने सही कहा था भारत ने एक इंच ज़मीन भी नहीं गंवाई,General Naravane said on China - PM Modi was right that India did not lose even an inch of land.,0.0,neutral,"[('General Naravane', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,इंडिया गठबंधन की बैठक के बाद क्या बोले तेजस्वी यादव?","What did Tejashwi Yadav say after the live, India alliance meeting?",0.0,neutral,"[('Tejashwi Yadav', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी' बनाने से पहले अभिजीत दीपके क्या कर रहे थे,What was Abhijeet Deepke doing before forming 'Cockroach Janata Party'?,0.0,neutral,"[('Abhijeet Deepke', 'PERSON'), (""Cockroach Janata Party'"", 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,आप कहां रहते हैं? इस सवाल पर क्यों ठहर जाते हैं इस गांव के लोग,Where do you live? Why do the people of this village stop on this question?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ईरानी सेना ने कहा वो इसराइल पर हमले रोक रही है, लेकिन साथ ही दी एक चेतावनी","Iranian army said it is stopping attacks on Israel, but also gave a warning",-1.0,negative,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वैभव सूर्यवंशी बोले, 'मुझे सिर्फ़ क्रिकेट नहीं खेलना,10-20 साल डॉमिनेट करना है'","Vaibhav Suryavanshi said, 'I don't just want to play cricket, I want to dominate for 10-20 years'",0.0,neutral,"[('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), (""10-20 years'"", 'DATE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ट्रंप ने क्यों बीच में छोड़ दिया इंटरव्यू, पत्रकार को कहा 'बेईमान और बेवकूफ़'","Why did Trump leave the interview midway, called the journalist 'dishonest and stupid'",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,कांग्रेस के लिए आज होने वाली इंडिया गठबंधन की बैठक कितनी अहम?,How important is the India Alliance meeting to be held today for Congress?,0.0,neutral,"[('India Alliance', 'GPE'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"टीएमसी पार्षदों के इस्तीफ़े और गिरफ़्तारी का सिलसिला, आख़िर नेताओं को किसका है डर?","A series of resignations and arrests of TMC councilors, after all what are the leaders afraid of?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,जेन ज़ी आंदोलन के सवाल पर भारत आए नेपाल के विदेश मंत्री ने कही ये बात,"Nepal's Foreign Minister, who came to India on the question of Gen Z movement, said this",0.0,neutral,"[(""Nepal's"", 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Gen Z', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,PEC da Liberdade ou Escravidão? O que pode mudar no regime de trabalho por hora proposto por Flávio Bolsonaro para barrar fim da 6x1,PEC of Freedom or Slavery? What could change in the hourly work regime proposed by Flávio Bolsonaro to stop the end of 6x1,0.0,neutral,"[('PEC', 'ORG'), ('Slavery', 'ORG'), ('hourly', 'TIME'), ('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('6x1', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que Xi Jinping visita a Coreia do Norte — e o que está em jogo na disputa com a Rússia,Why Xi Jinping visits North Korea — and what's at stake in the dispute with Russia,0.0,neutral,"[('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Já basta': o temor de Trump de que nova troca de ataques entre Israel e Irã atrapalhe negociações entre EUA e iranianos para fim da guerra,'Enough is enough': Trump's fear that a new exchange of attacks between Israel and Iran will hinder negotiations between the US and Iranians to end the war,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Eleições no Peru: Keiko Fujimori lidera com pequena vantagem sobre Sánchez em contagem apertada com resultado ainda incerto,Elections in Peru: Keiko Fujimori leads with a small advantage over Sánchez in a tight count with the result still uncertain,0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Sánchez', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Melhor que qualquer 'hacker' humano: o que é o novo modelo de inteligência artificial que assusta o sistema financeiro,Better than any human 'hacker': what is the new artificial intelligence model that scares the financial system,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"O que se sabe sobre terremoto de magnitude 7,8 que atingiu as Filipinas e causou alerta de tsunami e destruição",What is known about the 7.8 magnitude earthquake that hit the Philippines and caused a tsunami warning and destruction,-1.0,negative,"[('7.8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como a Copa do Mundo de futebol expõe a relação tensa entre seus três países-sede,How football's World Cup exposes the tense relationship between its three host countries,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que mulheres vivem mais do que os homens?,Why do women live longer than men?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Super El Niño: os gráficos que mostram por que ele pode ser o fenômeno mais extremo em décadas — e quais seus efeitos,Super El Niño: the graphics that show why it could be the most extreme phenomenon in decades — and what its effects are,0.0,neutral,"[('Super El Niño', 'PERSON'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Укрепить режим и сдержать Россию: зачем лидер КНР Си Цзиньпин полетел в Северную Корею?,Strengthen the regime and contain Russia: why did Chinese leader Xi Jinping fly to North Korea?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Борьба мира и войны на выборах в Армении: партия Пашиняна набрала почти 50% голосов,The struggle between peace and war in the elections in Armenia: Pashinyan’s party gained almost 50% of the votes,0.0,neutral,"[('Armenia', 'GPE'), ('almost 50%', 'PERCENT')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Выборы президента в Перу грозят тупиком в подсчетах. И не впервые,The presidential election in Peru is threatening a deadlock in the counting. And not for the first time,0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: удар по поезду в Крыму «существенно осложняет» попытки мирных переговоров, заявили в Кремле","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Attack on train in Crimea 'significantly complicates' attempts at peace talks, Kremlin says",-0.3333,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Crimea', 'ORG'), ('Kremlin', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Кристиан Эриксен пришел в сознание после того, как упал в обморок во время товарищеского матча Дания-Украина",Christian Eriksen regained consciousness after collapsing during the Denmark-Ukraine friendly,0.0,neutral,"[('Christian Eriksen', 'PERSON'), ('Denmark', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Иран и Израиль обменялись ударами впервые с момента прекращения огня,Iran and Israel exchanged blows for the first time since the ceasefire,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Мощное землетрясение на юге Филиппин унесло жизни 19 человек,Powerful earthquake in southern Philippines kills 19 people,-1.0,negative,"[('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('19', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Армении завершились парламентские выборы. В стране их называют судьбоносными,Parliamentary elections have ended in Armenia. In the country they are called fateful,0.0,neutral,"[('Armenia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,На мессе папы римского в Мадриде собралось более миллиона верующих,More than a million believers gathered at the Pope's Mass in Madrid,0.0,neutral,"[('More than a million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Madrid', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп готовит новую торговую войну со всем миром. На этот раз предлог — защита трудящихся,Trump is preparing a new trade war with the whole world. This time the pretext is the protection of workers,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イスラエル、イランによるミサイル攻撃に報復,Israel retaliates against Iranian missile attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、米NBCインタビューをいきなり打ち切る　「仕組まれた選挙」めぐるやりとりの後,Trump abruptly ends NBC interview after exchange over ``rigged election'',0.0,neutral,"[('NBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,フィリピン南部沖で地震、死傷者多数　沿岸部で複数の建物倒壊,"Earthquake off the southern coast of the Philippines leaves many dead and injured, and multiple buildings collapse along the coast",0.0,neutral,"[('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イラン代表チーム、メキシコに到着　米国とビザ問題で揺れるなか,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Iran national team arrives in Mexico amidst turmoil over visa issues with the US,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ支える英仏独首脳、ロシアとの和平協議に5条件示す,"UK, France, and Germany leaders supporting Ukraine offer five conditions for peace talks with Russia",1.0,positive,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ラミー英副首相、ヴァンス米副大統領に「間違いだ」と伝えたと　英学生刺殺事件めぐる発言について,"British Deputy Prime Minister Lamy says he told US Vice President Vance that it was a mistake, regarding his comments regarding the British student stabbing incident",0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Lamy', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Vance', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,【解説】米株式市場はAIバブルの中にあるのか　崩壊の可能性は？, 所要時間 1,32","Video, [Commentary] Is the US stock market in an AI bubble? Is there a possibility of it bursting? , time required 1,32",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('AI', 'GPE'), ('1,32', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,遭難したエヴェレストの山岳ガイド、6日後に救出　氷をかじって生き延びたと, 所要時間 2,03","Video, Mount Everest mountain guide rescued after 6 days, survives by chewing on ice, Duration 2,03",1.0,positive,"[('Mount Everest', 'LOC'), ('6 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,プーチン氏、ゼレンスキー氏との会談は「意味がない」　戦争終結のための対面協議を拒否,"Putin's meeting with Zelensky is 'meaningless', rejects face-to-face talks to end war",-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,習氏、7年ぶりに北朝鮮を訪れ金氏と会談へ　どんなことが話し合われるのか,Mr. Xi visits North Korea for the first time in 7 years to meet with Mr. Kim. What will be discussed?,0.0,neutral,"[('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('7 years', 'DATE'), ('Kim', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Tunasitisha mashambulizi dhidi ya Israel, lakini tutaanza tena iwapo Israel itaishambulia Lebanon - Iran","Directly, We stop the attacks against Israel, but we will start again if Israel attacks Lebanon - Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Unajua ukubwa wa dola trilioni moja? Mifano 7 ya utajiri 'wa kufuru' wa Elon Musk,Do you know the size of one trillion dollars? 7 examples of Elon Musk's 'blasphemous' wealth,0.0,neutral,"[('one trillion dollars', 'MONEY'), ('7', 'CARDINAL'), (""Elon Musk's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"'Lazima uwe mwongo, na mjinga,' Trump alisema, akiinuka na kuondoka","'You must be a liar, and an idiot,' Trump said, getting up and walking away",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Urafiki au kujiimarisha: Kwanini Xi Jinping anazuru Korea Kaskazini?,Friendship or strengthening: Why is Xi Jinping visiting North Korea?,0.0,neutral,"[('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Simulizi za Waafrika waliotekwa vitani Ukraine,Narratives of Africans captured in the war in Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Africans', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kuanzia kuuawa kwa Khamenei hadi tishio la Trump ''kuingamiza Iran"": Matukio 10 muhimu ya siku 100 za kwanza za vita",From Khamenei's assassination to Trump's threat to 'destroy Iran': 10 key events of the first 100 days of war,-1.0,negative,"[('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('the first 100 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ziara ya Rais Samia Urusi: Tulichojifunza na maswali mapya,President Samia's visit to Russia: What we learned and new questions,0.0,neutral,"[('Samia', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Iran yasema haina makubaliano rasmi ya kusitisha mapigano na Marekani,Iran says it does not have an official ceasefire agreement with the United States,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini uhusiano kati ya Iran na UAE unaelekea kuwa mgogoro mkali?,Why does the relationship between Iran and the UAE tend to be a bitter conflict?,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, wanawake huwa na huruma kuliko wanaume?",Are women more compassionate than men?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Armenian PM Pashinyan declares victory in parliamentary elections,Armenian PM Pashinyan declares victory in parliamentary elections,1.0,positive,"[('Armenian PM Pashinyan', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Could ex-ISIL fighters be used against Iran, as a Russian official claimed?","Could ex-ISIL fighters be used against Iran, as a Russian official claimed?",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran and Israel bomb each other: Is the ceasefire over?,Iran and Israel bomb each other: Is the ceasefire over?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Pashinyan’s pro-Europe party wins Armenia election,Pashinyan’s pro-Europe party wins Armenia election,1.0,positive,"[('pro-Europe', 'ORG'), ('Armenia', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Philippines earthquake kills 15, prompts tsunami fears: All to know","Philippines earthquake kills 15, prompts tsunami fears: All to know",-1.0,negative,"[('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,China’s Xi Jinping arrives in North Korea on rare state visit,China’s Xi Jinping arrives in North Korea on rare state visit,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Israel’s strikes on Iran expose Trump’s failure to restrain Netanyahu,Israel’s strikes on Iran expose Trump’s failure to restrain Netanyahu,-1.0,negative,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Netanyahu', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Asia’s stock markets dive amid Iran-Israel conflict, Wall Street jitters","Asia’s stock markets dive amid Iran-Israel conflict, Wall Street jitters",-1.0,negative,"[('Asia', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Ukraine, Russia trade fire as Zelenskyy allies back call for direct talks","Ukraine, Russia trade fire as Zelenskyy allies back call for direct talks",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskyy', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"New York stabbing, Kansas City shooting raise World Cup security concerns","New York stabbing, Kansas City shooting raise World Cup security concerns",0.0,neutral,"[('New York', 'GPE'), ('Kansas City', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Application window for verification and re-evaluation of answer papers remained fully functional, says CBSE","Application window for verification and re-evaluation of answer papers remained fully functional, says CBSE",1.0,positive,"[('CBSE', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,NEET-UG 2026 retest: IAF to transport question papers for June 21 entrance examination,NEET-UG 2026 retest: IAF to transport question papers for June 21 entrance examination,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('June 21', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Trinamool Congress leader and Falta candidate Jahangir Khan arrested near Nepal border,Trinamool Congress leader and Falta candidate Jahangir Khan arrested near Nepal border,0.0,neutral,"[('Trinamool Congress', 'ORG'), ('Falta', 'GPE'), ('Jahangir Khan', 'PERSON'), ('Nepal', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia war LIVE: Iran ends military operations against Israel, warns of harsher attacks if strikes on Lebanon persist","West Asia war LIVE: Iran ends military operations against Israel, warns of harsher attacks if strikes on Lebanon persist",-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Anti-encroachment drive turns violent in Kolkata,Anti-encroachment drive turns violent in Kolkata,0.0,neutral,"[('Kolkata', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Allahabad HC upholds POCSO conviction; reaffirms child victim’s sole testimony sufficient if credible,Allahabad HC upholds POCSO conviction; reaffirms child victim’s sole testimony sufficient if credible,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Pinarayi Vijayan likens Revanth Reddy’s political temperament to Hitler over HYDRAA remark,Pinarayi Vijayan likens Revanth Reddy’s political temperament to Hitler over HYDRAA remark,0.0,neutral,"[('Revanth Reddy', 'PERSON'), ('Hitler', 'PERSON'), ('HYDRAA', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Northern lights in India? Here’s how to see Auroras tonight,Northern lights in India? Here’s how to see Auroras tonight,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Auroras', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Tamil Nadu CM Vijay plays chess with Grandmaster Praggnanandhaa,Tamil Nadu CM Vijay plays chess with Grandmaster Praggnanandhaa,0.0,neutral,"[('Tamil Nadu CM Vijay', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,​Testing times: On India’s GDP growth data,​Testing times: On India’s GDP growth data,1.0,positive,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,At least 32 dead after major earthquake strikes southern Philippines,At least 32 dead after major earthquake strikes southern Philippines,0.0,neutral,"[('At least 32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Rare footage captured of Great White shark in Mediterranean Sea,Rare footage captured of Great White shark in Mediterranean Sea,1.0,positive,"[('Great White', 'FAC'), ('Mediterranean Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Armenia's pro-West government wins election despite Russian pressure,Armenia's pro-West government wins election despite Russian pressure,1.0,positive,"[('Armenia', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Knicks' long-awaited NBA run electrifies NYC, with Trump set to attend key game","Knicks' long-awaited NBA run electrifies NYC, with Trump set to attend key game",0.0,neutral,"[('Knicks', 'ORG'), ('NBA', 'ORG'), ('NYC', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Zelensky's close European allies set out five conditions for peace talks,Zelensky's close European allies set out five conditions for peace talks,1.0,positive,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('five', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump abruptly ends NBC interview after clash over 'rigged election' claim,Trump abruptly ends NBC interview after clash over 'rigged election' claim,0.0,neutral,"[('NBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'A World Cup for them not us': Fans' anger at US travel bans and visa restrictions,'A World Cup for them not us': Fans' anger at US travel bans and visa restrictions,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Malawians repatriated from South Africa amid xenophobia concerns,Malawians repatriated from South Africa amid xenophobia concerns,0.0,neutral,"[('Malawians', 'NORP'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Stock markets fall on tech plunge and renewed Middle East attacks,Stock markets fall on tech plunge and renewed Middle East attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Middle East', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Peru election result close as vote counting continues,Peru election result close as vote counting continues,0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Live Updates: Iran Signals It Will Halt Strikes Against Israel After Hours of Attacks,Live Updates: Iran Signals It Will Halt Strikes Against Israel After Hours of Attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Hours', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Nikol Pashinyan Wins Re-election in Armenia,Nikol Pashinyan Wins Re-election in Armenia,1.0,positive,"[('Nikol Pashinyan Wins Re-election', 'PERSON'), ('Armenia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,At Least 32 Dead After Earthquake and Landslide in the Philippines,At Least 32 Dead After Earthquake and Landslide in the Philippines,0.0,neutral,"[('At Least 32', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Artisanal or Exploitative? Unraveling the Story of Mexico’s World Cup Jerseys,Artisanal or Exploitative? Unraveling the Story of Mexico’s World Cup Jerseys,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Jerseys', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A ‘Miraculous Transformation’: How Kim Jong-un Fortified North Korea,A ‘Miraculous Transformation’: How Kim Jong-un Fortified North Korea,0.0,neutral,"[('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Searching for Shade When It’s 125 Degrees,Searching for Shade When It’s 125 Degrees,0.0,neutral,"[('125 Degrees', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"One Is the Pope, the Other an Atheist. They Both Oppose Trump.","One Is the Pope, the Other an Atheist. They Both Oppose Trump.",0.0,neutral,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Atheist', 'GPE'), ('Oppose Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iranians Sink Into Despair Facing War Deaths and Skyrocketing Inflation,Iranians Sink Into Despair Facing War Deaths and Skyrocketing Inflation,-1.0,negative,"[('Iranians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Neo-Nazi Party Member Loses Close Mayoral Race in German Town,Neo-Nazi Party Member Loses Close Mayoral Race in German Town,0.0,neutral,"[('Neo-Nazi Party', 'ORG'), ('Loses Close Mayoral Race', 'ORG'), ('German', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine Turns to Europe as U.S. Steps Back as Mediator in Peace Talks,Ukraine Turns to Europe as U.S. Steps Back as Mediator in Peace Talks,1.0,positive,"[('Ukraine Turns', 'PERSON'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
