Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué pasó en la guerra de Biafra, el primer desastre humanitario televisado en el mundo cuyas heridas siguen abiertas","What happened in the Biafra war, the first televised humanitarian disaster in the world whose wounds remain open",-1.0,negative,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Comiendo chocolate y masticando hielo: el guía dado por muerto en el Everest relató a la BBC cómo sobrevivió 6 días en la montaña más alta del mundo,Eating chocolate and chewing ice: the guide presumed dead on Everest told the BBC how he survived 6 days on the highest mountain in the world,1.0,positive,"[('Everest', 'LOC'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('6 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las denuncias por la falta de protección a las mujeres en Argentina tras el brutal asesinato de Agostina Vega,Complaints about the lack of protection for women in Argentina after the brutal murder of Agostina Vega,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Agostina Vega', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Marjane Satrapi falleció ""de tristeza"": ¿realmente se puede morir de pena por la pérdida de un ser querido?","Marjane Satrapi died ""of sadness"": can you really die of grief over the loss of a loved one?",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo la luz está empezando a invadir uno de los lugares más oscuros de la Tierra,How light is starting to invade one of the darkest places on Earth,0.0,neutral,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Earth', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Backrooms: cómo surgió la idea de la perturbadora película que se convirtió en uno de los mayores éxitos de 2026,Backrooms: how the idea for the disturbing film that became one of the biggest hits of 2026 came about,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Pasé de llorar con su hija, a verlo llegar arrastrándose"": el emocionante relato del escalador que perdió al guía que sobrevivió durante 6 días en el Everest","""I went from crying with his daughter to seeing him arrive crawling"": the moving story of the climber who lost the guide who survived for 6 days on Everest",0.0,neutral,"[('6 days', 'DATE'), ('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Diabetes tipo 5, la nueva y desconocida categoría de la enfermedad que divide a científicos y médicos","Type 5 diabetes, the new and unknown category of the disease that divides scientists and doctors",0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Quiénes son Roberto Sánchez y Keiko Fujimori y qué puede decidir la carrera por presidir el inestable Perú,Who are Roberto Sánchez and Keiko Fujimori and what can decide the race to preside over unstable Peru,0.0,neutral,"[('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Peru', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere apuñalado James Handy, actor de Jumanji y Top Gun: Maverick, y arrestan al hijo de su novia","James Handy, actor of Jumanji and Top Gun: Maverick, is stabbed to death and his girlfriend's son is arrested",-1.0,negative,"[('James Handy', 'PERSON'), ('Jumanji', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी: अभिजीत दीपके ने जंतर मंतर से सरकार को लेकर क्या कहा,Cockroach Janata Party: What Abhijeet Deepke said about the government from Jantar Mantar,0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG'), ('Abhijeet Deepke', 'PERSON'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"श्रेयस अय्यर को क्यों चुना गया टी-20 टीम का कप्तान, क्या वैभव सूर्यवंशी तोड़ पाएंगे सचिन का रिकॉर्ड","Why was Shreyas Iyer chosen as the captain of T20 team, will Vaibhav Suryavanshi be able to break Sachin's record?",0.0,neutral,"[('Shreyas Iyer', 'PERSON'), ('T20', 'ORG'), ('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('Sachin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,नॉर्वे चेस टाइटल जीतने वाले पहले भारतीय बने प्रज्ञानानंद, पीएम मोदी और सीएम विजय ने दी बधाई","Live, Praggnanand became the first Indian to win Norway chess title, PM Modi and CM Vijay congratulated",1.0,positive,"[('Praggnanand', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('PM Modi', 'ORG'), ('CM Vijay', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वीडियो,सीजेपी प्रदर्शन: जंतर-मंतर पर क्या हो रहा है?, अवधि 8,49","Video,CJP protest: What's happening at Jantar Mantar?, Duration 8,49",0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,उत्तर प्रदेश की गवर्नर आनंदीबेन पटेल का लंबा कार्यकाल चर्चा में क्यों है?,Why is the long tenure of Uttar Pradesh Governor Anandiben Patel in discussion?,0.0,neutral,"[('Uttar Pradesh', 'ORG'), ('Anandiben Patel', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका और ईरान ने एक-दूसरे पर फिर हमले किए, खाड़ी में संघर्ष विराम पर संकट गहराया","America and Iran attack each other again, crisis over ceasefire in Gulf deepens",-1.0,negative,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अन्नामलाई के बाद तमिलनाडु में इन नेताओं ने  भी छोड़ी बीजेपी,"After Annamalai, these leaders also left BJP in Tamil Nadu",0.0,neutral,"[('Annamalai', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG'), ('Tamil Nadu', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"आर्मी हैलिकॉप्टर के सामने यूनिफ़ॉर्म में कैप्टन ने किया मंगेतर को प्रपोज़, सोशल मीडिया पर छिड़ी बहस","Captain in uniform proposed to his fiancee in front of army helicopter, debate broke out on social media",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"भोपाल के बरकतुल्ला विश्वविद्यालय का नाम बदलने के प्रस्ताव का विरोध, कौन थे बरकतुल्ला भोपाली?","Opposition to the proposal to change the name of Bhopal's Barkatullah University, who was Barkatullah Bhopali?",0.0,neutral,"[('Bhopal', 'GPE'), ('Barkatullah University', 'ORG'), ('Barkatullah Bhopali', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कॉकरोच जनता पार्टी ने पीएम मोदी से की ये अपील, बताया अभिजीत दीपके क्या-क्या करेंगे?","Cockroach Janata Party made this appeal to PM Modi, told what Abhijeet Deepke will do?",0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG'), ('Abhijeet Deepke', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Por que classificar PCC e CV como terroristas pode fortalecer facções, segundo especialista dos EUA","Why classifying PCC and CV as terrorists can strengthen factions, according to US expert",-1.0,negative,"[('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,EUA oficializam classificação do PCC e CV como terroristas: a linha do tempo da decisão,US officially classifies the PCC and CV as terrorists: the timeline of the decision,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('PCC', 'ORG'), ('CV', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Preços dos ingressos da Copa estão em queda — a Fifa está tentando se livrar deles para evitar fiasco?,World Cup ticket prices are falling — is FIFA trying to get rid of them to avoid a fiasco?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('FIFA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A solução de Oxford para reduzir polarização entre lulistas e bolsonaristas,The Oxford solution to reduce polarization between Lulistas and Bolsonaristas,0.0,neutral,"[('Oxford', 'ORG'), ('Lulistas', 'GPE'), ('Bolsonaristas', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O relato emocionante do alpinista que perdeu o guia encontrado após 6 dias no Everest,The moving account of the climber who lost the guide found after 6 days on Everest,0.0,neutral,"[('6 days', 'DATE'), ('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,A vacina inédita desenvolvida por inteligência artificial,The unprecedented vaccine developed by artificial intelligence,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"James Handy, ator de Jumanji, é morto a facadas aos 81 anos nos EUA, e enteado é suspeito de assassinato","Jumanji actor James Handy is stabbed to death at age 81 in the US, and stepson is suspected of murder",-1.0,negative,"[('Jumanji', 'GPE'), ('James Handy', 'PERSON'), ('age 81', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Aos 10 anos, me preparava para ser prisioneira política': Marjane Satrapi, a autora que retratou transformação do Irã sob a Revolução Islâmica","'At 10 years old, I was preparing to be a political prisoner': Marjane Satrapi, the author who portrayed Iran's transformation under the Islamic Revolution",0.0,neutral,"[('10 years old', 'DATE'), ('Marjane Satrapi', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Islamic Revolution', 'LAW')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Como fui enganada por mulher que dizia ser uma adolescente de 12 anos com autismo : 'Dei carinho, afeto, comida. Não tinha como desconfiar'","How I was deceived by a woman who claimed to be a 12-year-old teenager with autism: 'I gave affection, food. There was no way to suspect",0.0,neutral,"[('12-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский подтвердил массированную атаку на Петербург и Краснодарский край; в Запорожье семь пострадавших","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: Zelensky confirmed a massive attack on St. Petersburg and the Krasnodar region; in Zaporozhye seven victims",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('Krasnodar', 'ORG'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Чемпионат мира по футболу: все, что нужно знать перед стартом главного турнира лета",FIFA World Cup: everything you need to know before the start of the main tournament of the summer,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«По милости божьей»: как индустрия лабораторных алмазов захватывает рынок у старателей в Африке,'By the grace of God': how the lab-grown diamond industry is taking over the market from miners in Africa,0.0,neutral,"[('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Почему Ким Чен Ын никогда не говорит о своей матери,Why Kim Jong-un never talks about his mother,0.0,neutral,"[('Kim Jong-un', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Вэнс связал убийство Генри Новака с «вторжением мигрантов». Правительство Британии назвало это «разжиганием розни»,"Vance linked Henry Novak's murder to a ""migrant invasion."" The British government called it ""incitement to hatred""",0.0,neutral,"[(""Henry Novak's"", 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"США заявили, что Иран выпустил семь ракет по Кувейту и Бахрейну. До этого американские военные ударили по иранским радарам","The US said Iran fired seven missiles at Kuwait and Bahrain. Before this, the US military hit Iranian radars",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Bahrain', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Пол Маккартни снова возглавил британский хит-парад. Он делал это чаще всех в истории,Paul McCartney topped the British charts again. He did it more often than anyone in history,0.0,neutral,"[('Paul McCartney', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,«Пока не вижу смысла». Путин ответил на предложение Зеленского встретиться и договориться о прекращении огня,“I don’t see the point yet.” Putin responded to Zelensky’s proposal to meet and agree on a ceasefire,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Бывший принц Эндрю сдает в субаренду предоставленные ему коттеджи на территории Виндзорского замка,Former Prince Andrew subleases the cottages provided to him on the grounds of Windsor Castle,1.0,positive,"[('Prince Andrew', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Астронавты МКС ненадолго укрылись на корабле SpaceX Crew Dragon из-за утечки воздуха в российском модуле,ISS astronauts briefly took refuge on the SpaceX Crew Dragon due to an air leak in the Russian module,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,プーチン氏、ゼレンスキー氏との会談は「意味がない」　戦争終結のための対面協議を拒否,"Putin's meeting with Zelensky is 'meaningless', rejects face-to-face talks to end war",-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米軍、イランのドローンとレーダー施設を攻撃と発表,US military announces attack on Iranian drone and radar facilities,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,習氏、7年ぶりに北朝鮮を訪れ金氏と会談へ　どんなことが話し合われるのか,Mr. Xi visits North Korea for the first time in 7 years to meet with Mr. Kim. What will be discussed?,0.0,neutral,"[('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('7 years', 'DATE'), ('Kim', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゼレンスキー氏、プーチン氏に直接会談を提案　公開書簡で,Zelensky proposes direct talks with Putin in open letter,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヒズボラ、イスラエルとレバノンが合意した停戦を拒否,Hezbollah rejects ceasefire agreed by Israel and Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,AIの進化、遅らせる策が必要　米アンソロピック共同創業者がBBC番組で主張,"We need measures to slow down the evolution of AI, co-founder of Anthropic argues on BBC program",0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ストレスと疲労、食料や水の問題も……ホルムズ海峡で足止めされている船員たち,"Stress and fatigue, food and water problems... Sailors stranded in the Strait of Hormuz",0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 アメリカ、メキシコ、カナダは相違を乗り越えられるのか　初の3カ国共催,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Can the United States, Mexico, and Canada overcome their differences? First three countries to co-host",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,マスク氏のAI「Grok」にビキニ写真生成された英下院議員が提訴　スターマー首相も訴えを支持,"British House of Commons member files suit after Musk's AI ""Grok"" generated bikini photo; Prime Minister Starmer supports the lawsuit",0.0,neutral,"[('British House of Commons', 'ORG'), ('Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Grok', 'PERSON'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英首相、マスク氏やファラージ氏が「分断をあおっている」と非難　ノヴァクさん殺害事件めぐり,British Prime Minister slams Musk and Farage for ``stoking division'' over Novak murder case,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Novak', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yaishambulia tena Iran, Tehran yajibu","Directly, the United States attacks Iran again, Tehran responds",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wachezaji 7 wa Afrika wa kutazamwa katika Kombe la Dunia,7 African players to watch in the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Nini siri ya mwanga mwekundu katika kuboresha ngozi?,What is the secret of red light in improving the skin?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kipi kitaanza kumalizika, akiba za mafuta au vita Iran?","Which will begin to end, oil reserves or the war in Iran?",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya: Madrid kutoa ofa ya dunia kwa Oliseh,European Football Rumors: Madrid to make a world offer for Oliseh,0.0,neutral,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Madrid', 'GPE'), ('Oliseh', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kushuka kwa takwimu rasmi za Ebola ni habari njema, lakini hatari bado ipo","The drop in official Ebola figures is good news, but the danger remains",1.0,positive,[]
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Aina mpya ya ugonjwa wa kisukari unaowapasua vichwa wataalamu,A new type of diabetes that has experts scratching their heads,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mashambulizi ya makombora na 'hatari inayowakabili viongozi wa Iran',Missile attacks and the 'danger facing Iran's leaders',-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kijiji ambacho watu husafiri kilomita 45  kuchaji simu zao,A village where people travel 45 kilometers to charge their phones,0.0,neutral,"[('45 kilometers', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_06,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Elon Musk kuwa trilionea wa kwanza duniani?",Will Elon Musk become the first trillionaire in the world?,0.0,neutral,"[('Will Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Badge of honour’: Israeli settlers shrug off global condemnation,‘Badge of honour’: Israeli settlers shrug off global condemnation,0.0,neutral,"[('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Supporters of the Cockroach People’s Party hold protest in New Delhi,Supporters of the Cockroach People’s Party hold protest in New Delhi,0.0,neutral,"[('the Cockroach People’s Party', 'ORG'), ('New Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Man dies in Western Australia after shark attack,Man dies in Western Australia after shark attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Western Australia', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US intercepts Iranian attacks as Israel continues to bomb Lebanon,US intercepts Iranian attacks as Israel continues to bomb Lebanon,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"North Korea’s Kim orders navy to build 10,000-tonne destroyer: State media","North Korea’s Kim orders navy to build 10,000-tonne destroyer: State media",0.0,neutral,"[('North Korea’s', 'GPE'), ('Kim', 'PERSON'), ('10,000-tonne', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,From sensor-equipped balls to robot dogs: What’s new at the World Cup?,From sensor-equipped balls to robot dogs: What’s new at the World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,New York Knicks hold off San Antonio Spurs 105-104 for 2-0 NBA Finals lead,New York Knicks hold off San Antonio Spurs 105-104 for 2-0 NBA Finals lead,0.0,neutral,"[('New York Knicks', 'ORG'), ('San Antonio', 'GPE'), ('105', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('NBA', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Arrests of critics in Ghana spark alarm over free speech under Mahama,Arrests of critics in Ghana spark alarm over free speech under Mahama,0.0,neutral,"[('Ghana', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Iran fires missiles at Kuwait, Bahrain after US hits Iranian drones, radars","Iran fires missiles at Kuwait, Bahrain after US hits Iranian drones, radars",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('Bahrain', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_06,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Trump makes pitch to farmers hard-hit by tariffs, high prices in Wisconsin","Trump makes pitch to farmers hard-hit by tariffs, high prices in Wisconsin",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Wisconsin', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The Hindu Huddle Day 2 | Watch live,The Hindu Huddle Day 2 | Watch live,0.0,neutral,"[('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"The Hindu Huddle 2026 LIVE: Not true that AI has taken away jobs, says ex-Cognizant CEO","The Hindu Huddle 2026 LIVE: Not true that AI has taken away jobs, says ex-Cognizant CEO",0.0,neutral,"[('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Regional parties assert independence, stress national interest at Hindu Huddle 2026","Regional parties assert independence, stress national interest at Hindu Huddle 2026",0.0,neutral,"[('Hindu Huddle', 'ORG'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Politician Vijay more powerful than actor Vijay, says TVK Minister K.G. Arunraj","Politician Vijay more powerful than actor Vijay, says TVK Minister K.G. Arunraj",0.0,neutral,"[('Politician Vijay', 'PERSON'), ('Vijay', 'PERSON'), ('TVK', 'ORG'), ('K.G. Arunraj', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Character AI poses unique risks for young users, mental health experts warn","Character AI poses unique risks for young users, mental health experts warn",-1.0,negative,[]
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The Hindu Huddle amid a ‘world in transition’,The Hindu Huddle amid a ‘world in transition’,0.0,neutral,"[('Hindu', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Cockroach Janta Party protest LIVE: Sonam Wangchuk joins protest at Jantar Mantar,Cockroach Janta Party protest LIVE: Sonam Wangchuk joins protest at Jantar Mantar,0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janta Party', 'ORG'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Four former AIADMK Ministers join TVK amid fresh wave of defections,Four former AIADMK Ministers join TVK amid fresh wave of defections,0.0,neutral,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('AIADMK Ministers', 'ORG'), ('TVK', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Praggnanandhaa says winning Norway Chess title ‘more special’ than beating Magnus Carlsen,Praggnanandhaa says winning Norway Chess title ‘more special’ than beating Magnus Carlsen,1.0,positive,"[('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Magnus Carlsen', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US and Iran exchange strikes in Gulf in latest test of ceasefire,US and Iran exchange strikes in Gulf in latest test of ceasefire,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Gulf', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Putin says there is 'no point' meeting Zelensky over ending Ukraine war,Putin says there is 'no point' meeting Zelensky over ending Ukraine war,-1.0,negative,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Rumours and speculation as fans forecast date of Taylor Swift's wedding,Rumours and speculation as fans forecast date of Taylor Swift's wedding,0.0,neutral,"[(""Taylor Swift's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Armenia braces for election as Russia piles pressure on pro-West government,Armenia braces for election as Russia piles pressure on pro-West government,0.0,neutral,"[('Armenia', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Iran's football team granted visas to enter US for World Cup, officials say","Iran's football team granted visas to enter US for World Cup, officials say",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Canada bans Texas cattle over flesh-eating screwworm outbreak in US,Canada bans Texas cattle over flesh-eating screwworm outbreak in US,0.0,neutral,"[('Canada', 'GPE'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Tributes to Buffy and Ted Lasso star Anthony Head after death aged 72,Tributes to Buffy and Ted Lasso star Anthony Head after death aged 72,-1.0,negative,"[('Buffy', 'ORG'), ('Ted Lasso', 'PERSON'), ('Anthony Head', 'PERSON'), ('72', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Palestinian baby killed by Israeli gunfire in West Bank, health ministry says","Palestinian baby killed by Israeli gunfire in West Bank, health ministry says",-1.0,negative,"[('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nearly 50 people die of thirst in Sahara desert after lorry breaks down,Nearly 50 people die of thirst in Sahara desert after lorry breaks down,0.0,neutral,"[('Nearly 50', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sahara', 'LOC'), ('lorry', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US stocks slump as fears over Big Tech shake Wall Street,US stocks slump as fears over Big Tech shake Wall Street,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Big Tech', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In Venezuela, the Debt Collector Is the Devil","In Venezuela, the Debt Collector Is the Devil",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('the Debt Collector Is the Devil', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Pope Leo, After Taking on Trump and A.I., Prepares for New Duels in Spain","Pope Leo, After Taking on Trump and A.I., Prepares for New Duels in Spain",0.0,neutral,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('A.I.', 'ORG'), ('Spain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Ebola Spreads in East Africa, Will China Step Up?","As Ebola Spreads in East Africa, Will China Step Up?",0.0,neutral,"[('East Africa', 'GPE'), ('Will China', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,What Visual Evidence Tells Us About Israel’s Use of White Phosphorus in Lebanon,What Visual Evidence Tells Us About Israel’s Use of White Phosphorus in Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Us', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mali Conflict Escalates as Rebel Alliance Seizes Key Cities,Mali Conflict Escalates as Rebel Alliance Seizes Key Cities,-1.0,negative,"[('Mali Conflict Escalates', 'PERSON'), ('Rebel Alliance Seizes Key Cities', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Laboring Under Delhi’s Harsh Heat, Workers Must Choose Health or Wages","Laboring Under Delhi’s Harsh Heat, Workers Must Choose Health or Wages",0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi’s Harsh Heat', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"A President, His Prime Minister and the Bitter Rift Dividing Senegal","A President, His Prime Minister and the Bitter Rift Dividing Senegal",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Gold Mines at the Heart of This Ebola Outbreak,The Gold Mines at the Heart of This Ebola Outbreak,0.0,neutral,"[('the Heart of This Ebola Outbreak', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Hopes of Lebanon Cease-Fire Falter as Israel and Hezbollah Fight On,Hopes of Lebanon Cease-Fire Falter as Israel and Hezbollah Fight On,0.0,neutral,"[('Lebanon Cease-Fire Falter', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah Fight', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_06,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Backed by Trump, Opposed by Putin, and Fighting for His Political Life","Backed by Trump, Opposed by Putin, and Fighting for His Political Life",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
