Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La BBC investiga la práctica de asesinar a personas para vender partes de sus cuerpos como ""amuletos mágicos"" en África",BBC investigates practice of killing people to sell body parts as 'magic amulets' in Africa,0.5,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Trump anuncia que indultará al expresidente Juan Orlando Hernández a dos días de las presidenciales en Honduras,Trump announces that he will pardon former president Juan Orlando Hernández two days before the presidential elections in Honduras,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Juan Orlando Hernández', 'PERSON'), ('two days', 'DATE'), ('Honduras', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Por qué Honduras sigue siendo el país más pobre de Centroamérica pese a una década de crecimiento,Why Honduras remains the poorest country in Central America despite a decade of growth,0.0,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('Central America', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Gustavo Villatoro, el hombre al frente del plan de seguridad de Bukele en El Salvador y aliado de Kast en su carrera por la presidencia de Chile","Gustavo Villatoro, the man in charge of Bukele's security plan in El Salvador and an ally of Kast in his race for the presidency of Chile",0.0,"[('Gustavo Villatoro', 'PERSON'), ('Bukele', 'ORG'), ('El Salvador', 'GPE'), ('Kast', 'LOC'), ('Chile', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Airbus advierte de disrupciones en el tráfico aéreo tras detectar un problema en más de 6.000 de sus aviones,"Airbus warns of disruptions in air traffic after detecting a problem in more than 6,000 of its planes",0.5,"[('Airbus', 'ORG'), ('more than 6,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"महाराजा दलीप सिंह: दो कुर्सियों की ​​नीलामी, मिस्र की मुलर से शादी और ग़रीबी में बीते आख़िरी पल की कहानी","Maharaja Dalip Singh: Auction of two chairs, marriage to Egypt's Muller and the story of his last moments in poverty",0.0,"[('Maharaja', 'GPE'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Muller', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,पश्चिम बंगाल: ममता सरकार ने नए वक़्फ़ संशोधन क़ानून को दी मंज़ूरी","Live, West Bengal: Mamata government approves new Waqf Amendment Act",0.13636363636363635,"[('Mamata', 'ORG'), ('Waqf Amendment Act', 'LAW')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"थर्ड वर्ल्ड क्या है, क्या भारत भी इसमें शामिल है? जानिए अहम सवालों के जवाब","What is Third World, is India also included in it? Know the answers to important questions",0.2,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"टेस्ट क्रिकेट में भारत की गिरी प्रतिष्ठा, गौतम गंभीर के जिन फ़ैसलों पर उठ रहे हैं सवाल","India's reputation has fallen in Test cricket, questions are being raised on Gautam Gambhir's decisions.",0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), (""Gautam Gambhir's"", 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पाकिस्तान के ये तीन भाई, सूरज डूबते ही हो जाते थे, 'लकवाग्रस्त'",These three brothers of Pakistan used to become 'paralysed' as soon as the sun sets,0.0,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जेआरडी टाटा और जवाहरलाल नेहरू में कभी दोस्ती तो कभी तीखे मतभेद,Sometimes friendship and sometimes sharp differences between JRD Tata and Jawaharlal Nehru,-0.125,"[('JRD Tata', 'ORG'), ('Jawaharlal Nehru', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,ज़ीनत अमान: जिन्होंने हिंदी फ़िल्मों की हीरोइन के लिए तय सीमाएं बदल दीं,Zeenat Aman: Who changed the boundaries set for heroines in Hindi films,0.0,"[('Zeenat Aman', 'PERSON'), ('Hindi', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"उपेंद्र कुशवाहा की पार्टी में इस्तीफ़ों की झड़ी, बेटे को मंत्री बनाने से बढ़ा असंतोष","A wave of resignations in Upendra Kushwaha's party, dissatisfaction increased after making his son a minister.",0.0,"[(""Upendra Kushwaha's"", 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान: बारिश में आइसक्रीम की तलाश में निकली बच्ची 17 साल बाद यूं लौटी घर,Pakistan: The girl who went in search of ice cream in the rain returned home like this after 17 years,0.0,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('17 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Defesa de Bolsonaro entra com recurso após Moraes encerrar processo; o que acontece agora?,Bolsonaro's defense files an appeal after Moraes ends the process; what happens now?,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Moraes', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Por que incêndio em condomínio de Hong Kong foi tão devastador, com mais de 120 mortos","Why the Hong Kong condominium fire was so devastating, with more than 120 dead",-0.2333333333333333,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('more than 120', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Icônicos andaimes de bambu podem ter ajudado a espalhar fogo em incêndio devastador em Hong Kong,Iconic bamboo scaffolding may have helped spread fire in devastating Hong Kong fire,-0.25,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Trump e Maduro se falaram por telefone na semana passada, diz New York Times","Trump and Maduro spoke on the phone last week, says New York Times",0.06818181818181818,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON'), ('last week', 'DATE'), ('New York Times', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A colombiana que sobreviveu ao tráfico de pessoas no México: 'Uma amiga me enganou e me levou para uma rede de exploração sexual',The Colombian woman who survived human trafficking in Mexico: 'A friend deceived me and took me into a sexual exploitation network',0.25,"[('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Sem líder claro, direita está dividida após prisão de Bolsonaro, diz Economist","Without a clear leader, the right is divided after Bolsonaro's arrest, says Economist",0.11190476190476191,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As freiras fugitivas que viraram 'hit' nas redes sociais e voltaram para convento sem autorização,The fugitive nuns who became a hit on social media and returned to the convent without authorization,0.03333333333333333,[]
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Trump afirma que EUA irá suspender migração de 'países do Terceiro Mundo',Trump says US will suspend migration from 'Third World countries',0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Pão vira inimigo se você pensar só em proteína e carboidrato, diz Rita Lobo","Bread becomes the enemy if you only think about protein and carbohydrates, says Rita Lobo",0.0,"[('Rita Lobo', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Киев снова подвергся массированной атаке, есть жертвы","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Kyiv was again subjected to a massive attack, there were casualties",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Отставка главы офиса президента Украины Андрея Ермака в вопросах и ответах,Resignation of the head of the office of the President of Ukraine Andriy Ermak in questions and answers,0.0,"[('Ukraine Andriy Ermak', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Зеленский уволил Ермака на фоне коррупционного скандала. Что привело к отставке?,Zelensky fired Ermak amid a corruption scandal. What led to the resignation?,0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Ermak', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Тысячи самолетов Airbus подвержены ошибке приборов. Это может привести к перебоям и отменам рейсов,Thousands of Airbus aircraft are susceptible to instrument error. This could lead to disruptions and flight cancellations,0.0,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Airbus', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Мы просто хотим домой». Гражданин ЮАР рассказал, как дочь экс-президента Зумы обманом завербовала его воевать в Украине на стороне России","""We just want to go home."" A South African citizen told how the daughter of ex-President Zuma tricked him into fighting in Ukraine on the side of Russia.",0.0,"[('South African', 'NORP'), ('Zuma', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Орбан снова приехал в Москву назло партнерам по ЕС. Атмосфера встречи с Путиным оказалась прохладной,Orban came to Moscow again to spite his EU partners. The atmosphere of the meeting with Putin was cool,0.35,"[('Orban', 'PERSON'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Космонавтика на паузе? Авария на Байконуре грозит большим перерывом в полетах космонавтов на МКС,Space exploration on pause? The accident at Baikonur threatens a big break in the flights of astronauts to the ISS,0.0,"[('Baikonur', 'GPE'), ('ISS', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Фронт у Гуляйполя: трагедия 102-й бригады ВСУ, расстрел пленных и захват Зеленого Гая","Front near Gulyai-Polye: tragedy of the 102nd brigade of the Ukrainian Armed Forces, execution of prisoners and capture of Zeleny Gai",0.1,"[('102nd', 'ORG'), ('the Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Zeleny Gai', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Разрыв между городом и деревней: что известно о потерях России в Украине к декабрю,The gap between city and countryside: what is known about Russia’s losses in Ukraine by December,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('December', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Монахиням, сбежавшим из дома престарелых в свой монастырь, разрешили остаться там при условии, что они уйдут из соцсетей",Nuns who escaped from a nursing home to their monastery were allowed to stay there on the condition that they leave social networks,0.03333333333333333,[]
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港の高層住宅群火災、死者少なくとも128人に　さらに８人を汚職容疑で逮捕,At least 128 people killed in Hong Kong high-rise housing fire; 8 more arrested on corruption charges,0.0,"[('At least 128', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('8', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏の側近、イェルマーク長官が辞任　汚職対策当局が自宅を強制捜査,Zelenskiy's close aide Yermak resigns; anti-corruption authorities raid his home,0.0,"[('Zelenskiy', 'ORG'), ('Yermak', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,同性婚認めない現行法の規定、東京高裁は「合憲」と　 ほか5件と判断分かれる,"The Tokyo High Court rules that the current law prohibiting same-sex marriage is constitutional, along with 5 other cases.",0.011666666666666667,"[('Tokyo', 'GPE'), ('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、すべての亡命申請に対して決定停止　トランプ氏は途上国からの移民を「恒久的に停止」と,US suspends decisions on all asylum applications; Trump calls for ``permanently halting'' immigration from developing countries,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,行方不明者の家族ら、苦しみのなか待ち続ける　香港高層住宅群火災,Families of missing people continue to wait in agony as fire breaks out in Hong Kong high-rise housing complex,-0.25,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル部隊、投降したとみられるパレスチナ人2人を殺害　映像が浮上,Video emerges of Israeli troops killing two Palestinians believed to have surrendered,0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ルーヴル美術館、欧州圏以外からの来場者の入場料を45％値上げへ　改修資金に,Louvre Museum to raise admission fee by 45% for visitors from outside Europe to fund renovations,0.0,"[('Louvre Museum', 'ORG'), ('45%', 'PERCENT'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,フランスが限定的な兵役を再導入へ、徴兵制廃止から25年,"France to reintroduce limited military service, 25 years after abolishing conscription",-0.08571428571428572,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('25 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米首都銃撃で負傷した州兵1人が死亡、容疑者は過去にアフガニスタンで米CIAと協力,One National Guard soldier injured in US capital shooting dies; suspect previously worked with US CIA in Afghanistan,-0.16666666666666666,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('National Guard', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Afghanistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tanzania: Tunashughulikia azimio la Umoja wa Ulaya kidiplomasia,Tanzania: We are handling the EU resolution diplomatically,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumamosi: Manchester City yamlenga mchezaji wa Nottingham Forest,European football rumors on Saturday: Manchester City target Nottingham Forest player,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE'), ('Nottingham Forest', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Serikali ya Tanzania: Azimio la EU halina chembe ya ukweli,Government of Tanzania: The EU resolution has no grain of truth,0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hatua ya bunge la Ulaya dhidi ya Tanzania ina maana gani?,What does the action of the European Parliament against Tanzania mean?,-0.07083333333333333,"[('the European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kutoka Zidane hadi Van Persie, makocha waliowapa 'ulaji' watoto wao","From Zidane to Van Persie, the coaches who gave 'eating' to their children",0.0,"[('Zidane', 'PERSON'), ('Van Persie', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"""Vijana wa Kiukraine wanaoshawishiwa kwa fedha mtandaoni kuishambulia nchi yao""","""Ukrainian youth lured by online money to attack their country""",0.0,[]
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Hali ya Hezbollah mwaka mmoja baada ya kusitishwa kwa mapigano,The state of Hezbollah one year after the ceasefire,0.0,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('one year', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Afrika na zimwi la mapinduzi yasiyoisha,Africa and the monster of endless revolution,-0.125,"[('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais Kagame aonyesha matumaini juu ya mazungumzo yaliyopangwa na Rais wa Congo,President Kagame expresses hope about the talks organized by the President of the Congo,0.0,"[('Kagame', 'PERSON'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_29,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Rais aliyeondolewa madarakani wa Guinea-Bissau awasili Senegal,The deposed president of Guinea-Bissau arrives in Senegal,0.0,"[('Guinea-Bissau', 'ORG'), ('Senegal', 'GPE')]"
