Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""¿Tú qué hiciste durante el genocidio?"": la provocadora pregunta con que la escritora Arwa Mahdawi reflexiona sobre la ofensiva de Israel en Gaza","""What did you do during the genocide?"": the provocative question with which the writer Arwa Mahdawi reflects on Israel's offensive in Gaza",0.0,"[('Arwa Mahdawi', 'PERSON'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo Trump está remodelando la Casa Blanca en su propia imagen,How Trump is reshaping the White House in his own image,0.3,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('the White House', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Kim Yong-nam, el impasible jefe de Estado de Corea del Norte que sobrevivió a las brutales purgas del régimen y sirvió a tres generaciones de la dinastía Kim","Kim Yong-nam, the stolid head of state of North Korea who survived the regime's brutal purges and served three generations of the Kim dynasty",-0.875,"[('Kim Yong-nam', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Kim dynasty', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Perú global"": cómo los grandes acontecimientos de la historia del mundo definieron el rumbo del país","""Global Peru"": how the great events in world history defined the country's course",0.4,"[('Global Peru', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Nuestra visión del mundo está distorsionada por los mapas que ponen a Europa y EE.UU. en la cima. En realidad, no hay ni arriba ni abajo""","""Our view of the world is distorted by maps that put Europe and the US at the top. In reality, there is no up or down""",0.17222222222222222,"[('Europe', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,आज़ादी के बाद जूनागढ़ कैसे बना भारत का हिस्सा?- विवेचना,How did Junagadh become a part of India after independence?- Discussion,0.0,"[('Junagadh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव: जब अवैध शराब की भट्टी तक पहुंचा बीबीसी,Bihar elections: When BBC reached the distillery of illegal liquor,-0.5,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अमेरिका: फ़्लोरिडा में तेज़ रफ़्तार कार बार से टकराई, 4 लोगों की मौत","Live, America: Speeding car collides with bar in Florida, 4 people died",0.13636363636363635,"[('Florida', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सऊदी क्राउन प्रिंस का अमेरिका दौरा: एफ़-35 जेट का समझौता क्या इसराइल को परेशान कर सकता है?,Saudi Crown Prince's visit to America: Could the F-35 jet deal trouble Israel?,-0.2,"[('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('F-35', 'PRODUCT'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव: क्या महिलाएं चुनाव नतीजों की दिशा बदलने वाली 'साइलेंट फ़ोर्स' बन रही हैं,Bihar Elections: Are women becoming the 'silent force' changing the direction of election results?,0.225,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,दक्षिण भारत के इस प्रसिद्ध हिंदू मंदिर से सोना चोरी के विवाद का पूरा मामला क्या है?,What is the whole matter of the controversy of gold theft from this famous Hindu temple of South India?,0.35,"[('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('South India', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,वर्ल्ड चैंपियन बनकर घर लौटीं उमा छेत्री के स्वागत को लेकर हुआ विवाद आख़िर क्या है?,"What is the controversy over welcoming Uma Chhetri, who returned home after becoming world champion?",0.45,"[('Uma Chhetri', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार चुनाव: समस्तीपुर में लावारिस मिलीं वीवीपैट पर्चियां, विपक्ष ने उठाए सवाल","Bihar Elections: VVPAT slips found unclaimed in Samastipur, opposition raised questions",0.0,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON'), ('VVPAT', 'ORG'), ('Samastipur', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मोहन और मोहम्मद, इतिहास रचने वाली दो समानांतर ज़िंदगियाँ","Mohan and Mohammed, two parallel lives that made history",0.0,"[('Mohan', 'PERSON'), ('Mohammed', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Tornado destrói 90% de cidade e deixa 6 mortos no Paraná; o que se sabe,Tornado destroys 90% of the city and leaves 6 dead in Paraná; what is known,-0.2,"[('Tornado', 'ORG'), ('90%', 'PERCENT'), ('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Paraná', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,4 impactos para o Brasil de uma ação dos EUA na Venezuela,4 impacts for Brazil of US action in Venezuela,0.1,"[('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que papa quer 'corrigir' devoção a Nossa Senhora?,Why does the Pope want to 'correct' devotion to Our Lady?,0.0,[]
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Qual é a situação dos cristãos na Nigéria e por que Trump está ameaçando intervir no país?,What is the situation of Christians in Nigeria and why is Trump threatening to intervene in the country?,0.0,"[('Christians', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O misterioso empresário que orquestrou fraude de US$ 14 bi com 'tortura e extorsão de trabalhadores',The mysterious businessman who orchestrated US$14 billion fraud with 'torture and extortion of workers',0.0,"[('US$14 billion', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A história do ornitorrinco que Churchill ganhou de presente em plena 2ª Guerra (e a verdade sobre seu misterioso fim),The story of the platypus that Churchill received as a gift during World War II (and the truth about its mysterious end),0.0,"[('Churchill', 'PERSON'), ('World War II', 'EVENT')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Aquiles, Falópio, Broca: as histórias de poder por trás dos nomes das partes do corpo humano","Achilles, Fallopian, Broca: the stories of power behind the names of human body parts",-0.2,"[('Achilles', 'GPE'), ('Fallopian', 'NORP'), ('Broca', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como a 'esquerda caviar' influencia a política e por que é desprezada pela esquerda radical?,How does the 'caviar left' influence politics and why is it despised by the radical left?,0.0,[]
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A foto de brasileira que virou centro de acusação de fraude eleitoral na Índia,The photo of a Brazilian woman who became the center of accusations of electoral fraud in India,-0.1,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сирийский лидер впервые совершает официальный визит в США. О чем будут говорить Ахмед аш-Шараа и Дональд Трамп?,The Syrian leader is making an official visit to the United States for the first time. What will Ahmed al-Sharaa and Donald Trump talk about?,0.25,"[('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Ahmed al-Sharaa', 'PERSON'), ('Donald Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Рабыни божьи». Как индийские девушки, став девадаси, попадают в ловушку сексуальной эксплуатации","""Slaves of God."" How Indian girls become devadasi and fall into the trap of sexual exploitation",0.5,"[('Slaves of God', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Более 1400 авиарейсов отменены в США из-за шатдауна,"More than 1,400 flights canceled in the US due to shutdown",0.1875,"[('More than 1,400', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Массированный обстрел Украины: в ряде областей нет света, в Днепре есть погибшие при попадании беспилотника в жилой дом","Massive shelling of Ukraine: there is no power in a number of regions, in the Dnieper there are those killed when a drone hit a residential building",-0.1,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Dnieper', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Как Трамп может помешать планам Мамдани в Нью-Йорке,How Trump can thwart Mamdani's plans in New York,0.13636363636363635,"[('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: беспилотник ударил по многоэтажному дому в Днепре, есть погибшие","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: a drone hit a multi-storey building in the Dnieper, there are dead",-0.2,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Dnieper', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Баку масштабно отметили вторую годовщину победы Азербайджана в войне за Карабах. К Алиеву приехал Эрдоган,The second anniversary of Azerbaijan's victory in the war for Karabakh was celebrated on a large scale in Baku. Erdogan came to Aliyev,0.1880952380952381,"[('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Azerbaijan', 'GPE'), ('Karabakh', 'PERSON'), ('Baku', 'GPE'), ('Erdogan', 'PERSON'), ('Aliyev', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Просто консультировала». Подробности нового «дела о торговле детьми» в Москве,“Just consulting.” Details of the new “child trafficking case” in Moscow,0.13636363636363635,"[('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Вернувшийся из Газы израильский заложник рассказал, что его там подвергали сексуализированному насилию",An Israeli hostage who returned from Gaza said he was subjected to sexualized violence there.,0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Открытие археологов: древнейшие люди начали стабильно делать орудия труда на сотни тысяч лет раньше, чем считалось до сих пор",Archaeological discovery: ancient people began to consistently make tools hundreds of thousands of years earlier than previously thought,0.020833333333333336,"[('hundreds of thousands', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏によるポートランドへの州兵派遣は「違法」、米連邦地裁が判断,"Trump's deployment of the National Guard to Portland was ""illegal,"" a federal judge rules.",-0.5,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('the National Guard', 'ORG'), ('Portland', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ各地で数千フライトに欠航や遅延　連邦政府閉鎖の影響で便数削減命令,Thousands of flights canceled or delayed across the U.S. Order to reduce flight numbers due to federal government shutdown,-0.125,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,幸運のネコ、ぼろぼろのサッカーボール……2年間の戦争でガザ住民が手放さなかったもの,"A lucky cat, a tattered soccer ball...things that Gaza residents didn't let go of during two years of war.",0.3333333333333333,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('two years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,DNAの構造解明でノーベル賞、ジェイムズ・ワトソン氏死去　97歳,"James Watson, winner of Nobel Prize for elucidating the structure of DNA, dies at age 97",0.0,"[('James Watson', 'PERSON'), ('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('age 97', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、ハマスから棺を受け取る　人質の遺体が入っているとハマス説明,Israel receives coffin from Hamas; Hamas says it contains the bodies of hostages,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タンザニア大統領選めぐる抗議デモ、少なくとも240人を反逆罪で起訴　暴力的弾圧で多数死傷,At least 240 people charged with treason during protests over Tanzanian presidential election; violent crackdown leaves many dead and injured,-0.2,"[('At least 240', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ペロシ元米下院議長が引退を表明、20年にわたり下院で民主党を率いる,"Former U.S. House Speaker Pelosi announces retirement, leading Democrats in the House of Representatives for 20 years",0.0,"[('U.S. House', 'ORG'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('the House of Representatives', 'ORG'), ('20 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,口論し、原稿を破り、「国内の敵」と……引退表明のペロシ氏とトランプ氏の確執, 所要時間 0,48","Video, Bickering, tearing up manuscripts, calling out ``domestic enemies''... Pelosi announces retirement and Trump feud, Duration 0,48",0.0,"[('Bickering', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ミス・ユニバース、各国代表が抗議の「集団退席」　運営側がメキシコ代表を叱ったあと, 所要時間 1,31","Video, Miss Universe representatives from each country ``mass walk out'' in protest after management scolds Mexico representative, Duration 1,31",0.0,"[('Universe', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Zaidi ya safari za ndege 1,400 zafutwa huku hatua ya kupunguzwa kwa safari ikiingia siku ya pili  Marekani","Live, More than 1,400 flights canceled as travel restrictions enter second day in US",0.21212121212121213,"[('More than 1,400', 'CARDINAL'), ('second day', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Zaidi ya watu 400 washtakiwa katika mikoa mbalimbali,Protests in Tanzania: More than 400 people accused in various regions,0.25,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('More than 400', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Ngozi yangu ilichibuka': Jinsi wanawake wa Kiafrika walivyolaghaiwa kutengeneza ndege za kivita za Urusi,'My skin came off': How African women were tricked into building Russian fighter jets,0.0,"[('African', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumapili:Spurs wanamtaka winga wa Everton Ndiaye,Football rumors Sunday: Spurs want Everton winger Ndiaye,0.0,"[('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Everton', 'PERSON'), ('Ndiaye', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Maandamano Tanzania: Askofu Gwajima, makada wa Chadema wasakwa na polisi","Protests in Tanzania: Bishop Gwajima, Chadema cadres are wanted by the police",0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('Bishop Gwajima', 'ORG'), ('Chadema', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Madhara ya kuvuta sigara ya kielektroniki kwa vijana wadogo,Effects of electronic cigarette smoking on young people,0.1,[]
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Masuala yaliyoibuliwa na waangalizi wa uchaguzi mkuu wa Tanzania,Issues raised by Tanzanian general election observers,0.05000000000000002,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ni marufuku kuyatembelea maeneo haya duniani,It is forbidden to visit these places in the world,0.0,[]
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Nilikimbia kivyangu na mume wangu kivyake',Protests in Tanzania: 'I ran separately and my husband separately',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Serikali ya Israel yatambua mwili wa mwanafunzi wa Tanzania aliyekuwa mateka Gaza,The Israeli government recognizes the body of a Tanzanian student who was held captive in Gaza,0.2,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
