Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo es el dron marítimo con el que EE.UU. rescató a los tripulantes del helicóptero Apache derribado en el estrecho de Ormuz,What is the maritime drone with which the US rescued the crew of the Apache helicopter shot down in the Strait of Hormuz?,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Apache', 'PRODUCT'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,La princesa Bajrakitiyabha de Tailandia muere tras pasar más de 3 años en coma,Princess Bajrakitiyabha of Thailand dies after spending more than 3 years in a coma,0.0,neutral,"[('Bajrakitiyabha', 'GPE'), ('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('more than 3 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Los científicos dicen que el fenómeno de El Niño ya empezó y advierten de los efectos climáticos extremos que puede traer,Scientists say that the El Niño phenomenon has already begun and warn of the extreme climate effects it can bring,-1.0,negative,"[('El Niño', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Por qué en EE.UU. le dicen al fútbol soccer y cuál es el origen de esa palabra (no, no la crearon los estadounidenses)","Why in the US do they call football soccer and what is the origin of that word (no, the Americans did not create it)",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Americans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""El fútbol ha pasado de ser una fiesta popular a convertirse en un producto prémium con EE.UU. encima del negocio""","""Soccer has gone from being a popular festival to becoming a premium product with the US on top of the business""",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,México comienza el Mundial con paso firme: 2-0 ante Sudáfrica y emoción de Raúl Jiménez,Mexico begins the World Cup with a firm step: 2-0 against South Africa and emotion from Raúl Jiménez,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Raúl Jiménez', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Elecciones en Perú: Keiko Fujimori adelanta a Roberto Sánchez, pero poco más de 1.000 votos los separan en las disputadas presidenciales","Elections in Peru: Keiko Fujimori overtakes Roberto Sánchez, but just over 1,000 votes separate them in the disputed presidential elections",0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON'), ('just over 1,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Trump apunta a la posible firma de un acuerdo para poner fin a la guerra tras cancelar los ataques previstos contra Irán,Trump points to possible signing of agreement to end war after canceling planned attacks on Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las interrogantes que plantea la milagrosa supervivencia de un sherpa en el Everest,The questions raised by the miraculous survival of a Sherpa on Everest,0.0,neutral,"[('Sherpa', 'FAC')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quién es Julián Quiñones, el colombo-mexicano que anotó el primer gol del Mundial 2026 en el triunfo del Tri ante Sudáfrica en el partido inaugural","Who is Julián Quiñones, the Colombian-Mexican who scored the first goal of the 2026 World Cup in El Tri's victory against South Africa in the opening match",1.0,positive,"[('Julián Quiñones', 'PERSON'), ('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), (""El Tri's"", 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अहमदाबाद प्लेन क्रैश का एक सालः हादसे की वजह पर क्यों है इतना विवाद, क्या कहते हैं विशेषज्ञ","One year of Ahmedabad plane crash: Why is there so much controversy over the cause of the accident, what do experts say",0.0,neutral,"[('One year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,मीनाक्षी नटराजन का नामांकन रद्द किए जाने के ख़िलाफ़ कांग्रेस का दिल्ली में प्रदर्शन","Live, Congress protest in Delhi against cancellation of nomination of Meenakshi Natarajan",0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Meenakshi Natarajan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,कनेक्टेड दुनिया में अकेलेपन की क्या हैं मुश्किलें,What are the difficulties of loneliness in a connected world?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिकी हमले में मारे गए सुरेश पटनाला की आख़िरी बातचीत में अपनी पत्नी से किया वादा अधूरा रह गया,"In the last conversation of Suresh Patnala, who was killed in the American attack, the promise made to his wife remained unfulfilled.",-1.0,negative,"[('Suresh Patnala', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"मीनाक्षी नटराजन मामले में सुप्रीम कोर्ट से कांग्रेस को नहीं मिली राहत, अदालत ने दिया ये तर्क","Congress did not get relief from Supreme Court in Meenakshi Natarajan case, the court gave this argument",0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Meenakshi Natarajan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अमेरिकी हमले में तीन भारतीय नाविकों के मारे जाने के बाद मोदी सरकार का रुख़ घेरे में,Modi government's stance under siege after three Indian sailors were killed in American attack,-1.0,negative,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,पाकिस्तान के धुरंधर बल्लेबाज़ जावेद मियांदाद इन दिनों क्या कर रहे हैं?,What is Pakistan's great batsman Javed Miandad doing these days?,1.0,positive,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Javed Miandad', 'PERSON'), ('these days', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अभिषेक बनर्जी पर अब ममता समर्थक भी उठाने लगे हैं गंभीर सवाल,Now Mamata supporters have also started raising serious questions on Abhishek Banerjee.,0.0,neutral,"[('Mamata', 'ORG'), ('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"जब भारतीय फ़ुटबॉल टीम को मिला था वर्ल्ड कप में हिस्सा लेने का मौक़ा, लेकिन क्यों नहीं खेली टीम","When the Indian football team got a chance to participate in the World Cup, but why did the team not play?",0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अहमदाबाद प्लेन क्रैश: एयर होस्टेस मैथिली की मां बोलीं- लगता है वो कहीं से आकर बात करेगी,Ahmedabad plane crash: Air hostess Maithili's mother said - Looks like she will come from somewhere and talk,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O Mundial 'mais caro e mais politizado': 4 pontos importantes sobre a Copa do Mundo de 2026,The 'most expensive and most politicized' World Cup: 4 important points about the 2026 World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem é o maior jogador de todas as Copas? Lista da BBC tem 3 brasileiros,Who is the greatest player of all World Cups? BBC list has 3 Brazilians,1.0,positive,"[('World Cups', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Brazilians', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem era a princesa tailandesa morta após mais de 3 anos em coma — e o dilema que deixa sobre futuro da monarquia no país,Who was the Thai princess who died after more than 3 years in a coma — and the dilemma she leaves about the future of the monarchy in the country,0.0,neutral,"[('Thai', 'NORP'), ('more than 3 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como é o drone marítimo usado pelos EUA para resgatar tripulantes de helicóptero abatido no estreito de Ormuz,What the US uses to rescue the crew of a downed helicopter in the Strait of Hormuz looks like,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Eleições no Peru: com mais de 98% de urnas apuradas, Keiko Fujimori lidera com pequena vantagem sobre Roberto Sánchez","Elections in Peru: with more than 98% of votes counted, Keiko Fujimori leads with a small advantage over Roberto Sánchez",0.0,neutral,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('more than 98%', 'PERCENT'), ('Keiko Fujimori', 'PERSON'), ('Roberto Sánchez', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que o Dia dos Namorados é em junho no Brasil e em fevereiro no resto do mundo?,Why is Valentine's Day in June in Brazil and in February in the rest of the world?,0.0,neutral,"[('Valentine', 'PERSON'), ('June', 'DATE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('February', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Elon Musk, o primeiro trilionário da história? SpaceX é avaliada em mais de R$ 9 trilhões antes de estrear na bolsa","Elon Musk, the first trillionaire in history? SpaceX is valued at more than R$9 trillion before debuting on the stock exchange",0.0,neutral,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('SpaceX', 'PERSON'), ('more than R$9 trillion', 'MONEY')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,El Niño está a caminho: os gráficos que mostram por que ele pode ser o fenômeno mais extremo em décadas (e quais seriam seus efeitos),El Niño is on the way: the graphics that show why it could be the most extreme phenomenon in decades (and what its effects could be),0.0,neutral,"[('El Niño', 'ORG'), ('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Lágrimas, protagonista brasileiro e mais jovem da Copa em campo: como foi México 2 x 0 África do Sul","Tears, Brazilian and youngest protagonist of the World Cup on the field: how it was Mexico 2 x 0 South Africa",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico 2', 'ORG'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Tudo que você precisa saber para conversar sobre a Copa do Mundo – mesmo sem gostar de futebol,Everything you need to know to talk about the World Cup – even if you don't like football,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,60 дней на переговоры? Что известно о будущем «меморандуме о взаимопонимании» Ирана и США,60 days for negotiations? What is known about the future “memorandum of understanding” between Iran and the United States,0.0,neutral,"[('60 days', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: ВСУ заявили о поражении двух НПЗ в Нижнекамске и каучукового завода в Тольятти","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: The Ukrainian Armed Forces announced the defeat of two oil refineries in Nizhnekamsk and a rubber plant in Tolyatti",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nizhnekamsk', 'ORG'), ('Tolyatti', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Первый погибший 2008 года рождения. Что мы узнали о потерях России в Украине к середине июня,The first victim was born in 2008. What we learned about Russian losses in Ukraine by mid-June,0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('2008', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('mid-June', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Умер британский художник Дэвид Хокни,British artist David Hockney dies,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('David Hockney', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Иранскую студентку депортировали на 30 лет из Минска за посты в соцсетях; новые задержания по делу ЕГУ. Главное в Беларуси за неделю,An Iranian student was deported from Minsk for 30 years for posts on social networks; new arrests in the YSU case. The main things in Belarus in a week,0.0,neutral,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Minsk', 'GPE'), ('30 years', 'DATE'), ('YSU', 'ORG'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Экс-президенту Южной Кореи добавили еще 30 лет к пожизненному сроку,Former South Korean President added another 30 years to life sentence,0.0,neutral,"[('South Korean', 'NORP'), ('another 30 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Умерла тайская принцесса Баджракитиябха — старшая дочь короля и защитница прав заключенных. Три года она была в коме,"Thai Princess Bajrakitiyabha, the king's eldest daughter and defender of prisoners' rights, has died. She was in a coma for three years",0.0,neutral,"[('Thai', 'NORP'), ('Bajrakitiyabha', 'GPE'), ('three years', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп выбрал нового главу Национальной разведки США вместе Тулси Габбард. Его предыдущего кандидата раскритиковали в Конгрессе,Trump chose a new head of US National Intelligence along with Tulsi Gabbard. His previous candidate was criticized in Congress,0.0,neutral,"[('US National Intelligence', 'ORG'), ('Tulsi Gabbard', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Компания SpaceX привлекла $75 млрд перед рекордным выходом на фондовый рынок. Маск может стать первым в мире триллионером,SpaceX has raised $75 billion ahead of a record-breaking stock market debut. Musk could become the world's first trillionaire,0.0,neutral,"[('SpaceX', 'PERSON'), ('$75 billion', 'MONEY'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"В Северной Америке начался самый дорогой в истории чемпионат мира по футболу, в первом матче победила Мексика","The most expensive World Cup in history began in North America, Mexico won the first match",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、戦争終結の合意に近づいていると表明　対イラン攻撃の中止を発表後,"Trump says he is close to a deal to end the war, after announcing a halt to attacks on Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英国防相が辞任、防衛費めぐり政府内で対立　スターマー氏の指導力に新たな打撃,UK Defense Minister resigns as government conflict over defense spending deals another blow to Starmer's leadership,-1.0,negative,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Starmer', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 英国防相の辞任、スターマー政権と防衛計画にどんな影響があるのか,[Commentary] What impact does the resignation of the UK Defense Secretary have on the Starmer government and defense planning?,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 メキシコで開幕、いきなり3人退場の波乱　色鮮やかな開会式も,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Opening in Mexico, turbulent with 3 people suddenly sent off, colorful opening ceremony too",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup] Opening', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本はどんなチームなのか　BBCスポーツ記者が分析,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] What kind of team is Japan? BBC sports reporter analyzes,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,北アイルランドの騒乱が収束　2夜続いたあと,Unrest in Northern Ireland comes to an end after two nights,0.0,neutral,"[('Northern Ireland', 'GPE'), ('two nights', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,アメリカとの国境線上にある図書館、カナダ側にも入り口を新設　トランプ政権の規制強化で, 所要時間 2,26","Video, A library on the border with the United States has a new entrance on the Canadian side. Due to the Trump administration's tightened regulations, the time required is 2.26",0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Canadian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('2.26', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,トランプ氏、米国家情報長官にクレイトン検事を指名　プルティ氏に批判集まり,"Trump nominates Prosecutor Clayton as Director of National Intelligence, drawing criticism from Pruti",1.0,positive,"[('Prosecutor Clayton', 'PERSON'), ('National Intelligence', 'ORG'), ('Pruti', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、ロシア深部の軍需工場をミサイル攻撃,Ukraine launches missile attack on military factory deep in Russia,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 優勝候補は？　興味深い対戦は？　今大会の特色を解説,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Who are the winning candidates? Any interesting matchups? Explaining the characteristics of this tournament,1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Iran yakanusha madai ya Trump, na kusema hakuna makubaliano yaliyoafikiwa.","Directly, Iran denied Trump's claims, and said no agreement had been reached.",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mataifa 10 ya Afrika yaliyo na uwezo mkubwa wa kiviwanda: Morocco yaipiku Afrika Kusini,10 African countries with the greatest industrial potential: Morocco surpasses South Africa,1.0,positive,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Marekani itabadili msimamo na 'kupinga' uhuru wa Taiwan?",Will the United States change its position and 'oppose' Taiwan's independence?,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tanzania inavyoufanya mtihani wa diplomasia ya dunia,Tanzania is doing the test of world diplomacy,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Mexico yaichapa Afrika Kusini, kadi nyekundu tatu zatolewa","World Cup 2026: Mexico beats South Africa, three red cards are issued",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Ifahamu droni ya baharini iliyotumiwa na Marekani kuwaokoa wanajeshi wake,Get to know the marine drone used by the United States to rescue its soldiers,0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ijumaa: Lewis Hall wa Newcastle ana nia ya kuondoka,Football rumors Friday: Newcastle's Lewis Hall is keen to leave,0.0,neutral,"[('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Newcastle', 'GPE'), ('Lewis Hall', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Netanyahu anatajwa kuwa kikwazo katika makubaliano ya amani kati ya Marekani na Iran?,Why is Netanyahu mentioned as an obstacle in the peace agreement between the United States and Iran?,1.0,positive,"[('Netanyahu', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Wachezaji 10 wenye asili ya Afrika wanaopeperusha bendera za Ulaya,World Cup 2026: 10 players of African origin flying European flags,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"'Ndoa ya pamoja' ilivyotibuka: Mabwana harusi 42 walifika, mabibi harusi hawakujitokeza","The 'joint marriage' was cured: 42 grooms showed up, the brides didn't show up",0.0,neutral,"[('42', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Nigeria killed more than 13,000 ‘terrorists’ in past year, president says","Nigeria killed more than 13,000 ‘terrorists’ in past year, president says",-1.0,negative,"[('more than 13,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('past year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Riots, violence, hate: Anti-immigrant unrest spells danger in Belfast","Riots, violence, hate: Anti-immigrant unrest spells danger in Belfast",0.0,neutral,"[('Belfast', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,New Zealand great Kane Williamson retires from international cricket,New Zealand great Kane Williamson retires from international cricket,1.0,positive,"[('New Zealand', 'GPE'), ('Kane Williamson', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iraq’s paramilitary groups say they will disarm. Will that ever happen?,Iraq’s paramilitary groups say they will disarm. Will that ever happen?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iraq', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,USA face tricky Paraguay in opening match of World Cup 2026,USA face tricky Paraguay in opening match of World Cup 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,China arrests US researcher it says is suspected of ‘spying’,China arrests US researcher it says is suspected of ‘spying’,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,One in 17 children is working: Here are the industries driving child labour,One in 17 children is working: Here are the industries driving child labour,0.0,neutral,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('17', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup 2026 opening day takeaways: Red cards, VAR and hydration breaks","World Cup 2026 opening day takeaways: Red cards, VAR and hydration breaks",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('VAR', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Air India crash: Grieving families say justice remains elusive a year later,Air India crash: Grieving families say justice remains elusive a year later,0.0,neutral,"[('Air India', 'ORG'), ('a year later', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Three killed as Ukraine and Russia exchange cross-border attacks,Three killed as Ukraine and Russia exchange cross-border attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"BSF, BGB discuss illegal and forced border crossings at DG-level talks","BSF, BGB discuss illegal and forced border crossings at DG-level talks",0.0,neutral,"[('BSF', 'ORG'), ('BGB', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,India summons U.S. Deputy Chief of Mission again after another attack on merchant ship with Indian crew,India summons U.S. Deputy Chief of Mission again after another attack on merchant ship with Indian crew,-1.0,negative,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Kane Williamson, former New Zealand captain, announces retirement from international cricket","Kane Williamson, former New Zealand captain, announces retirement from international cricket",0.0,neutral,"[('Kane Williamson', 'PERSON'), ('New Zealand', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Dissident Trinamool faction to approach Lok Sabha Speaker, seek recognition as 'real TMC'","Dissident Trinamool faction to approach Lok Sabha Speaker, seek recognition as 'real TMC'",0.0,neutral,"[('Dissident Trinamool', 'ORG'), ('Lok Sabha Speaker', 'PERSON'), ('TMC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Supreme Court dismisses Meenakshi Natarajan’s plea against rejection of Rajya Sabha candidature,Supreme Court dismisses Meenakshi Natarajan’s plea against rejection of Rajya Sabha candidature,0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Meenakshi Natarajan’s', 'PERSON'), ('Rajya Sabha', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia War LIVE: Tehran would not cede control of Hormuz under draft U.S. deal, says Iran media","West Asia War LIVE: Tehran would not cede control of Hormuz under draft U.S. deal, says Iran media",-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia War', 'LOC'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Beyond Congress-mukt Bharat: the shrinking space for regional parties,Beyond Congress-mukt Bharat: the shrinking space for regional parties,0.0,neutral,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Bharat', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Sensex jumps 1,695 points, Nifty rises 2% propelled by global rally as U.S. 'ends war' with Iran","Sensex jumps 1,695 points, Nifty rises 2% propelled by global rally as U.S. 'ends war' with Iran",-1.0,negative,"[('1,695', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nifty', 'ORG'), ('2%', 'PERCENT'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why is Nicobar debating elections? | Explained,Why is Nicobar debating elections? | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('Nicobar', 'ORG'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Nipah case in Kerala: Patient on ventilator, 77 contacts under watch","Nipah case in Kerala: Patient on ventilator, 77 contacts under watch",0.0,neutral,"[('Nipah', 'ORG'), ('Kerala', 'GPE'), ('77', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Tehran says 'nothing' finalised after Trump claims deal to end Iran war near,Tehran says 'nothing' finalised after Trump claims deal to end Iran war near,-1.0,negative,"[('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Flip flop or deliberate? - Unpacking Trump’s strategy on Iran,Flip flop or deliberate? - Unpacking Trump’s strategy on Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Thai Princess Bajrakitiyabha dies after more than three years in coma,Thai Princess Bajrakitiyabha dies after more than three years in coma,0.0,neutral,"[('Thai', 'NORP'), ('Bajrakitiyabha', 'GPE'), ('more than three years', 'DATE'), ('coma', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Why the economics make this the craziest World Cup ever,Why the economics make this the craziest World Cup ever,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'They destroyed the future': Palestinian anger at rise in Israeli demolitions in East Jerusalem,'They destroyed the future': Palestinian anger at rise in Israeli demolitions in East Jerusalem,0.0,neutral,"[('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('East Jerusalem', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Deadly Sudan drone strike targets funeral procession,Deadly Sudan drone strike targets funeral procession,0.0,neutral,"[('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"World Cup kicks off in Mexico with Shakira, dancing, and protests","World Cup kicks off in Mexico with Shakira, dancing, and protests",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nigeria evacuates citizens from South Africa as anti-migrant sentiment rises,Nigeria evacuates citizens from South Africa as anti-migrant sentiment rises,0.0,neutral,"[('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Artan to referee Uefa Super Cup after losing World Cup role,Artan to referee Uefa Super Cup after losing World Cup role,0.0,neutral,"[('Artan', 'GPE'), ('Uefa Super Cup', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Pope Leo visits Canary Islands to highlight perilous journeys of migrants,Pope Leo visits Canary Islands to highlight perilous journeys of migrants,0.0,neutral,"[('Pope Leo', 'PERSON'), ('Canary Islands', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran War Live Updates: Tense Calm Grips Mideast as Trump Again Claims Deal Is Close,Iran War Live Updates: Tense Calm Grips Mideast as Trump Again Claims Deal Is Close,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran War Live Updates: Tense Calm Grips Mideast', 'EVENT'), ('Trump Again Claims Deal', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Neither Peace Nor War: Iran Conflict Leaves World in Dangerous Limbo,Neither Peace Nor War: Iran Conflict Leaves World in Dangerous Limbo,-0.3333,negative,"[('Dangerous Limbo', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,World Cup Ticket Prices in Mexico City Too Expensive for Most Fans,World Cup Ticket Prices in Mexico City Too Expensive for Most Fans,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Ticket Prices', 'EVENT'), ('Mexico City', 'GPE'), ('Fans', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Bring the Kids and Grab Some Barbecue: A Day at the Ukrainian Drone Races,Bring the Kids and Grab Some Barbecue: A Day at the Ukrainian Drone Races,0.0,neutral,"[('A Day', 'DATE'), ('the Ukrainian Drone Races', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Plan Is Said to Pull a Third of Fighter Jets It Provides NATO for Europe,U.S. Plan Is Said to Pull a Third of Fighter Jets It Provides NATO for Europe,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Drones Flown Over North Korea Were Part of Martial Law Plot by Former South Korean President,Drones Flown Over North Korea Were Part of Martial Law Plot by Former South Korean President,0.0,neutral,"[('North Korea', 'GPE'), ('Martial Law Plot', 'ORG'), ('South Korean', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Globe-Spanning Collection of Children’s Art May Lose Its Home,A Globe-Spanning Collection of Children’s Art May Lose Its Home,0.0,neutral,"[('Globe-Spanning Collection of Children’s Art May Lose Its Home', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘Operation Pushkin’: Paris Trial Puts Spotlight on Rare-Book Heists,‘Operation Pushkin’: Paris Trial Puts Spotlight on Rare-Book Heists,0.0,neutral,"[('Paris', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"U.K. Defense Secretary Resigns, in a Blow to Starmer","U.K. Defense Secretary Resigns, in a Blow to Starmer",0.0,neutral,"[('U.K.', 'GPE'), ('Defense', 'ORG'), ('Resigns', 'PERSON'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"This Is Mexico and Canada’s World Cup, Too. Don’t Expect Unity.","This Is Mexico and Canada’s World Cup, Too. Don’t Expect Unity.",0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
