Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Una Siria en ruinas y dividida trata de levantarse un año después de la caída de Al Assad,A Syria in ruins and divided tries to rise a year after the fall of Al Assad,-0.125,"[('Syria', 'GPE'), ('a year', 'DATE'), ('Al Assad', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los mapas que muestran las islas caribeñas que están ayudando a EE.UU. en sus operaciones militares contra lanchas de Venezuela,The maps showing the Caribbean islands that are helping the US in its military operations against Venezuelan boats,-0.1,"[('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuelan', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Trump amenaza a México con un arancel del 5% si ""continúa incumpliendo"" el Tratado de Aguas suscrito con EE.UU. en 1944","Trump threatens Mexico with a 5% tariff if it ""continues to breach"" the Water Treaty signed with the US in 1944",0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('5%', 'PERCENT'), ('the Water Treaty', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('1944', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Honduras pide ejecutar una orden de captura de 2023 contra el expresidente Juan Orlando Hernández, indultado por Trump","Honduras asks to execute a 2023 arrest warrant against former president Juan Orlando Hernández, pardoned by Trump",-0.025,"[('Honduras', 'GPE'), ('2023', 'CARDINAL'), ('Juan Orlando Hernández', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La doble vida de Jasveen Sangha, la ""reina de la ketamina"" enjuiciada por la muerte del actor Matthew Perry","The double life of Jasveen Sangha, the ""queen of ketamine"" on trial for the death of actor Matthew Perry",0.0,"[('Jasveen Sangha', 'PERSON'), ('Matthew Perry', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इंडिगो संकटः कुछ के पैसे ख़त्म तो कई एयरपोर्ट पर ही सोने को मजबूर, दिल्ली एयरपोर्ट का आंखों देखा हाल","Indigo crisis: Some people ran out of money and many were forced to sleep at the airport, saw the condition of Delhi airport with our own eyes.",0.26666666666666666,"[('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"'भारत हमारे साथ ऐसा नहीं कर सकता', ये क्यों बोले ट्रंप","'India can't do this to us', why did Trump say this?",0.0,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,चुनाव सुधार पर लोकसभा में चर्चा, कांग्रेस सांसद मनीष तिवारी ने उठाए ये मुद्दे","Live, discussion in Lok Sabha on election reforms, Congress MP Manish Tiwari raised these issues",0.13636363636363635,"[('Lok Sabha', 'PERSON'), ('Congress', 'ORG'), ('Manish Tiwari', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ना आज़म ना कोहली, इस भारतीय क्रिकेटर को पाकिस्तान में गूगल पर सबसे ज़्यादा सर्च किया गया","Neither Azam nor Kohli, this Indian cricketer was most searched on Google in Pakistan.",0.5,"[('Azam', 'PERSON'), ('Kohli', 'PERSON'), ('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"केदारनाथ त्रासदी में 'मृत' घोषित व्यक्ति परिवार को पुणे में इस हाल में मिला, जानिए पूरी कहानी","The family of the person declared 'dead' in Kedarnath tragedy found in this condition in Pune, know the whole story",0.0,"[('Kedarnath', 'GPE'), ('Pune', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जब वसीम अकरम ने बाबर आज़म से पीएसएल में 'रोटी' की कहानी के बारे में पूछा,When Wasim Akram asked Babar Azam about 'Roti' story in PSL,0.0,"[('Wasim Akram', 'PERSON'), ('Babar Azam', 'PERSON'), ('Roti', 'PERSON'), ('PSL', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वंदे मातरम: पीएम मोदी और प्रियंका गांधी ने नेहरू पर क्या कहा, ओवैसी बोले- वफ़ादारी का सर्टिफ़िकेट न मांगा जाए","Vande Mataram: What did PM Modi and Priyanka Gandhi say on Nehru, Owaisi said - certificate of loyalty should not be asked",0.0,"[('PM Modi', 'ORG'), ('Priyanka Gandhi', 'PERSON'), ('Nehru', 'GPE'), ('Owaisi', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"थाईलैंड और कंबोडिया के बीच फिर छिड़ा संघर्ष, ट्रंप ने करवाया था शांति समझौता","Conflict broke out again between Thailand and Cambodia, Trump had made peace agreement",0.0,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत की वो पांच एयरलाइंस जिनकी उड़ान अचानक थम गई,Those five airlines of India whose flights suddenly stopped,0.0,"[('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Especialista americano defende classificar facções e milícias como terroristas: 'País está ameaçado, é preciso arriscar'","American expert defends classifying factions and militias as terrorists: 'The country is threatened, we have to take risks'",0.0,"[('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Seu psicólogo pode estar usando IA para registrar sessões de terapia: quais os riscos dessa prática?,Your psychologist may be using AI to record therapy sessions: what are the risks of this practice?,0.0,"[('AI', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O ciclone de 'altíssimo risco' que se aproxima do Rio Grande do Sul,The 'very high risk' cyclone approaching Rio Grande do Sul,0.10400000000000001,[]
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que 'O Agente Secreto' e Wagner Moura já fazem história na disputa pelo Globo de Ouro,Why 'The Secret Agent' and Wagner Moura are already making history in the dispute for the Golden Globe,-0.05000000000000002,"[(""The Secret Agent'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Wagner Moura', 'ORG'), ('the Golden Globe', 'FAC')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Wagner Moura e 'O Agente Secreto' são indicados ao Globo de Ouro 2026; veja todos os indicados,Wagner Moura and 'The Secret Agent' are nominated for the 2026 Golden Globe; see all nominees,-0.05000000000000002,"[('Wagner Moura', 'ORG'), (""The Secret Agent'"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A música brasileira que rodou o mundo, foi cantada por Stevie Wonder e virou hino do Partido Socialista francês","The Brazilian song that traveled the world, was sung by Stevie Wonder and became an anthem of the French Socialist Party",0.0,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('Stevie Wonder', 'PERSON'), ('the French Socialist Party', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que se sabe sobre o roubo das obras de Matisse e Portinari em São Paulo,What is known about the theft of the works of Matisse and Portinari in São Paulo,0.0,"[('Matisse', 'ORG'), ('Portinari', 'ORG'), ('São Paulo', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bukele: Brasil poderia imitar estratégia de segurança do presidente de El Salvador?,Bukele: Could Brazil imitate the security strategy of the president of El Salvador?,0.0,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('El Salvador', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Ave-maria: como uma oração milenar de analfabetos se tornou a mais popular prece católica,Hail Mary: how an ancient prayer of illiterate people became the most popular Catholic prayer,0.3666666666666667,"[('Catholic', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Возмущаются, но тихо». Как школьников и родителей в России вынуждают установить госмессенджер Max","“They are outraged, but quietly.” How schoolchildren and parents in Russia are forced to install the state messenger Max",-0.4000000000000001,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Max', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Чебоксарах в результате атаки украинских дронов есть пострадавшие","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: there are casualties in Cheboksary as a result of an attack by Ukrainian drones",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Cheboksary', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Зохран Мамдани решил переселиться в особняк мэров Нью-Йорка. Его критиковали за съем квартиры на льготных условиях,Zohran Mamdani decided to move into the mansion of the mayors of New York. He was criticized for renting an apartment on preferential terms,0.13636363636363635,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Мы — вымирающий вид». Белые южноафриканцы надеются уехать в США как беженцы,"""We are an endangered species."" White South Africans hope to go to US as refugees",0.0,"[('South Africans', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Paramount, возглавляемый близким к Трампу миллиардером, вступил в борьбу с Netflix за Warner Bros","Paramount, led by a billionaire close to Trump, entered the battle with Netflix for Warner Bros.",0.0,"[('Paramount', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Netflix for', 'ORG'), ('Warner Bros.', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Умер Мартин Парр, культовый стрит-фотограф и летописец британского абсурда","Martin Parr, iconic street photographer and chronicler of British absurdity, has died",0.25,"[('Martin Parr', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В США объявлены номинанты на «Золотой глобус». Больше всего номинаций — у «Битвы за битвой» с Ди Каприо,Nominees for the Golden Globes have been announced in the United States. “Battle after Battle” with DiCaprio has the most nominations,0.4,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Battle after Battle', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('DiCaprio', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,После переговоров с американцами Зеленский встретился в Лондоне с лидерами «коалиции желающих»,"After negotiations with the Americans, Zelensky met in London with the leaders of the “coalition of the willing”",0.25,"[('Americans', 'NORP'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В библиотеке Лувра из-за протечки пострадали книги и документы,Books and documents were damaged due to a leak in the Louvre library,-0.125,"[('Louvre', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Таиланд и Камбоджа возобновили бои, обвинив друг друга в нарушении перемирия, достигнутого при участии Трампа","Thailand and Cambodia resume fighting, accusing each other of violating the truce reached with the participation of Trump",-0.125,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Cambodia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英仏独ウクライナの4首脳、ロンドンで会談　ゼレンスキー氏は領土問題に懸念,"Four leaders of Britain, France, Germany and Ukraine meet in London; Mr. Zelenskiy is concerned about territorial issues",0.0,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('London', 'GPE'), ('Zelenskiy', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,東北地方の太平洋沖で震度6強の地震　津波注意報はすべて解除,Earthquake with a seismic intensity of 6+ off the coast of the Pacific Ocean in the Tohoku region; all tsunami warnings lifted,0.0,"[('6+', 'DATE'), ('the Pacific Ocean', 'LOC'), ('Tohoku', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,アサド政権崩壊から1年、シリアの人々が語る思い, 所要時間 1,41","Video, One year since the fall of the Assad regime, thoughts expressed by Syrian people, Duration 1,41",0.0,"[('One year', 'DATE'), ('Assad', 'PERSON'), ('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('1,41', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル首相、ガザ和平計画の「第2段階」は近いと,Israeli PM says 'second phase' of Gaza peace plan is near,0.05,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ニュージャージー州連邦検察トップが辞任、トランプ氏による任命は「違法」との控訴裁判断受け,"New Jersey's top federal prosecutor resigns after appeals court rules Trump's appointment is ""illegal""",0.04545454545454545,"[(""New Jersey's"", 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米パラマウント、ワーナーに新たな買収案提示　ネットフリックスに対抗,US Paramount presents new acquisition proposal to Warner to compete with Netflix,0.13636363636363635,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Paramount', 'ORG'), ('Warner', 'ORG'), ('Netflix', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシア政府、アメリカの「安全保障戦略」を前向き評価　自分たちの見方に沿うものだと,"Russian government positively evaluates US security strategy, saying it is in line with its own view",0.27575757575757576,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,イエス・キリストの生誕地ベツレヘム、3年ぶりにクリスマスの祝祭を再開　ガザでの停戦受け, 所要時間 0,45","Video, Bethlehem, birthplace of Jesus Christ, resumes Christmas festivities for the first time in three years following ceasefire in Gaza, Duration 0,45",0.125,"[('Bethlehem', 'ORG'), ('Jesus Christ', 'PERSON'), ('Christmas', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('three years', 'DATE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,チョルノービリ原発の外部シェルター、ドローン攻撃で「安全機能喪失」と国際原子力機関,"External shelter at Chernobyl nuclear power plant ``lost safety functions'' due to drone attack, International Atomic Energy Agency says",-0.041666666666666664,"[('Chernobyl', 'GPE'), ('International Atomic Energy Agency', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,「手遅れになる前に」「戦争は最悪の選択」兵役導入にドイツの学生たちが抗議, 所要時間 0,55","Video, ``Before it's too late'' ``War is the worst choice'' German students protest against introduction of military service, Duration 0,55",-0.35000000000000003,"[(""Before it's"", 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('War', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('German', 'NORP'), ('Duration 0,55', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Miji mikuu yabaki tulivu asubuhi ya Disemba 9 huku tahadhari zikiongezeka,Protests in Tanzania: Major cities remain quiet on the morning of December 9 as precautions increase,0.03125,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('the morning', 'TIME'), ('December 9', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Wakati muhimu zaidi wa kuiunga mkono Ukraine ni sasa- Washirika wa Ulaya","Directly, the most important time to support Ukraine is now - European partners",0.25,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Mapinduzi yaliyofeli nchini Benin: Je, kiongozi wa putsch ni nani?",The failed coup in Benin: Who is the leader of the putsch?,-0.5,"[('Benin', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Siasa za Afrika upinzani au uadui?,African politics opposition or hostility?,0.0,"[('African', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Liverpool, Man City zinamtaka Diomande","European football rumours: Liverpool, Man City want Diomande",0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Liverpool', 'GPE'), ('Man City', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Serikali ya Tanzania yawataka wananchi wasiokuwa na dharura kubaki nyumbani Disemba 9,The Tanzanian government asks citizens who do not have an emergency to stay at home on December 9,0.0,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('December 9', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, unaweza kumzuia mtoto wako kutumia mitandao ya kijamii?",Can you stop your child from using social media?,0.03333333333333333,[]
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Polisi Tanzania wakosolewa kwa kukamata watuhumiwa wakiwa wamevaa 'kininja',Tanzanian police are criticized for arresting suspects wearing 'kininja',0.0,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Hofu ya machafuko yazua ununuzi wa dharura,Protests in Tanzania: Fear of chaos sparks emergency shopping,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_09,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kuanzia Maria hadi Fatima:  Kwa nini mama yake Yesu ana zaidi ya majina elfu moja?,From Mary to Fatima: Why does the mother of Jesus have more than a thousand names?,0.5,"[('Mary', 'PERSON'), ('Fatima', 'PERSON'), ('Jesus', 'PERSON'), ('more than a thousand', 'CARDINAL')]"
