Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Cómo los tentáculos del narcotráfico se están infiltrando en Bélgica, un país en el corazón de la Unión Europea","How the tentacles of drug trafficking are infiltrating Belgium, a country at the heart of the European Union",0.0,"[('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('the European Union', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quiénes son Nasry Asfura y Salvador Nasralla, los candidatos enfrentados en un ""empate técnico"" en el recuento de las elecciones presidenciales en Honduras","Who are Nasry Asfura and Salvador Nasralla, the candidates facing a ""technical tie"" in the recount of the presidential elections in Honduras",0.0,"[('Nasry Asfura', 'PERSON'), ('Salvador Nasralla', 'PERSON'), ('Honduras', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La autoridad electoral de Honduras describe como ""empate técnico"" el cara a cara entre el candidato presidencial conservador Asfura, apoyado por Trump, y el centrista Nasralla","The Honduran electoral authority describes the face-to-face between the conservative presidential candidate Asfura, supported by Trump, and the centrist Nasralla as a ""technical tie""",0.0,"[('Honduran', 'NORP'), ('Asfura', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Nasralla', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Mi familia está allá, no puedo decir nada"": el miedo de los venezolanos en Miami a opinar sobre la amenaza militar de Trump contra su país","""My family is there, I can't say anything"": the fear of Venezuelans in Miami to give their opinion on Trump's military threat against their country",-0.1,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP'), ('Miami', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Joaquín Guzmán, uno de los hijos de ""El Chapo"", se declara culpable de cargos de narcotráfico en EE.UU.","Joaquín Guzmán, one of ""El Chapo's"" sons, pleads guilty to drug trafficking charges in the US.",-0.5,"[('Joaquín Guzmán', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), (""El Chapo's"", 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बांग्लादेश: ख़ालिदा ज़िया को पीएम मोदी ने हर संभव मदद करने की बात कही, क्या हैं इसके मायने","Bangladesh: PM Modi talked about providing all possible help to Khaleda Zia, what is its meaning?",0.0,"[('Khaleda Zia', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,'संचार साथी' ऐप पर उठे विवाद के बाद मंत्री ज्योतिरादित्य सिंधिया ने ये कहा","Minister Jyotiraditya Scindia said this after the controversy over Live, 'Sanchar Sathi' app",0.13636363636363635,"[('Jyotiraditya Scindia', 'PERSON'), (""Sanchar Sathi'"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"संचार साथी ऐप क्या है, जिसे हर फ़ोन में इंस्टॉल कराना चाहती है सरकार, विपक्ष ने घेरा","What is Sanchar Sathi app, which the government wants to install in every phone, the opposition surrounded it",0.2,"[('Sanchar Sathi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,एसआईआर को लेकर बांग्लादेश से सटे पश्चिम बंगाल के इलाक़ों में क्यों है डर- ग्राउंड रिपोर्ट,Why is there fear in the areas of West Bengal adjacent to Bangladesh regarding SIR – Ground Report,0.0,"[('West Bengal', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भुला दी गई इन तस्वीरों में दिखी वे महिलाएं जिन्होंने आज़ादी की लड़ाई में दिखाया दमखम,These forgotten pictures show the women who showed strength in the fight for freedom,0.0,[]
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,क्या सच में सर्दियां रोमांस का मौसम है?,Is winter really the season of romance?,0.2,"[('winter', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"आईएमएफ़ ने भारत को दिया 'सी' ग्रेड, जीडीपी के आंकड़ों पर क्यों उठ रहे हैं सवाल","IMF gave 'C' grade to India, why questions are being raised on GDP figures",0.0,"[('IMF', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जया बोलीं- इसलिए मैंने अमिताभ बच्चन से शादी की,Jaya said- That's why I married Amitabh Bachchan,0.25,"[('Amitabh Bachchan', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,22 करोड़ जुए में जीतने वाले पति-पत्नी को पुलिस ने क्यों पकड़ा?,Why did the police catch the husband and wife who won Rs 22 crore in gambling?,0.0,"[('22', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A corrida contra o tempo para descobrir espécies da Amazônia antes que desapareçam,The race against time to discover Amazonian species before they disappear,0.0,"[('Amazonian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A facção 'evangélica' que emerge como terceira força do crime organizado do Brasil,The 'evangelical' faction that emerges as the third force in organized crime in Brazil,0.0,"[('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Isca de raiva' das redes sociais é eleita termo do ano por dicionário britânico,'Rage bait' from social media is named term of the year by British dictionary,0.016666666666666666,"[('the year', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A brasileira que viraliza traduzindo o caos da IA: 'As pessoas estão perdidas',The Brazilian who goes viral translating the chaos of AI: 'People are lost',0.0,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Bairros flutuantes, a ousada solução holandesa para um mundo que está afundando no mar","Floating neighborhoods, the bold Dutch solution for a world that is sinking into the sea",0.3333333333333333,"[('Dutch', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A tecnologia revolucionária que promete detectar tsunamis antes que cheguem à praia,The revolutionary technology that promises to detect tsunamis before they reach the beach,0.0,[]
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A polêmica 'prova para pais' na Dinamarca que tirou bebês de suas famílias: 'queriam saber se eu era civilizada',The controversial 'parent test' in Denmark that took babies from their families: 'they wanted to know if I was civilized',0.47500000000000003,"[('Denmark', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Vaca Muerta: a nova riqueza do boom do petróleo da Argentina,Vaca Muerta: the new wealth of Argentina's oil boom,0.13636363636363635,"[('Vaca Muerta', 'PERSON'), ('Argentina', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A situação dos voos na Venezuela após anúncios de Trump sobre o fechamento do espaço aéreo do país,The situation with flights in Venezuela after Trump's announcements about the closure of the country's airspace,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que a compra de uma seguradora para agentes do serviço secreto dos EUA revela sobre a onda de investimentos da China no Ocidente,What the purchase of an insurance company for US Secret Service agents reveals about China's wave of investment in the West,-0.4,"[('US Secret Service', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Путин примет Уиткоффа после доклада генералов о продвижении на фронте","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Putin will receive Witkoff after the generals report on progress at the front",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Witkoff', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Нью-Йорке начинается процесс над Луиджи Манджоне. Его обвиняют в убийстве главы страховой компании, всколыхнувшем США","The trial of Luigi Mangione begins in New York. He is accused of murdering the head of an insurance company, which rocked the United States.",0.13636363636363635,"[('Luigi Mangione', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Оказалось, что у меня высокий уровень «вечных химикатов» в крови. Что это за вещества и что я могу с этим сделать?",It turned out that I had high levels of “eternal chemicals” in my blood. What are these substances and what can I do about it?,0.16,[]
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Вопрос территорий — самый сложный». Зеленский рассказал о трех приоритетах перед переговорами Уиткоффа в Москве о мирном плане,“The issue of territories is the most difficult.” Zelensky spoke about three priorities ahead of Witkoff's peace plan talks in Moscow,0.0,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('about three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Witkoff', 'ORG'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Южной Корее хакеры взломали более 120 тысяч домашних камер наблюдения ради откровенных видео,"In South Korea, hackers hacked more than 120 thousand home surveillance cameras for explicit videos.",0.5,"[('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('more than 120 thousand', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Пожар в высотке: как правильно действовать, чтобы не погибнуть?",Fire in a high-rise building: how to act correctly so as not to die?,0.0,[]
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Оксфордский словарь назвал словом года rage bait. Что это такое?,The Oxford Dictionary named rage bait as its word of the year. What is it?,0.0,"[('The Oxford Dictionary', 'ORG'), ('the year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Сингапуре за два дня повесили трех человек. Казней за наркотрафик становится все больше,Three people were hanged in Singapore in two days. More and more executions for drug trafficking are taking place,0.5,"[('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Singapore', 'GPE'), ('two days', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Азербайджане арестовали Али Керимли — лидера одной из старейших оппозиционных партий,"Ali Karimli, the leader of one of the oldest opposition parties, was arrested in Azerbaijan.",0.0,"[('Ali Karimli', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Azerbaijan', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В ЮАР радиоведущую и еще четырех человек задержали по подозрению в вербовке в российскую армию на войну в Украине,"In South Africa, a radio presenter and four other people were detained on suspicion of recruiting into the Russian army for the war in Ukraine",-0.0625,"[('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ゼレンスキー氏、領土問題が和平交渉で「最も困難」　 米特使はプーチン氏と会談へ,Zelenskiy says territorial issue is 'the most difficult' in peace talks; US envoy to meet with Putin,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヴェネズエラ「麻薬船」への追い打ち攻撃、米海軍司令官が命令とホワイトハウス,US Navy commander orders White House attack on drug ship in Venezuela,0.0,"[('US Navy', 'ORG'), ('White House', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ氏、詐欺で禁錮刑の経営者を減刑　刑期開始から数日で釈放,Trump commutes sentence of businessman sentenced to prison for fraud and releases him within days of starting sentence,0.0,"[('days', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,IPカメラ12万台以上をハッキング、性的搾取映像を作成した疑い　韓国で4人逮捕,"Four people arrested in South Korea on suspicion of hacking over 120,000 IP cameras and creating sexual exploitation videos",0.5,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Korea', 'GPE'), ('120,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('IP', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,東南アジア・南アジアを襲う豪雨、洪水や土砂崩れでの被害拡大, 所要時間 1,47","Video, Expanding damage from heavy rains, floods and landslides hitting Southeast Asia and South Asia, Required time 1,47",-0.2,"[('Southeast Asia', 'LOC'), ('South Asia', 'LOC'), ('1,47', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英劇作家サー・トム・ストッパード氏が死去　知性と思索と遊び心,"British playwright Sir Tom Stoppard dies: intelligence, speculation and playfulness",0.0,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Tom Stoppard', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,シンガポールが2日間で3人の死刑執行、薬物犯罪で　今年は2003年以降で最多,"Singapore executes 3 people in 2 days for drug crimes this year, the highest number since 2003",0.0,"[('Singapore', 'GPE'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('2 days', 'DATE'), ('this year', 'DATE'), ('2003', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,今年の単語は「レイジ・ベイト」に、英オックスフォード英語辞典　意図的に「炎上」狙うコンテンツの意味,"This year's word is ""rage bait,"" according to the Oxford English Dictionary, meaning content that intentionally aims to cause a stir.",0.0,"[('year', 'DATE'), ('English Dictionary', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スリランカ、洪水と土砂崩れで死者330人超　非常事態を宣言,Sri Lanka declares state of emergency as floods and landslides kill more than 330 people,0.5,"[('Sri Lanka', 'PERSON'), ('more than 330', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Zelensky asema ardhi ya Ukraine ndio suala gumu katika mazungumzo na Urusi","Directly, Zelensky says the land of Ukraine is the most difficult issue in negotiations with Russia",0.033333333333333326,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"'Je, huu ndio mwanzo wa maisha ya Liverpool bila Salah?'",'Is this the beginning of Liverpool's life without Salah?',0.0,"[('Liverpool', 'ORG'), ('Salah', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Vita vya Siku 12; Iran yatoa video za mashambulizi ya Israel kwenye kituo cha mfumo wa ulinzi,12 Day War; Iran releases videos of Israeli attacks on defense system facilities,0.0,"[('12 Day War', 'DATE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Jumanne: Trafford anataka kuondoka Manchester City,Football rumors Tuesday: Trafford wants to leave Manchester City,0.2,"[('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Trafford', 'ORG'), ('Manchester City', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mandamano Tanzania: Maswali 9 magumu kwa Tume ya Oktoba 29,Mandamano Tanzania: 9 difficult questions for the October 29 Commission,-0.5,"[('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('October 29', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Urusi yasema matamshi ya NATO juu ya vita vya Ukraine ni kutowajibika,Russia says NATO's comments on the war in Ukraine are irresponsible,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi bakteria kwenye uke wanavyoweza kuboresha afya yako,How bacteria in the vagina can improve your health,0.0,[]
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mchungaji na bibi harusi watekwa nyara katika mashambulizi ya hivi punde Nigeria,A pastor and a bride have been kidnapped in the latest attacks in Nigeria,0.5,"[('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Nchi 10 za Afrika zilizoathirika na tathmini mpya  ya 'Green Card', Tanzania ipo?","10 African countries affected by the new 'Green Card' assessment, Tanzania is there?",-0.02121212121212122,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), (""Green Card'"", 'PRODUCT'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maelfu ya watu wanadhaniwa kuathiriwa na kemikali hatari wakati wa maandamano ya kupinga serikali Georgia,Thousands of people are thought to have been exposed to dangerous chemicals during anti-government protests in Georgia,-0.6,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')]"
