Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo pasó Escocia de ser la capital de los asesinatos en Europa a uno de los lugares más seguros del mundo,How Scotland went from being the murder capital of Europe to one of the safest places in the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Scotland', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Rivales encarnizados: el esperado partido en el que Messi enfrentará por primera vez a Inglaterra,Fierce rivals: the long-awaited match in which Messi will face England for the first time,0.0,neutral,"[('Fierce', 'ORG'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Por qué el declive de población deja al descubierto las antiguas divisiones de Alemania,Why population decline exposes Germany's ancient divisions,0.0,neutral,"[('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"La historia de Ruth Ellis, la última mujer en ser ejecutada en la horca en Reino Unido y a la que ahora el rey indultó","The story of Ruth Ellis, the last woman to be hanged in the United Kingdom and who has now been pardoned by the king",0.0,neutral,"[('Ruth Ellis', 'PERSON'), ('the United Kingdom', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Cuerpo de teléfono"": cómo la tecnología nos arruga el cuello y debilita las manos","""Phone body"": how technology wrinkles our necks and weakens our hands",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Así te lo contamos: Argentina vence a Suiza y peleará con Inglaterra por un puesto en la final del Mundial,This is how we tell you: Argentina beats Switzerland and will fight with England for a place in the World Cup final,0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere a los 25 años Jayden Adams, futbolista sudafricano que disputó el Mundial 2026","Jayden Adams, South African footballer who played in the 2026 World Cup, dies at 25",0.0,neutral,"[('Jayden Adams', 'PERSON'), ('South African', 'NORP'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('25', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Llevamos el almuerzo al trabajo durante 10 años y pudimos jubilarnos a los 35 y 40 años""","""We brought lunch to work for 10 years and were able to retire at ages 35 and 40""",0.0,neutral,"[('10 years', 'DATE'), ('ages 35 and 40', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Ponte a prueba: ¿eres capaz de detectar un rostro generado por IA?,Test yourself: can you detect a face generated by AI?,0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Sexo, estrategia y poder"": cómo las mujeres moldean ""La Odisea"", el clásico de Homero que Christopher Nolan lleva a la pantalla","""Sex, strategy and power"": how women shape ""The Odyssey"", the Homer classic that Christopher Nolan brings to the screen",0.0,neutral,"[('The Odyssey', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Christopher Nolan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वियतनाम नाव हादसा: लाइफ़ जैकेट पहनने के बावजूद कैसे हुई 15 भारतीयों की मौत, चश्मदीद ने क्या बताया","Vietnam boat accident: How 15 Indians died despite wearing life jackets, what eyewitness told",0.0,neutral,"[('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,ईरान बोला- एकतरफ़ा डील का दौर अब ख़त्म, अगले आदेश तक होर्मुज़ स्ट्रेट बंद","Live, Iran said - the era of one-sided deal is now over, Hormuz Strait closed till further orders",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hormuz Strait', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ओमान तट के पास जहाज़ पर हमला: 10 भारतीयों को बचाया गया, एक अब भी लापता","Ship attack off Oman coast: 10 Indians rescued, one still missing",-1.0,negative,"[('Oman', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'सतलुज' दुनियाभर में ओटीटी प्लेटफ़ॉर्म से हटाई गई, पंजाब में कई जगह फ़िल्म की स्क्रीनिंग जारी","'Sutlej' removed from OTT platforms worldwide, screening of the film continues at many places in Punjab",0.0,neutral,"[('Sutlej', 'PERSON'), ('OTT', 'ORG'), ('Punjab', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"इंग्लैंड-आयरलैंड में सिरीज़ हारने के बाद गौतम गंभीर और श्रेयस अय्यर पर सवाल, क्या कह रहे हैं पूर्व खिलाड़ी और फैंस","Questions on Gautam Gambhir and Shreyas Iyer after losing the series in England-Ireland, what are former players and fans saying?",0.0,neutral,"[('Gautam Gambhir', 'PERSON'), ('Shreyas Iyer', 'PERSON'), ('England-Ireland', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बांकीपुर उप चुनाव: प्रशांत किशोर और बीजेपी-आरजेडी के उम्मीदवारों पर क्या कह रहे हैं लोग और क्या हैं ज़मीनी मुद्दे,Bankipur by-election: What are people saying about Prashant Kishor and BJP-RJD candidates and what are the ground issues,0.0,neutral,"[('Bankipur', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ई20 पेट्रोल की सबसे बड़ी क़ीमत कौन चुका रहा है?,Who is paying the highest price for E20 petrol?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ट्रंप की धमकी के बाद मोजतबा ख़ामेनेई का आया संदेश, 'ख़ून का बदला' लेने की कही बात","Mojtaba Khamenei's message after Trump's threat, talks about taking 'blood revenge'",0.0,neutral,"[(""Mojtaba Khamenei's"", 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,प्रेग्नेंसी में ली गई दवाइयां क्या बच्चे तक पहुंचती हैं? भारत में चल रहा एक्सपेरिमेंट देगा जवाब,Do the medicines taken during pregnancy reach the baby? The experiment going on in India will give the answer,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,नरोत्तम मिश्रा को दतिया में क्यों नहीं मिला टिकट और आरएसएस की क्या है चर्चा?,Why did Narottam Mishra not get ticket in Datia and what is the discussion about RSS?,0.0,neutral,"[('Narottam Mishra', 'PERSON'), ('Datia', 'GPE'), ('RSS', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Carta de Bolsonaro é tentativa de desviar atenção de denúncia contra Valdemar e possível vídeo de Flávio, diz cientista político","Bolsonaro's letter is an attempt to divert attention from the complaint against Valdemar and a possible video of Flávio, says political scientist",0.0,neutral,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Valdemar', 'GPE'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Polícia investiga morte de Jayden Adams, jogador que disputou a Copa pela África do Sul","Police investigate death of Jayden Adams, player who played in the World Cup for South Africa",-1.0,negative,"[('Jayden Adams', 'PERSON'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem são os jogadores que vão liderar a Seleção na próxima Copa e tentar acabar com jejum do Brasil,Who are the players who will lead the Seleção in the next World Cup and try to end Brazil's fast,0.0,neutral,"[('Seleção', 'ORG'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que 'Wonderwall' do Oasis se tornou hino da Inglaterra na Copa do Mundo,Why Oasis' 'Wonderwall' became England's World Cup anthem,0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As mentiras que alimentam ataques contra profissionais de saúde que combatem o ebola: 'Disseram que não era real',The lies that fuel attacks against health professionals fighting Ebola: 'They said it wasn't real',-1.0,negative,[]
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,São Sebastião: como um soldado romano brutalmente torturado até a morte foi santificado e virou ícone gay,Saint Sebastian: how a Roman soldier brutally tortured to death was sanctified and became a gay icon,-1.0,negative,"[('Saint Sebastian', 'PERSON'), ('Roman', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As micronações que bilionários das criptomoedas tentam construir em nome da liberdade a qualquer custo,The micronations that cryptocurrency billionaires try to build in the name of freedom at any cost,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,As novas regras do governo para a publicidade de bets após polêmica na Copa do Mundo: veja o que é proibido,The government's new rules for betting advertising after the World Cup controversy: see what is prohibited,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Por que o governo Trump, que capturou Maduro, está ajudando a Venezuela a lidar com os terremotos?","Why is the Trump administration, which captured Maduro, helping Venezuela deal with earthquakes?",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Maduro', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que PF e Flávio Dino apontam presidente do PL como suspeito de indicar emendas irregularmente,Why PF and Flávio Dino point to PL president as suspected of irregularly indicating amendments,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Dino', 'PERSON'), ('PL', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Влиятельный сенатор-республиканец Линдси Грэм скоропостижно умер,Influential Republican Senator Lindsey Graham died suddenly,0.0,neutral,"[('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Обострение ситуации вокруг Ирана: США нанесли новые удары, КСИР перекрыл Ормуз, Моджтаба Хаменеи обещает отомстить за убийство отца","Aggravation of the situation around Iran: the US launched new strikes, the IRGC blocked Hormuz, Mojtaba Khamenei promises to take revenge for the murder of his father",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('IRGC', 'ORG'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('Mojtaba Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: сообщения об ударе по Сызрани; пятеро погибших после субботней бомбардировки Сум","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: reports of an attack on Syzran; five dead after Saturday's bombing of Sumy",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Syzran', 'GPE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Saturday', 'DATE'), ('Sumy', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Англия победила Норвегию и сыграет с Аргентиной в полуфинале ЧМ-2026. Главные звезды Кейн и Холанд забить не смогли,England defeated Norway and will play Argentina in the semi-finals of the 2026 World Cup. Main stars Kane and Holland failed to score,-1.0,negative,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Kane', 'PERSON'), ('Holland', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Проблема дальних космических миссий: что происходит с мозгом астронавтов и в чем главная опасность?,The problem of long-distance space missions: what happens to the astronauts’ brains and what is the main danger?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Почему женщины переносят жару хуже мужчин?,Why do women tolerate heat worse than men?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Apple подала иск против компании OpenAI и ее сотрудников, обвинив их в краже коммерческой тайны","Apple filed a lawsuit against OpenAI and its employees, accusing them of stealing trade secrets",0.0,neutral,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('OpenAI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Викинг против англосакса: Эрлинг Холанд и Гарри Кейн выводят Норвегию и Англию на решающий бой,Viking vs Anglo-Saxon: Erling Haaland and Harry Kane lead Norway and England to decisive battle,0.0,neutral,"[('Harry Kane', 'PERSON'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('England', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Трамп заявил о готовности нанести ракетный удар по Ирану в случае покушения на него,Trump announced his readiness to launch a missile strike on Iran in the event of an assassination attempt,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Анализ: как долго Россия сможет обстреливать столицу Украины баллистическими ракетами?,Analysis: How long can Russia bombard the Ukrainian capital with ballistic missiles?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカが新たにイラン攻撃、イランはホルムズ海峡を当面閉じると発表,"US launches new attack on Iran, Iran announces closure of Strait of Hormuz for the time being",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】イングランド、ノルウェーに逆転勝ちでベスト4　ベリンガム2得点,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] England come from behind to beat Norway to reach top 4, Bellingham scores 2 goals",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('4', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bellingham', 'PERSON'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米移民当局ICE、テキサスで出勤途中の男性を射殺　取締作戦の対象者ではなかったと国土安全保障省,US immigration agency ICE fatally shoots man on his way to work in Texas; Department of Homeland Security says he was not the target of an enforcement operation,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Texas', 'GPE'), ('Department of Homeland Security', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカ、ホルムズ海峡での船舶攻撃の停止を誓うようイランに要求,US asks Iran to pledge to stop attacking ships in Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 スペイン、ベルギー破りベスト4　メリノが土壇場決勝ゴール,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Spain defeats Belgium in the final four; Merino scores last-minute winning goal,1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Belgium', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Merino', 'PERSON'), ('last-minute', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米アップル、オープンAIと従業員を提訴　企業秘密を盗んだと主張,"Apple sues OpenAI and employees, claiming they stole trade secrets",0.0,neutral,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('OpenAI', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ガザでW杯観戦会を開催の活動家、イスラエル軍に殺される　パレスチナ人から悼む声,Activist holding World Cup watching party in Gaza killed by Israeli army; voices of mourning from Palestinians,-1.0,negative,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Palestinians', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,バーナム氏、次のイギリス首相になる見通し　労働党議員322人が党首指名投票で支持,Burnham expected to become the next British Prime Minister; 322 Labor Party MPs support him in leadership nomination vote,0.0,neutral,"[('Burnham', 'ORG'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('322', 'CARDINAL'), ('Labor Party', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,スペイン、山火事で12人死亡　南欧で熱波続く,12 people killed in wildfires in Spain; heatwave continues in southern Europe,-1.0,negative,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、クリミア沖で燃料輸送中のロシア船を攻撃　燃料供給網への攻撃強化,"Ukraine attacks a Russian ship transporting fuel off the coast of Crimea, intensifying attacks on the fuel supply network",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Crimea', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yafanya mashambulizi mapya; Iran yafunga mlango wa bahari wa Hormuz","Immediately, the United States makes a new attack; Iran closes the Strait of Hormuz",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mikutano mitano mikubwa zaidi ya kidini duniani,The five largest religious gatherings in the world,0.0,neutral,"[('five', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Mlo ulioniacha na vimelea 38 kwenye ubongo','The diet that left me with 38 parasites in my brain',0.0,neutral,"[('38', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumapili: Man Utd na Liverpool vitani kwa Joao Gomes,European football rumors on Sunday: Man Utd and Liverpool in battle for Joao Gomes,0.0,neutral,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Sunday', 'DATE'), ('Liverpool', 'ORG'), ('Joao Gomes', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jumuiya ya Madola yapendekeza kesi ya Tundu Lissu 'imalizwe'  ndani ya siku 30,The Commonwealth recommends the Tundu Lissu case be 'ended' within 30 days,0.0,neutral,"[('Commonwealth', 'ORG'), ('Tundu Lissu', 'PERSON'), ('30 days', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mambo 5 ambayo huenda huyajui kumhusu Erling Haaland,5 things you may not know about Erling Haaland,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Erling Haaland', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Lazima tulipize kisasi mauaji ya Ali Khamenei - Iran,We must avenge the assassination of Ali Khamenei - Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('Ali Khamenei - Iran', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Mwanamume asimulia alivyonusurika shambulio la simba,A man tells how he survived a lion attack,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tunafanya mazungumzo na Iran ila usitishaji mapigano umefutiliwa mbali - Trump,We are negotiating with Iran but the ceasefire has been scrapped - Trump,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini Uturuki iliwazawadia viongozi wa NATO bastola zenye risasi sita?,Why did Turkey reward NATO leaders with six-shot pistols?,-1.0,negative,"[('Turkey', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('six', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US CENTCOM completes third round of strikes on Iran,US CENTCOM completes third round of strikes on Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US attacks Iran overnight; Tehran targets US sites in the region,US attacks Iran overnight; Tehran targets US sites in the region,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('overnight', 'TIME'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Texas shootout: All to know before France-Spain clash in World Cup semi,Texas shootout: All to know before France-Spain clash in World Cup semi,0.0,neutral,"[('Texas', 'GPE'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,IRGC vows ‘crushing response’ to any further US attacks,IRGC vows ‘crushing response’ to any further US attacks,-1.0,negative,"[('IRGC', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Lindsey Graham, one of Israel’s strongest US Senate allies, dies at 71","Lindsey Graham, one of Israel’s strongest US Senate allies, dies at 71",0.0,neutral,"[('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('71', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ghana slavery apology: Why many descendants say words are not enough,Ghana slavery apology: Why many descendants say words are not enough,0.0,neutral,"[('Ghana', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Sheikh Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani, architect of modern Qatar","Sheikh Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani, architect of modern Qatar",0.0,neutral,"[('Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani', 'PERSON'), ('Qatar', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Former Emir of Qatar Sheikh Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani dies aged 74,Former Emir of Qatar Sheikh Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani dies aged 74,0.0,neutral,"[('Emir', 'PERSON'), ('Qatar', 'GPE'), ('Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani', 'PERSON'), ('74', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US forces launch new strikes on Iran; Tehran closes Strait of Hormuz,US forces launch new strikes on Iran; Tehran closes Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Why doesn’t Indian PM Modi hold unscripted press conferences?,Why doesn’t Indian PM Modi hold unscripted press conferences?,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The voice of the south,The voice of the south,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,S. Janaki’s early life in Telangana village shaped her interest in film music,S. Janaki’s early life in Telangana village shaped her interest in film music,0.0,neutral,"[('S. Janaki’s', 'PERSON'), ('Telangana village', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"S. Janaki: Not Kerala-born, but forever its voice","S. Janaki: Not Kerala-born, but forever its voice",0.0,neutral,"[('S. Janaki', 'PERSON'), ('Kerala', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,When S. Janaki rejected the Padma Bhushan,When S. Janaki rejected the Padma Bhushan,0.0,neutral,"[('S. Janaki', 'PERSON'), ('Bhushan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia war LIVE: 10 Indians rescued, one missing after vessel attacked off Oman","West Asia war LIVE: 10 Indians rescued, one missing after vessel attacked off Oman",-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Indians', 'NORP'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Oman', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,U.S. Senator Lindsey Graham passes away at 71,U.S. Senator Lindsey Graham passes away at 71,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON'), ('71', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Wayanad debris slip: Lone missing project manager’s body recovered; death toll rises to eight,Wayanad debris slip: Lone missing project manager’s body recovered; death toll rises to eight,-1.0,negative,"[('Wayanad', 'ORG'), ('Lone', 'ORG'), ('eight', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Price of peace in the time of war,Price of peace in the time of war,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"U.S., U.K., and 12 other nations reaffirm 2016 ruling invalidating China’s claims in South China Sea","U.S., U.K., and 12 other nations reaffirm 2016 ruling invalidating China’s claims in South China Sea",0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('U.K.', 'GPE'), ('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('2016', 'DATE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('South China Sea', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_12,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,CJP protest day 23: Wangchuk’s health worsens as fast enters 15th day,CJP protest day 23: Wangchuk’s health worsens as fast enters 15th day,0.0,neutral,"[('CJP', 'ORG'), ('day 23', 'DATE'), ('Wangchuk', 'ORG'), ('15th day', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US launches fresh strikes as Iran closes Strait of Hormuz,US launches fresh strikes as Iran closes Strait of Hormuz,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Strait', 'LOC'), ('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US Senator and close Trump ally Lindsey Graham dies after 'brief and sudden illness',US Senator and close Trump ally Lindsey Graham dies after 'brief and sudden illness',0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Lindsey Graham', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,China evacuates nearly two million people as powerful typhoon makes landfall,China evacuates nearly two million people as powerful typhoon makes landfall,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('nearly two million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,At least two killed in Toronto street festival shooting,At least two killed in Toronto street festival shooting,-1.0,negative,"[('At least two', 'CARDINAL'), ('Toronto', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,T. rex could become most expensive fossil ever - but it's a ​problem for scientists,T. rex could become most expensive fossil ever - but it's a ​problem for scientists,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump administration subpoenas New York Times journalists over Air Force One reporting,Trump administration subpoenas New York Times journalists over Air Force One reporting,0.0,neutral,"[('New York Times', 'ORG'), ('Air Force', 'ORG'), ('One', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Spain battles to contain one of its deadliest wildfires as at least 12 killed,Spain battles to contain one of its deadliest wildfires as at least 12 killed,-1.0,negative,"[('Spain', 'GPE'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('at least 12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US Democrat Ro Khanna says he was detained by armed Israeli settlers,US Democrat Ro Khanna says he was detained by armed Israeli settlers,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Ro Khanna', 'PERSON'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Muslim judge in India faces death threats after convicting 'cow vigilantes',Muslim judge in India faces death threats after convicting 'cow vigilantes',-1.0,negative,"[('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Polish PM pledges memorial to victims of WW2 'genocide by Ukrainian nationalists',Polish PM pledges memorial to victims of WW2 'genocide by Ukrainian nationalists',0.0,neutral,"[('Polish', 'NORP'), ('WW2', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Hard-Liners in Iran Want to Keep Fighting America,Hard-Liners in Iran Want to Keep Fighting America,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Keep Fighting America', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Putin Turned Japan Into a Den of Spies,How Putin Turned Japan Into a Den of Spies,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Inside Herat, Where a Taliban Campaign Targets a Cosmopolitan Outpost","Inside Herat, Where a Taliban Campaign Targets a Cosmopolitan Outpost",0.0,neutral,"[('Inside Herat', 'ORG'), ('Taliban', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Typhoon Bavi Hits China, Causing Evacuations, Floods and Flight Delays","Typhoon Bavi Hits China, Causing Evacuations, Floods and Flight Delays",0.0,neutral,"[('Typhoon Bavi Hits', 'FAC'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Causing Evacuations', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As India Erases Its Colonial Past, Delhi’s Elite Feel Targeted","As India Erases Its Colonial Past, Delhi’s Elite Feel Targeted",0.0,neutral,"[('India Erases Its Colonial Past', 'ORG'), ('Delhi’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Man Arrested in Killing of U.K. Ex-Lawmaker Is Released,Man Arrested in Killing of U.K. Ex-Lawmaker Is Released,-1.0,negative,"[('Killing', 'GPE'), ('U.K. Ex-Lawmaker Is Released', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,England and Norway Resurrect a Rivalry for the World Cup,England and Norway Resurrect a Rivalry for the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('Norway Resurrect a Rivalry', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Wildfire Killed 12 People in Southern Spain. Here’s the Latest.,A Wildfire Killed 12 People in Southern Spain. Here’s the Latest.,-1.0,negative,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('Southern Spain', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘They Don’t Need People’: The Workers Left Behind by China’s Robot Drive,‘They Don’t Need People’: The Workers Left Behind by China’s Robot Drive,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_12,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,U.S. Citizen Tests Positive for Ebola in Democratic Republic of Congo,U.S. Citizen Tests Positive for Ebola in Democratic Republic of Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Democratic Republic of Congo', 'GPE')]"
