Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los niños ucranianos a los que Rusia entrena para luchar contra su propio país,The Ukrainian children whom Russia trains to fight against their own country,0.6,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Franco Parisi, el candidato antisistema que sorprendió al ser tercero en las elecciones de Chile y cuyos votos serán clave para el balotaje entre Kast y Jara","Franco Parisi, the anti-system candidate who surprised by being third in the Chilean elections and whose votes will be key for the runoff between Kast and Jara",0.03333333333333333,"[('Franco Parisi', 'GPE'), ('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Chilean', 'NORP'), ('Kast', 'LOC'), ('Jara', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Condenan a muerte a Sheikh Hasina, el ícono de la democracia en Bangladesh que se convirtió en autócrata","Sheikh Hasina, the icon of democracy in Bangladesh who became an autocrat, is sentenced to death",0.0,"[('Hasina', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo China ganó con sorprendente rapidez la carrera mundial por las baterías para vehículos eléctricos,How China surprisingly quickly won the global race for electric vehicle batteries,0.16666666666666666,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""A mis 16 años, la CIA realizó conmigo experimentos sobre control mental""","""When I was 16, the CIA conducted experiments on mind control with me""",0.0,"[('16', 'DATE'), ('CIA', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,आंध्र प्रदेश पुलिस ने अहम माओवादी नेता हिड़मा के मारे जाने की पुष्टि की","Live, Andhra Pradesh Police confirms the killing of important Maoist leader Hidma.",0.2681818181818182,"[('Maoist', 'NORP'), ('Hidma', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार में नीतीश कुमार की जीत पर अंतरराष्ट्रीय मीडिया में छिड़ी ऐसी चर्चा,Such discussion broke out in international media on Nitish Kumar's victory in Bihar,0.0,"[(""Nitish Kumar's"", 'ORG'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,मुंबई के एक स्कूल में देरी पर छात्रा से 100 उठक-बैठक और बाद में हॉस्पिटल में मौत का मामला,Case of 100 sit-ups with a girl student for delay in a school in Mumbai and later death in the hospital.,0.0,"[('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Mumbai', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,थायरॉइड कैंसर के होने की वजहें और जानिए कहाँ रहना चाहिए सतर्क,Know the causes of thyroid cancer and where you should be cautious,0.0,[]
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,रोहिणी आचार्य के आरोप और लालू परिवार में आपसी कलह की कहानी,Story of Rohini Acharya's allegations and infighting in Lalu family,0.0,"[(""Rohini Acharya's"", 'PERSON'), ('Lalu', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,प्रशांत किशोर की जन सुराज पार्टी बिहार चुनाव में क्यों चारों खाने चित हो गई?,Why did Prashant Kishor's Jan Suraj Party get defeated in Bihar elections?,0.0,"[('Kishor', 'GPE'), ('Suraj Party', 'ORG'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"रमीज़ ख़ान कौन हैं, जिन पर लालू यादव की बेटी रोहिणी आचार्य ने लगाए हैं गंभीर आरोप","Who is Rameez Khan, against whom Lalu Yadav's daughter Rohini Acharya has made serious allegations?",-0.3333333333333333,"[('Rameez Khan', 'PERSON'), (""Lalu Yadav's"", 'PERSON'), ('Rohini Acharya', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार नतीजों पर असम के मंत्री की पोस्ट को भागलपुर दंगे से क्यों जोड़ा जा रहा है?,Why is Assam minister's post on Bihar results being linked to Bhagalpur riots?,0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE'), ('Bhagalpur', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"शेख़ हसीना को सज़ा-ए-मौत: बांग्लादेश ने भारत से उन्हें सौंपने को कहा, मोदी सरकार का आया ये जवाब","Death sentence to Sheikh Hasina: Bangladesh asked India to hand her over, this was the reply of Modi government",0.0,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Modi', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Plano de Trump para Gaza é aprovado pelo Conselho de Segurança da ONU,Trump's plan for Gaza is approved by the UN Security Council,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('the UN Security Council', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Casas destruídas e preços exorbitantes: moradores relatam a vida em Gaza um mês após cessar-fogo,Destroyed houses and exorbitant prices: residents report life in Gaza a month after ceasefire,0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"A capital com mais dias de calor extremo do Brasil: 'Não tem como dormir, te degrada muito'","The capital with the most days of extreme heat in Brazil: 'You can't sleep, it degrades you a lot'",0.1875,"[('the most days', 'DATE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Prefeito de Belém chama de 'arrogante e preconceituosa' declaração de premiê alemão sobre a capital paraense,Mayor of Belém calls German Prime Minister's statement about the capital of Pará 'arrogant and prejudiced',0.0,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('Pará', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Primeiro-ministro alemão compara Alemanha ao Brasil e diz ter ficado feliz ao ir embora de Belém,German Prime Minister compares Germany to Brazil and says he was happy to leave Belém,0.4,"[('German', 'NORP'), ('Germany', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Belém', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A pequena ilha do Caribe prestes a fazer história na Copa do Mundo de futebol,The small Caribbean island about to make history at the football World Cup,-0.25,"[('Caribbean', 'LOC'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,COP30: o 'cabo de guerra' sobre petróleo e dinheiro para responder às mudanças climáticas,COP30: the 'tug of war' over oil and money to respond to climate change,0.0,[]
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os dados que revelam o abismo entre ricos e pobres e brancos e negros no ensino médio do Brasil,Data that reveals the gap between rich and poor and white and black in high school in Brazil,-0.006333333333333335,"[('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Trump não conseguiu convencer Putin a acabar com a guerra na Ucrânia?,Why couldn't Trump convince Putin to end the war in Ukraine?,0.0,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Противодронная стена» Европы — нужна ли она и возможна ли она,“Anti-drone wall” of Europe - is it needed and is it possible?,0.0,"[('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Совбез ООН одобрил мирный план Трампа для Газы. Россия и Китай воздержались,The UN Security Council approved Trump's peace plan for Gaza. Russia and China abstained,0.0,"[('The UN Security Council', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: OFAC считает, что санкции против «Роснефти» и «Лукойла» помогли уменьшить доходы России","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: OFAC believes that sanctions against Rosneft and Lukoil have helped reduce Russia's revenues",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Rosneft', 'ORG'), ('Lukoil', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Правящая партия Грузии хочет лишить избирателей возможности голосовать за рубежом,Georgia's ruling party wants to deprive voters of the opportunity to vote abroad,0.2,"[('Georgia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Зеленский и Макрон анонсировали поставку Украине 100 истребителей Rafale. Почему это важно,Zelensky and Macron announced the delivery of 100 Rafale fighter jets to Ukraine. Why is this important,0.4,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Macron', 'PERSON'), ('100', 'CARDINAL'), ('Rafale', 'PRODUCT'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Методички НАТО больше не работают». Почему украинских военных в Польше не учат воевать дронами?,“NATO manuals no longer work.” Why aren’t the Ukrainian military in Poland trained to fight with drones?,-0.1,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Poland', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Авиационный новострой. Какими получаются импортозамещенные российские самолеты?,Aviation new building. How do import-substituted Russian aircraft turn out?,0.06818181818181818,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Почему комета 3I/Atlas стала поводом для разговоров о «корабле пришельцев»?,Why has Comet 3I/Atlas sparked talk of an “alien ship”?,-0.25,[]
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Суд в Бангладеш приговорил к казни экс-премьера Шейх Хасину за разгон протестов. Ее судили заочно,A court in Bangladesh sentenced former Prime Minister Sheikh Hasina to death for dispersing protests. She was tried in absentia,0.0,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Sheikh Hasina', 'PERSON'), ('absentia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Трамп призвал республиканцев проголосовать за раскрытие «файлов Эпштейна». О каких именно документах идет речь,Trump called on Republicans to vote to release the Epstein Files. What documents exactly are we talking about?,0.25,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('the Epstein Files', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,国連安保理、トランプ氏のガザ和平案を支持する決議案を採択,UN Security Council adopts resolution supporting Trump's Gaza peace plan,0.25,"[('UN Security Council', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英内相、難民受け入れ制度の厳格化意義を下院で強調　現行制度は「制御不能」と,"UK Home Secretary emphasizes the significance of tightening the refugee admission system in the House of Commons, calling the current system ""out of control""",0.0,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('the House of Commons', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,バングラデシュのハシナ前首相に死刑判決、人道に対する罪などで有罪に　昨年の反政府デモを弾圧,"Former Bangladesh Prime Minister Hasina sentenced to death, found guilty of crimes against humanity, crackdown on last year's anti-government demonstrations",-0.16666666666666666,"[('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Hasina', 'PERSON'), (""last year's"", 'DATE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,映画「クレヨンしんちゃん」、中国で公開延期に　台湾めぐる高市氏の答弁が影響か,"The release of the movie ""Crayon Shin-chan"" has been postponed in China, perhaps due to Takaichi's response regarding Taiwan?",-0.125,"[('Crayon Shin-chan', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Takaichi', 'ORG'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,生放送中に「ブレインフォグ」　BBC記者の経験談が大きな話題に,"""Brain Fog"" during live broadcast - BBC reporter's experience becomes a hot topic",0.19318181818181818,"[('Brain Fog', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エプスティーン元被告のファイル完全公開、トランプ氏が一転し支持　共和党議員らも要求,Trump backs full disclosure of Epstein's files; Republican lawmakers also demand,0.35,"[('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Republican', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,日本の観光・小売株が下落、台湾めぐる中国との対立で,Japan's tourism and retail stocks fall due to conflict with China over Taiwan,-0.125,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,化石燃料による排出が再び増加　一方で再生可能エネルギーも急成長、気候変動対策に希望,"Emissions from fossil fuels are on the rise again, while renewable energy is also growing rapidly, offering hope for climate change countermeasures",0.0,[]
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,イギリスの難民受け入れ政策、内相が大幅変更目指す　デンマークを手本に, 所要時間 2,50","Video, Home Secretary aims to drastically change Britain's refugee acceptance policy, modeled after Denmark, time required: 2,50",0.0,"[('Home', 'ORG'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Denmark', 'GPE'), ('2,50', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mpango wa Trump kwa Gaza waungwa mkono na Baraza la Usalama la Umoja wa Mataifa","Directly, Trump's plan for Gaza should be supported by the United Nations Security Council",0.1,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('the United Nations Security Council', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Chakwera anatumai serikali ya Tanzania itamkaribisha kuanza maridhiano,Chakwera hopes the Tanzanian government will welcome him to start reconciliation,0.8,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Sheikh Hasina: Mwanasiasa mpenda demokrasia aliyegeuka kuwa mtawala wa kiimla,Sheikh Hasina: A pro-democracy politician turned autocrat,0.0,[]
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Tuliwaona mamluki wa Urusi wakiwatesa na kuwaua watu' - wakimbizi wa Mali,'We saw Russian mercenaries torturing and killing people' - Malian refugees,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nini kimeibadilisha DRC? Safari ya kufuzu Kombe la Dunia,What has changed the DRC? World Cup qualification journey,0.0,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Rais Samia atangaza baraza jipya la mawaziri, saba watemwa","President Samia announces a new cabinet, seven will be appointed",0.13636363636363635,"[('Samia', 'PERSON'), ('seven', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jumuiya ya Madola yamteua Chakwera kuwa msuluhishi Tanzania,The Commonwealth appointed Chakwera to be the arbitrator in Tanzania,0.0,"[('Commonwealth', 'ORG'), ('Chakwera', 'PRODUCT'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Jinsi polisi walivyotumia nguvu kuvunja  maandamano Tanzania,How the police used force to break up protests in Tanzania,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumanne: Man City inamfuatilia El Mala Cologne,European Football Rumors Tuesday: Man City are tracking El Mala Cologne,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Man City', 'GPE'), ('El Mala Cologne', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_18,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kuna siri kuhusu manowari ya nyuklia kati ya Marekani na Korea Kusini?,Is there a secret about nuclear submarines between the US and South Korea?,-0.4,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('South Korea', 'GPE')]"
