Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Neorrurales"": los jóvenes españoles que han abandonado las grandes ciudades para asentarse en el campo escapando de los altos precios de la vivienda","""Neorrurals"": young Spaniards who have left big cities to settle in the countryside, escaping high housing prices",0.065,"[('Spaniards', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Al menos 40 muertos y 115 heridos tras un incendio en un bar en un centro turístico de esquí en Suiza,At least 40 dead and 115 injured after fire in bar at ski resort in Switzerland,-0.25,"[('At least 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('115', 'CARDINAL'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Me escondí para protegerme del intenso calor"": testigos describen su huida del incendio en un bar en un resort de esquí en Suiza","""I hid to protect myself from the intense heat"": witnesses describe their escape from the fire in a bar at a ski resort in Switzerland",0.2,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué encontré de Colombia (y qué no) en el mundo de los sonideros ""colombianos"" de la ciudad mexicana de Monterrey","What I found about Colombia (and what I didn't) in the world of ""Colombian"" sonideros from the Mexican city of Monterrey",0.0,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Colombian', 'NORP'), ('Mexican', 'NORP'), ('Monterrey', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,5 razones para mirar el futuro con optimismo,5 reasons to look at the future with optimism,0.0,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ज़ोहरान ममदानी ने उमर ख़ालिद के लिए लिखा नोट, अमेरिकी सांसदों ने भी की ये अपील","Zohran Mamdani wrote a note for Omar Khalid, American lawmakers also made this appeal",0.0,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('Omar Khalid', 'PERSON'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,ताइवान के आसपास चीन के सैन्य अभ्यास पर अमेरिका की कड़ी प्रतिक्रिया","Live, America's strong reaction to China's military exercises around Taiwan",0.15656565656565655,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सऊदी अरब और यूएई में तनाव से क्या पाकिस्तान की बढ़ेंगी मुश्किलें?,Will Pakistan's problems increase due to tension between Saudi Arabia and UAE?,-0.125,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,जयशंकर ढाका जाकर भी बांग्लादेश की अंतरिम सरकार के प्रमुख मोहम्मद यूनुस से क्यों नहीं मिले,"Why did Jaishankar not meet Mohammad Yunus, the head of the interim government of Bangladesh, even after going to Dhaka?",0.0,"[('Jaishankar', 'PERSON'), ('Mohammad Yunus', 'PERSON'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE'), ('Dhaka', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"स्विट्ज़रलैंड: नए साल के जश्न के दौरान बार में आग लगने से कम से कम 40 लोगों की मौत, जानिए पूरा मामला","Switzerland: At least 40 people died in fire in bar during New Year celebrations, know the whole matter",0.012121212121212125,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('At least 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('New Year', 'EVENT')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नान के शाही दरबारों से निकलने और हमारी थाली तक पहुँचने की कहानी,The story of Naan emerging from the royal courts and reaching our plates,0.0,"[('Naan', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,भारत के बारे में बांग्लादेश जमात-ए इस्लामी के अमीर ने ऐसा क्या कहा कि देनी पड़ी सफ़ाई,What did the Amir of Bangladesh Jamaat-e-Islami say about India that he had to clarify?,0.0,"[('Bangladesh Jamaat-e-Islami', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"चीन: जनसंख्या बढ़ाने के लिए सरकार ने महंगे किए कंडोम, लोगों ने उड़ाया मज़ाक और विशेषज्ञों ने जताई चिंता","China: Government made condoms expensive to increase population, people made fun and experts expressed concern",-0.1,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,'हमारा कैलेंडर आज भी गोरों के हिसाब से चलता है': हनीफ़ का व्लॉग,'Our calendar still works according to the whites': Hanif's vlog,0.0,"[('Hanif', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'Em questão de segundos, todo o teto estava em chamas': os relatos de sobreviventes do incêndio que matou ao menos 40 na Suíça","'In a matter of seconds, the entire ceiling was on fire': reports from survivors of the fire that killed at least 40 in Switzerland",-0.16666666666666666,"[('seconds', 'TIME'), ('at least 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"'A história se repete', diz grupo de sobreviventes da Boate Kiss sobre incêndio na Suíça; veja números das  tragédias em baladas no mundo","'History repeats itself', says group of Kiss Nightclub survivors about fire in Switzerland; see numbers of tragedies in clubs around the world",0.0,"[('Kiss Nightclub', 'ORG'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Vídeo mostra fogo se espalhando pelo teto de bar na Suíça: 'Alegria virou tragédia', Duration 0,58","Video,Video shows fire spreading through the ceiling of a bar in Switzerland: 'Joy turned into tragedy', Duration 0.58",0.8,"[('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro tem alta hospitalar e volta para prisão na sede da PF,Bolsonaro is discharged from hospital and returns to prison at the PF headquarters,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Zohran Mamdani assume prefeitura de Nova York e começa teste de fogo para 'nova esquerda' global,Zohran Mamdani takes over New York mayor and begins acid test for global 'new left',0.06818181818181818,"[('Zohran Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('New York', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que os chineses vão ter que pagar mais para usar camisinha a partir de 2026,Why Chinese people will have to pay more to use condoms from 2026,0.25,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Lobotomia, o polêmico procedimento no cérebro que era considerado 'mais fácil do que tratar uma dor de dente'","Lobotomy, the controversial brain procedure that was considered 'easier than treating a toothache'",0.55,[]
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como se decidiu que o ano começaria em 1º de janeiro,How it was decided that the year would start on January 1st,0.0,"[('the year', 'DATE'), ('January 1st', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Luxo ostentação' e outras cinco tendências de estilo para 2026,'Ostentatious luxury' and five other style trends for 2026,-0.125,"[('Ostentatious', 'PRODUCT'), ('five', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В ЦРУ считают, что украинские дроны не целились в дом Путина. К попыткам переубедить США подключился шеф ГРУ",The CIA believes that the Ukrainian drones were not aimed at Putin's house. The GRU chief joined in the attempts to convince the United States,0.0,"[('CIA', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('GRU', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Иране произошли столкновения между протестующими и силами безопасности, несколько человек погибли","Clashes between protesters and security forces in Iran, killing several people",0.0,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: ВСУ отвергают российские обвинения в смертельном ударе по оккупированной части Херсонской области","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: Ukrainian Armed Forces reject Russian accusations of a deadly strike on the occupied part of the Kherson region",-0.1,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kherson', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В пожаре на швейцарском горнолыжном курорте погибли около 40 человек, сообщила полиция","About 40 people have died in a fire at a Swiss ski resort, police said.",0.0,"[('About 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Дьявол носит Prada», «Крик» и еще 18 самых ожидаемых кинопремьер 2026 года","“The Devil Wears Prada,” “Scream” and 18 more of the most anticipated film premieres of 2026",0.5,"[('The Devil Wears Prada', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Когда микроскоп превращает невидимое в искусство: мир слизевиков,When the Microscope Turns the Invisible into Art: The World of Slime Mold,0.0,[]
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Мир встречает новый 2026 год. Фотографии,The world is celebrating the new year 2026. Photos,0.13636363636363635,"[('the new year 2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Трамп выводит войска из Чикаго, Лос-Анджелеса и Портленда","Trump withdraws troops from Chicago, Los Angeles and Portland",0.0,"[('Chicago', 'GPE'), ('Los Angeles', 'GPE'), ('Portland', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Израиль запретит деятельность 37 международных НПО в Газе. Британия и ЕС предупреждают о серьезных последствиях,Israel will ban the activities of 37 international NGOs in Gaza. Britain and EU warn of serious consequences,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('37', 'CARDINAL'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Финская полиция задержала судно, подозреваемое в повреждении подводного кабеля по пути из России",Finnish police detained a ship suspected of damaging a submarine cable en route from Russia,0.0,"[('Finnish', 'NORP'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,スイスのスキーリゾートのバーで出火、多数死傷,"Fire breaks out at bar at Swiss ski resort, many dead and injured",0.15,"[('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,EU外交トップ、ウクライナがプーチン氏公邸を攻撃したとするロシアの主張を否定　和平プロセスへの妨害と非難,"EU diplomat denies Russia's claim that Ukraine attacked Putin's residence, accuses it of interfering with peace process",0.0,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米議会、スミス元特別検察官の証言を公開　トランプ氏の起訴について,U.S. Congress releases former special counsel Smith's testimony regarding Trump's indictment,0.17857142857142858,"[('U.S. Congress', 'ORG'), ('Smith', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【写真で見る】 2026年を迎えた各地の様子　花火と黙祷,[See photos] Various locations celebrating 2026 with fireworks and silence,0.0,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,世界各地で花火やダンス、2026年の始まり祝う,Fireworks and dances around the world celebrate the start of 2026,0.0,"[('Fireworks', 'PERSON'), ('the start of 2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ユーロスターの運行復旧　電力障害で大混乱の後,Eurostar service restored after power outage caused chaos,0.0,"[('Eurostar', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米首都のケネディ・センター公演、中止相次ぐ　トランプ氏の名前入れた改称にアーティストから異議,Performances at the Kennedy Center in the US capital are canceled one after another; artists object to name change to include Trump's name,-0.1,"[('the Kennedy Center', 'FAC'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ドイツで銀行金庫から3000万ユーロ盗まれる　ドリル使用か,A drill was used to steal 30 million euros from a bank safe in Germany,0.5,"[('30 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,40以上の戦争を取材してきた、しかし2025年のような年は見たことがない――シンプソンBBC世界情勢編集長,"I've covered more than 40 wars, but I've never seen a year like 2025 - BBC World Affairs Editor-in-Chief Simpson",0.5,"[('more than 40', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Venezuela iko tayari kwa mazungumzo ya Marekani kuhusu ulanguzi wa dawa za kulevya - Maduro","Directly, Venezuela is ready for US talks on drug trafficking - Maduro",0.15000000000000002,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marais watano wa Afrika walioondoka madarakani kwa hiari,Five African presidents who left power voluntarily,0.0,"[('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Gabon yavunja timu ya taifa, yamfukuza kocha na nahodha Aubameyang","Gabon disbands the national team, dismisses coach and captain Aubameyang",0.0,"[('Aubameyang', 'ORG')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Israel imezishambulia nchi hizi 7?,Why has Israel attacked these 7 countries?,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('7', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini mwaka mpya hauanzi Januari 1 katika nchi zote duniani?,Why doesn't the new year start on January 1 in all countries in the world?,0.13636363636363635,"[('the new year start', 'DATE'), ('January 1', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Roma inataka kumsajili Mohamed Salah,European Football Rumors Friday: Roma want to sign Mohamed Salah,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Mohamed Salah', 'PERSON')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ndoto zako za mwaka 2026 unazianzaje?,How do you start your dreams for 2026?,0.0,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"AFCON 2025: Sahau 16 bora, haya ni mafanikio mengine 5 ya Tanzania","AFCON 2025: Forget the top 16, here are 5 more successes for Tanzania",0.5,"[('2025', 'DATE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi 10 tajiri zaidi duniani mwaka 2025,The 10 richest countries in the world in 2025,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2026_01_02,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Matukio ya kukumbukwa Tanzania mwaka 2025,Memorable events in Tanzania in 2025,0.5,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
