Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Esta puede ser la última vez que escuches mi voz"": el preocupante aumento de las ejecuciones políticas en Irán desde el inicio de la guerra","""This may be the last time you hear my voice"": the worrying increase in political executions in Iran since the start of the war",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Gasolina basura"" y otros 3 motivos que explican las crecientes protestas en Bolivia que el gobierno atribuye a Evo Morales y su entorno","""Junk gasoline"" and 3 other reasons that explain the growing protests in Bolivia that the government attributes to Evo Morales and his entourage",1.0,positive,"[('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Bolivia', 'GPE'), ('Evo Morales', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Quién es Nadia Marcinko, la novia de Epstein señalada como cómplice de abusos sexuales que alegó ser víctima y goza de inmunidad","Who is Nadia Marcinko, Epstein's girlfriend identified as an accomplice in sexual abuse who claimed to be a victim and enjoys immunity",-1.0,negative,"[('Nadia Marcinko', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"El tiburón fantasma, la esponja carnívora y otras 1.100 especies marinas descubiertas en solo un año","The ghost shark, the carnivorous sponge and 1,100 other marine species discovered in just one year",0.0,neutral,"[('1,100', 'CARDINAL'), ('just one year', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""La tristeza tiene incontables lecciones que enseñarnos y una muy importante es que es transitoria""","""Sadness has countless lessons to teach us and a very important one is that it is transitory""",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Acusan al hijo del fundador de Mango del homicidio de su padre, quien murió al caer por una montaña cuando ambos hacían senderismo en Barcelona","The son of the founder of Mango is accused of the murder of his father, who died after falling down a mountain when they were both hiking in Barcelona",0.0,neutral,"[('Mango', 'GPE'), ('Barcelona', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué tan preocupante es el brote de ébola que ya causó 179 muertes y se está propagando más rápido de lo que se pensaba, según la OMS","How worrying is the Ebola outbreak that has already caused 179 deaths and is spreading faster than thought, according to the WHO",-1.0,negative,"[('179', 'CARDINAL'), ('WHO', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cómo 5 minutos de ejercicio al día pueden mejorar y alargar nuestras vidas,How 5 minutes of exercise a day can improve and lengthen our lives,1.0,positive,"[('5 minutes', 'TIME')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Carmen Navas, la madre venezolana que murió tras buscar a su hijo durante más de 16 meses y enterarse de que el Estado ya lo había enterrado","Carmen Navas, the Venezuelan mother who died after searching for her son for more than 16 months and learning that the State had already buried him",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuelan', 'NORP'), ('more than 16 months', 'DATE'), ('State', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Imputan en España al expresidente Zapatero por presuntamente liderar una trama de corrupción con vínculos con Venezuela,Former President Zapatero is charged in Spain for allegedly leading a corruption plot with links to Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('Zapatero', 'PERSON'), ('Spain', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"भोपाल पुलिस का दावा, 'त्विषा ने ख़ुदकुशी की', परिवार का सवाल- शरीर पर चोट के निशान क्यों?","Bhopal Police's claim, 'Tvisha committed suicide', family's question - why injury marks on the body?",0.0,neutral,"[('Tvisha', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,फाल्टा में मतदान से ठीक पहले जहाँगीर ख़ान का पलटना अभिषेक बनर्जी के लिए बड़ा झटका क्यों?,Why is Jahangir Khan's reversal just before voting in Falta a big shock for Abhishek Banerjee?,0.0,neutral,"[(""Jahangir Khan's"", 'PERSON'), ('Falta', 'GPE'), ('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,अरशद मदनी बोले, ""गाय को राष्ट्रीय पशु का दर्जा देना चाहिए""","Live, Arshad Madani said, ""Cow should be given the status of national animal""",0.0,neutral,"[('Arshad Madani', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तेल के बढ़ते दाम का भारत की अर्थव्यवस्था पर क्या और कितना हो सकता है असर,What and how much impact can rising oil prices have on India's economy?,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नॉर्वे भारत को लोकतंत्र क्यों मानता है? इस सवाल पर क्या बोले वहां के प्रधानमंत्री,Why does Norway consider India a democracy? What did the Prime Minister say on this question?,0.0,neutral,"[('Norway', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लू कब बन जाती है जानलेवा, जानिए इससे बचने के क्या हैं तरीके","When does heatstroke become fatal, know the ways to avoid it",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पीएम मोदी को नॉर्वे के अख़बार ने 'सँपेरे' के रूप में दिखाया और क्या-क्या लिखा?,Norwegian newspaper showed PM Modi as a 'snake' and what else wrote?,0.0,neutral,"[('Norwegian', 'NORP'), ('PM Modi', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,चीन और रूस के बीच नज़दीकियों की वजह क्या है?,What is the reason for the closeness between China and Russia?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"वीडियो,इबोला के लक्षण क्या हैं और इससे बचाव कैसे हो सकता है?, अवधि 0,53","Video, What are the symptoms of Ebola and how can it be prevented?, Duration 0,53",0.0,neutral,"[('Ebola', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,नॉर्वे की पत्रकार ने बताया उन्होंने पीएम मोदी से सवाल पूछने की क्यों की थी कोशिश,Norwegian journalist told why she tried to ask questions to PM Modi,0.0,neutral,"[('Norwegian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Ricardo Salles sobre relação de Flávio Bolsonaro com Daniel Vorcaro: 'É no mínimo imoral',Ricardo Salles on Flávio Bolsonaro's relationship with Daniel Vorcaro: 'It's immoral to say the least',0.0,neutral,"[('Ricardo Salles', 'ORG'), (""Flávio Bolsonaro's"", 'PERSON'), ('Daniel Vorcaro', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que Vladimir Putin e Xi Jinping discutiram na visita do presidente russo a Pequim uma semana após viagem de Trump à China,What Vladimir Putin and Xi Jinping discussed during the Russian president's visit to Beijing a week after Trump's trip to China,0.0,neutral,"[('Vladimir Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Xi Jinping', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Beijing', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A preocupação dos proprietários de hotéis nos EUA frente ao baixo nível de reservas antes da Copa do Mundo,The concern of hotel owners in the USA regarding the low level of reservations before the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Waldirene, a 1ª mulher trans a passar por cirurgia de mudança de sexo no Brasil, morta aos 80 anos","Waldirene, the first trans woman to undergo sex change surgery in Brazil, died at age 80",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('age 80', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Estão entregando a eleição de mão beijada': como bolsonaristas e indecisos reagiram à revelação do elo entre Flávio e Vorcaro,'They're handing over the election': how Bolsonarists and undecided voters reacted to the revelation of the link between Flávio and Vorcaro,0.0,neutral,"[('Bolsonarists', 'NORP'), ('Flávio', 'PERSON'), ('Vorcaro', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As denúncias de estupro que fizeram reality show sobre casais virar caso de polícia,The rape allegations that made the reality show about couples become a police case,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Surto de Ebola pode estar se espalhando mais rápido que o esperado, alerta médica da OMS","Ebola outbreak may be spreading faster than expected, WHO medical warning",-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que o lançamento de um relógio gerou confrontos e fechou lojas ao redor do mundo,Why the launch of a watch sparked clashes and closed stores around the world,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Lula ultrapassa Flávio Bolsonaro no 2º turno no Agregador de Pesquisas da BBC News Brasil após resultado da AtlasIntel,Lula overtakes Flávio Bolsonaro in the 2nd round in the BBC News Brasil Research Aggregator after AtlasIntel results,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('2nd', 'ORDINAL'), ('BBC News', 'ORG'), ('AtlasIntel', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que Flávio Bolsonaro diz sobre encontro com Vorcaro após primeira prisão do banqueiro do Master,What Flávio Bolsonaro says about meeting with Vorcaro after the Master’s banker’s first arrest,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Vorcaro', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Британия смягчила нефтяные санкции против России вслед за США,Britain eased oil sanctions against Russia following the United States,1.0,positive,"[('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в Литве в связи с угрозой беспилотников объявляли тревогу, в Вильнюсе жители спускались в убежища","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: in Lithuania, due to the threat of drones, the alarm was declared; in Vilnius, residents went to shelters",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Lithuania', 'GPE'), ('Vilnius', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Путин и Си встретились в Пекине. О сроках строительства «Силы Сибири 2» не договорились,Putin and Xi met in Beijing. There was no agreement on the construction timeline for Power of Siberia 2,1.0,positive,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('Beijing', 'GPE'), ('Power of Siberia 2', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Город — манкурт». Как и почему в Бишкеке сносят исторические объекты и памятники архитектуры,"""The city is mankurt."" How and why historical sites and architectural monuments are being demolished in Bishkek",0.0,neutral,"[('Bishkek', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Жертва или пособница? Подругу Эпштейна Надю Марцинко могут допросить, несмотря на ее сделку со следствием в обмен на иммунитет",Victim or accomplice? Epstein's girlfriend Nadya Martsinko may be questioned despite her deal with investigators in exchange for immunity,-1.0,negative,"[('Victim', 'PERSON'), ('Epstein', 'PERSON'), ('Nadya Martsinko', 'PERSON')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Арсенал» стал чемпионом Англии после 22-летнего перерыва,Arsenal became champions of England after a 22-year break,0.0,neutral,"[('England', 'GPE'), ('22-year', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Россия вывела на крупнейшие учения стратегические ядерные силы. Что это значит?,Russia has brought its strategic nuclear forces to the largest exercises. What does it mean?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Продать ребенка, чтобы выжить. Истории голодающих жителей Афганистана, перед которыми встал ужасный выбор",Selling a child to survive. Stories of starving Afghans faced with terrible choices,0.0,neutral,"[('Afghans', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Каталонии задержали Джонатана Андика — сына основателя сети магазинов одежды Mango — по подозрению в убийстве отца,"In Catalonia, Jonathan Andik, the son of the founder of the Mango clothing chain, was detained on suspicion of murdering his father.",0.0,neutral,"[('Catalonia', 'GPE'), ('Jonathan Andik', 'PERSON'), ('Mango', 'LOC')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Права ЛГБТ, алименты и защита частных данных. В Украине разгорелись споры о новом Гражданском кодексе","LGBT rights, alimony and privacy protection. Disputes flared up in Ukraine over the new Civil Code",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン氏が訪中、習氏と会談　双方の関係は「かつてないほど高いレベル」と強調,"Mr. Putin visits China and meets with Mr. Xi, emphasizing that relations between the two sides are ""at an unprecedented level""",0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エボラ出血熱、当初予想より急速に拡大か　WHO専門家が警告,"Ebola hemorrhagic fever may spread faster than initially expected, WHO experts warn",-1.0,negative,[]
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イギリス、ロシア産石油への制裁を緩和　燃料価格の高騰受け,UK eases sanctions on Russian oil due to soaring fuel prices,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイ、ビザなし滞在期間を60日から30日へ短縮　日本・イギリスなど93カ国対象,Thailand shortens visa-free stay period from 60 to 30 days for 93 countries including Japan and the UK,0.0,neutral,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('60 to 30 days', 'DATE'), ('93', 'CARDINAL'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,中ロ首脳会談、習氏とプーチン氏は親友なのか？　2人の関係を特派員が分析, 所要時間 1,25","Video, China-Russia summit, are Mr. Xi and Mr. Putin best friends? A correspondent analyzes the relationship between the two, time required 1,25",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Xi', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエルの極右閣僚、ICC検察官が逮捕状請求と主張　対抗措置で西岸地区の村に退去命令,"Far-right Israeli minister, ICC prosecutor claims to seek arrest warrant, ordered to leave West Bank village as countermeasures",-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('West Bank', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米グーグル、新型スマートグラスを今秋発売　初期モデルの販売中止から10年超,"Google releases new smart glasses this fall, more than 10 years after discontinuing sales of the initial model",0.0,neutral,"[('Google', 'ORG'), ('this fall', 'DATE'), ('more than 10 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,エストニア、領空内に飛来したドローンをNATO戦闘機が撃墜と発表,Estonia announces NATO jet shoots down drone that flew into its airspace,0.0,neutral,"[('Estonia', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,レバノン、イスラエルの空爆で少なくとも19人死亡と発表,Lebanon says Israeli airstrike kills at least 19 people,-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('at least 19', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「僕の声を聞くのはこれが最後かもしれない」　イランで政治的処刑が急増、戦争開始後さらに,"``This may be the last time you hear my voice.'' Political executions increase rapidly in Iran, even more after war begins",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Rais wa Urusi, Vladimir Putin, akutana na Rais wa China Xi Jinping","Directly, the President of Russia, Vladimir Putin, meets with the President of China, Xi Jinping",0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Vladimir Putin', 'PERSON'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,'Ebola imetutesa': Hofu yatanda mashariki mwa DR Congo huku virusi hatari vikienea,'Ebola has afflicted us': Fear spreads in eastern DR Congo as the deadly virus spreads,0.0,neutral,"[('DR Congo', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,WARIDI WA BBC: 'Nina sehemu mbili za uke',BBC Rose: 'I have two vaginas',0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kiongozi wa ISIS aliyelengwa na Marekani kaskazini mashariki mwa Nigeria,ISIS leader targeted by US in northeastern Nigeria,0.0,neutral,"[('ISIS', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Matukio 8 yaliyoipa Arsenal ubingwa wa EPL msimu huu,8 events that gave Arsenal the EPL championship this season,0.0,neutral,"[('8', 'CARDINAL'), ('Arsenal the EPL', 'ORG'), ('this season', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Arsenal yatwaa ubingwa EPL,Arsenal will win the EPL championship,1.0,positive,"[('EPL', 'ORG')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Pasipoti zenye nguvu zaidi Duniani 2026,The most powerful passports in the world 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Sarmat: Lifahamu kombora la Urusi lenye uwezo wa kuruka umbali mrefu zaidi duniani,Sarmat: Know the Russian missile capable of flying the longest distance in the world,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wakina baba wanaofanya uamuzi mgumu wa kuwauza watoto wao ili kujikimu,Fathers who make the difficult decision to sell their children to support themselves,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_05_20,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ebola ni nini na kwa nini kuzuia mlipuko huu ni vigumu sana?,What is Ebola and why is preventing this outbreak so difficult?,0.0,neutral,[]
