Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Lo que una investigación de la BBC revela sobre la red de ""cárceles de tortura"" de Rusia en Ucrania",What a BBC investigation reveals about Russia's network of 'torture prisons' in Ukraine,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Los adolescentes que ensayaban su baile de fin de curso cuando ocurrieron los terremotos de Venezuela y a los que sus padres aún buscan entre los escombros casi ""sin ayuda""","The teenagers who were rehearsing their prom when the earthquakes in Venezuela occurred and for whom their parents are still searching through the rubble almost ""without help""",0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Egipto estalla de indignación por la ""injusticia"" de su eliminación ante Argentina en los últimos minutos y acusa a la FIFA de favoritismo hacia Messi","Egypt explodes with indignation at the ""injustice"" of its elimination against Argentina in the last minutes and accuses FIFA of favoritism towards Messi",-1.0,negative,"[('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('the last minutes', 'TIME'), ('Messi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo es vivir en las 5 ciudades con mayor calidad de vida en 2026,What it is like to live in the 5 cities with the highest quality of life in 2026,0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Mi abuela me ayudó a traducir mi primer cover al quechua y ahora canto en ese idioma por el mundo""","""My grandmother helped me translate my first cover into Quechua and now I sing in that language all over the world""",0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Quechua', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué le faltó a Colombia para avanzar a cuartos de final tras ilusionar con buen juego en el Mundial 2026,What was missing for Colombia to advance to the quarterfinals after exciting with a good game in the 2026 World Cup?,1.0,positive,"[('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Argentina avanza tras una remontada épica contra Egipto y enfrenta en cuartos de final a Suiza, que eliminó a Colombia del Mundial 2026","Argentina advances after an epic comeback against Egypt and faces Switzerland in the quarterfinals, which eliminated Colombia from the 2026 World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('the 2026', 'EVENT'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El funcionario chino condenado a muerte por aceptar US$325 millones en sobornos,Chinese official sentenced to death for accepting $325 million in bribes,-1.0,negative,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('$325 million', 'MONEY')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Una mujer despreciable e indigna"": Mbappé condena los mensajes racistas de una senadora paraguaya que ahora lo amenaza con acciones legales","""A despicable and unworthy woman"": Mbappé condemns the racist messages of a Paraguayan senator who now threatens him with legal action",0.0,neutral,"[('Mbappé', 'PERSON'), ('Paraguayan', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El cementerio de emergencia en el que Venezuela entierra a los muertos tras los terremotos,The emergency cemetery in which Venezuela buries the dead after the earthquakes,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वैभव सूर्यवंशी के लिए संजू सैमसन को बाहर बैठाने पर सवाल क्यों उठ रहे हैं?,Why are questions being raised on leaving Sanju Samson out for Vaibhav Suryavanshi?,0.0,neutral,"[('Sanju Samson', 'PERSON'), ('Vaibhav Suryavanshi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,ईरान ने सीज़फ़ायर टूटने का अमेरिका पर लगाया आरोप, जवाबी हमलों को लेकर ये कहा","Live, Iran accused America of breaking ceasefire, said this about retaliatory attacks",-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"वियतनाम ने नकली लग्ज़री सामान के बड़े बाज़ार पर कसा शिकंजा, क्या मिलेगी कामयाबी?","Vietnam tightens its grip on the big market of counterfeit luxury goods, will it be successful?",1.0,positive,"[('Vietnam', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ख़ामेनेई की अंतिम विदाई में ईरान का अमेरिका और इसराइल को सीधा संदेश,Iran's direct message to America and Israel in Khamenei's last farewell,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बारुईपुर नाबालिग रेप और मर्डर केस: अभियुक्त की एनकाउंटर में मौत, पुलिस कार्रवाई पर उठे सवाल","Baruipur minor rape and murder case: Accused dies in encounter, questions raised on police action",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,रूस के सैकड़ों बम ग़लती से 'कब्ज़े वाले यूक्रेनी इलाक़े' पर कैसे गिर गए?,How did hundreds of Russian bombs accidentally fall on 'occupied Ukrainian territory'?,0.0,neutral,"[('hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अमेरिका: लॉरेंस बिश्नोई गैंग समेत कई गिरोहों पर एक्शन, कहा -'गुंडों के लिए कोई जगह नहींं'","America: Action against many gangs including Lawrence Bishnoi gang, said - 'No place for goons'",0.0,neutral,"[('Lawrence Bishnoi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"अर्जेंटीना के ख़िलाफ़ मिली हार के बाद मिस्र ने क्यों कहा- 'हुई नाइंसाफ़ी', मेसी पर भी साधा निशाना","After the defeat against Argentina, why did Egypt say - 'Injustice happened', also targeted Messi",0.0,neutral,"[('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Messi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,'यहीं मकान दो या दूसरी जगह रहने का इंतज़ाम करो'; ढहाए गए घरों पर गुजरात हाईकोर्ट का सख़्त निर्देश,'Give me a house here or make arrangements to live somewhere else'; Gujarat High Court's strict instructions on demolished houses,0.0,neutral,"[(""Gujarat High Court's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"सिंधु जल समझौते पर अब पाकिस्तानी सेना भी बोली, बिलावल भुट्टो ने कहा- जंग भी करने को तैयार","Now Pakistani Army also spoke on Indus Water Agreement, Bilawal Bhutto said- ready to fight also",0.0,neutral,"[('Pakistani Army', 'ORG'), ('Indus Water Agreement', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Bilawal Bhutto', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como a 'dolarização' do Rio expulsa moradores dos bairros mais cobiçados por turistas e investidores,How Rio's 'dollarization' expels residents from the neighborhoods most coveted by tourists and investors,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Trump diz que cessar-fogo 'acabou' após troca de ataques entre EUA e Irã,Trump says ceasefire is 'over' after exchange of attacks between US and Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Governo Lula abre caminho para expulsão de suposto espião russo,Lula government opens the way for the expulsion of alleged Russian spy,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O cemitério de emergência onde a Venezuela enterra vítimas dos terremotos,The emergency cemetery where Venezuela buries earthquake victims,0.0,neutral,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Flávio Bolsonaro discursa por 5 minutos em audiência nos EUA sobre novo tarifaço: 'Pix também beneficiou empresas americanas',Flávio Bolsonaro speaks for 5 minutes at an audience in the US about new pricing: 'Pix also benefited American companies',0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('5 minutes', 'TIME'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como Benedito Ruy Barbosa revoluciou a novela rural e levou até o MST para a hora do jantar,How Benedito Ruy Barbosa revolutionized the rural soap opera and took it to the MST for dinner time,0.0,neutral,"[('MST', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Petroleiros atacados e reação dos EUA com bombardeio: por que guerra voltou a esquentar no Estreito de Ormuz,Oil tankers attacked and US reaction with bombing: why war heats up again in the Strait of Hormuz,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Artilheiro da Copa: Messi marca contra o Egito e toma dianteira na batalha,World Cup top scorer: Messi scores against Egypt and takes the lead in the battle,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('Egypt', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Qual a distância entre Lula e Flávio Bolsonaro nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,What is the distance between Lula and Flávio Bolsonaro in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Biotônico Fontoura: o remédio alcoólico popularizado por Monteiro Lobato que fez parte da infância brasileira no século 20,Biotônico Fontoura: the alcoholic medicine popularized by Monteiro Lobato that was part of Brazilian childhood in the 20th century,0.0,neutral,"[('Biotônico Fontoura', 'PERSON'), ('Monteiro Lobato', 'PERSON'), ('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('the 20th century', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"США и Иран обменялись новыми ударами, Трамп заявил, что «для него» перемирие закончилось","The US and Iran exchanged new blows, Trump said that “for him” the truce is over",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: глава НАТО призвал Путина «не играть» с альянсом; в Киеве один погибший после новой атаки баллистикой","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: NATO head called on Putin “not to play” with the alliance; in Kyiv one person died after a new ballistic attack",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Окно возможностей. Как может измениться иранский режим?,Window of opportunity. How can the Iranian regime change?,1.0,positive,"[('Iranian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Польша рассекретила данные о военной помощи Украине с 2022 года — в ответ на критику о поставках Киеву ракет для систем Patriot,Poland has declassified data on military assistance to Ukraine since 2022 - in response to criticism about the supply of missiles to Kyiv for Patriot systems,0.0,neutral,"[('Poland', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('2022', 'DATE'), ('Kyiv for Patriot', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Поставки ракет Украине, дроны и «дальнобойные санкции». Главное по итогам первого дня саммита НАТО в Анкаре","Missile supplies to Ukraine, drones and “long-range sanctions.” The main results of the first day of the NATO summit in Ankara",0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('the first day', 'DATE'), ('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Ankara', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Египет едва не выбил Аргентину в 1/8 финала ЧМ-2026. Чемпионы мира по футболу спасли матч на последних минутах,Egypt almost eliminated Argentina in the round of 16 of the 2026 World Cup. The World Cup champions saved the match in the last minutes,0.0,neutral,"[('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('The World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('the last minutes', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Женщина, подозреваемая в покушении на бизнесмена Ермолаева в Монако, найдена застреленной в Украине",A woman suspected of an attempt on the life of businessman Ermolaev in Monaco was found shot dead in Ukraine,0.0,neutral,"[('Ermolaev', 'PERSON'), ('Monaco', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Конституционный суд Казахстана обнулил президентский срок Токаева. Теперь он сможет возглавлять страну до 2036 года,The Constitutional Court of Kazakhstan nullified Tokayev's presidential term. Now he will be able to lead the country until 2036,0.0,neutral,"[('The Constitutional Court of Kazakhstan', 'ORG'), ('Tokayev', 'PERSON'), ('2036', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Развязка в деле об убийстве без тела: осужденный француз признался в убийстве жены,The denouement in the case of murder without a body: the convicted Frenchman confessed to the murder of his wife,0.0,neutral,"[('Frenchman', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,МОК временно восстановил членство Олимпийского комитета России. Что это значит для российских спортсменов?,The IOC has temporarily restored the membership of the Russian Olympic Committee. What does this mean for Russian athletes?,0.0,neutral,"[('IOC', 'ORG'), ('the Russian Olympic Committee', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,米軍がイラン再攻撃、イランによるタンカー攻撃に対応と　トランプ氏は停戦合意は「おしまいだ」と発言,"US military responds to renewed attack on Iran, Iranian tanker attack, Trump says ceasefire agreement is ``done''",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,右翼ル・ペン氏、仏大統領選への立候補を表明　有罪判決について上告の意向,"Right-wing Le Pen announces candidacy for French presidential election, intends to appeal conviction",1.0,positive,"[('Le Pen', 'ORG'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゼレンスキー氏、NATOに防空システムの提供求める　ロシアの大規模攻撃受け,Zelenskiy asks NATO to provide air defense system following large-scale Russian attack,0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 トランプ氏の介入で奮起した　ベルギー選手たちが明かす,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Belgian players inspired by Trump's intervention reveal,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('Belgian', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ハンガリー国営メディアが放送を一時停止　オルバン前政権時代のプロパガンダ一掃のため,Hungarian state media temporarily suspends broadcasting to clean up propaganda from the former Orbán regime,0.0,neutral,"[('Hungarian', 'NORP'), ('Orbán', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシア、2028年ロサンゼルス五輪に出場の可能性　IOCが参加制限を解除,Russia may participate in 2028 Los Angeles Olympics; IOC lifts restrictions on participation,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('2028', 'DATE'), ('Los Angeles Olympics', 'EVENT'), ('IOC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,仏大統領訪問中のシリア首都で爆発、18人負傷,Explosion in Syrian capital during French president's visit injures 18 people,0.0,neutral,"[('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('18', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ出身富豪を狙いモナコで爆発事件、容疑者の遺体がウクライナで見つかる,Suspect in Monaco explosion targeting Ukrainian billionaire's body found in Ukraine,0.0,neutral,"[('Monaco', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英野党リフォームUKのファラージ党首、議員辞職し補選に出ると表明　政治資金問題の渦中,UK opposition Reform UK leader Farage announces resignation as MP and running for by-election amid political funding controversy,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Reform', 'ORG'), ('Farage', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 トランプ氏、FIFAに米選手の出場停止見直し求めたと認める　試合はベルギーが勝利,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Trump admits he asked FIFA to review the suspension of US players, Belgium wins the match",1.0,positive,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Belgium', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yafanya mashambulizi dhidi ya Iran baada ya meli za mafuta kushambuliwa katika Mlango wa Hormuz","Directly, the United States attacks Iran after oil tankers were attacked in the Strait of Hormuz",-1.0,negative,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: 'Anazunguka uwanjani kama mzee': Ronaldo akosolewa baada ya Ureno kuondolewa,World Cup 2026: 'He walks around the pitch like an old man': Ronaldo criticized after Portugal's elimination,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Ronaldo', 'PERSON'), ('Portugal', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Rais wa Zimbabwe, Emmerson Mnangagwa asaini sheria inayoongeza muda wa urais wake","The President of Zimbabwe, Emmerson Mnangagwa signs a law extending the term of his presidency",0.0,neutral,"[('Zimbabwe', 'GPE'), ('Emmerson Mnangagwa', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Samatta astaafu kuchezea timu ya taifa ya Tanzania,Samatta retired to play for the Tanzanian national team,0.0,neutral,"[('Samatta', 'PRODUCT'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini nchi za Afrika zinaongoza katika orodha ya mataifa karimu zaidi duniani?,Why are African countries leading in the list of the most generous countries in the world?,0.0,neutral,"[('African', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini ndege za Urusi zinadondosha mabomu katika himaya yake?,Why are Russian planes dropping bombs on his empire?,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,‎Maandamano Saba saba: 10 wakamatwa Nairobi huku Tanzania kukiwa kimya,Seven protests: 10 arrested in Nairobi while Tanzania remains silent,0.0,neutral,"[('Seven', 'CARDINAL'), ('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Nairobi', 'GPE'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka Ulaya Jumatano: Arsenal wampatia kipau mbele Morgan Rogers,European Football Rumors Wednesday: Arsenal to sign forward Morgan Rogers,-1.0,negative,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Morgan Rogers', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Hali ni Shwari - Jeshi la Polisi Tanzania,The situation is stable - Tanzania Police Force,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_08,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Kutoka kuwa watawa hadi wapenzi wa jinsia moja','From nuns to homosexuals',0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,FIFA World Cup Day 28: Quarterfinals are here and Egypt FIFA dispute,FIFA World Cup Day 28: Quarterfinals are here and Egypt FIFA dispute,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day', 'EVENT'), ('28', 'CARDINAL'), ('Egypt', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Funeral events for Iran’s slain Supreme Leader Khamenei under way in Iraq,Funeral events for Iran’s slain Supreme Leader Khamenei under way in Iraq,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Supreme', 'ORG'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Iraq', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,‘Where do I get that from?’: UK asylum seekers face hefty repayment bill,‘Where do I get that from?’: UK asylum seekers face hefty repayment bill,0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Australian World Cup star Mabil fires back at far-right politician,Australian World Cup star Mabil fires back at far-right politician,0.0,neutral,"[('Australian World Cup', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Trump, world leaders meet in Turkiye for second day of key NATO summit","Trump, world leaders meet in Turkiye for second day of key NATO summit",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Turkiye', 'GPE'), ('second', 'ORDINAL'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran’s economy faces long road to recovery as fragile truce tested,Iran’s economy faces long road to recovery as fragile truce tested,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,France vs Morocco: Key talking points ahead of FIFA World Cup quarterfinal,France vs Morocco: Key talking points ahead of FIFA World Cup quarterfinal,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('FIFA World Cup', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"At UN, Cuba rallies support against ‘ruthless’ US blockade","At UN, Cuba rallies support against ‘ruthless’ US blockade",0.0,neutral,"[('UN', 'ORG'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Childhood on hold: How Gaza’s children spend a summer without play,Childhood on hold: How Gaza’s children spend a summer without play,0.0,neutral,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Syria grapples with unrest as government faces old and new threats,Syria grapples with unrest as government faces old and new threats,0.0,neutral,"[('Syria', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Wayanad debris slip Live: Search on for 5 missing; Amit Shah pledges Centre's support,Wayanad debris slip Live: Search on for 5 missing; Amit Shah pledges Centre's support,0.0,neutral,"[('Wayanad', 'ORG'), ('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Amit Shah', 'ORG'), ('Centre', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,T.N. asks State Election Commissioner Jothi Nirmalasamy to step down,T.N. asks State Election Commissioner Jothi Nirmalasamy to step down,0.0,neutral,"[('T.N.', 'ORG'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Jothi Nirmalasamy', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The 2008 Ahmedabad serial blasts case and Gujarat High Court verdict | Explained,The 2008 Ahmedabad serial blasts case and Gujarat High Court verdict | Explained,0.0,neutral,"[('2008', 'DATE'), ('Gujarat High Court', 'ORG'), ('Explained', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"A missing girl, mob violence, and an encounter: What happened in West Bengal’s Baruipur?","A missing girl, mob violence, and an encounter: What happened in West Bengal’s Baruipur?",0.0,neutral,"[('West Bengal’s Baruipur', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Cultural heritage connect us, thank Indonesian people for preserving it: Modi at Prambanan Temple complex","Cultural heritage connect us, thank Indonesian people for preserving it: Modi at Prambanan Temple complex",0.0,neutral,"[('Indonesian', 'NORP'), ('Prambanan Temple', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,How India’s life insurance sector funds government expenditure,How India’s life insurance sector funds government expenditure,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Case against Sena corporator on charges of assaulting doctors in Thane hospital,Case against Sena corporator on charges of assaulting doctors in Thane hospital,0.0,neutral,"[('Thane', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Wildflower season is here: From Kaas Plateau to Dzukou Valley, where to trek this season","Wildflower season is here: From Kaas Plateau to Dzukou Valley, where to trek this season",0.0,neutral,"[('Kaas Plateau', 'PERSON'), ('Dzukou Valley', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Grand ambitions: On India’s cooperative sector,Grand ambitions: On India’s cooperative sector,0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Deceptive dispute: On the Taj Mahal,Deceptive dispute: On the Taj Mahal,0.0,neutral,"[('the Taj Mahal', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Will Le Pen rise again? French nationalist leader defiant after court's ruling,Will Le Pen rise again? French nationalist leader defiant after court's ruling,0.0,neutral,"[('Will Le', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nato allies announce £37bn for new missile project,Nato allies announce £37bn for new missile project,0.0,neutral,"[('Nato', 'ORG'), ('37bn', 'MONEY')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Russian fuel shortages bite – but will Putin change tack in Ukraine war?,Russian fuel shortages bite – but will Putin change tack in Ukraine war?,-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,'The water just came so fast': Typhoon triggers floods and rare tornadoes in China,'The water just came so fast': Typhoon triggers floods and rare tornadoes in China,0.0,neutral,"[('Typhoon', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Suspect ate Chick-fil-A and interacted with Charlie Kirk staff before shooting, court hears","Suspect ate Chick-fil-A and interacted with Charlie Kirk staff before shooting, court hears",0.0,neutral,"[('Chick', 'GPE'), ('Charlie Kirk', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trains and emergency calls affected after major outage at Australia's largest telecoms company,Trains and emergency calls affected after major outage at Australia's largest telecoms company,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Utah boarding school where Paris Hilton alleged abuse as a teen loses its licence,Utah boarding school where Paris Hilton alleged abuse as a teen loses its licence,0.0,neutral,"[('Utah', 'GPE'), ('Paris Hilton', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Australia dock workers call for 28-hour week in AI talks,Australia dock workers call for 28-hour week in AI talks,0.0,neutral,"[('Australia', 'GPE'), ('28-hour', 'TIME'), ('AI', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Top Democrats press Maine Senate candidate to drop out of race over sexual assault allegation,Top Democrats press Maine Senate candidate to drop out of race over sexual assault allegation,0.0,neutral,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Maine Senate', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Woman suspected of Monaco bomb attack found dead in Ukraine,Woman suspected of Monaco bomb attack found dead in Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Monaco', 'ORG'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"In NATO’s Next Act, Can Europe Lead?","In NATO’s Next Act, Can Europe Lead?",0.0,neutral,"[('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Mass Mournings In Qom, Where Khamenei Ruled Supreme Over Iran’s Clerics","Mass Mournings In Qom, Where Khamenei Ruled Supreme Over Iran’s Clerics",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Farage Resigns and Says He Will Run Again in Special Election,Farage Resigns and Says He Will Run Again in Special Election,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Estonia Won the War on Fentanyl. What Came Next Was Even Worse.,Estonia Won the War on Fentanyl. What Came Next Was Even Worse.,-1.0,negative,"[('Estonia Won the War on', 'ORG'), ('Fentanyl', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Le Pen Says She Will Run for Presidency After Court Lifts Ban,Le Pen Says She Will Run for Presidency After Court Lifts Ban,0.0,neutral,"[('Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Venezuelans Criticize Own Government Response After Twin Earthquakes,Venezuelans Criticize Own Government Response After Twin Earthquakes,1.0,positive,"[('Venezuelans Criticize Own Government Response', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Suspect in Monaco Bombing Attack Is Found Dead in Ukraine,Suspect in Monaco Bombing Attack Is Found Dead in Ukraine,-1.0,negative,"[('Monaco Bombing Attack Is Found Dead', 'FAC'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,A Supreme Leader’s Final Crowds,A Supreme Leader’s Final Crowds,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Prince Harry Loses Privacy Lawsuit Against Daily Mail Publisher,Prince Harry Loses Privacy Lawsuit Against Daily Mail Publisher,0.0,neutral,"[('Prince Harry Loses Privacy Lawsuit Against Daily Mail', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_08,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How a Four-Generation Cuban Family Survives on $60 a Month,How a Four-Generation Cuban Family Survives on $60 a Month,0.0,neutral,"[('60', 'MONEY')]"
