Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Qué tipo de país representan De la Espriella y Cepeda, los antagónicos aspirantes a presidir Colombia","What type of country do De la Espriella and Cepeda, the antagonistic candidates to preside over Colombia, represent?",0.0,neutral,"[('De la Espriella and Cepeda', 'ORG'), ('Colombia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Para qué sirvió la guerra?: la pregunta inevitable que plantea el acuerdo entre EE.UU. e Irán,What was the war for?: the inevitable question raised by the US-Iran deal,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,El escalofriante caso del hombre que arrojó a un niño de 3 años al foso de los cocodrilos en un zoológico de Reino Unido,The chilling case of the man who threw a 3-year-old boy into the crocodile pit at a UK zoo,0.0,neutral,"[('3-year-old', 'DATE'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Investigación BBC: los ""agentes"" de OnlyFans que amenazan a los creadores y se quedan con la mitad de sus ganancias","BBC investigation: OnlyFans ""agents"" who threaten creators and take half of their profits",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC', 'ORG'), ('OnlyFans', 'NORP'), ('half', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Su triunfo llena de orgullo a todo México"": el festejo de Sheinbaum y los hinchas luego de que el Tri se convirtiera en el primer equipo en clasificarse para la siguiente fase del Mundial","""His victory fills all of Mexico with pride"": the celebration of Sheinbaum and the fans after El Tri became the first team to qualify for the next phase of the World Cup",1.0,positive,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Sheinbaum', 'ORG'), ('El Tri', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Ucrania lanza el mayor ataque con drones sobre Moscú desde el inicio de la guerra,Ukraine launches largest drone attack on Moscow since start of war,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,¿Por qué cada vez más mujeres en China usan ropa de hombre?,Why do more and more women in China wear men's clothing?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Me convertí en una prisionera dentro de mi propia casa"": las bandas narco en Reino Unido que ocupan cientos de viviendas con sus habitantes adentro","""I became a prisoner inside my own house"": the drug gangs in the United Kingdom that occupy hundreds of homes with their inhabitants inside",0.0,neutral,"[('the United Kingdom', 'GPE'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Las imágenes de la inauguración repleta de estrellas del controvertido Centro Presidencial Obama en Chicago,Images from the star-studded inauguration of the controversial Obama Presidential Center in Chicago,0.0,neutral,"[('Obama Presidential Center', 'FAC'), ('Chicago', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Mundial 2026: el ranking de la BBC de todos los equipos después de la primera ronda de partidos (con 3 latinoamericanos entre los 10 primeros),World Cup 2026: the BBC ranking of all teams after the first round of matches (with 3 Latin Americans in the top 10),0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Latin Americans', 'NORP'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"परिमल नाथवानी कौन हैं, जिनके सामने झारखंड राज्यसभा चुनाव में 'टूट' गया इंडिया गठबंधन","Who is Parimal Nathwani, in front of whom India alliance 'broke' in Jharkhand Rajya Sabha elections?",0.0,neutral,"[('Parimal Nathwani', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Jharkhand Rajya Sabha', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,ममता बनर्जी और अभिषेक बनर्जी को अदालत की अवमानना के आरोप में नोटिस","Live, notice to Mamata Banerjee and Abhishek Banerjee on contempt of court charges",0.0,neutral,"[('Mamata Banerjee', 'ORG'), ('Abhishek Banerjee', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"टीएमसी के बाग़ी सांसदों और एनसीपीआई के बहाने, भारत के हज़ारों 'काग़ज़ी दलों' की पड़ताल",Investigation of thousands of 'paper parties' of India under the pretext of rebel TMC MPs and NCPI,0.0,neutral,"[('thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('TMC', 'ORG'), ('NCPI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"दो साल की बच्ची की तलाश में सैकड़ों जवान, ड्रोन और खोजी दस्ते, साथ गए कुत्ते की मौत से रहस्य गहराया","Hundreds of soldiers, drones and search teams were deployed in search of a two-year-old girl, the mystery deepened due to the death of the dog accompanying her.",-1.0,negative,"[('Hundreds', 'CARDINAL'), ('two-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बिहार के बेगूसराय में पति को कमरे में बंद कर महिला के साथ गैंगरेप का आरोप, क्‍या है मामला?","In Begusarai, Bihar, there is an allegation of gang rape of a woman after locking her husband in a room, what is the matter?",0.0,neutral,"[('Begusarai', 'GPE'), ('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"राम मंदिर ट्रस्ट पर उठते सवालों के बीच, जानिए कौन हैं महासचिव चंपत राय?","Amidst the questions arising on Ram Mandir Trust, know who is General Secretary Champat Rai?",0.0,neutral,"[('Ram Mandir Trust', 'ORG'), ('Champat Rai', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,टेलीग्राम पर लगी अस्थाई रोक जारी रहेगी: दिल्ली हाई कोर्ट का फ़ैसला,Temporary ban on Telegram will continue: Delhi High Court's decision,0.0,neutral,"[('Telegram', 'ORG'), (""Delhi High Court's"", 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,शिवसेना (यूबीटी) के वो 6 सांसद कौन हैं जो पार्टी की बैठक में पहुंचे ही नहीं,Who are those 6 MPs of Shiv Sena (UBT) who did not reach the party meeting?,0.0,neutral,"[('6 MPs', 'MONEY'), ('Shiv Sena', 'ORG'), ('UBT', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"बिहार में पुलिस ने जिसे पहले बताया 'मानसिक अस्वस्थ', बाद में उसी का किया एनकाउंटर, पूरा मामला क्या है?","In Bihar, the police first encountered the person whom they described as 'mentally unwell', then they encountered the same person, what is the whole matter?",0.0,neutral,"[('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वर्ल्ड कप फ़ुटबॉल 2026: जानें ताज़ा नतीजे और आने वाले मैच,World Cup Football 2026: Know latest results and upcoming matches,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Football', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"A Copa do Mundo dos ultrarricos: pacote de R$ 20 milhões para a final, jatinho entre os estádios e encontro com jogadores","The World Cup for the ultra-rich: R$20 million package for the final, jet between stadiums and meeting with players",0.0,neutral,"[('The World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('R$20 million', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Investigação sobre Jaques Wagner aproxima caso Master do governo Lula, diz imprensa internacional","Investigation into Jaques Wagner brings the Master case closer to the Lula government, says international press",0.0,neutral,"[('Jaques Wagner', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Para que serviu a guerra? A pergunta inevitável levantada pelo acordo entre EUA e Irã,What was the war for? The inevitable question raised by the US-Iran deal,-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O que tinha a camisa da seleção do Haiti que foi proibida pela Fifa na Copa,What was on the shirt of the Haiti team that was banned by FIFA at the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Brasil x Haiti: qual resultado a Seleção precisa na partida de hoje para chegar à próxima fase da Copa?,Brazil x Haiti: what result does the Seleção need in today's match to reach the next stage of the World Cup?,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('Seleção', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Copa do Mundo de 2026: o ranking da BBC das seleções após a primeira rodada — com o Brasil entre as 10 primeiras,2026 World Cup: BBC ranking of teams after the first round — with Brazil in the top 10,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Toy Story 5': o filme mais traumático do ano — para os pais,'Toy Story 5': the most traumatic film of the year — for parents,0.0,neutral,"[('the year', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Robin Hood não era herói': como foram apagadas as sombrias e violentas origens medievais do personagem,'Robin Hood was no hero': how the character's dark and violent medieval origins were erased,0.0,neutral,"[('Robin Hood', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como foi o maior ataque da Ucrânia contra Moscou desde o início da guerra,What was Ukraine's biggest attack on Moscow since the start of the war?,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,'Ganhei viagem com tudo pago para a Copa do Mundo e tive o visto negado','I won an all-expenses-paid trip to the World Cup and was denied a visa',0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Переговоры США и Ирана в Швейцарии в пятницу не состоятся, Джей Ди Вэнс отменил поездку","US-Iran talks in Switzerland on Friday will not take place, J.D. Vance cancels trip",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('J.D. Vance', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Ормузский пролив открывается: когда ждать обвала цен на нефть?,The Strait of Hormuz opens: when can we expect a collapse in oil prices?,0.0,neutral,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: в результате вчерашнего удара по Подмосковью погибла 8-летняя девочка; удары по Одесской и Харьковской областям","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: as a result of yesterday's strike in the Moscow region, an 8-year-old girl died; attacks on Odessa and Kharkov regions",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('yesterday', 'DATE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('8-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Odessa', 'GPE'), ('Kharkov', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Победа Энди Бёрнема на выборах открывает ему путь к борьбе за пост премьер-министра Великобритании,Andy Burnham's election victory clears the way for him to compete for the post of British Prime Minister,1.0,positive,"[(""Andy Burnham's"", 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Джереми Боуэн: Трампу не избежать вопросов о том, ради чего он начал войну с Ираном",Jeremy Bowen: Trump will not avoid questions about why he went to war with Iran,-1.0,negative,"[('Jeremy Bowen', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Крупнейшая за годы атака дронов на Москву. Что известно к вечеру четверга,The largest drone attack on Moscow in years. What is known by Thursday evening,-1.0,negative,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('years', 'DATE'), ('Thursday', 'DATE'), ('evening', 'TIME')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Глава Пентагона Хегсет заявил, что США проведут ревизию своих войск в Европе и сократят участие в силах НАТО",Pentagon chief Hegseth said that the United States will conduct an audit of its troops in Europe and reduce participation in NATO forces,0.0,neutral,"[('Pentagon', 'ORG'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('NATO', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Судно российского теневого флота вошло в Ла-Манш — впервые после задержания танкера Smyrtos в выходные. Оно идет под российским флагом,A Russian shadow fleet vessel has entered the English Channel for the first time since the Smyrtos tanker was detained at the weekend. It flies under the Russian flag,0.0,neutral,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('the English Channel', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Smyrtos', 'PERSON'), ('the weekend', 'DATE'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В Великобритании за шпионаж в пользу Китая осуждены сотрудник погранслужбы аэропорта «Хитроу» и его куратор,"In the UK, a border guard at Heathrow Airport and his supervisor were convicted of spying for China.",0.0,neutral,"[('UK', 'GPE'), ('Heathrow Airport', 'FAC'), ('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Легендарный дуб Робин Гуда в Шервудском лесу окончательно засох. Но не от старости, говорят эксперты","The legendary Robin Hood oak tree in Sherwood Forest has completely dried up. But not from old age, experts say",0.0,neutral,"[('Robin Hood', 'PERSON'), ('Sherwood Forest', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカがイランの海上封鎖を解除　イラン最高指導者はトランプ氏が「絶望」して合意と,"US lifts naval blockade of Iran; Iran's supreme leader says Trump is ""desperate"" to agree",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英下院補選、労働党のバーナム市長が当選　党首選でスターマー首相への挑戦の道開く,"Labor Party's Mayor Burnham wins British House of Commons by-election, paving the way for challenge to Prime Minister Starmer in leadership race",1.0,positive,"[(""Labor Party's"", 'ORG'), ('Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('British House of Commons', 'ORG'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナ、モスクワに最大規模の攻撃で製油所直撃　地面や服に黒い染みと住民,"Ukraine's largest attack hits Moscow refinery, leaving residents with black stains on ground and clothes",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【解説】 米・イランは共に合意を「勝利」と主張、実際はどうなのか,"[Commentary] Both the US and Iran claim the agreement is a “victory”, but what is the reality?",1.0,positive,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 日本人サポーターがスタジアムを清掃、家でもやろうと女性から注文,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Japanese supporters clean stadium, woman orders to do it at home",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ウクライナ、モスクワ近郊の製油所をドローン攻撃　タンクのふた吹き飛ぶ, 所要時間 0,48","Video, Drone attack on oil refinery near Moscow, Ukraine, blows off tank lid, Duration 0,48",-1.0,negative,"[('Drone', 'PRODUCT'), ('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アザラシの赤ちゃん1万頭以上が鳥インフルエンザで死ぬ、豪離島で　研究報告,"More than 10,000 baby seals die from bird flu on remote Australian island, research report",0.0,neutral,"[('More than 10,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Australian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イギリスで中国情報機関のためスパイ活動、2被告に禁錮刑,Two defendants sentenced to prison in UK for spying for Chinese intelligence agency,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】元オランダ代表ファン・デル・ファールト氏、日本代表への差別発言を謝罪,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Former Netherlands representative Van der Vaart apologizes for discriminatory remarks against Japan representative,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('Netherlands', 'GPE'), ('Van der Vaart', 'ORG'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,アメリカとイラン、14項目の合意文書に署名　何が書かれているのか,America and Iran sign 14-point agreement; what's in it?,0.0,neutral,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('14', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Mazungumzo kati ya Marekani na Iran yaahirishwa huku Vance akijiondoa katika safari ya Uswizi","Directly, Talks between the US and Iran are postponed as Vance pulls out of a trip to Switzerland",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Vance', 'ORG'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Iran na Marekani wananufaika vipi na makubaliano yaliyoafikiwa, ugumu wa kuyadumisha ni upi?","How do Iran and the United States benefit from the agreement reached, what is the difficulty in maintaining it?",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tofauti za kauli kati ya Trump na Vance zamuweka Vance kikaangoni,The differences in statements between Trump and Vance put Vance in the crosshairs,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kuna hatari gani kuingia ndani ya nyumba ukiwa umevaa viatu?,What is the risk of entering the house while wearing shoes?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Simulizi ya kijana aliyempeleka kuku wake mgonjwa hospitalini ilivyobadili maisha yake,The story of a young man who took his sick chicken to the hospital changed his life,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za Soka: Ofa ya kwanza ya Arsenal kwa Monga 'yapigwa chini',Football Rumors: Arsenal's first offer for Monga 'shot down',0.0,neutral,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Monga', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini aina hizi 11 za saratani zinaangamiza sana vijana?,Why are these 11 types of cancer so devastating to young people?,0.0,neutral,"[('11', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Kombe la Dunia 2026: Ratiba, msimamo na matokeo","World Cup 2026: Schedule, standings and results",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,'Ndugu yangu alijificha kwenye gunia la mchele': Nyota wakimbizi wanaocheza Kombe la Dunia,'My brother hid in a sack of rice': Refugee stars playing in the World Cup,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Hegseth aonya Marekani itarejesha kizuizi cha majini makubaliano ya Iran yasipozingatiwa,Hegseth warns the US will restore the naval blockade if the Iran deal is not respected,-1.0,negative,"[('Hegseth', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Could the HPV vaccine eliminate cervical cancer deaths?,Could the HPV vaccine eliminate cervical cancer deaths?,-1.0,negative,"[('HPV', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Trump hints at new approach to North Korea’s nuclear programme,Trump hints at new approach to North Korea’s nuclear programme,0.0,neutral,"[('North Korea’s', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,World Cup: Five keys to USA vs Australia – Pulisic fit? Can USMNT qualify?,World Cup: Five keys to USA vs Australia – Pulisic fit? Can USMNT qualify?,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Five', 'CARDINAL'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Australia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Arsenal to begin Premier League title defence against promoted Coventry,Arsenal to begin Premier League title defence against promoted Coventry,0.0,neutral,"[('Coventry', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Bruised Brazil face tiny Haiti in search of World Cup reset,Bruised Brazil face tiny Haiti in search of World Cup reset,0.0,neutral,"[('Bruised', 'NORP'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Haiti', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Syrian activist Hassan Akkad detained in Damascus,Syrian activist Hassan Akkad detained in Damascus,0.0,neutral,"[('Syrian', 'NORP'), ('Hassan Akkad', 'PERSON'), ('Damascus', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Indian court rejects appeal over ban on Telegram app,Indian court rejects appeal over ban on Telegram app,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP'), ('Telegram', 'PRODUCT')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Morocco’s World Cup captain Achraf Hakimi to stand trial on rape charge,Morocco’s World Cup captain Achraf Hakimi to stand trial on rape charge,0.0,neutral,"[('Morocco’s', 'ORG'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Achraf Hakimi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"World Cup Day 9: USA, Brazil and Morocco return to action","World Cup Day 9: USA, Brazil and Morocco return to action",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup Day', 'EVENT'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('USA', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US export ban on Anthropic’s AI models further strains alliances,US export ban on Anthropic’s AI models further strains alliances,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Anthropic’s AI', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"West Asia war LIVE: Iran-U.S. deal under strain as Israel targets Lebanon, Swiss talks postponed","West Asia war LIVE: Iran-U.S. deal under strain as Israel targets Lebanon, Swiss talks postponed",-1.0,negative,"[('West Asia war', 'LOC'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Supreme Court declares right to walk on footpath a fundamental right, wants law","Supreme Court declares right to walk on footpath a fundamental right, wants law",0.0,neutral,"[('Supreme Court', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"SC flags ‘brain drain’ in legal profession, directs creation of fund for young lawyers","SC flags ‘brain drain’ in legal profession, directs creation of fund for young lawyers",0.0,neutral,"[('SC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,‘Operation Tiger’: Aaditya Thackeray calls six dissident Shiv Sena (UBT) MPs ‘shameless and ungrateful’,‘Operation Tiger’: Aaditya Thackeray calls six dissident Shiv Sena (UBT) MPs ‘shameless and ungrateful’,0.0,neutral,"[('Aaditya Thackeray', 'PERSON'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Shiv Sena', 'PERSON'), ('UBT', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,T.N. Assembly unanimously adopts resolution against Karnataka government’s Mekedatu dam proposal,T.N. Assembly unanimously adopts resolution against Karnataka government’s Mekedatu dam proposal,0.0,neutral,"[('T.N. Assembly', 'ORG'), ('Karnataka', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Great Nicobar project: Jairam Ramesh says Environment Minister Yadav’s defence ‘disappointing’,Great Nicobar project: Jairam Ramesh says Environment Minister Yadav’s defence ‘disappointing’,1.0,positive,"[('Great Nicobar', 'ORG'), ('Jairam Ramesh', 'PERSON'), ('Yadav’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,India calls Pakistan a ‘Frankenstein state' at U.N.; accuses it of supporting terrorism,India calls Pakistan a ‘Frankenstein state' at U.N.; accuses it of supporting terrorism,-1.0,negative,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('U.N.', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ex-Bengal minister Jyoti Priya Mallick quits TMC posts; Goutam Deb resigns as Siliguri mayor,Ex-Bengal minister Jyoti Priya Mallick quits TMC posts; Goutam Deb resigns as Siliguri mayor,0.0,neutral,"[('Jyoti Priya Mallick', 'PERSON'), ('Goutam Deb', 'PERSON'), ('Siliguri', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,N. Murali appointed Chairman of The Hindu Group Publishing Private Limited,N. Murali appointed Chairman of The Hindu Group Publishing Private Limited,0.0,neutral,"[('N. Murali', 'PERSON'), ('The Hindu Group Publishing Private Limited', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Kerala Budget bets on silver economy, launches elderly welfare initiatives","Kerala Budget bets on silver economy, launches elderly welfare initiatives",0.0,neutral,"[('Kerala Budget', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,US-Iran talks postponed as Vance pulls out of Switzerland trip,US-Iran talks postponed as Vance pulls out of Switzerland trip,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Vance', 'ORG'), ('Switzerland', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Lebanon says Israeli strikes kill 18 as Israel says four soldiers killed by Hezbollah,Lebanon says Israeli strikes kill 18 as Israel says four soldiers killed by Hezbollah,-1.0,negative,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('18', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,What Iran and US get from deal and why both could struggle to keep it,What Iran and US get from deal and why both could struggle to keep it,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Do it at home too, women tell Japanese fans who cleaned World Cup stadium","Do it at home too, women tell Japanese fans who cleaned World Cup stadium",0.0,neutral,"[('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Zimbabwe MPs pass bill to extend president's time in power,Zimbabwe MPs pass bill to extend president's time in power,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Moscow residents complain of black rain after largest Ukrainian attack hits oil refinery,Moscow residents complain of black rain after largest Ukrainian attack hits oil refinery,-1.0,negative,"[('Moscow', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Thirty-five killed as gunmen attack Niger's biggest airport,Thirty-five killed as gunmen attack Niger's biggest airport,-1.0,negative,"[('Thirty-five', 'CARDINAL'), ('Niger', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Asia's richest man Ambani announces what could be India's biggest share sale,Asia's richest man Ambani announces what could be India's biggest share sale,0.0,neutral,"[('Asia', 'LOC'), ('Ambani', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"In Trump's shadow, Vance becomes face of Iran deal","In Trump's shadow, Vance becomes face of Iran deal",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Vance', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Bowen: US-Iran deal raises inescapable question of what the war was for,Bowen: US-Iran deal raises inescapable question of what the war was for,-1.0,negative,"[('Bowen', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mideast Live Updates: Deadly Attacks in Lebanon and Delay in Talks Test U.S.-Iran Deal,Mideast Live Updates: Deadly Attacks in Lebanon and Delay in Talks Test U.S.-Iran Deal,-1.0,negative,"[('Mideast Live Updates', 'ORG'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Delay', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Swiss Officials Say Iran Talks Are Off, for Now","Swiss Officials Say Iran Talks Are Off, for Now",0.0,neutral,"[('Swiss', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,‘Game Changer’? Too Soon to Tell. But Ukraine Flexed in Striking Moscow.,‘Game Changer’? Too Soon to Tell. But Ukraine Flexed in Striking Moscow.,0.0,neutral,"[('Tell', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine Flexed', 'FAC'), ('Moscow', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mexico’s Laws Have a New Target: Journalists,Mexico’s Laws Have a New Target: Journalists,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico’s Laws Have a New Target', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Who Is Andy Burnham, the Man Who Could Be Britain’s Next Prime Minister?","Who Is Andy Burnham, the Man Who Could Be Britain’s Next Prime Minister?",0.0,neutral,"[('Andy Burnham', 'PERSON'), ('the Man Who Could Be Britain’s Next', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"What Does It All Mean? Once a Year, French Students Try to Explain.","What Does It All Mean? Once a Year, French Students Try to Explain.",0.0,neutral,"[('French Students Try', 'ORG'), ('Explain', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Critics of Russia Say This Critic Isn’t Critical Enough,Critics of Russia Say This Critic Isn’t Critical Enough,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Iran and the U.S. Have an Understanding. Will It Lead to a Deal?,Iran and the U.S. Have an Understanding. Will It Lead to a Deal?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('U.S.', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Ukraine Strikes Moscow Refinery in Large-Scale Drone Attack,Ukraine Strikes Moscow Refinery in Large-Scale Drone Attack,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Large-Scale Drone Attack', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_19,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Gunmen Attack a Major Airport in Niger,Gunmen Attack a Major Airport in Niger,-1.0,negative,"[('Niger', 'DATE')]"
