Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Skipper: cómo el petrolero confiscado por EE.UU. frente a las costas de Venezuela falseó su ubicación para burlar las sanciones,Skipper: how the oil tanker confiscated by the US off the coast of Venezuela falsified its location to circumvent sanctions,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Qué es la flota de buques fantasma por la que se acusa a Venezuela de burlar las sanciones para exportar su petróleo,What is the fleet of ghost ships for which Venezuela is accused of circumventing sanctions to export its oil?,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Por supuesto que voy a regresar a Venezuela, sé los riesgos que estoy asumiendo"": María Corina Machado habla con la BBC tras reaparecer en Oslo","""Of course I am going to return to Venezuela, I know the risks I am taking"": María Corina Machado speaks to the BBC after reappearing in Oslo",0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('Oslo', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"La ""psicosis"" en Francia por el auge de los asesinatos de menores a manos de bandas de narcotraficantes","The ""psychosis"" in France due to the rise in murders of minors at the hands of drug trafficking gangs",-0.125,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Son absolutamente escandalosos"": la indignación de los aficionados al fútbol tras conocerse los precios de las entradas del Mundial 2026","""They are absolutely scandalous"": the indignation of football fans after knowing the ticket prices for the 2026 World Cup",0.2,"[('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"15 हज़ार सैनिकों और युद्धपोत की तैनाती, ट्रंप क्यों इस नेता के पीछे पड़ गए हैं?","Deploying 15 thousand soldiers and warships, why has Trump gone after this leader?",0.0,"[('15 thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,सुनील गावस्कर की याचिका पर दिल्ली हाईकोर्ट ने गूगल, मेटा, एक्स को दिए निर्देश","Live, Delhi High Court gives instructions to Google, Meta, X on Sunil Gavaskar's petition",0.1481818181818182,"[('Delhi High Court', 'PERSON'), ('Google', 'ORG'), ('Meta', 'ORG'), (""Sunil Gavaskar's"", 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"अर्शदीप पर गंभीर का 'ग़ुस्सा', भारत की हार के बाद इन बातों की हो रही है चर्चा","Gambhir's 'anger' on Arshdeep, these things are being discussed after India's defeat",-0.7,"[('Gambhir', 'ORG'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,आग लगने पर जलने से ज़्यादा मौतें दम घुटने से क्यों होती हैं?,Why do more deaths occur due to suffocation than burns?,0.1875,[]
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सऊदी अरब और यूएई में किस मामले को लेकर बढ़ रही है कड़वाहट,On which issue is bitterness increasing between Saudi Arabia and UAE?,0.0,"[('Saudi Arabia', 'GPE'), ('UAE', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"मेक्सिको ने लगाया भारत पर 50 फ़ीसदी टैरिफ़, कितना होगा असर","Mexico imposes 50 percent tariff on India, what will be the impact",0.0,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('50 percent', 'PERCENT'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,इंडिगो संकट के लिए ज़िम्मेदार कौन?,Who is responsible for Indigo crisis?,0.2,"[('Indigo', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,कभी दूसरों पर निर्भर तुर्की कैसे बना हथियारों के बाज़ार का बड़ा खिलाड़ी,"How Türkiye, once dependent on others, became a big player in the arms market",0.0,"[('Türkiye', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"पाकिस्तानी नौजवानों को नहीं मिल रही नौकरी, बूढ़े माँ-बाप को बनना पड़ रहा सहारा","Pakistani youth are not getting jobs, old parents have to support them",0.1,"[('Pakistani', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As conexões de Daniel Vorcaro e do Banco Master com ministros do STF,Daniel Vorcaro and Banco Master’s connections with STF ministers,0.0,"[('Daniel Vorcaro', 'PERSON'), ('Banco Master’s', 'ORG'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Alexandre de Moraes anula decisão da Câmara e determina perda imediata de mandato de Carla Zambelli,Alexandre de Moraes annuls the Chamber’s decision and determines the immediate loss of Carla Zambelli’s mandate,0.0,"[('Alexandre de Moraes', 'PERSON'), ('Chamber', 'ORG'), ('Carla Zambelli’s', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que é a frota de navios fantasmas que os EUA acusam a Venezuela de usar para burlar sanções e exportar petróleo?,What is the fleet of ghost ships that the US accuses Venezuela of using to circumvent sanctions and export oil?,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que se sabe sobre a apreensão de petroleiro pelos EUA na costa da Venezuela,What is known about the US seizure of an oil tanker off the coast of Venezuela,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,'Bolsonaro tem que pagar. Não adianta choramingar', diz Lula sobre redução de pena do ex-presidente, Duration 0,47","Video,'Bolsonaro has to pay. There's no point in whining', says Lula about reducing the former president's sentence, Duration 0.47",0.0,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('0.47', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O adolescente peruano que viralizou narrando final da Libertadores entre Flamengo e Palmeiras do alto de morro,The Peruvian teenager who went viral narrating the Libertadores final between Flamengo and Palmeiras from the top of the hill,0.25,"[('Peruvian', 'NORP'), ('Libertadores', 'PERSON'), ('Flamengo', 'PERSON'), ('Palmeiras', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A revolta de torcedores com preços de ingressos da Copa do Mundo: 'Traição monumental',Fans' revolt over World Cup ticket prices: 'Monumental betrayal',0.0,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Monumental', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Descoberta arqueológica aponta que humanos dominaram fogo 350 mil anos antes do que se pensava,"Archaeological discovery shows that humans mastered fire 350,000 years earlier than previously thought",-0.05555555555555555,"[('350,000 years earlier', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Revista Time elege 'arquitetos da IA' como Pessoa do Ano de 2025,Time Magazine names 'AI architects' as 2025 Person of the Year,0.0,"[('Time Magazine', 'ORG'), ('the Year', 'EVENT')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сгорающие на передовой: треть подтвержденных погибших в Украине российских военных — добровольцы,Burning on the front lines: a third of confirmed Russian military deaths in Ukraine are volunteers,0.07500000000000001,"[('third', 'ORDINAL'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: Зеленский допускает референдум по вопросу территорий, Трамп еще не решил, поедут ли его посланники в Европу на переговоры по Украине","LIVELive, War in Ukraine: Zelensky allows a referendum on the issue of territories, Trump has not yet decided whether his envoys will go to Europe for negotiations on Ukraine",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Europe', 'LOC'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,ЕС выделил 30 млн евро на поддержку гражданского общества;  конфликт с Литвой ушел на новый виток. Главное в Беларуси за неделю,The EU has allocated €30 million to support civil society;  the conflict with Lithuania took a new turn. The main things in Belarus in a week,0.1515151515151515,"[('EU', 'ORG'), ('€30 million', 'MONEY'), ('Lithuania', 'GPE'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Судно ВМФ Британии сопроводило за пределы британских вод российскую подлодку, замеченную в проливе Ла-Манш",A British Navy vessel escorted a Russian submarine spotted in the English Channel out of British waters,0.0,"[('British Navy', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('English', 'LANGUAGE'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Фактически лишение гражданства». В Думу внесли законопроект о новом ограничении прав преследуемых в России эмигрантов,“Effectively deprivation of citizenship.” A bill on new restrictions on the rights of emigrants persecuted in Russia was introduced into the Duma,0.36818181818181817,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,По миру катится новая волна гриппа. Чем опасен новый штамм вируса?,A new wave of flu is sweeping the world. How dangerous is the new strain of the virus?,-0.10909090909090909,[]
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В России хотят ввести запрет на передачу данных россиян в «небезопасные» страны,Russia wants to introduce a ban on the transfer of data of Russians to “unsafe” countries,0.2,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Russians', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Премьер-министр и правительство Болгарии ушли в отставку после массовых протестов,Bulgarian Prime Minister and Government Resign After Mass Protests,0.0,"[('Bulgarian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Из хранилища Бристольского музея похитили 600 ценных экспонатов,600 valuable exhibits were stolen from the Bristol Museum storage facility,0.0,"[('600', 'CARDINAL'), ('the Bristol Museum', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Сотрудников лондонской полиции обязали декларировать членство в масонских ложах,London police officers were required to declare membership in Masonic lodges,0.0,"[('London', 'GPE'), ('Masonic', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウクライナ前線を「特別経済区域」に　アメリカから提案受けたとゼレンスキー氏,"Zelenskiy says he has received a proposal from the US to turn the Ukrainian front line into a ""special economic zone""",0.2785714285714286,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,通訳が涙で言葉出ず……ロシアの攻撃で母親を失ったウクライナの少年が欧州議会で証言, 所要時間 1,19","Video, Interpreter is in tears and speechless... Ukrainian boy who lost his mother in Russian attack testifies at European Parliament, Duration: 1,19",0.0,"[('Interpreter', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('1,19', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,NATOトップ、ロシアが5年以内に攻撃してくる可能性を警告,NATO chief warns of possible Russian attack within five years,0.0,"[('NATO', 'ORG'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), ('five years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイのアヌティン首相、議会を解散　「政治権力を国民に返す」,Thai Prime Minister Anutin dissolves parliament and ``returns political power to the people'',0.0,"[('Thai', 'NORP'), ('Anutin', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 チケット価格、決勝は最低60万円超か　サポーターは「裏切り」と批判,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Ticket prices for the final will be at least 600,000 yen, supporters criticize as ""betrayal""",-0.15,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('at least 600,000 yen', 'MONEY')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノーベル平和賞のマチャド氏、ノルウェー到着　10カ月ぶり公の場に,"Nobel Peace Prize winner Machado arrives in Norway, making his first public appearance in 10 months",0.125,"[('Nobel Peace Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Machado', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('10 months', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アメリカ、観光客に過去5年間のSNS情報を求める方針　英国人や日本人も対象,"US plans to ask tourists for social media information from the past five years, including British and Japanese nationals",-0.05416666666666667,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('the past five years', 'DATE'), ('British', 'NORP'), ('Japanese', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イタリア料理がユネスコ無形文化遺産に　「家族やコミュニティーとつながる手段」,"Italian cuisine designated as a UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage, ``a means of connecting with family and community''",0.05,"[('Italian', 'NORP'), ('UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米軍、ヴェネズエラ沖で石油タンカーを拿捕　トランプ政権が圧力強める,U.S. military seizes oil tanker off Venezuela; Trump administration increases pressure,-0.1,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Marekani yazuia meli sita zaidi baada ya kuikamata meli ya mafuta karibu na Venezuela","Directly, the United States blocks six more ships after seizing an oil tanker near Venezuela",0.2333333333333333,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Nchi 10 zenye madeni makubwa zaidi Afrika,10 countries with the biggest debts in Africa,0.0,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('Africa', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wimbi la vifo vya wapinzani linavyoongezeka duniani,The wave of death of opponents is increasing in the world,0.0,[]
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mahakama ya Kenya imesitisha mpango wa msaada wa afya wa Marekani kutokana na masuala ya faragha,A Kenyan court has suspended the US health aid program due to privacy concerns,-0.125,"[('Kenyan', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Bayern kutupa ndoano kwa Guehi Januari,European football rumours: Bayern to throw the hook for Guehi in January,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Guehi', 'PERSON'), ('January', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Waandishi bila mipaka: Israel bado inaongoza kusababisha vifo vya waandishi wa habari,Reporters Without Borders: Israel still leads in killing of journalists,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,F-35 hadi KAAN: Kwanini Uturuki inawekeza kwenye ndege tofauti za kivita?,F-35 to KAAN: Why is Turkey investing in different fighter jets?,0.0,"[('Turkey', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini mapinduzi ya Benin yalifeli wakati mengine yalifanikiwa Afrika Magharibi?,Why did the Benin revolution fail when others succeeded in West Africa?,-0.5,"[('Benin', 'PERSON'), ('West Africa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu kuhusu meli ya mafuta iliyokamatwa na Marekani karibu na pwani ya Venezuela,Learn about the oil tanker seized by the US off the coast of Venezuela,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_12,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Kwanini ndege ya kijeshi ya Nigeria iliivamia Burkina Faso, Traore kujibu mapigo?","Why did the Nigerian military plane attack Burkina Faso, Traore in response to the blows?",-0.1,"[('Nigerian', 'NORP'), ('Burkina Faso', 'ORG')]"
