Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Fujian: cómo es el portaaviones de última generación que China sumó a su flota para desafiar el poderío naval de EE.UU. en el Pacífico,Fujian: what is the next-generation aircraft carrier that China added to its fleet to challenge US naval power in the Pacific?,0.0,"[('Fujian', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Pacific', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Hannah Arendt, la filósofa de ""la banalidad del mal"" cuyo legado resuena en el conflictivo mundo actual a 50 años de su muerte","Hannah Arendt, the philosopher of ""the banality of evil"" whose legacy resonates in today's conflictive world 50 years after her death",-1.0,"[('Hannah Arendt', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('50 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué papel juega EE.UU. en Somalia, el país del que Trump no quiere inmigrantes y el Pentágono lleva años bombardeando","What role does the US play in Somalia, the country from which Trump does not want immigrants and the Pentagon has been bombing for years?",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Somalia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Pentagon', 'ORG'), ('years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Victoria regia, la asombrosa planta sudamericana que transformó los espacios en los que vivimos (y sigue inspirando revoluciones)","Victoria regia, the amazing South American plant that transformed the spaces we live in (and continues to inspire revolutions)",0.24545454545454548,"[('Victoria regia', 'PERSON'), ('South American', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Así quedaron los 12 grupos del Mundial de fútbol 2026: ¿cuándo y contra quién debuta tu equipo en la primera fase?,This is how the 12 groups of the 2026 World Cup were: when and against whom does your team debut in the first phase?,0.25,"[('12', 'CARDINAL'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,अंग्रेज़ों की नाक में दम करने वाले टीपू के पिता हैदर अली की कहानी,"The story of Tipu's father Hyder Ali, who troubled the British.",-0.25,"[('Tipu', 'GPE'), ('Hyder Ali', 'PERSON'), ('British', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पीएम मोदी ने जिस 'हिंदू रेट ऑफ़ ग्रोथ' का ज़िक्र किया वो क्या है,What is the 'Hindu rate of growth' that PM Modi mentioned?,0.0,"[('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('PM Modi', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,टीम इंडिया पर टिप्पणी को लेकर दक्षिण अफ़्रीका के कोच ने तोड़ी चुप्पी","Live, South Africa coach breaks silence regarding comments on Team India",0.13636363636363635,"[('South Africa', 'GPE'), ('Team India', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पुतिन के भारत दौरे का सबसे बड़ा हासिल क्या है?,What is the biggest achievement of Putin's visit to India?,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"गोवा के नाइट क्लब में भीषण आग लगने से 25 लोगों की मौत, आधी रात को हुआ क्या था","25 people died in massive fire in Goa's night club, what happened at midnight",0.0,"[('25', 'CARDINAL'), ('midnight', 'TIME')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,रोहित और विराट के शानदार प्रदर्शन की चर्चा के बीच गंभीर बोले- वर्ल्ड कप अभी दो साल दूर,"Amidst the discussion about the brilliant performance of Rohit and Virat, Gambhir said - World Cup is still two years away.",0.9,"[('Rohit', 'ORG'), ('Virat', 'ORG'), ('Gambhir', 'ORG'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('two years', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"इंडिगो मामले के बीच सरकार ने तय किया विमान किराया, टिकट के दाम अब इतने हज़ार से ज़्यादा नहीं","Amidst the Indigo issue, the government fixed the air fare, ticket prices are now not more than Rs. 1,000.",-0.075,"[('Indigo', 'ORG'), ('1,000', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"हुमायूं कबीर ने रखी 'बाबरी मस्जिद की नींव', बीजेपी ने कहा- ममता आग से खेल रही हैं","Humayun Kabir laid the 'foundation of Babri Masjid', BJP said - Mamata is playing with fire",0.0,"[('Humayun Kabir', 'PERSON'), (""Babri Masjid'"", 'ORG'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,तुर्की का ऐसा 'मानवरहित लड़ाकू विमान' जिससे एफ़-16 को निशाना बनाने का किया जा रहा दावा,Türkiye's 'unmanned fighter plane' which is claimed to target F-16,0.0,"[('Türkiye', 'GPE'), ('F-16', 'PRODUCT')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O padre que assumiu a tutela de 26 crianças com pais sob risco de deportação nos EUA,The priest who took guardianship of 26 children whose parents were at risk of deportation in the US,0.0,"[('26', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Incêndio em casa noturna de Goa, na Índia, deixa ao menos 23 mortos","Fire at nightclub in Goa, India, leaves at least 23 dead",-0.25,"[('Goa', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('at least 23', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O cálculo de Lula para lidar com crise entre Trump e Maduro,Lula's calculation to deal with the crisis between Trump and Maduro,0.0,"[('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Maduro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que fazer se você não gosta do parceiro da sua amiga,What to do if you don't like your friend's partner,0.0,[]
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,As três palavras que vão te ajudar a impor limites no trabalho,The three words that will help you set limits at work,0.0,"[('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que o primeiro cocô do bebê pode revelar sobre a saúde dele no futuro,What your baby's first poop can reveal about his future health,0.125,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Imagem falsa gerada por IA leva a cancelamento de trens na Inglaterra,AI-generated fake image leads to train cancellations in England,-0.5,"[('England', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que cantar é surpreendentemente bom para a saúde,Why singing is surprisingly good for your health,0.7,[]
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os smartwatches estão controlando demais nossa vida?,Are smartwatches controlling our lives too much?,0.2,[]
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Carros estão ficando cada vez maiores (e mais populares): por que isso é um problema?,Cars are getting bigger (and more popular): why is this a problem?,0.3666666666666667,[]
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Год без Асада и Путина. Куда ведут Сирию новые власти и что будет дальше,A year without Assad and Putin. Where are the new authorities leading Syria and what will happen next?,0.06818181818181818,"[('A year', 'DATE'), ('Assad', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Syria', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"В Иране арестовали организаторов марафона за то, что участвующие в забеге женщины не надели хиджаб","In Iran, marathon organizers were arrested because women participating in the race did not wear a hijab.",0.0,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: атаки на Полтавскую и Черниговскую области; Зеленский поговорил с Уиткоффом и Кушнером","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: attacks on Poltava and Chernigov regions; Zelensky spoke with Witkoff and Kushner",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Poltava', 'ORG'), ('Chernigov', 'ORG'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Witkoff', 'ORG'), ('Kushner', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Поезда все еще курсируют, и это дает надежду». Как украинки ездят на фронт к любимым","“Trains are still running, which gives hope.” How Ukrainian women go to the front to see their loved ones",0.7,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нужно ли призывать ультраортодоксов в армию? Споры об этом грозят Израилю серьезным кризисом,Should the ultra-Orthodox be drafted into the army? Disputes about this threaten Israel with a serious crisis.,-0.3333333333333333,"[('ultra-Orthodox', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,СДВГ: как работают мозг и психика людей с дефицитом внимания,ADHD: how the brain and psyche of people with attention deficit work,0.0,[]
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Почему мы так любим собак? Вот что говорит наука,Why do we love dogs so much? Here's what science says,0.35,[]
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Серьезная потеря для детей? Что такое Roblox и почему российские власти его заблокировали,A serious loss for children? What is Roblox and why did Russian authorities block it?,-0.16666666666666666,"[('Roblox', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Умер архитектор Фрэнк Гери. Среди его работ — музей Гуггенхайма в Бильбао,Architect Frank Gehry has died. Among his works is the Guggenheim Museum in Bilbao,0.0,"[('Frank Gehry', 'PERSON'), ('the Guggenheim Museum', 'ORG'), ('Bilbao', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Конец эры массовой миграции, непобедимая армия и доктрина Монро. США обнародовали новую стратегию национальной безопасности","The end of the era of mass migration, the invincible army and the Monroe Doctrine. US unveils new national security strategy",0.13636363636363635,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,米連邦最高裁、市民権の「出生地主義」めぐる訴訟を受理　トランプ政権は廃止目指す,U.S. Supreme Court accepts lawsuit over citizenship citizenship; Trump administration aims to abolish it,0.0,"[('U.S. Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 米ネットフリックスがワーナーの主要事業を買収へ　何が起こっているのか,[Commentary] US Netflix to acquire Warner's main business - what's going on?,0.16666666666666666,"[('Warner', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 プーチン氏とモディ氏、デリー会談で何を得たのか,[Commentary] What did Mr. Putin and Mr. Modi gain from the Delhi meeting?,0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Modi', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,トランプ米政権、ヨーロッパは「文明消滅」の危機と警告　新たな戦略文書で,Trump administration warns that Europe is at risk of ``annihilation of civilization'' in new strategic document,0.13636363636363635,"[('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 抽選会で組み合わせ決定　FIFAがトランプ氏に「平和賞」を授与,[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Pairings determined by lottery; FIFA awards Trump the Peace Prize,0.0,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('FIFA', 'ORG'), ('Trump the Peace Prize', 'ORG')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,プーチン氏、ウクライナ軍撤退なければドンバスを「武力で掌握」と警告,"Putin warns that if Ukrainian troops do not withdraw, he will seize Donbas by force",0.0,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Donbas', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ヘグセス米長官は「全員殺せ」と命令していないと海軍提督　連邦議員たちに証言,Navy admiral tells federal lawmakers that US Secretary of State Hegseth did not give order to kill everyone,0.0,"[('Navy', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Hegseth', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,欧州歌合戦「ユーロヴィジョン」、来年のイスラエルの出場認める　アイルランドなど4カ国がボイコット表明,"Four countries, including Ireland, announce boycott of European singing competition ``Eurovision'' to allow Israel to participate next year",0.0,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ireland', 'GPE'), ('European', 'NORP'), ('Eurovision', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('next year', 'DATE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,オットセイの赤ちゃんがバーに侵入、ニュージーランド, 所要時間 1,12","Video, Baby fur seal breaks into bar, New Zealand, Duration 1,12",0.13636363636363635,"[('New Zealand', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mazungumzo ya mpango wa amani na Marekani yanasonga mbele - Zelensky","Directly, Peace deal talks with the US are moving forward - Zelensky",0.1,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Watoto 33 wauawa shule ya Chekechea ikishambuliwa,33 children were killed when a kindergarten was attacked,-0.2,"[('33', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu masuala sita kuhusu mvutano wa DRC na Rwanda,Know six issues about the tension between the DRC and Rwanda,0.0,"[('six', 'CARDINAL'), ('DRC', 'ORG'), ('Rwanda', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Wavamia hosteli na kuua 11 kwa risasi Afrika Kusini,They attacked a hostel and killed 11 in South Africa,-0.2,"[('11', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Africa', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: PSG inamtaka Rashford,European football rumours: PSG want Rashford,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Rashford', 'PERSON')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, Tanzania kutengwa kidiplomasia?",Is Tanzania diplomatically isolated?,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Unaweza kuzitambua video zilizotengenezwa kwa AI?,Can you recognize videos made with AI?,0.0,"[('AI', 'GPE')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Droo yazipanga makundi magumu timu za Afrika,World Cup 2026: The draw organizes difficult groups for African teams,-0.25,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('African', 'NORP')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Klabu 12 zinamtaka Mainoo,European football rumours: 12 clubs want Mainoo,0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('12', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_12_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Serikali  yaijibu jamii ya kimataifa,Protests in Tanzania: The government responds to the international community,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
