Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""Carteles gringos"": las pandillas que venden en EE.UU. la droga producida en América Latina (y por qué no tienen capos como ""El Chapo"")","""Gringos"": the gangs sold in the US",0.0,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,मैथ्स को देखते ही कुछ लोग क्यों कहते हैं 'हमसे ना हो पाएगा',Why do some people say 'we can't do it' as soon as they see maths?,0.0,[]
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"हिमाचल प्रदेश: बिलासपुर में लैंडस्लाइड की चपेट में बस, 15 लोगों की मौत","Himachal Pradesh: Bus hit by landslide in Bilaspur, 15 people died",0.0,"[('Bilaspur', 'GPE'), ('15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,वो रात जब अमेरिकी पायलट बने ईरान के खिलाफ़ इसराइल की ढाल,That night when Israel's shield against Iran became an American pilot,0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार चुनाव: नीतीश कुमार कमज़ोर पड़े तो बीजेपी के लिए कितना बड़ा झटका,"Bihar Elections: If Nitish Kumar becomes weak, what a big blow it will be for BJP.",-0.1875,"[('Bihar Elections', 'PERSON'), ('Nitish', 'NORP'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Tarifas, juros e demissões: Suprema Corte dos EUA vai redefinir poderes de Trump","Tariffs, interest and layoffs: US Supreme Court will redefine Trump's powers",0.0,"[('US Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Carro de Daniel Noboa, presidente do Equador, é atacado; o que se sabe","Car of Daniel Noboa, president of Ecuador, is attacked; what is known",0.0,"[('Daniel Noboa', 'PERSON'), ('Ecuador', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Alpinistas são resgatados após ficarem presos em nevasca no Everest,Climbers rescued after being trapped in blizzard on Everest,-0.2,"[('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Renováveis ultrapassam carvão e se tornam maior fonte de energia elétrica pela 1ª vez na história,Renewables exceed charcoal and become a greater source of electricity for the first time in history,0.375,"[('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O trabalho sobre computadores quânticos que deu Prêmio Nobel de Física a pesquisadores,The work on quantum computers that gave researchers the Nobel Prize in Physics,0.0,"[('the Nobel Prize in Physics', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Após dois anos de guerra e destruição, Israel e Hamas estão mais próximos do fim do conflito?","After two years of war and destruction, are Israel and Hamas closer to the end of the conflict?",0.0,"[('two years', 'DATE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Vídeo,Metanol: BBC investiga venda de lacres falsos e garrafas de bebidas alcoólicas no Facebook, Duration 2,59","Video, Methanol: BBC investigates sales of fake seals and bottles of alcohol on Facebook, Duration 2.59",-0.5,"[('Methanol', 'ORG'), ('BBC', 'ORG'), ('2.59', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que uma família se mudou para Israel e outra deixou o país após os ataques de 7 de outubro?,Why has one family moved to Israel and another left the country after October 7 attacks?,0.0,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('October 7', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O deslocamento 'sem precedentes' da população de Gaza em dois anos de guerra,The 'unprecedented' displacement of the Gaza population in two years of war,0.6,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('two years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"«Картина мира разрушается полностью». Как психологи работают с украинскими детьми, вернувшимися из оккупации","""The picture of the world is completely destroyed."" How psychologists work with Ukrainian children who returned from the occupation",0.1,"[('Ukrainian', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Почему одна семья после 7 октября переехала в Израиль, а другая — покинула страну?","Why did one family move to Israel after October 7, while the other left the country?",-0.0625,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('October 7', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,В Израиле вспоминают жертв нападения ХАМАС 7 октября 2023 года. Фото,"Israel remembers the victims of the Hamas attack on October 7, 2023. Photo",0.0,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('October 7, 2023', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: власти сообщили об атаках на Днепропетровскую область, есть пострадавшие","Livelive, war in Ukraine: the authorities reported attacks on the Dnipropetrovsk region, there are victims",0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Dnipropetrovsk', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Нобеля по физике получили ученые, открывшие макроскопическое квантово-механическое туннелирование",Scientists who discovered macroscopic quantum mechanical tunneling received a Nobel in physics,0.0,"[('Nobel', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Нападение с ножом на бургомистра в Германии: полиция не видит политического мотива,A attack with a knife on a burgomaster in Germany: the police do not see a political motive,0.0,"[('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Предварительные итоги выборов в Сирии: в новый парламент прошли несколько женщин,Preliminary election results in Syria: several women entered the new parliament,0.06818181818181818,"[('Syria', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"ВОЗ встревожена числом курящих электронные сигареты, в том числе детей","WHO is alarmed by the number of people smoking e-cigarettes, including children",0.0,[]
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Израиль и ХАМАС начали переговоры. В чем главные проблемы мирного плана Трампа?,Israel and Hamas began negotiations. What are the main problems with Trump's peace plan?,0.16666666666666666,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Во Франции опять нет премьер-министра. Почему это случилось и что будет дальше,"In France, there is no prime minister again. Why did this happen and what will happen next",0.0,"[('France', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ハマスのイスラエル襲撃から2年……各地で集会、ガザでは攻撃続く　エジプトで交渉2日目,"Two years have passed since Hamas' attack on Israel... rallies everywhere, attacks continue in Gaza; second day of negotiations in Egypt",0.0,"[('Two years', 'DATE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('second day', 'DATE'), ('Egypt', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「あまりにも多くを失った」　戦争開始から2年の犠牲を見つめるパレスチナ人たち,"""We lost so much"" Palestinians staring at the sacrifices two years after the start of the war",0.2,"[('Palestinians', 'NORP'), ('two years', 'DATE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,【検証】 ガザに残る人質はいま……ハマス襲撃から2年, 所要時間 3,07","Video, [Verification] Hostages remain in Gaza...2 years after Hamas attack, time required 3,07",0.0,"[('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('2 years', 'DATE'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('3,07', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノーベル物理学賞、米国拠点の3教授に　量子コンピューターの基礎技術を発見,Nobel Prize in Physics Discovers Basic Technology of Quantum Computers by Three Professors at the US,0.0,"[('Nobel Prize', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ルコルニュ首相が辞任、就任からわずか26日　フランス政界は新たな混乱に,"Prime Minister Le Cornu resigns, just 26 days after taking office, leading to new turmoil in French politics",0.06818181818181818,"[('Le Cornu', 'PERSON'), ('just 26 days', 'DATE'), ('French', 'NORP')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ノーベル生理学・医学賞、坂口志文氏ら3人に　免疫反応抑える「制御性T細胞」を発見,"Nobel Prize in Physiology and Medicine, Sakaguchi Shifumi, discovered ""regulatory T cells"" that suppress immune responses",0.0,"[('Nobel Prize in Physiology and Medicine', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Sakaguchi Shifumi', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イスラエル、トゥーンベリ氏ら活動家170人を国外追放　拘束中に不当な扱い受けたと活動家たち,Israel deports 170 activists including Thunberg; activists say they were treated unfairly during detention,-0.5,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('170', 'CARDINAL'), ('Thunberg', 'ORG')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ロシアのミサイルとドローン、イギリスや日本など外国製の部品を使用とゼレンスキー氏,Zelenskiy says Russian missiles and drones use parts from foreign countries such as Britain and Japan,-0.041666666666666664,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Britain', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,20年間亡命の政治家、来年2月の総選挙に向け帰国へ　バングラデシュ,"Politician in exile for 20 years returns to Japan for the general election in February next year, Bangladesh",0.02500000000000001,"[('20 years', 'DATE'), ('Japan', 'GPE'), ('February next year', 'DATE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025: Mambo matatu yanayoutofautisha uchaguzi wa Zanzibar na Tanzania,ELECTION TANZANIA 2025: Three things that distinguish Zanzibar and Tanzania elections,0.0,"[('2025', 'CARDINAL'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL'), ('Zanzibar', 'NORP'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Mjumbe maalum wa Marekani, mkwe wa Trump kujiunga na mazungumzo ya amani ya Gaza","Directly, US Special Envoy, Trump's son -in -law to join Gaza's peace talks",0.35714285714285715,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mama Polepole: Nirudishieni mwanangu akiwa hai au amekufa,Mother slowly: Return me to my son alive or dead,-0.13333333333333333,[]
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Waridi wa BBC: 'Nina urefu wa cm 85 lakini hilo halinizuii kuishi maisha ya kawaida',BBC Roses: 'I have a height of 85 cm but that doesn't stop me living a normal life',0.15,"[('BBC Roses', 'ORG'), ('85 cm', 'QUANTITY')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Jumatano: Zirkzee haitaki tena Man Utd,European football rumors on Wednesday: Zirkzee no longer wants Man utd,0.1,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('Zirkzee', 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Humphrey Polepole anayeripotiwa kutekwa Tanzania ni nani?,Who is Humphrey Slowly reportedly abducted in Tanzania?,-0.30000000000000004,"[('Humphrey Slowly', 'PERSON'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mtanzania aliyekuwa Israel: ‘Kupiga ng'ombe kuliniepusha kuuawa na Hamas Oktoba 7’,Israeli Tanzanian: 'Beating cows avoided killing Hamas on October 7',0.0,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), (""October 7'"", 'DATE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, mwisho wa vita Gaza wakaribia?",Is the end of the war Gaza near?,0.1,"[('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Humphrey Polepole: Familia yathibitisha 'katekwa na wasiojulikana',Humphrey Slowly: Family Confirms 'captured by unknown',-0.2,"[(""Humphrey Slowly: Family Confirms '"", 'PERSON')]"
2025_10_08,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwanini Samia ameshindwa kukamilisha mageuzi kwa namna na kiwango alichoahidi?,Why has Samia failed to complete the reform in the form and level he promised?,-0.2,"[('Samia', 'PERSON')]"
