Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo Putin se obsesionó con controlar hasta el último detalle de su imagen pública,How Putin became obsessed with controlling every last detail of his public image,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Super El Niño"": los gráficos que muestran por qué puede ser el fenómeno más extremo en décadas (y cuáles serían sus efectos)","""Super El Niño"": the graphs that show why it may be the most extreme phenomenon in decades (and what its effects would be)",0.0,neutral,"[('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Miraba dónde vivía y pensaba: ¿cómo eso va a pasar?"": el inesperado éxito de Yudi Heredia, la música cubana que conquistó a Rosalía y dirige la orquesta del Lux Tour","""I looked where I lived and thought: how is that going to happen?"": the unexpected success of Yudi Heredia, the Cuban musician who conquered Rosalía and directs the Lux Tour orchestra",1.0,positive,"[('Yudi Heredia', 'PERSON'), ('Cuban', 'NORP'), ('Rosalía', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Diabetes tipo 5, la nueva y desconocida categoría de la enfermedad que divide a científicos y médicos","Type 5 diabetes, the new and unknown category of the disease that divides scientists and doctors",0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Pasé de llorar con su hija, a verlo llegar arrastrándose"": el emocionante relato del escalador que perdió al guía que sobrevivió solo durante 6 días en el Everest","""I went from crying with his daughter to seeing him arrive crawling"": the moving story of the climber who lost the guide who survived alone for 6 days on Everest",0.0,neutral,"[('6 days', 'DATE'), ('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"El sherpa dado por muerto en el Everest que fue encontrado ""milagrosamente"" cuando descendía por el hielo a rastras","The Sherpa presumed dead on Everest who was found ""miraculously"" while crawling down the ice",0.0,neutral,"[('Sherpa', 'ORG'), ('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué supone para Cuba la retirada de las principales multinacionales hoteleras que operaban en el país,What does the withdrawal of the main hotel multinationals that operated in the country mean for Cuba?,0.0,neutral,"[('Cuba', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo el Mundial de fútbol expone la tensa relación que mantienen los 3 países vecinos de Norteamérica,How the World Cup exposes the tense relationship between the three neighboring countries of North America,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('North America', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Zelensky propone conversaciones cara a cara con Putin en una carta abierta al presidente ruso,Zelensky proposes face-to-face talks with Putin in open letter to Russian president,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Muere ""de tristeza"" a los 56 años Marjane Satrapi, la novelista gráfica y cineasta franco-iraní de ""Persépolis""","Marjane Satrapi, the French-Iranian graphic novelist and filmmaker of ""Persepolis,"" dies ""of sadness"" at the age of 56",0.0,neutral,"[('Marjane Satrapi', 'PERSON'), ('French', 'NORP'), ('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('the age of', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,राजेश एक्सपोर्ट्स: 15 लाख करोड़ रुपए की 'फ़र्जी कमाई' दिखाने वाली कंपनी में एलआईसी के भारी निवेश पर उठे सवाल,Rajesh Exports: Questions raised on LIC's huge investment in a company showing 'fake earnings' of Rs 15 lakh crore,1.0,positive,"[('LIC', 'ORG'), ('15', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,भारत ने बांग्लादेश के 'जबरन लोगों को सीमा पार भेजने' के आरोपों पर क्या जवाब दिया?","Live, How did India respond to Bangladesh's allegations of 'forcibly sending people across the border'?",0.0,neutral,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Bangladesh', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,इस गांव में फ़ोन चार्ज करने के लिए 45 किलोमीटर दूर जाने को मजबूर हैं लोग,People are forced to go 45 kilometers away to charge their phones in this village.,0.0,neutral,"[('45 kilometers', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कॉकरोच जनता पार्टीः जंतर-मंतर पर धरना-प्रदर्शन की अपील, दिल्ली पुलिस के क्या हैं नियम","Cockroach Janata Party: Appeal for protest at Jantar Mantar, what are the rules of Delhi Police?",0.0,neutral,"[('Cockroach Janata Party', 'ORG'), ('Jantar Mantar', 'PERSON'), ('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"कुवैत एयरपोर्ट हमले में उज्जैन के शख़्स की मौत, शादी में शामिल होने भारत आ रहे थे","Ujjain man dies in Kuwait airport attack, was coming to India to attend wedding",-1.0,negative,"[('Kuwait', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,ममता बनर्जी से मुसलमान विधायक भी दूरी क्यों बना रहे हैं?,Why are Muslim MLAs also keeping distance from Mamata Banerjee?,0.0,neutral,"[('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Mamata Banerjee', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,दिल्ली आग हादसाः पिता और बेटे ने  समझदारी से बचाई कई लोगों की जान,Delhi fire accident: Father and son wisely saved the lives of many people,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"पुतिन ने क्यों कहा, अमेरिका भारत पर बेकार दबाव बना रहा",Why did Putin say America is putting unnecessary pressure on India?,0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,दिल्ली से चेन्नई तक: भारतीय शहर क्यों गर्म होते जा रहे हैं,From Delhi to Chennai: Why Indian cities are getting hotter,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi', 'GPE'), ('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"'सरकार ने नीट ठीक से कराई होती तो मेरी बेटी ज़िंदा होती', नागपुर की स्टूडेंट ने की आत्महत्या, पुलिस ने क्या बताया?","'Had the government conducted NEET properly, my daughter would have been alive', Nagpur student commits suicide, what did the police tell?",0.0,neutral,"[('NEET', 'ORG'), ('Nagpur', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"O que aconteceu no México, na Colômbia e na Venezuela após  organizações serem classificadas como terroristas pelos EUA","What happened in Mexico, Colombia and Venezuela after organizations were classified as terrorist by the US",-1.0,negative,"[('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Colombia', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Como fui enganada por mulher que dizia ser uma adolescente de 12 anos com autismo : 'Dei carinho, afeto, comida. Não tinha como desconfiar'","How I was deceived by a woman who claimed to be a 12-year-old teenager with autism: 'I gave affection, food. There was no way to suspect",0.0,neutral,"[('12-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,O sherpa dado como morto e encontrado 'milagrosamente' 6 dias após desaparecer no Everest,Sherpa presumed dead and 'miraculously' found 6 days after disappearing on Everest,0.0,neutral,"[('6 days', 'DATE'), ('Everest', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Aos 10 anos, me preparava para ser prisioneira política': Marjane Satrapi, a autora que retratou transformação do Irã sob a Revolução Islâmica","'At 10 years old, I was preparing to be a political prisoner': Marjane Satrapi, the author who portrayed Iran's transformation under the Islamic Revolution",0.0,neutral,"[('10 years old', 'DATE'), ('Marjane Satrapi', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE'), ('the Islamic Revolution', 'LAW')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Quem foi Catulo da Paixão Cearense, o violeiro que traduziu o popular para a elite","Who was Catulo da Paixão Cearense, the guitarist who translated the popular for the elite",0.0,neutral,"[('Catulo da Paixão Cearense', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"'Pix americano'? O que é o Zelle, sistema de pagamentos citado por Eduardo Bolsonaro para negociação entre Brasil e EUA","'American Pix'? What is Zelle, a payment system mentioned by Eduardo Bolsonaro for negotiations between Brazil and the USA",0.0,neutral,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('Zelle', 'PERSON'), ('Eduardo Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Afinal, quem criou o Pix? Como nasceu o sistema de pagamentos que está na mira do governo Trump","After all, who created Pix? How the payment system that is in the Trump administration's sights was born",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Zelensky propõe encontro com Putin e cessar-fogo: 'A escolha agora é sua, chega de guerra'","Zelensky proposes meeting with Putin and ceasefire: 'The choice is yours now, no more war'",-1.0,negative,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Quem está à frente nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,Who is ahead in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que Padre Zezinho está (de novo) na mira de católicos tradicionalistas: 'Falam que sou um câncer para a Igreja',Why Father Zezinho is (again) in the crosshairs of traditionalist Catholics: 'They say I'm a cancer for the Church',0.0,neutral,"[('Zezinho', 'PERSON'), ('Catholics', 'NORP'), ('Church', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Apple удалила мессенджер «Макс» из App Store. В компании объяснили это соблюдением санкций,Apple has removed the Max messenger from the App Store. The company explained this by compliance with sanctions,0.0,neutral,"[('Apple', 'ORG'), ('Max', 'PERSON'), ('App Store', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Бунт машин? Компания-разработчик ИИ Anthropic призывает техгигантов «нажать на тормоз» в развитии технологий, пока системы не вышли из-под контроля человека",Riot of cars? AI developer Anthropic calls on tech giants to “pull the brakes” on technology development before systems get out of human control,0.0,neutral,"[('Riot', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: четыре человека погибли при атаке на завод детского питания в Киевской области, сообщили власти","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: four people died in an attack on a baby food factory in the Kyiv region, authorities said",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Эпоха танков завершается. Как и почему Украина хочет вернуть их на поле боя,The era of tanks is ending. How and why Ukraine wants to return them to the battlefield,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Армения на распутье: к чему приведут санкции со стороны России и сможет ли Армения стать полноценным партнером ЕС,Armenia is at a crossroads: what will sanctions from Russia lead to and can Armenia become a full-fledged partner of the EU,0.0,neutral,"[('Armenia', 'ORG'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('EU', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Вы можете остановить свою войну». Зеленский написал письмо Путину, тот рассказал на ПМЭФ об украинских дронах и «Орешнике»","""You can stop your war."" Zelensky wrote a letter to Putin, who spoke at SPIEF about Ukrainian drones and Oreshnik",-1.0,negative,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('SPIEF', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Oreshnik', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Белорусские власти проводят обыски из-за связей с ЕГУ; Тихановская встретилась со Стармером. Главное в Беларуси за неделю,Belarusian authorities conduct searches due to links with EHU; Tikhanovskaya met with Starmer. The main things in Belarus in a week,0.0,neutral,"[('Belarusian', 'NORP'), ('EHU', 'ORG'), ('Tikhanovskaya', 'ORG'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON'), ('Belarus', 'GPE'), ('a week', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Бывший советник Трампа Джон Болтон согласился признать свою вину в утечке секретной информации,Former Trump adviser John Bolton agreed to plead guilty to leaking classified information,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('John Bolton', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В полуфинале «Ролан Гаррос» россиянка Андреева победила украинку Костюк. После игры рукопожатия не было,"In the semi-finals of Roland Garros, Russian Andreeva defeated Ukrainian Kostyuk. There was no handshake after the game.",0.0,neutral,"[('Roland Garros', 'PERSON'), ('Russian Andreeva', 'PERSON'), ('Ukrainian Kostyuk', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Израиль и Ливан договорились о прекращении огня при условии отказа «Хезболлы» от обстрелов. Группировка соглашение отвергла,Israel and Lebanon agreed to a ceasefire on condition that Hezbollah ceased shelling. The group rejected the agreement,0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Hezbollah', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ゼレンスキー氏、プーチン氏に直接会談を提案　公開書簡で,Zelensky proposes direct talks with Putin in open letter,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヒズボラ、イスラエルとレバノンが合意した停戦を拒否,Hezbollah rejects ceasefire agreed by Israel and Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,AIの進化、遅らせる策が必要　米アンソロピック共同創業者がBBC番組で主張,"We need measures to slow down the evolution of AI, co-founder of Anthropic argues on BBC program",0.0,neutral,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ストレスと疲労、食料や水の問題も……ホルムズ海峡で足止めされている船員たち,"Stress and fatigue, food and water problems... Sailors stranded in the Strait of Hormuz",0.0,neutral,"[('the Strait of Hormuz', 'LOC')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 アメリカ、メキシコ、カナダは相違を乗り越えられるのか　初の3カ国共催,"[2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Can the United States, Mexico, and Canada overcome their differences? First three countries to co-host",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('the United States', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE'), ('Canada', 'GPE'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,マスク氏のAI「Grok」にビキニ写真生成された英下院議員が提訴　スターマー首相も訴えを支持,"British House of Commons member files suit after Musk's AI ""Grok"" generated bikini photo; Prime Minister Starmer supports the lawsuit",0.0,neutral,"[('British House of Commons', 'ORG'), ('Musk', 'PERSON'), ('Grok', 'PERSON'), ('Starmer', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英首相、マスク氏やファラージ氏が「分断をあおっている」と非難　ノヴァクさん殺害事件めぐり,British Prime Minister slams Musk and Farage for ``stoking division'' over Novak murder case,0.0,neutral,"[('British', 'NORP'), ('Novak', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,W杯選手の像を裸に……教師らが待遇改善求め抗議、メキシコ首都, 所要時間 0,57","Video, Statue of World Cup player stripped...Teachers protest demanding better treatment, Mexican capital, Duration 0,57",0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Mexican', 'NORP')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】各国代表が北米に続々と到着　11日に開幕, 所要時間 1,38","Video, [2026 Men's Soccer World Cup] Representatives from each country arrive in North America one after another. Starts on the 11th, Required time 1,38",0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'CARDINAL'), (""Men's Soccer World Cup] Representatives"", 'ORG'), ('North America', 'LOC'), ('the 11th', 'DATE'), ('1,38', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ウクライナがロシア・サンクトペテルブルクを攻撃、経済フォーラム開幕のなか,"Ukraine attacks St. Petersburg, Russia as economic forum opens",-1.0,negative,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Zelensky apendekeza mazungumzo ya ana kwa ana na Putin ili kumaliza vita vya Ukraine","Directly, Zelensky proposes face-to-face talks with Putin to end the war in Ukraine",-1.0,negative,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kijiji ambacho watu husafiri kilomita 45  kuchaji simu zao,A village where people travel 45 kilometers to charge their phones,0.0,neutral,"[('45 kilometers', 'QUANTITY')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, Elon Musk kuwa trilionea wa kwanza duniani?",Will Elon Musk become the first trillionaire in the world?,0.0,neutral,"[('Will Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Iwapo Iran na Marekani wataafikia makubaliano, Israel itakuwa na chaguo gani?","If Iran and the US reach an agreement, what options will Israel have?",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, vidonda vya mdomo visivyopona ni dalili ya saratani?",Are non-healing mouth ulcers a sign of cancer?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wachunguzi Zanzibari wasema mwanamitindo wa Marekani Ashlee alijiua,Investigators in Zanzibar say American model Ashlee committed suicide,0.0,neutral,"[('Zanzibar', 'NORP'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('Ashlee', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, ni akina nani wanaoshikilia rekodi za Kombe la Dunia?",Who are the World Cup record holders?,0.0,neutral,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Familia 10 tajiri zaidi Duniani,10 richest families in the world,0.0,neutral,"[('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Hezbollah yapinga makubaliano mapya ya usitishaji vita kati ya Israel na Lebanon,Hezbollah opposes the new ceasefire agreement between Israel and Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Hifadhi za urani iliyorutubishwa za Iran ziko wapi?,Where are Iran's enriched uranium reserves?,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ranking the World Cup 2026 groups: Which teams are favourites to progress?,Ranking the World Cup 2026 groups: Which teams are favourites to progress?,1.0,positive,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,IAEA brokers Ukraine ceasefire to allow nuclear plant repairs,IAEA brokers Ukraine ceasefire to allow nuclear plant repairs,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"Zelenskyy asks Putin for meeting: What’s he offering, could Russia accept?","Zelenskyy asks Putin for meeting: What’s he offering, could Russia accept?",0.0,neutral,"[('Putin', 'PERSON'), ('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"How the world failed a mother’s children, killed in Israeli strikes on Gaza","How the world failed a mother’s children, killed in Israeli strikes on Gaza",-1.0,negative,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Thousands protest in Albania over Kushner-linked resort project,Thousands protest in Albania over Kushner-linked resort project,0.0,neutral,"[('Thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('Albania', 'GPE'), ('Kushner', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,From NFL-style half-time show to best kits: The World Cup talking points,From NFL-style half-time show to best kits: The World Cup talking points,0.0,neutral,"[('NFL', 'ORG'), ('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('The World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Iran beat Mali in final warm-up before heading to World Cup,Iran beat Mali in final warm-up before heading to World Cup,-1.0,negative,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Mali', 'PERSON'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,US raises pressure on Cuba as it sanctions President Diaz-Canel,US raises pressure on Cuba as it sanctions President Diaz-Canel,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('Cuba', 'GPE'), ('Diaz-Canel', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Sooryavanshi in line for T20 call as India fast-track 15-year-old to top,Sooryavanshi in line for T20 call as India fast-track 15-year-old to top,0.0,neutral,"[('Sooryavanshi', 'PERSON'), ('T20', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('15-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Fireball seen after explosion at Mexico gas facility,Fireball seen after explosion at Mexico gas facility,0.0,neutral,"[('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,The Hindu Huddle Day 1 | Watch live,The Hindu Huddle Day 1 | Watch live,0.0,neutral,"[('1', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"The Hindu Huddle 2026: AI chatbots' support for mental health could be bridge to access, Dr. Amit Malik says","The Hindu Huddle 2026: AI chatbots' support for mental health could be bridge to access, Dr. Amit Malik says",0.0,neutral,"[('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('2026', 'DATE'), ('Amit Malik', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,India-China relations have improved from ‘reset and fresh start’ to ‘new level’: Chinese envoy Xu Feihong,India-China relations have improved from ‘reset and fresh start’ to ‘new level’: Chinese envoy Xu Feihong,1.0,positive,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Xu Feihong', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Compensatory afforestation for biodiversity loss in Nicobar is bogus argument: Jairam Ramesh,Compensatory afforestation for biodiversity loss in Nicobar is bogus argument: Jairam Ramesh,0.0,neutral,"[('Nicobar', 'GPE'), ('Jairam Ramesh', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Bengaluru has the biggest talent pool in Asia, says CM Shivakumar","Bengaluru has the biggest talent pool in Asia, says CM Shivakumar",0.0,neutral,"[('Bengaluru', 'GPE'), ('Asia', 'LOC'), ('CM Shivakumar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Abrogation of Article 370 was the biggest policy mistake by India, says Omar Abdullah","Abrogation of Article 370 was the biggest policy mistake by India, says Omar Abdullah",0.0,neutral,"[('Article 370', 'LAW'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Omar Abdullah', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,In pictures: The Hindu Huddle 2026 | Day 1,In pictures: The Hindu Huddle 2026 | Day 1,0.0,neutral,"[('Hindu', 'NORP'), ('2026', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Annamalai floats political movement, to fight next general election","Annamalai floats political movement, to fight next general election",0.0,neutral,"[('Annamalai', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Vladimir Putin pledges non-interference in ‘delicate’ India-China ties; backs Modi, Xi to resolve border issues amicably","Vladimir Putin pledges non-interference in ‘delicate’ India-China ties; backs Modi, Xi to resolve border issues amicably",0.0,neutral,"[('Vladimir Putin', 'PERSON'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Modi', 'GPE'), ('Xi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Delhi HC refuses urgent hearing on plea against CJP protest,Delhi HC refuses urgent hearing on plea against CJP protest,0.0,neutral,"[('Delhi HC', 'PERSON'), ('CJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Zelensky proposes face-to-face talks in open letter to Putin,Zelensky proposes face-to-face talks in open letter to Putin,0.0,neutral,"[('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Hezbollah rejects renewed ceasefire agreed by Israel and Lebanon,Hezbollah rejects renewed ceasefire agreed by Israel and Lebanon,0.0,neutral,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Lebanon', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,How Trump's White House ballroom plan has doubled in size and cost over a year,How Trump's White House ballroom plan has doubled in size and cost over a year,0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('White House', 'ORG')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Nearly 50 people die of thirst in Sahara desert after lorry breaks down,Nearly 50 people die of thirst in Sahara desert after lorry breaks down,0.0,neutral,"[('Nearly 50', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sahara', 'LOC'), ('lorry', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US actor James Handy stabbed to death, with girlfriend's son arrested","US actor James Handy stabbed to death, with girlfriend's son arrested",-1.0,negative,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('James Handy', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"Ex-wife of Dubai ruler's nephew in custody, prosecutors say","Ex-wife of Dubai ruler's nephew in custody, prosecutors say",0.0,neutral,"[('Dubai', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Mangrove forests are healing after decades of human destruction,Mangrove forests are healing after decades of human destruction,0.0,neutral,"[('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"China cracks down on soft porn, violence and materialism in viral micro dramas","China cracks down on soft porn, violence and materialism in viral micro dramas",0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Xi Jinping to meet Kim Jong Un in rare visit to North Korea,Xi Jinping to meet Kim Jong Un in rare visit to North Korea,0.0,neutral,"[('Kim Jong Un', 'PERSON'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Trump hits back at 'unpatriotic' vote after House rebukes him over Iran,Trump hits back at 'unpatriotic' vote after House rebukes him over Iran,0.0,neutral,"[('House', 'ORG'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,How Gold Is Driving the Spread of Ebola,How Gold Is Driving the Spread of Ebola,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Europe Needs New Military Alliance to Defend Itself, Italy Says","Europe Needs New Military Alliance to Defend Itself, Italy Says",0.0,neutral,"[('Europe Needs New Military Alliance', 'ORG'), ('Italy', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Former Prince Andrew Sublet Cottages on Royal Property Where He Lived Rent-Free,Former Prince Andrew Sublet Cottages on Royal Property Where He Lived Rent-Free,0.0,neutral,"[('Prince Andrew Sublet', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Backed by Trump, Opposed by Putin, and Fighting for His Political Life","Backed by Trump, Opposed by Putin, and Fighting for His Political Life",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,On Patrol With Tokyo’s New Litter Police,On Patrol With Tokyo’s New Litter Police,0.0,neutral,"[('Patrol With Tokyo’s New Litter Police', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,The Priests Revered in the Land of Five Genders,The Priests Revered in the Land of Five Genders,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Russia Floods Armenia With Disinformation Ahead of Election,Russia Floods Armenia With Disinformation Ahead of Election,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,What To Know as China’s Xi Jinping Heads to North Korea,What To Know as China’s Xi Jinping Heads to North Korea,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('North Korea', 'GPE')]"
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Russia Rails Against the West but Welcomes Candace Owens and Andrew Tate,Russia Rails Against the West but Welcomes Candace Owens and Andrew Tate,0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Candace Owens', 'PERSON'), ('Andrew Tate', 'PERSON')]"
2026_06_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Hezbollah’s Fiber-Optic Drones Expose Cracks in Israeli Defenses,Hezbollah’s Fiber-Optic Drones Expose Cracks in Israeli Defenses,0.0,neutral,"[('Hezbollah', 'ORG'), ('Fiber-Optic Drones Expose Cracks', 'ORG'), ('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Defenses', 'GPE')]"
