Scrape_Date,Source_Name,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Source_Region,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Sentiment_Label,Entities_Raw
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Qué sentí al volver a La Guaira y ver que el lugar en el que nací está ahora devastado y con cadáveres apilados,What did it feel like to return to La Guaira and see that the place where I was born is now devastated and with corpses piled up?,0.0,neutral,"[('La Guaira', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Cómo el expansionismo en territorio y población de EE.UU. a lo largo de 250 años convirtió al país en una superpotencia pero con profundas divisiones,How expansionism in US territory and population over 250 years turned the country into a superpower but with deep divisions,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('250 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,“Cuando me giré ya no quedaba nada”: el fulminante colapso del Ritasol Palace por los terremotos que sacudieron Venezuela,“When I turned around there was nothing left”: the sudden collapse of the Ritasol Palace due to the earthquakes that shook Venezuela,0.0,neutral,"[('the Ritasol Palace', 'ORG'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"6 cosas que quizá no sabías de Cabo Verde, el pequeño país que hizo historia en el Mundial 2026","6 things you may not have known about Cape Verde, the small country that made history in the 2026 World Cup",0.0,neutral,"[('6', 'CARDINAL'), ('Cape Verde', 'LOC'), ('the 2026 World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Francia destruye el sueño de Paraguay con un gol de penal de Mbappé,France destroys Paraguay's dream with a penalty goal from Mbappé,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('Mbappé', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Locura absoluta"": la controversia que genera el plan para demoler un búnker nazi bajo Berlín","""Absolute madness"": the controversy generated by the plan to demolish a Nazi bunker under Berlin",0.0,neutral,"[('Nazi', 'NORP'), ('Berlin', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"Quiénes fueron las ""madres fundadoras"", clave en la formación de Estados Unidos hace 250 años","Who were the ""founding mothers"", key in the formation of the United States 250 years ago",0.0,neutral,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('250 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Me da miedo lo que voy a ver allá dentro"": BBC Mundo visita la morgue improvisada de Los Silos, donde los cadáveres se acumulan al aire libre tras los terremotos en Venezuela","""I'm afraid of what I'm going to see in there"": BBC Mundo visits the improvised morgue of Los Silos, where corpses accumulate in the open air after the earthquakes in Venezuela",0.0,neutral,"[('BBC Mundo', 'ORG'), ('Los Silos', 'GPE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,Estoy en terapia para superar la adicción que me hace pasar 14 horas al día con el celular,I am in therapy to overcome the addiction that makes me spend 14 hours a day on my cell phone.,0.0,neutral,"[('14 hours', 'TIME')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Mundo,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Latin America,"""Los terremotos marcan a los países durante décadas y las consecuencias emocionales se llevan para siempre""","""Earthquakes mark countries for decades and the emotional consequences are carried forever""",0.0,neutral,"[('decades', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,राम मंदिर चंदा मामला: अयोध्या में अब श्रद्धालु क्या सोच रहे हैं और आगे की राह क्या होगी?,Ram Mandir donation case: What are the devotees thinking now in Ayodhya and what will be the way forward?,-1.0,negative,"[('Ram Mandir', 'PERSON'), ('Ayodhya', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"प्रशांत किशोर लड़ेंगे उपचुनाव, बीजेपी अध्यक्ष की छोड़ी गई सीट से बनेंगे जन सुराज के उम्मीदवार","Prashant Kishor will contest by-election, Jan Suraj will be the candidate from the seat vacated by BJP President.",0.0,neutral,"[('Jan Suraj', 'PERSON'), ('BJP', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"लाइव,आरएसएस प्रमुख मोहन भागवत ने राम मंदिर चढ़ावा मामले से जुड़े सवाल पर क्या कहा","Live, what RSS chief Mohan Bhagwat said on the question related to Ram temple offering case",0.0,neutral,"[('RSS', 'ORG'), ('Mohan Bhagwat', 'PERSON'), ('Ram', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,वैभव सूर्यवंशी के 14 रन बनाम सचिन के 15 रन लेकिन इन सबके बीच चर्चा में रवि बिश्नोई,Vaibhav Suryavanshi's 14 runs vs Sachin's 15 runs but amidst all this Ravi Bishnoi is in discussion.,0.0,neutral,"[(""Vaibhav Suryavanshi's"", 'PERSON'), ('14', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sachin', 'PERSON'), ('15', 'CARDINAL'), ('Ravi Bishnoi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,अर्दोआन पाकिस्तान के साथ जो लंबे समय से करना चाहते हैं वो भारत और तुर्की में पहले से ही,What Erdogan has been wanting to do with Pakistan for a long time is already happening in India and Türkiye.,0.0,neutral,"[('Erdogan', 'PERSON'), ('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('India', 'GPE'), ('Türkiye', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,जापान की प्रधानमंत्री के भारत दौरे पर चीन से ऐसी टिप्पणियां क्यों,Why such comments from China on Japanese Prime Minister's visit to India?,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Japanese', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,बच्चों में सब्ज़ियां खाने की आदत इन तरीक़ों से डालना है आसान,It is easy to inculcate the habit of eating vegetables in children in these ways.,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,तीजनबाई का निधन: पंडवानी की वजह से शादी टूटने से लेकर पद्म विभूषण तक,Death of Teejanbai: From marriage breakdown due to Pandavani to Padma Vibhushan,-1.0,negative,"[('Pandavani', 'GPE'), ('Padma', 'GPE'), ('Vibhushan', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"इसराइल ने रिपोर्ट को बताया पक्षपातपूर्ण, जस्टिस मुरलीधर ने दिया ये जवाब","Israel called the report biased, Justice Muralidhar gave this answer",0.0,neutral,"[('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Muralidhar', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Hindi,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,South Asia,"ई20 पेट्रोल पर ऑटो उद्योग की प्रेस कॉन्फ़्रेंस, एक कंपनी के शीर्ष अधिकारी के बयानों में विरोधाभास","Auto industry's press conference on E20 petrol, contradiction in statements of a company's top official",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Arrogância do Brasil no futebol contrasta com imagem de país alegre, diz comentarista inglês","Brazil's arrogance in football contrasts with its image as a happy country, says English commentator",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('English', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,5 motivos do 'boom' econômico do Paraguai (e seus efeitos para o país),5 reasons for Paraguay's economic boom (and its effects on the country),0.0,neutral,"[('5', 'CARDINAL'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Como expansão territorial e populacional dos EUA em 250 anos transformou o país em uma potência marcada por divisões,How the territorial and population expansion of the USA in 250 years transformed the country into a power marked by divisions,0.0,neutral,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('250 years', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Mãos fracas e visão turva: estamos ficando com 'corpo de celular'?,Weak hands and blurred vision: are we getting a 'cell phone body'?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"O que é 'TikTok Farlands', o submundo da rede hackeado pelos usuários","What is 'TikTok Farlands', the underworld of the network hacked by users",0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"No aniversário de 250 anos, Trump reacende o debate: quais os limites do poder nos EUA?","On the 250th anniversary, Trump reignites the debate: what are the limits of power in the USA?",0.0,neutral,"[('250th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('USA', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Bairro 'brasileiro' 'respira' na Copa após cerco de Trump,'Brazilian' neighborhood 'breathes' in the World Cup after Trump siege,0.0,neutral,"[('Brazilian', 'NORP'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,"Qual deve ser a escalação do Brasil contra a Noruega? As opções de Ancelloti, e as vantagens de cada cenário","What should Brazil's lineup be against Norway? Ancelloti's options, and the advantages of each scenario",0.0,neutral,"[('Brazil', 'GPE'), ('Norway', 'GPE'), ('Ancelloti', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Qual a distância entre Lula e Flávio Bolsonaro nas pesquisas para presidente? Veja no agregador da BBC News Brasil,What is the distance between Lula and Flávio Bolsonaro in the polls for president? See on the BBC News Brasil aggregator,0.0,neutral,"[('Flávio Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('BBC News', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Portuguese,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Latin America,Por que São Paulo é a 2ª cidade do mundo que mais ouve Taylor Swift no Spotify — e como casamento pode impulsionar ainda mais suas músicas,Why São Paulo is the 2nd city in the world that listens to Taylor Swift the most on Spotify — and how marriage can boost your music even further,0.0,neutral,"[('2nd', 'ORDINAL'), ('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Spotify', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Окно возможностей закрывается? Как изменились отношения между Украиной и Венгрией после ухода Орбана,Is the window of opportunity closing? How relations between Ukraine and Hungary have changed since Orban left,1.0,positive,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Hungary', 'GPE'), ('Orban', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"Россия заявила о захвате Константиновки, Зеленский это опроверг и позвал туда Путина на переговоры. Что известно","Russia announced the capture of Konstantinovka, Zelensky denied this and invited Putin there for negotiations. What is known",0.0,neutral,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Konstantinovka', 'GPE'), ('Zelensky', 'PERSON'), ('Putin', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: ВСУ опубликовали видео с украинскими военными в Константиновке, Евпатория осталась без света и воды","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: The Ukrainian Armed Forces published a video with the Ukrainian military in Konstantinovka, Yevpatoria was left without electricity and water",-1.0,negative,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('The Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('Ukrainian', 'NORP'), ('Konstantinovka', 'GPE'), ('Yevpatoria', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,В регионах бывшей ГДР убывает  население. Как это связано с прошлым и причем тут Берлинская стена?,"In the regions of the former GDR, the population is declining. How is this connected to the past and what does the Berlin Wall have to do with it?",0.0,neutral,"[('GDR', 'GPE'), ('the Berlin Wall', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,США отпраздновали свое 250-летие с рекордной помпой и при рекордной жаре,The United States celebrated its 250th anniversary with record fanfare and record heat.,0.0,neutral,"[('The United States', 'GPE'), ('250th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Восемь из десяти самых густонаселенных стран не участвуют в чемпионате мира. Почему?,Eight of the ten most populous countries are not participating in the World Cup. Why?,0.0,neutral,"[('Eight', 'CARDINAL'), ('ten', 'CARDINAL'), ('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Массированная атака дронов ВСУ по Петербургу: горит нефтяной терминал,Massive attack of Ukrainian Armed Forces drones in St. Petersburg: oil terminal is on fire,-1.0,negative,"[('Ukrainian Armed Forces', 'ORG'), ('St. Petersburg', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Принц Гарри все-таки не повезет Меган и детей в Лондон,Prince Harry still won't take Meghan and the children to London,0.0,neutral,"[('Harry', 'PERSON'), ('Meghan', 'PERSON'), ('London', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,"«Когда женщина рожает, будучи мэром». Япония спорит о решении главы города Явата уйти в декрет","""When a woman gives birth while she's mayor."" Japan debates Yawata city mayor's decision to go on maternity leave",0.0,neutral,"[('Japan', 'GPE'), ('Yawata', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Russian,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Eastern Europe,Звезды и поклонники празднуют свадьбу Тейлор Свифт и Трэвиса Келси: фото,Stars and fans celebrate the wedding of Taylor Swift and Travis Kelsey: photos,0.0,neutral,"[('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Travis Kelsey', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ポーランド首相、ロシアの脅威を念頭に警告　「今後数カ月が極めて重要」になり得ると,Polish Prime Minister warns of Russian threat: 'coming months could be crucial',-1.0,negative,"[('Polish', 'NORP'), ('Russian', 'NORP'), (""'coming months"", 'DATE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,イラン前最高指導者ハメネイ師の葬儀始まる,Funeral begins for former Iranian supreme leader Ayatollah Khamenei,0.0,neutral,"[('Iranian', 'NORP'), ('Ayatollah Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,イラン前最高指導者ハメネイ師の遺体を安置、アメリカとの不安定な停戦の中, 所要時間 0,41","Video, Iran's former supreme leader Ayatollah Khamenei's body laid to rest amid unstable ceasefire with US, Duration 0,41",0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('supreme', 'ORG'), (""Ayatollah Khamenei's"", 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,英で少女2人をレイプした少年2人に控訴審で拘禁刑　第一審の量刑が軽すぎると首相も批判,Two boys who raped two girls in the UK are sentenced to imprisonment by appeal court; the prime minister also criticizes the first trial's sentence as too lenient,0.0,neutral,"[('Two', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('UK', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ロシアのキーウ空爆、死者少なくとも30人に　「最大規模の攻撃」と市長,At least 30 killed in Russia's airstrike on KiV; mayor calls it 'largest attack',-1.0,negative,"[('At least 30', 'CARDINAL'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('KiV', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,"ビデオ,ロシアの攻撃、キーウの集合住宅を破壊　BBCが現地報告, 所要時間 1,27","Video, Russian attack destroys apartment complex in Kiv, BBC reports on the ground, Duration 1,27",-1.0,negative,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Kiv', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴェネズエラ地震発生から8日、生存者を倒壊した建物から救出,"8 days after Venezuela earthquake, survivors rescued from collapsed building",0.0,neutral,"[('8 days', 'DATE'), ('Venezuela', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,ヴァチカン、世界的なカトリック教会分派の信者らを破門　異例の厳しい対応,Vatican excommunicates members of a worldwide sect of the Catholic Church in an unusually harsh response,0.0,neutral,"[('Vatican', 'FAC'), ('the Catholic Church', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,【2026年サッカー男子W杯】 イングランドとウェールズのパブ、午前5時まで営業可能に　イングランド対メキシコ戦に合わせ,[2026 Men's World Cup] Pubs in England and Wales to be open until 5am for England vs. Mexico match,0.0,neutral,"[('2026', 'DATE'), ('World Cup]', 'EVENT'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Wales', 'GPE'), ('5am', 'TIME'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Japanese,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,East Asia,北京・最高層ビルの小型機衝突、操縦者の「個人的理由」が原因と　中国当局が発表,"Chinese authorities say the pilot's ""personal reasons"" were the cause of a small plane crashing into Beijing's tallest building",0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Beijing', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Moja kwa moja,Trump asema ameshangazwa na Wairani kulia katika mazishi ya Khamenei","Directly, Trump says he is surprised by Iranians crying at Khamenei's funeral",0.0,neutral,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Iranians', 'NORP'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini udi unaochomwa majumbani ni hatari?,Why is udi burned at home dangerous?,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jinsi vifaa vya kielektroniki vinavyoathiri miili yetu,How electronic devices affect our bodies,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwa nini kuna hofu kwamba Kanisa Katoliki linaweza kugawanyika?,Why is there a fear that the Catholic Church could be divided?,0.0,neutral,"[('the Catholic Church', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Jeshi la Tanzania latoa onyo dhidi ya wavunjifu wa amani,The Tanzanian army issues a warning against peace breakers,0.0,neutral,"[('Tanzanian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Tetesi za soka: Vigogo wanne wa Ligi Kuu England 'watoana roho' kwa Alex Scott,Football rumours: Four of England's Premier League 'give up' for Alex Scott,0.0,neutral,"[('Four', 'CARDINAL'), ('England', 'GPE'), ('Alex Scott', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Wairan waanza kumuaga Khamenei mashaka yakiongezeka kuhusu hatima ya Mojtaba,Iranians begin to say goodbye to Khamenei as doubts grow about Mojtaba's fate,1.0,positive,"[('Iranians', 'NORP'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Mojtaba', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kwaheri Cape Verde - timu 'kibonde' ambayo Kombe la Dunia halitaisahau,Goodbye Cape Verde - a 'basin' team that the World Cup will never forget,1.0,positive,"[('the World Cup', 'EVENT')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,"Je, msimamo wa Democrats kuhusu Israel ni upi?",What is the position of the Democrats on Israel?,0.0,neutral,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('Israel', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC Swahili,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Africa,Kombe la Dunia 2026: Misri kukutana na Argentina katika hatua ya 16,World Cup 2026: Egypt to meet Argentina in the round of 16,0.0,neutral,"[('World Cup 2026', 'EVENT'), ('Egypt', 'GPE'), ('Argentina', 'GPE'), ('16', 'CARDINAL')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"A name, a document, a future: Cameroon’s fight to register every child","A name, a document, a future: Cameroon’s fight to register every child",0.0,neutral,"[('Cameroon', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Severe weather disrupts US’s 250th celebrations,Severe weather disrupts US’s 250th celebrations,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('250th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,This immigrant served in the US military. Now he faces deportation,This immigrant served in the US military. Now he faces deportation,0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Huge crowds mourn Iran’s Khamenei as Trump vows to hold fire during funeral,Huge crowds mourn Iran’s Khamenei as Trump vows to hold fire during funeral,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE'), ('Khamenei', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,"White nationalists march in Washington, DC, area during July 4 festivities","White nationalists march in Washington, DC, area during July 4 festivities",0.0,neutral,"[('Washington, DC', 'GPE'), ('July 4', 'DATE')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ticket prices plunge for USA-Belgium World Cup last-16 match,Ticket prices plunge for USA-Belgium World Cup last-16 match,0.0,neutral,"[('USA-Belgium World Cup last-16', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Mbappe draws level with Messi as France beat Paraguay to set up Morocco tie,Mbappe draws level with Messi as France beat Paraguay to set up Morocco tie,0.0,neutral,"[('Messi', 'PERSON'), ('France', 'GPE'), ('Paraguay', 'ORG'), ('Morocco', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Lebanon’s Aoun calls on US to keep ‘always standing beside’ his country,Lebanon’s Aoun calls on US to keep ‘always standing beside’ his country,0.0,neutral,"[('Lebanon', 'GPE'), ('Aoun', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,Ounahi fires Morocco into World Cup quarterfinals with 3-0 win over Canada,Ounahi fires Morocco into World Cup quarterfinals with 3-0 win over Canada,1.0,positive,"[('Morocco', 'GPE'), ('World Cup', 'EVENT'), ('3', 'CARDINAL'), ('Canada', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,Al Jazeera,https://www.aljazeera.com/news,en,Middle East,At least 20 drown as boat carrying students after exams sinks in DR Congo,At least 20 drown as boat carrying students after exams sinks in DR Congo,0.0,neutral,"[('At least 20', 'CARDINAL'), ('DR', 'GPE'), ('Congo', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,When alone feels enough,When alone feels enough,0.0,neutral,[]
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,When hope takes wing | Review of Wild Winds: The Borderless Anthology of Poems,When hope takes wing | Review of Wild Winds: The Borderless Anthology of Poems,1.0,positive,"[('Review of Wild Winds', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Umar Khalid’s prison reading list,Umar Khalid’s prison reading list,0.0,neutral,"[('Umar Khalid’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,"Govt. issues notice to Meta on child sexual abuse material in Instagram ads, say sources","Govt. issues notice to Meta on child sexual abuse material in Instagram ads, say sources",0.0,neutral,"[('Meta', 'PERSON'), ('Instagram', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Ram temple donation row: VHP asks SIT to verify claims made by Opposition leaders,Ram temple donation row: VHP asks SIT to verify claims made by Opposition leaders,0.0,neutral,"[('VHP', 'ORG'), ('SIT', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Rights organisation files ‘war crimes’ complaint with India against Israeli soldier spotted along ‘hummus trail’,Rights organisation files ‘war crimes’ complaint with India against Israeli soldier spotted along ‘hummus trail’,-1.0,negative,"[('India', 'GPE'), ('Israeli', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Gaganyaan mission: ISRO successfully conducts first SOLVE ground test,Gaganyaan mission: ISRO successfully conducts first SOLVE ground test,1.0,positive,"[('SOLVE', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Pipavav | An Indian yard’s unlikely bet on cutting-edge shipbuilding,Pipavav | An Indian yard’s unlikely bet on cutting-edge shipbuilding,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Govt withdraws emergency gas curbs imposed during Hormuz disruption as LNG supplies normalise,Govt withdraws emergency gas curbs imposed during Hormuz disruption as LNG supplies normalise,0.0,neutral,"[('Hormuz', 'PERSON'), ('LNG', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,The Hindu,https://www.thehindu.com,en,South Asia,Why tanks still matter in modern warfare,Why tanks still matter in modern warfare,-1.0,negative,[]
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,"US marks 250th birthday with fireworks, flyovers and extreme weather","US marks 250th birthday with fireworks, flyovers and extreme weather",0.0,neutral,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('250th', 'ORDINAL')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Ukraine hits major oil terminal in Russia's St Petersburg,Ukraine hits major oil terminal in Russia's St Petersburg,0.0,neutral,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('St Petersburg', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Evacuations in Guam as super typhoon Bavi approaches,Evacuations in Guam as super typhoon Bavi approaches,0.0,neutral,"[('Guam', 'GPE'), ('Bavi', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Chinese underground church figure Jin Mingri freed from prison,Chinese underground church figure Jin Mingri freed from prison,0.0,neutral,"[('Chinese', 'NORP'), ('Jin Mingri', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Former chess champion Kramnik banned over cheating remarks,Former chess champion Kramnik banned over cheating remarks,0.0,neutral,"[('Kramnik', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Moment of destiny for France's Le Pen in verdict to decide her future in presidential race,Moment of destiny for France's Le Pen in verdict to decide her future in presidential race,0.0,neutral,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Le Pen', 'FAC')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Pope urges Europe to do more for migrants as he visits gateway island,Pope urges Europe to do more for migrants as he visits gateway island,0.0,neutral,"[('Europe', 'LOC')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Row after Indian state drops eggs from school lunch menu,Row after Indian state drops eggs from school lunch menu,0.0,neutral,"[('Indian', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Taylor Swift marries Travis Kelce in NYC ceremony officiated by Adam Sandler,Taylor Swift marries Travis Kelce in NYC ceremony officiated by Adam Sandler,0.0,neutral,"[('Taylor Swift', 'PERSON'), ('Travis Kelce', 'PERSON'), ('NYC', 'LOC'), ('Adam Sandler', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,BBC World RSS,https://feeds.bbci.co.uk/news/world/rss.xml,en,Global,Large crowds gather in Tehran on first day of Ayatollah Khamenei's funeral,Large crowds gather in Tehran on first day of Ayatollah Khamenei's funeral,0.0,neutral,"[('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('first day', 'DATE'), (""Ayatollah Khamenei's"", 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Years of Warnings About Public Housing Preceded Venezuela’s Earthquakes,Years of Warnings About Public Housing Preceded Venezuela’s Earthquakes,-1.0,negative,"[('Warnings About Public Housing Preceded Venezuela’s', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Mourners Chant ‘Revenge’ at Funeral Prayers for Iran’s Slain Supreme Leader,Mourners Chant ‘Revenge’ at Funeral Prayers for Iran’s Slain Supreme Leader,0.0,neutral,"[('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,China Frees Pastor Detained in Crackdown on Religion After Trump’s Urging,China Frees Pastor Detained in Crackdown on Religion After Trump’s Urging,0.0,neutral,"[('China Frees Pastor Detained', 'ORG'), ('Trump’s Urging', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Rebel Catholics Defy Vatican’s Calls to Return to Mainstream Church,Rebel Catholics Defy Vatican’s Calls to Return to Mainstream Church,0.0,neutral,"[('Rebel Catholics Defy Vatican’s', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Impeachment Trial of Philippine Vice President Set to Begin,Impeachment Trial of Philippine Vice President Set to Begin,0.0,neutral,"[('Philippine', 'NORP')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,China Raises Pressure on Taiwan With Expanded Coast Guard Patrols,China Raises Pressure on Taiwan With Expanded Coast Guard Patrols,0.0,neutral,"[('China', 'GPE'), ('Taiwan With Expanded Coast Guard Patrols', 'WORK_OF_ART')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Momentary Unity at a Funeral Masks Deep Divisions Among Iran’s Leaders,Momentary Unity at a Funeral Masks Deep Divisions Among Iran’s Leaders,0.0,neutral,"[('Momentary Unity', 'PERSON'), ('Iran', 'GPE')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"As Xi Looks to Extend His Rule, He Leans on a Longtime Ally","As Xi Looks to Extend His Rule, He Leans on a Longtime Ally",0.0,neutral,"[('Xi Looks', 'PERSON')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,Huge Crowds Mass in Tehran for Ayatollah’s State Funeral,Huge Crowds Mass in Tehran for Ayatollah’s State Funeral,0.0,neutral,"[('Tehran', 'GPE'), ('Ayatollah’s State Funeral', 'ORG')]"
2026_07_05,NYT World RSS,https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/World.xml,en,Global,"Prince Harry Will Travel to London, but Without His Family","Prince Harry Will Travel to London, but Without His Family",0.0,neutral,"[('London', 'GPE')]"
