Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Cuál es la situación de los cristianos en Nigeria y por qué Trump amenaza con intervenir en el país,What is the situation of Christians in Nigeria and why Trump threatens to intervene in the country,0.0,"[('Christians', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"""En el Perú, el mejor elogio que te pueden hacer es que no pareces peruano. Son pocos los peruanos que se identifican con su rostro, con su país""","""In Peru, the best compliment they can give you is that you don't look Peruvian. There are few Peruvians who identify with their face, with their country""",0.4,"[('Peru', 'GPE'), ('Peruvian', 'NORP'), ('Peruvians', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Lo que descubrí al investigar cómo murió mi padre en la toma del Palacio de Justicia en Bogotá hace 40 años,What I discovered when investigating how my father died in the storming of the Palace of Justice in Bogotá 40 years ago,0.0,"[('Bogotá', 'GPE'), ('40 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Se hizo rico vendiendo camellos y oro: ahora sus tropas controlan la mitad de Sudán,He became rich selling camels and gold: now his troops control half of Sudan,0.10416666666666667,"[('half', 'CARDINAL'), ('Sudan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Un jurado en EE.UU. otorga una indemnización de US$10 millones a la profesora a la que le disparó un alumno de 6 años,A jury in the US awards compensation of US$10 million to the teacher who was shot by a 6-year-old student,0.0,"[('US', 'GPE'), ('US$10 million', 'MONEY'), ('6-year-old', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,सुप्रीम कोर्ट का निर्देश- इन जगहों से आवारा कुत्तों और मवेशियों को हटाया जाए,Supreme Court's instructions - Stray dogs and cattle should be removed from these places,0.0,"[(""Supreme Court's"", 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"एलन मस्क को मिलेगा एक लाख करोड़ डॉलर का सैलरी पैकेज, लेकिन पूरी करनी होगी ये शर्त","Elon Musk will get a salary package of one trillion dollars, but this condition will have to be fulfilled",0.0,"[('Elon Musk', 'PERSON'), ('one trillion dollars', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,कालमेगी तूफ़ान से फ़िलीपींस और वियतनाम में अब तक 193 लोगों की मौत","Live, 193 people have died so far in Philippines and Vietnam due to Typhoon Kalmegi",0.03712121212121212,"[('193', 'CARDINAL'), ('Philippines', 'GPE'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('Typhoon Kalmegi', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"आयोजक बीच टूर्नामेंट से भागे, खिलाड़ी होटल में फंसे: कश्मीर में हुई ये क्रिकेट लीग क्यों हुई फ़ेल","Organizers ran away from the tournament, players trapped in hotel: Why did this cricket league in Kashmir fail?",-0.35,"[('Kashmir', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,बिहार विधानसभा चुनाव: ओवैसी इस बार सीमांचल में अपना करिश्मा दिखा पाएँगे?,Bihar Assembly Elections: Will Owaisi be able to show his charisma in Seemanchal this time?,0.5,"[('Bihar Assembly', 'ORG'), ('Owaisi', 'ORG'), ('Seemanchal', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ये चार चीज़ें, जो सिरदर्द में हो सकती हैं बहुत कारगर",These four things can be very effective in headache,0.78,"[('four', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार चुनाव: घुसपैठ से लेकर जंगलराज तक, तेज़ हुई बयानबाज़ी, सभी दलों ने किए बड़े दावे","Bihar elections: From infiltration to jungle raj, rhetoric intensified, all parties made big claims",0.0,"[('Bihar', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ग़ज़ाला हाशमी ने रचा इतिहास, चुनी गईं वर्जीनिया की पहली मुस्लिम लेफ्टिनेंट गवर्नर","Ghazala Hashmi created history, elected the first Muslim Lieutenant Governor of Virginia",0.25,"[('Ghazala Hashmi', 'PERSON'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Virginia', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"बिहार विधानसभा चुनाव: छिटपुट घटनाओं के बीच पहले चरण का मतदान ख़त्म, 64.66 प्रतिशत हुई वोटिंग","Bihar Assembly Elections: First phase of voting ends amid sporadic incidents, 64.66 percent voting took place",0.25,"[('Bihar Assembly', 'ORG'), ('First', 'ORDINAL'), ('64.66 percent', 'PERCENT')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Soraya Thronicke: 'Bolsonaro me enganou, mas eu permiti'","Soraya Thronicke: 'Bolsonaro deceived me, but I allowed it'",0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Por que Elon Musk pode estar mais perto de se tornar um trilionário,Why Elon Musk may be closer to becoming a trillionaire,0.45,[]
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'O senhor Trump está equivocado': críticas de latinos e moderação de Lula dão tom de cúpula em Belém,'Mr Trump is wrong': criticism from Latinos and Lula's moderation set the tone at the summit in Belém,-0.5,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Latinos', 'ORG'), ('Lula', 'PERSON'), ('Belém', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O que o governo Lula quer da COP30 e quais os principais obstáculos,What the Lula government wants from COP30 and what are the main obstacles,0.10555555555555557,[]
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O homem que atropelou suspeito de esfaquear pessoas em trem no Reino Unido,The man who ran over a suspect who stabbed people on a train in the UK,0.0,"[('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O depoimento de pai de jovem de 14 anos morto em operação contra Comando Vermelho: 'Ele se iludiu',The testimony of the father of a 14-year-old boy killed in an operation against Comando Vermelho: 'He was deluded',-0.2,"[('14-year-old', 'DATE'), (""Comando Vermelho: '"", 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Os detalhes da lista que polícia fez para divulgar suspeitos mortos em megaoperação no Rio,Details of the list that the police created to reveal suspects killed in a mega-operation in Rio,-0.2,"[('Rio', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A mais forte crítica do papa Leão 14 a Trump,Pope Leo 14's strongest criticism of Trump,0.0,"[(""Leo 14's"", 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Candidatas ao Miss Universo abandonam apresentação após organizador dar bronca na Miss México,Miss Universe candidates abandon performance after organizer scolds Miss Mexico,0.0,"[('Miss Mexico', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Автомат вместо учебника. Как Россия делает солдат из украинских детей,An automatic machine instead of a textbook. How Russia makes soldiers out of Ukrainian children,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: ночные атаки дронов на Запорожье, Чугуев и Одесскую область","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: night drone attacks on Zaporozhye, Chuguev and Odessa region",0.0,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('night', 'TIME'), ('Zaporozhye', 'PERSON'), ('Chuguev', 'PERSON'), ('Odessa', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Gunvor передумал покупать зарубежные активы «Лукойла» из-за позиции США,Gunvor changed its mind about buying foreign assets of Lukoil due to the position of the United States,-0.125,"[('Gunvor', 'PERSON'), ('Lukoil', 'ORG'), ('the United States', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Не только Мамдани: где еще в США победили демократы и почему это важно,Not only Mamdani: where else in the US did the Democrats win and why is it important?,0.4000000000000001,"[('Mamdani', 'PERSON'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Democrats', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Ресурсы и влияние России и Китая. Зачем Трамп встречался с лидерами стран Центральной Азии в Белом доме,Resources and influence of Russia and China. Why Trump met with Central Asian leaders at the White House,0.0,"[('Russia', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Central Asian', 'NORP'), ('the White House', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Акционеры Tesla одобрили потенциальную выплату Маску почти триллиона долларов,Tesla shareholders approve potential payout of nearly a trillion dollars to Musk,0.05,"[('nearly a trillion dollars', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Франция намерена приостановить работу сайта Shein из-за скандала с секс-куклами, напоминающими детей",France intends to suspend the operation of the Shein website due to the scandal with sex dolls resembling children,-0.125,"[('France', 'GPE'), ('Shein', 'LOC')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Скрытое проникновение: какие изменения в тактике российской армии показал штурм Покровска?,Covert penetration: what changes in the tactics of the Russian army did the assault on Pokrovsk show?,0.0,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Pokrovsk', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Словарь Collins Dictionary выбрал слово 2025 года: это «вайб-кодинг»,The Collins Dictionary has chosen the word of 2025: “vibe coding”,0.0,"[('The Collins Dictionary', 'ORG'), ('2025', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,85-летняя демократка Нэнси Пелоси заявила о завершении политической карьеры в 2027 году,85-year-old Democrat Nancy Pelosi announced her retirement from political career in 2027,0.0,"[('85-year-old', 'DATE'), ('Democrat', 'NORP'), ('Nancy Pelosi', 'PERSON'), ('2027', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ペロシ元米下院議長が引退を表明、20年にわたり下院で民主党を率いる,"Former U.S. House Speaker Pelosi announces retirement, leading Democrats in the House of Representatives for 20 years",0.0,"[('U.S. House', 'ORG'), ('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('the House of Representatives', 'ORG'), ('20 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,口論し、原稿を破り、「国内の敵」と……引退表明のペロシ氏とトランプ氏の確執, 所要時間 0,48","Video, Bickering, tearing up manuscripts, calling out ``domestic enemies''... Pelosi announces retirement and Trump feud, Duration 0,48",0.0,"[('Bickering', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,ミス・ユニバース、各国代表が抗議の「集団退席」　運営側がメキシコ代表を叱ったあと, 所要時間 1,31","Video, Miss Universe representatives from each country ``mass walk out'' in protest after management scolds Mexico representative, Duration 1,31",0.0,"[('Universe', 'PERSON'), ('Mexico', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,南アフリカ人17人、ドンバスで身動き取れず「救助要請」　ロシアとウクライナの戦争に参加,"17 South Africans stranded in Donbas 'request for rescue', participating in war between Russia and Ukraine",0.0,"[('17', 'CARDINAL'), ('South Africans', 'NORP'), ('Donbas', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,マスク氏への1兆ドル規模の報酬案、テスラ株主総会が承認,Tesla shareholder meeting approves $1 trillion compensation proposal for Musk,0.0,"[('Tesla', 'ORG'), ('$1 trillion', 'MONEY')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【検証】 ガソリンから生鮮食品まで、トランプ氏は物価を下げるとの公約を守っているのか,"[Test] Is Trump keeping his promise to lower prices, from gasoline to fresh food?",0.3,[]
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,投降したウクライナ兵を射殺したロシア兵に終身刑、捕虜殺害めぐり初の宣告,"Russian soldier who shot and killed surrendering Ukrainian soldier sentenced to life in prison, first sentence for killing a prisoner of war",0.016666666666666663,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Ukrainian', 'GPE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,「トランプ関税」の合憲性、米最高裁が厳しく追及　口頭弁論で保守派判事も疑問呈す,U.S. Supreme Court harshly pursues constitutionality of Trump tariffs; conservative justices also question during oral argument,-0.2,"[('U.S. Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【解説】 米民主党が盛り返し、重要なメッセージを手に入れた……注目の選挙から分かること,[Commentary] The US Democratic Party has made a comeback and received an important message... What we can learn from the closely watched election,0.4,"[('The US Democratic Party', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Wanamgambo wa RSF wakubali kusitisha mapigano kuruhusu misaada ya kibinadamu","Directly, the RSF Militants agreed to a ceasefire to allow humanitarian aid",0.1,[]
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: 'Nilikimbia kivyangu na mume wangu kivyake',Protests in Tanzania: 'I ran separately and my husband separately',0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Je, ni kweli Wakristo wanateswa Nigeria kama anavyodai Trump?",Are Christians really persecuted in Nigeria as Trump claims?,0.2,"[('Christians', 'NORP'), ('Nigeria', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Serikali ya Israel yatambua mwili wa mwanafunzi wa Tanzania aliyekuwa mateka Gaza,The Israeli government recognizes the body of a Tanzanian student who was held captive in Gaza,0.2,"[('Israeli', 'NORP'), ('Tanzanian', 'NORP'), ('Gaza', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Tetesi za Soka Ulaya Ijumaa: Tottenham itafanikiwa kumrejesha Ivan Toney EPL?,European Football Rumors Friday: Will Tottenham succeed in bringing Ivan Toney back to the EPL?,0.0,"[('European Football Rumors', 'ORG'), ('Friday', 'DATE'), ('Will Tottenham', 'PERSON'), ('Ivan Toney', 'PERSON'), ('EPL', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maandamano Tanzania: Familia zahaha kupata miili ya ndugu zao,Protests in Tanzania: Families seek to find the bodies of their relatives,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Uchaguzi Tanzania 2025 ulikiuka maadili ya kidemokrasia - AU,The Tanzania 2025 election violated democratic values ​​- AU,0.0,"[('Tanzania', 'GPE'), ('2025', 'DATE'), ('democratic', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Lipa fidia ama ufe: Simulizi za 'kutisha' kutoka kwa jamaa za wafungwa wa RSF El Fasher,Pay ransom or die: 'Horrifying' stories from relatives of RSF El Fasher prisoners,-0.9,"[('El Fasher', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Alikumbatia mauti: Jinsi Mfalme wa Saudi alivyouawa na mpwa wake miaka 50 iliyopita,He embraced death: How the Saudi King was killed by his nephew 50 years ago,-0.2,"[('Saudi', 'NORP'), ('50 years ago', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_07,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Sauti,'Heche anakabiliwa na mashtaka mawili ya ugaidi' – Wakili wake, Muda 3,58","Sauti, 'Heche faces two charges of terrorism' - His lawyer, Time 3,58",0.0,"[('Heche', 'ORG'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]"
