Scrape_Date,Source_URL,Source_Language_Code,Original_Headline,Translated_Headline,Polarity,Entities_Raw
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Los grupos armados palestinos enfrentados a Hamás en Gaza que son apoyados por Israel y EE.UU.,The Palestinian armed groups confronting Hamas in Gaza that are supported by Israel and the US.,0.0,"[('Palestinian', 'NORP'), ('Hamas', 'ORG'), ('Gaza', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Un enorme incendio en un complejo de rascacielos residenciales en Hong Kong deja al menos 55 muertos y cientos de desaparecidos,A huge fire in a residential skyscraper complex in Hong Kong leaves at least 55 dead and hundreds missing,-0.11999999999999997,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('at least 55', 'CARDINAL'), ('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,Venezuela revoca los derechos de tráfico a seis aerolíneas internacionales luego de que cancelaran sus vuelos al país,Venezuela revokes the traffic rights of six international airlines after they canceled their flights to the country,0.0,"[('Venezuela', 'GPE'), ('six', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Qué dice sobre el fin del poder de las maras en El Salvador el regreso al fútbol de los ""números malditos"" 13 y 18","What the return to soccer of the ""cursed numbers"" 13 and 18 says about the end of the power of the gangs in El Salvador",0.0,"[('13', 'CARDINAL'), ('18', 'DATE'), ('El Salvador', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/mundo,es,"Por qué si todos viviéramos como Uruguay se frenaría la ""estafa piramidal"" que estamos haciendo con los recursos del planeta","Why if we all lived like Uruguay would stop the ""pyramid scam"" that we are doing with the planet's resources",0.0,"[('Uruguay', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,व्हाइट हाउस के पास हुई गोलीबारी के संदिग्ध हमलावर अफ़ग़ान नागरिक के बारे में जो बातें सामने आईं,"Things that came to light about the Afghan citizen, the suspected attacker of the shooting near the White House",0.16666666666666666,"[('Afghan', 'NORP'), ('the White House', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"लाइव,धर्मेंद्र के निधन पर हेमा मालिनी की पहली सार्वजनिक प्रतिक्रिया","Live, Hema Malini's first public reaction on Dharmendra's demise",0.12878787878787878,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Dharmendra', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"जम्मू-कश्मीर: माता वैष्णो देवी मेडिकल कॉलेज में मुस्लिम छात्रों के एडमिशन पर विवाद, कॉलेज ने कहा- यहाँ किसी को आरक्षण नहीं","Jammu and Kashmir: Controversy over admission of Muslim students in Mata Vaishno Devi Medical College, college said - no reservation for anyone here",0.0,"[('Jammu', 'GPE'), ('Kashmir', 'LOC'), ('Muslim', 'NORP'), ('Mata Vaishno Devi Medical College', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पाकिस्तान में इस साल चिलग़ोज़ा इतना सस्ता कैसे हो गया?,How did pine nuts become so cheap in Pakistan this year?,0.4,"[('Pakistan', 'GPE'), ('this year', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,हांगकांग में भीषण आग पर उस रिहायशी इलाक़े के लोग क्या कह रहे हैं?,What are the people of that residential area saying about the massive fire in Hong Kong?,0.0,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"हांगकांग के अपार्टमेंट ब्लॉक्स में लगी भीषण आग, कम से कम 44 लोगों की मौत और 279 लापता","Massive fire breaks out in Hong Kong's apartment blocks, at least 44 dead and 279 missing",-0.175,"[(""Hong Kong's"", 'GPE'), ('at least 44', 'CARDINAL'), ('279', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,हांगकांग के अपार्टमेंट ब्लॉक्स में लगी भीषण आग की त्रासदी इन 10 तस्वीरों में देखिए,See the tragedy of the massive fire in Hong Kong's apartment blocks in these 10 pictures.,0.0,"[(""Hong Kong's"", 'GPE'), ('10', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,"ट्रांसजेंडर व्यक्ति भी क्या बन सकेंगे 'अपने बच्चों के मां-बाप', केरल हाईकोर्ट करेगा फ़ैसला","Will transgender people also be able to become 'parents of their children', Kerala High Court will decide.",0.33,"[('Kerala High Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/hindi,hi,पीएम मोदी के राम मंदिर पर ध्वज फहराने का क्या कोई सियासी मतलब भी है?,Is there any political meaning in PM Modi hoisting the flag on Ram temple?,0.0,"[('PM Modi', 'GPE'), ('Ram', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,'Salário de CEO' e benefícios turbinados: as estratégias de empresas na disputa por talentos em IA no Brasil,'CEO salary' and boosted benefits: companies' strategies in the fight for AI talent in Brazil,0.0,"[('AI', 'GPE'), ('Brazil', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,A tragédia do incêndio em Hong Kong que deixou mais de 40 mortos: 'Dava para ver as chamas por dentro',The tragedy of the fire in Hong Kong that left more than 40 people dead: 'You could see the flames inside',0.09999999999999999,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('more than 40', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Bolsonaro virou 'aposta arriscada' para Trump, diz pesquisador americano","Bolsonaro became a 'risky bet' for Trump, says American researcher",0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,"Michelle, filhos, Tarcísio: as fichas de cada 'herdeiro' na disputa pelo capital político de Bolsonaro","Michelle, children, Tarcísio: the records of each 'heir' in the dispute for Bolsonaro's political capital",0.0,"[('Michelle', 'ORG'), ('Tarcísio', 'PERSON'), ('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Defesa de Bolsonaro ainda pode recorrer de condenação no STF?,Can Bolsonaro's defense still appeal his conviction in the STF?,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('STF', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Bolsonaro começa a cumprir pena de 27 anos de prisão em sala da Polícia Federal,Bolsonaro begins serving a 27-year prison sentence in a Federal Police room,0.0,"[('Bolsonaro', 'PERSON'), ('27-year', 'DATE'), ('Federal Police', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Como vivem os venezuelanos com a possibilidade de ataque dos EUA: 'O que mais preocupa é a comida',How Venezuelans live with the possibility of a US attack: 'What worries most is food',0.3181818181818182,"[('Venezuelans', 'NORP'), ('US', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,Quando estreia nova temporada de 'Stranger Things' e tudo o que você precisa saber sobre a série da Netflix,When does the new season of 'Stranger Things' premiere and everything you need to know about the Netflix series,0.13636363636363635,"[('Netflix', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/portuguese,pt,O comovente reencontro de casal separado por 40 anos após uma gravidez na adolescência,The touching reunion of a couple separated for 40 years after a teenage pregnancy,0.25,"[('40 years', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"Стрельба в Вашингтоне возле Белого дома: двое бойцов Нацгвардии в критическом состоянии, нападавший задержан","Shooting in Washington near the White House: two National Guard soldiers in critical condition, attacker detained",0.03333333333333333,"[('Washington', 'GPE'), ('the White House', 'FAC'), ('two', 'CARDINAL'), ('National Guard', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Число жертв пожара в жилом комплексе в Гонконге растет. По делу о пожаре задержаны три человека,The number of victims of a fire in a residential complex in Hong Kong is growing. Three people were detained in connection with the fire,-0.3,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('Three', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,"LIVELive,Война в Украине: новые атаки дронов в Херсоне, Одесской и Днепропетровской областях","LIVELive,War in Ukraine: new drone attacks in Kherson, Odessa and Dnepropetrovsk regions",0.13636363636363635,"[('War', 'GPE'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Kherson', 'GPE'), ('Odessa', 'GPE'), ('Dnepropetrovsk', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Новая норма — почему публикация разговора Уиткоффа с Ушаковым (не) поставит крест на переговорах о мире в Украине,The new normal - why the publication of Witkoff’s conversation with Ushakov will (not) put an end to peace negotiations in Ukraine,0.1431818181818182,"[('Witkoff', 'ORG'), ('Ushakov', 'PERSON'), ('Ukraine', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Юность длится до 30 лет: новое исследование определило пять этапов возраста человеческого мозга,Adolescence lasts up to 30 years: new study identifies five stages of human brain age,0.06818181818181818,"[('up to 30 years', 'DATE'), ('five', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Последний шанс Кира Стармера. Когда ждать смены власти в Британии?,Keir Starmer's last chance. When can we expect a change of power in Britain?,0.0,"[(""Keir Starmer's"", 'PERSON'), ('Britain', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Парламент Италии единогласно признал фемицид уголовным преступлением,Italian Parliament unanimously recognizes femicide as a criminal offense,-0.2,"[('Italian Parliament', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Миллион евро монетками. Инспектора парковки в Германии подозревают в краже гигантской суммы из паркоматов,Million euros in coins. Parking inspector in Germany is suspected of stealing a huge sum from parking meters,0.4000000000000001,"[('Million', 'CARDINAL'), ('Germany', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,Российских наемников обвиняют в жестоких убийствах в Мали. Би-би-си поговорила с очевидцами,Russian mercenaries are accused of brutal killings in Mali. The BBC spoke to eyewitnesses,-0.4375,"[('Russian', 'NORP'), ('Mali', 'GPE'), ('BBC', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/russian,ru,«Ему нужно продать это Украине и России». Что Трамп и другие говорят о прослушке разговора Уиткоффа с Ушаковым,“He needs to sell it to Ukraine and Russia.” What Trump and others are saying about the wiretapping of Witkoff's conversation with Ushakov,0.0,"[('Ukraine', 'GPE'), ('Russia', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Witkoff', 'PERSON'), ('Ushakov', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港の高層住宅群で大規模火災、少なくとも44人死亡　279人が行方不明,"Massive fire in Hong Kong high-rise residential complex, at least 44 dead, 279 missing",-0.2,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE'), ('at least 44', 'CARDINAL'), ('279', 'CARDINAL')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,香港の住民、現実を受け止めきれず「打ちのめされている」　高層住宅群火災,"Hong Kong residents are ""devastated"" unable to accept the reality of high-rise residential complex fire",-0.4,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,ウィトコフ米特使がロシア高官に助言か　音声記録流出、トランプ氏は擁護,Trump defends audio recording leaked of US special envoy Witkoff giving advice to Russian officials,0.17857142857142858,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Witkoff', 'PERSON'), ('Russian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,英秋季予算案で260億ポンドの増税、野党は「約束破った」と財務相を批判,Opposition criticizes Chancellor of the Exchequer for ``broken promise'' over £26 billion tax hike in UK autumn budget,-0.4,"[('Exchequer', 'ORG'), ('over £26 billion', 'MONEY'), ('UK', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,イタリア議会、全会一致で「フェミサイド」を独立した犯罪に　自動的に終身刑,"Italian parliament unanimously declares 'femicide' an independent crime, automatically punishable by life imprisonment",0.0,"[('Italian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,アサヒ、顧客データ150万件が流出と発表　9月のランサムウエア攻撃,Asahi announces 1.5 million customer data leaked due to ransomware attack in September,-0.125,"[('Asahi', 'ORG'), ('1.5 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('September', 'DATE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,"ビデオ,複数の高層住宅が巨大な炎と煙に包まれ……香港で大規模火災, 所要時間 0,48","Video, Multiple high-rise buildings engulfed in flames and smoke...Massive fire in Hong Kong, Duration 0,48",0.0,"[('Hong Kong', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,タイ南部で「300年に一度」の豪雨　東南アジア各国でも洪水被害,``once-in-300-years'' heavy rains in southern Thailand; flood damage also occurs in Southeast Asian countries,-0.06666666666666667,"[('Thailand', 'GPE'), ('Southeast Asian', 'NORP')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/japanese,ja,【検証】 アメリカ政治のアカウントの拠点がインドに……Xの位置情報機能で明らかになったこと,[Verification] American political accounts are based in India...X's location information feature revealed,0.0,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('India', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Yafahamu mambo 9 yatakayojadiliwa na Bunge la Ulaya kuhusu Tanzania,Know the 9 things that will be discussed by the European Parliament about Tanzania,0.0,"[('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('the European Parliament', 'ORG'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Moja kwa moja,Wanajeshi wa Marekani wapigwa risasi karibu na Ikulu ya White House","Directly, American soldiers are shot near the White House",0.03333333333333333,"[('American', 'NORP'), ('the White House', 'FAC')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Fahamu jinsi Mahakama ya ICC inavyofanya kazi,Find out how the ICC Court works,0.0,"[('the ICC Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Viongozi 10 maarufu Afrika waliowahi kushtakiwa Mahakama ya ICC,10 famous African leaders who have been accused by the ICC Court,0.25,"[('10', 'CARDINAL'), ('African', 'NORP'), ('the ICC Court', 'ORG')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Mapinduzi ya kijeshi yafanyika Guinea-Bissau,A military coup takes place in Guinea-Bissau,-0.1,"[('Guinea', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,"Tetesi za soka Ulaya: Samu azichanganya Arsenal, Chelsea na Spurs","European football rumours: Samu will mix Arsenal, Chelsea and Spurs",0.0,"[('European', 'NORP'), ('Samu', 'ORG'), ('Arsenal', 'ORG'), ('Chelsea', 'PERSON'), ('Spurs', 'PERSON')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Maswali 7 magumu kwa Waziri Mkuu kuhusu Oktoba 29 Tanzania,7 difficult questions for the Prime Minister about October 29 Tanzania,-0.5,"[('7', 'CARDINAL'), ('Tanzania', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Kwa nini Visiwa vya Ryukyu vimekuwa mahala pa mvutano kati ya China na Japan?,Why have the Ryukyu Islands become a place of tension between China and Japan?,0.0,"[('the Ryukyu Islands', 'GPE'), ('China', 'GPE'), ('Japan', 'GPE')]"
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Marais na mawaziri wakuu waliowahi kufungwa duniani,Presidents and prime ministers who were ever imprisoned in the world,0.0,[]
2025_11_27,https://www.bbc.com/swahili,sw,Ufahamu ugonjwa wa ajabu unaofanya watu wasiogope hata kifo,Understand the strange disease that makes people not even afraid of death,-0.325,[]
